Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Hey, Sack-Happy, how you doing?
Hey, there, Rubber Thumbs.
Hey, I thought you'd be
on a dim route by now.
I don't see you pushing
many number one sacks
there, Clavin.
What the heck
are they talking about?
It's kind of a postal rap.
Hey, there's a flap that you
had a brush with utility.
Ah, 604 is all the way.
- Yeah, well, you
know the scheme fin.
- Yeah.
You know, I actually once
thought of asking Cliff
what it all meant,
but
then it occurred to me
he might tell me.
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got.
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot.
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go.
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same.
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
Well, I, I can't put this off
another minute.
What's up, Frasier?
I'm a man in a predicament, Sam.
I've got to find a gift
for the dearest, sweetest,
most wonderful woman on Earth.
So, you finally
dumped Lilith, huh?
No.
It's our one-month anniversary,
and I'm just stumped
about what to get her.
- Any suggestions?
- Well, you could get her
a nice "mank."
- "Mank"?
- Yeah. You know,
it's a mock mink.
I got one for Vera.
You cannot tell it
from the real thing.
It's great.
Unless, of course, it rains,
and then you just
toss it in the dryer,
and you leave the house
for a couple hours.
Well, I suppose
I'll think of something.
Wish me luck.
Hey, Cliff, new suit?
Oh, well, no, actually,
I just had it dry cleaned
there, Doc.
Uh, hey, Woody.
A beer, and uh, one for
mi compadre here, Normie.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, no, it's just...
Sorry. I thought Cliff was
going to buy me a beer.
Well, uh, well, I am.
Hey, hey, Norm,
Norm, no, come on, now,
knock it off there, will you?
Geez. It's just that my annual
civil service raise
came in today, you know,
at three and a half percent,
just like clockwork,
you know, as if, uh,
carrying that bag
wasn't honor enough.
- Wow, Mr. Clavin, you
got a raise, huh?
- Yup.
I've been hoping
for a raise for two years now.
I haven't gotten diddly.
Well, Woody, that is an outrage.
You ought to walk
right up to Miss Howe,
look her square in the eye,
and demand diddly.
Ah, tell you what,
you work overtime,
you get over-diddly, pal.
And, uh, diddly-
and-a-half on weekends,
and, uh, golden diddly
on holidays, too.
Uh, Cliff, Cliff...
The secret
is knowing when to stop.
Hey, uh, Sam? Yeah?
Do you think Miss Howe
would give me a raise
if I asked her?
Well, let's see, uh,
you're a good bartender,
you've never had a vacation,
you never been out sick.
Probably not.
- Aw, gee, really, Sam?
- Oh, she's tough.
- Maybe if you get her
in a good mood.
- Uh, how do I do that?
Well, put her in a good mood,
you know?
Be nice to her; Compliment her.
Compliment... right. Yeah.
Okay, thanks, Sam. Mm-hmm.
I'll do it.
Uh, what should I compliment?
I don't know;
First thing you see, Woody.
Come in.
Miss Howe, did I ever tell you
you have a nice...?
Uh, smile?
Thank you, Woody.
Was there something you wanted?
Well, uh, Miss Howe,
I've been here at Cheers
for quite a while now.
I'm a good worker,
I don't take vacations,
I'm never sick,
and I was just wondering if...
No, Woody, Woody, I'm going
to have to stop you right there.
- I cannot give you a title.
- "Title"?
Yes, I know you deserve it,
but the front office
just doesn't let me
hand those things out.
No, Miss Howe,
you don't understand.
You know, sometimes people
work here ten, 15 years
before receiving a title.
- How can I justify...?
- Miss Howe, I want a raise.
Oh, is that all?
That's fine.
How much do you want?
- Just like that?
- Well, of course.
I thought you came in here
to beat me out of a title,
but if you just want
to settle for money,
well, that's fine.
Wait a minute.
Let's just stick
with this title thing.
No, no, Woody, you said
you would settle for a raise.
Now, I'm going
to hold you to it.
Oh, no, I blew it!
I should have demanded a title.
Money gets spent,
but titles are forever.
- No, Woody, I told you...
- Doggone it, Miss Howe,
you're not going
to palm some raise off on me.
I don't want money.
I-I deserve a title.
Woody, I've met some tough
negotiators in my life...
All right, you deserve it.
I'll go to the mat for you.
Congratulations.
You're the new Senior Bartender.
Get out! Senior Bartender?!
Wait till I tell my folks!
To think I came in here
asking for
a stupid little raise,
and now this.
I just hope
it doesn't go to my head.
Oh... that's what's nice
about you, Woody.
Nothing ever goes to your head.
Hey.
So, did you get the raise?
Sammy, Sammy, Sammy,
Sammy, Sammy.
There's more to life than money.
Oh, no,
you didn't get the raise.
I got something much better.
You're looking at Cheers'
new Senior Bartender.
Oh, Woody, you didn't fall
for that, did you?
- Fall for what?
- Oh, man, she conned you.
She talked you
into accepting a title
instead of a raise.
I don't believe you.
Hey, I'd like to
see you do better.
Hey...
she may be able to pull the wool
over your eyes, but not mine.
As a matter of fact,
I'll prove it to you.
You know, I'm due for a raise
around here.
Behold the master here.
- Woody, watch the bar.
- Sam. Mm-hmm.
Considering my new title,
I don't think you can just
give me orders like that.
You're right.
Please forgive me.
Um, I respectfully
request permission
to ask you
to watch the bar, sir.
Money can't buy
that kind of respect.
- I was wondering...
- The answer is no.
Oh, come on, a little raise
is not going to kill you.
No, a little raise
is not going to kill me.
And neither are those little
free rounds of drinks
we're always giving everyone.
Or the little bar tabs
all our friends are
always running up.
But you add them all together,
and they spell bankruptcy.
Which is probably
more than you can do.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean "bankruptcy"?
We're losing money, Sam.
And as long as we are,
no one's getting a raise.
Nothing.
All right, all right.
But if you want to go out there
and save face
in front of your friends,
I can give you a title
just like I did Woody.
Oh... come on.
A-a title to save face?
How childish do you think I am?
Senior Bartender, huh?
Well, Wood, you
know, I'd say a, uh,
little promotion like that
kind of deserves a round
of drinks on the house.
Aw, gee, Mr. Peterson,
I'd love to,
and I-I'm real sorry, but gosh,
I-I just don't think I'd better.
Boy, you give a guy a title,
he turns into a fascist.
So, Wood, now that you scratched
and clawed your way
to the top of your profession,
are you still going
to talk to us little people?
"Little people"?
Oh, right, uh,
you folks don't like
to be called midgets anymore.
Sure, I'll talk to you.
It won't be easy with
your tongue in another state.
So, Sam, how much did you get?
Well, it's kind of complicated,
Woody.
It's all tied up with bonuses
and stock options.
But I can
tell you that,
uh, you're looking at
the new
Executive
Supervising Bartender.
Well, congratulations, Sammy.
You know, I'd say a
promotion like that
kind of deserves a round
of drinks on the house.
Nice try, man. Well, you know.
You just couldn't stand it, Sam,
could you?
That I had a title
and you didn't.
Oh, come on, Woody.
These titles
don't mean anything.
- You want to switch?
- Right.
Senior Bartender.
Like I've been dying
for that one all my life.
Hey, at least mine's
a real great title
and not a stupid
made-up one like yours.
Hey, mine is not made up.
Hey, hey, all right,
all right, all right,
knock it off, all right?!
Will the Senior Idiot Bartender
and the Executive
Supervising Moron
shut their yaps
for about ten seconds?
You're bartenders.
That's it.
You're a bartender
and you're a bartender, period.
Carla's right.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
I, however, am
the Managing Director
of Waitresses.
Well, uh,
congratulations, Carla.
You know, I'd say...
Give it up, Norm.
That does it. What?
Miss Howe, I heard about Carla
and Sam's new titles,
and I must say
I've got a problem.
You've got a problem?
I'll tell you about problems.
I will tell you
all about problems.
We've been losing money
for the last three months.
I have just been informed
that if we continue
to lose money,
the bar is going to
be put on the block,
and then my career will be over,
and so will everyone's
drinking days here at Cheers.
Understood?
Well...
maybe it isn't exactly my
place to say this, but...
Cheers means about as much to me
as it does to anyone here.
This is, uh,
pretty bad news.
I'd say bad news like this
deserves a sympathy
round of drinks
on the house.
What? Oh, what?!
You really don't think
we're gonna lose the bar,
do you?
I mean,
what are we gonna do?
Where are we gonna go?
Home?
All right, listen,
listen, listen.
We-We got to think of some way
to drum up business.
Well, what do you want us to do,
force people to drink here?
- Pour beers down their throats?
- No, Carla.
Well, don't be hasty, Sam.
Let her talk.
- Norm,
you-you work for the big firms.
What do they do
when they need a lot of money?
All right, first off, they...
They go and fire
all the dead wood.
- Yeah, then what?
- I'm long gone by then, Sam.
Well, what if we got something
real valuable
that everybody wanted,
and then gave away chances
to win it?
A raffle?
Sam, would you mind giving
my idea a little consideration
before you just jump in
with yours?
No, no, no...
R-Rebecca, hey,
I think we, uh...
We put our heads together here
and came up with a
solution to your problem.
Sam, please. This is my problem.
I'll handle it by myself.
No, hey, listen.
Everybody needs a little
help now and then.
- All right, Sam,
what's your great idea?
- Well, I-I think
you're gonna like it.
It's-it's, uh, real special.
I-I think
you'll be pleasantly surprised.
It's, uh...
well, we hold a raffle.
- Oh, please.
- Well, actually,
it was, uh, Woody's idea.
We could give away
a Caribbean cruise.
Hey, Woodchuck, not a bad idea.
You think she just handed me
this title?
Listen, it'd be perfect.
I mean, people would be pouring
in here.
We'll be out of the red
in no time.
Come on, let's give it a shot.
All right.
Why not?
It's a mark of how
desperate I am
that I'm willing
to take any half-baked,
hair-brained scheme
from a bunch of bozos like this.
All we ask for
is a little faith.
Eureka!
I have found it.
Sam, anything
compare to the ebullient feeling
one gets
having discovered
and then purchased a fine work
of art?
Yeah, sticking your foot in
a pan of scalding hot water
when you got a fungus itch.
Well, you may not know art,
but you know what you like.
So, uh, correct me
if I'm wrong there, Doc,
but that's from the, uh,
Machiavellian Cubist era,
isn't it?
No, Cliff, but, uh,
thank you for participating
just the same.
No, my anniversary gift
to Lilith is an abstract
expressionist piece.
Would it be rude to ask
what something
like that might cost?
No, not if you like
and appreciate it.
Sorry to interrupt.
Say,
Frasier, w-why'd you buy her
a painting?
Why-Why not get her something
she might actually want?
Oh, no, Lilith will love this.
It's an original Tidwell.
See, it represents
man's struggle
against intransigent fate.
It's called Number Seven.
No. Here, here.
Drink it in for a moment.
And what does it say to you?
It says, we got a live one.
I don't know.
I kind of like it.
Looks like a couple of dogs
getting real familiar.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, it sure does.
- Somebody, hose 'em down.
I should have known better
than to show you Philistines
a fine work of art.
Rebecca?
Yes. Uh, do you mind
if I keep this
in your office for a few days?
- It's my anniversary gift
to Lilith.
- Certainly.
I hope she loves you very much.
Woody, aren't you
finished numbering
those Ping-Pong balls yet?
Almost. I'm just putting
happy faces on all the zeros.
There's a shocker.
Boy, I can't believe this.
This place has been
packed for two weeks now.
This contest was a great idea.
I don't know. I kind of like
the way it used
to be around here.
Yeah, know what you mean, Normy.
All these damn people here
treating us like some kind
of public gathering place.
I think this little raffle idea
of mine turned out pretty well,
don't you?
Don't you think you ought
to give me a little thank you?
A little pat on the back?
Or you on your back?
Oh, Sam, when you
say things like that,
you make me love you even more.
You're being sarcastic, right?
Are you?
Oh, Dr. Crane,
I'm glad you're here.
I hate to mention this, but
you've had that picture
of the two dogs in my office
for quite a while now.
- When are you giving
that to Lilith?
- I'm going to give it
to her tonight.
And by the way,
they are not...
and I can't
say this more emphatically...
two dogs.
Whatever. I want them out
of my office.
They keep reminding me
of how lousy my social life is.
Yeah, but to be honest with ya,
I wouldn't mind winning
that Caribbean cruise prize.
Yeah, call me
Ishmael, but, uh...
Well, the Clavin men, uh,
all go down to the sea.
I guess I must have salt water
in my veins.
Too bad
there isn't an air bubble.
Frasier?
Oh, why there she is now,
the ray of sunshine
I call my blushing bride.
Dear, that color jacket
is not good on you.
Yeah.
Sorry, fellas, she's all mine.
You can't have her.
Well, anyway, Happy
Anniversary, my sweet.
Same to you.
Are you ready for dinner?
Yes. Oh, just first, I've got
a little surprise for you.
Now close your eyes.
Oh, Frasier, love, I'm really
not a proponent of surprises.
My father once asked me
to close my eyes,
and he left for two years.
Well, then, keep your eyes open.
Uh, by the way, are you familiar
with the artist Tidwell?
Of course.
Isn't he the one
who did the painting
of the two dogs commingling,
then sold it
for an ungodly amount
of money to some ninny?
Yes, that's him.
Well, what's my surprise?
Oh, surprise.
Well, it's nothing, really.
It's no big deal.
It's just, um, my car.
Why, Frasier, I'm overwhelmed.
Your Mercedes?
You know, nothing says loving
like something from Stuttgart.
Shall we?
But what does this have
to do with Tidwell?
Oh, well, that's
his name, you see.
I give all my possessions,
uh, pet names.
Well, by the way,
my, uh, cufflinks,
Bert and Ernie.
Attention.
Attention, everyone.
Now's the moment
we've all been waiting for.
I hope you're as
excited as I am,
because this is probably
the most exciting event
I've ever been to
in my entire life.
Well, e-except for the time
that our prize cow
Velveeta
gave birth
to a two-headed calf.
Now I don't know how
many of you have seen
a two-headed calf get
born,
but the ones
who have will bear me out.
Woody, Woody.
Actually, it's not as exciting
as you might think.
Only one of the heads could move.
Woody.
The other one just
seemed kind of dazed.
- Hey, Woody, pick
the damn number, will you then?
- Oh, okay, okay.
And the winner...
of the Cheers
all-expense paid trip
to the Caribbean is...
Number 99.
Hey, that's me!
Say, Woody, uh,
when you turn this
99 upside down,
it kind of looks like
a 66, doesn't it?
It sure does.
excuse me.
We have a correction.
The winner
is 66.
I've got it. I'm 66!
Everybody,
stop the music, stop the music!
What's going on here?
You called 99.
It is 99!
Hey, stop the music here.
Uh, Wood, Woody, man,
we've got a little problem here.
W-What's the problem?
You chose 99 first.
Yeah, but...
but 66 comes before 99.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
what the hell kind
of place is this?
Who's the manager here,
and why aren't they serving
free drinks
to calm this angry crowd?
This is...
This starting to stink
as rotten as those, uh,
game show fixes
back in the '50s.
Gentlemen...
Gentlemen, excuse me here.
There's obviously been
some mistake,
and I'm very sorry
about that,
but would
one of you please
have the decency
to just give up the trip?
No way! Forget it.
- Forget it.
- No, lady, no.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa, come on.
You guys don't really want to go
to the Caribbean, do you?
Do you have any idea
what the sun does
to your skin down there?
Oh, what are you talking about?
I'll tell you what
I'm talking...
Here, I want to introduce you
to last year's winner, man.
He's actually 24.
- I fell asleep on the beach.
- Yeah, thank you.
See what I'm talking about.
Listen, lady,
I don't want to be a
hard case about this,
but if I don't get my trip,
you'll be hearing
from my lawyer.
Hey, what's your boss's name?
I want to complain.
That's it.
I've had it. My career is over.
Oh, no, come on,
don't give up now.
Listen, you have come
so far to get to where you are.
You gonna throw all that away?
Come on, go back out there
and fight.
Show them how tough you are.
- How?
- Cry your pretty little eyes out.
No man can resist that.
That is insulting.
I will not use those tactics.
I will handle this
in a professional,
businesslike manner.
All right, all right.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
There has been a mistake made,
but I am the manager,
and I'm willing to
take responsibility.
What's important to me is that
I have two satisfied customers,
so I'm going to see to it
that both of you get that trip.
All right.
Of course, that will probably
mean the end of my job.
My career.
My life, actually.
But I don't want that
to have any bearing on this.
I just want you both
to be really happy.
And maybe you could send me
a postcard
from the Caribbean
and address it to me at...
Oh, I don't know.
The YWCA or skid row
or something.
Now wait a minute, there,
dear, don't cry, uh...
You won't lose your job.
I'll, uh, give up the prize.
- You-You will?
- Yeah, sure. I never
win anything anyway.
I've always been a loser.
I've never been able to
hold down a job. Uh...
The, uh,
wife left me a couple
of years ago,
and the... my, uh...
My kids won't talk to me. I...
there, there.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
listen, uh...
I-I don't really need
to go to the Caribbean.
You go.
No, no.
No, no, no. No.
I-I want you to go.
Oh, yeah,
my wife will understand.
I'm married to the most
wonderful woman in the world.
I mean, she's so kind,
so understanding.
And to think
that she can maintain
such a wonderful attitude,
despite being...
confined to that wheelchair.
It's just...
That's the most
beautiful thing I've ever heard.
You know something,
they should both go.
Yeah, they should both go.
Hey, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
What about my sob story?
I got eight kids.
Heard it.
Well, how can they both go?
We don't have enough money
for two trips.
- Well, that figures, huh?
- Oh, what a rip-off!
Uh, whoa, whoa, hey,
hey, take it easy.
Take it easy now.
Maybe they can't
both go on a cruise,
but they can...
Uh, they can both win a prize.
What are you talking about?
Well, sure, sure, our
other first prize.
Listen, one of you guys
can go on the cruise,
and the other one
gets this very,
uh, very, special surprise.
Yeah, we have a...
We have a wonderful, uh,
wonderful other first prize.
It's a-a beautiful painting.
Oh, my God,
is that an original Tidwell?
Y-Yes, it certainly is.
I've always wanted a Tidwell.
Um...
Uh, would, uh...
Would mind taking the cruise?
- Not at all.
- Thanks.
Boy, I've dreamed
of owning a Tidwell
all of my life.
And you tried to tell us
you were a loser.
Thanks.
Oh, music.
Say, does that, uh, painting
give you any idea
how to thank me?
Yes, Sam.
Next week, we'll all chip
in and have you fixed.
Uh, excuse me, folks.
We still have the consolation
prize to give away.
847 hand-numbered
Ping-Pong balls.
No, Woody,
Woody, Woody, man,
don't do that.
And the winner of the Cheers
consolation prize is...
Number 11!
Oh, no, here we go again.
No, Woody, let me
explain something to you.
translate