Cliff: "CHEERS" IS FILMED
BEFORE A LIVE STUDIO AUDIENCE.
WHOO! SORRY I'M LATE.
BOY, YOU WILL NOT BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME.
I MADE A RIGHT-HAND
TURN ONTO BOYLSTON
AND RAN INTO THIS
STUPID PARADE.
THEN MY CAR BACKFIRED
AND SCARED THE TAR OUT OF
THESE TWO CUTE, LITTLE
POODLES IN TUTUS
WHO WERE DANCING BY.
DANCING POODLES.
YEAH. ANYWAY, THE DOGS
SPOOKED AND RAN AWAY,
AND THIS CUTE LITTLE GIRL
IN BLUE SEQUINS
RAN AFTER THEM
RIGHT IN FRONT OF THIS
LITTLE CAR
FULL OF CLOWNS
THAT SWERVED
TO MISS HER,
AND THE CAR RAN RIGHT
IN FRONT OF THIS ELEPHANT.
THE ELEPHANT REARED UP,
THREW THIS SWAMI GUY OFF
WHO WAS RIDING
ON HIS TUSK.
SAM, THIS IS THE LAMEST EXCUSE
YOU'VE EVER GIVEN ME.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST SAY,
"I'M SORRY, REBECCA.
I OVERSLEPT.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN."
THAT REALLY
MAKES ME...
I'M SORRY, REBECCA.
I JUST OVERSLEPT.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
* MAKIN' YOUR WAY
IN THE WORLD TODAY *
* TAKES EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GOT *
* TAKIN' A BREAK
FROM ALL YOUR WORRIES *
* SURE WOULD
HELP A LOT *
* WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO GET AWAY? *
* SOMETIMES
YOU WANT TO GO *
* WHERE EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* AND THEY'RE ALWAYS
GLAD YOU CAME *
* YOU WANT TO BE
WHERE YOU CAN SEE *
* OUR TROUBLES
ARE ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANT TO BE *
* WHERE EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* YOU WANT TO GO
WHERE PEOPLE KNOW *
* PEOPLE ARE
ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANT TO GO *
* WHERE EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOUR NAME *
FRASIER, I'M
DOUBLE-PARKED OUTSIDE.
FINISH YOUR DRINK,
AND LET'S GO.
IN A MINUTE.
I'VE JUST
TOUCHED MY GLASS.
DON'T BALK, JELLY BEAR.
I'M NOT BALKING,
MOON-PIE.
I'M SIMPLY TRYING
TO FINISH MY DRINK.
YOU'D UNDERSTAND
IF YOU'D HAD AS
TRYING A DAY
AS I'VE HAD.
THE KIND OF DAY
YOU'VE HAD?
LORD, IF I HEAR
ONE MORE YUPPIE
SNIVEL ABOUT HIS
INABILITY TO LOVE,
I'LL SMACK HIM.
BOO-HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO.
I SAW NINE CLIENTS
TODAY WITH NO LUNCH.
I SAW 10. 15, IF YOU COUNT
MULTIPLE PERSONALITIES.
OH, YEAH? WELL,
YOU SHOULD HAVE--
HEY, HEY,
COME ON, PLEASE.
YOU'RE
A LITTLE TENSE.
YOU GOT TO RELAX,
TAKE A FEW DAYS OFF,
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE A VACATION
OR SOMETHING.
VACATION? HA!
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
SO EASY, SAM,
AS IF ONE COULD
PICK UP JUST LIKE THAT.
WE ARE PROFESSIONALS
WITH COMMITMENTS
AND OBLIGATIONS.
OUR PATIENTS
DEPEND UPON US.
I'LL CLEAR MY SCHEDULE
IF YOU WILL.
- NASSAU OR SAINT THOMAS?
- LET'S GO TALK TO
THE TRAVEL AGENT.
THERE YOU GO.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
HAS ANYBODY SEEN
WOODY?
HE WAS SCHEDULED
TO BE HERE AT 6:00.
HE'S GONNA BE LATE.
GOOD GOD, PEOPLE!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY I BOTHER
TO PREPARE A WORK SCHEDULE.
EVERYBODY JUST COMES AND GOES
AS THEY DAMN WELL PLEASE.
YEAH. HE DID SEND THESE,
THOUGH.
"I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
PLEASE DOCK MY PAY."
NOW, THIS IS
THE WAY TO BE LATE.
WHERE IS THE LITTLE...
ANYWAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, NO, SAMMY.
I'VE BEEN A MOTHER
FOR 18 YEARS.
WHEN SOMEONE SAYS,
"I DON'T KNOW"
LIKE THAT,
THEY KNOW.
COUGH IT UP, OR I'M
GONNA GET IT OUT OF
YOU ANOTHER WAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
HE'S AUDITIONING
FOR A PLAY.
A PLAY?
YEAH.
HICKEY McHICK
FROM HICKSVILLE
WANTS TO ACT?
HE'S BEEN HANGING OUT
AT THIS LITTLE LOCAL PLAYHOUSE
DOING ALL
THE ODDS AND ENDS.
SWEEPING,
CLEANING TOILETS--
EVERYTHING NO ONE ELSE
WANTS TO DO.
I WONDER IF WOODY
WOULD LIKE TO ACT
OVER AT MY HOUSE.
HERE HE COMES.
HE'S VERY SENSITIVE
ABOUT THIS.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT HIS ACTING.
- HEY, EVERYBODY.
- HEY, WOODY.
IF I KNEW YOU WANTED
A ROLE, SO BADLY,
I WOULD HAVE STOPPED
AT THE BAKERY.
SAM.
I'M SORRY.
HOW DID
THE AUDITION GO?
GREAT. SAID MY LINES
FASTER THAN ANYONE ELSE.
NOW, WOODMAN,
WHEN DID YOU GET BIT
BY THE OLD ACTING BUG?
BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL
IN HANOVER.
I WAS IN THE CHORUS
OF TH SENIOR CLASS
PRODUCTION OF HELLO, DONALD.
ISN'T THAT
HELLO, DOLLY?
OH, NO, NO,
THEY HAD TO
CHANGE THE NAME.
DONALD WEXLER WAS THE ONLY
GUY WHO COULD SING THE PART.
SO WHAT'S THIS PLAY
YOU TRIED OUT FOR?
WELL, IT'S
A BRAND-NEW ONE.
IT'S CALLED
AUTHORS IN HELL.
I'M HOPING TO PLAY
EITHER MARK TWAIN,
ONE OF THE GUYS FROM
THE ALGONQUIN ROUND
TABLE,
OR SATAN.
BUT, HECK, I'D BE
JUST AS HAPPY PLAYING A
FIRE-BREATHING INCUBUS.
THEY GET TO STAY
ON-STAGE THE WHOLE
FOUR HOURS.
HEY, THAT'S MY DIRECTOR,
GRIF PALMER.
- THIS MUST MEAN
I GOT THE PART.
- OR THAT
HE'S THIRSTY.
- HI, MR. PALMER.
CAN I GET YOU A DRINK?
- NO, THANKS.
I GOT THE PART!
WOODY, YOU'RE
A MULTITALENTED
YOUNG MAN.
I DIDN'T GET
THE PART?
YOU KNOW,
I'VE TRIED OUT
SO MANY TIMES
AND I'VE NEVER
GOTTEN A PART.
MAYBE I'M JUST
WASTING MY TIME
IN THE THEATER.
COME ON, WOODY,
DON'T GIVE UP
SO EASILY.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A YOUNG MAN
NAMED GRIF PALMER
WHO ALSO AUDITIONED
FOR MANY A ROLE THAT
HE DIDN'T GET.
- AS MANY AS ME?
- WELL, NO.
WAIT. WAIT. I'VE
GOT A THOUGHT.
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY
IF I TOLD YOU
I'VE SELECTED
A FRESH NEW FACE
TO UNDERSTUDY THE ROLE
OF MARK TWAIN?
I THINK YOU'LL BE HEARING
HIS NAME QUITE A BIT
FROM NOW ON,
MR. WOODY BOYD.
HEY, THAT'S ME!
HEY, EVERYBODY,
I'M GOING TO BE
AN UNDERSTUDY!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S GOOD.
WOODY, THIS ISN'T
GOING TO INTERFERE
WITH YOUR JOB, IS IT?
GEE, I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL...
YEAH.
I'M SORRY, WOODY.
I NEED YOU HERE NIGHTS.
MISS HOWE, THIS IS
MY GOLDEN CHANCE.
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
I JUST GOT TO DO IT!
I JUST GOT TO!
THAT WAS
REALLY GOOD, MAN.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
JUST FOR A SECOND
HERE?
LET HIM DO IT.
- I WOULD LOVE TO,
BUT I NEED HIM HERE.
HE'LL BE HERE.
YOU SAW THAT
PERFORMANCE.
THEY'RE NOT
GONNA LET HIM
GO ON.
- BREAK A LEG, WOODY.
- ALL RIGHT!
WELCOME TO THE
THEATER, WOODY--
TO THE RANKS OF
THE LUNTS AND THE OLIVIERS.
TO A PROFESSION
RIPE WITH STYLE,
WITH HISTORY, WITH DIGNITY.
TO A CALLING
I ONLY HOPE WILL
BRING YOU AS MUCH JOY
AS IT HAS BROUGHT ME.
- HI.
- HELLO.
- YOU KNOW GRIF PALMER?
- YEAH. HE'S THE JANITOR
AT MY KIDS' SCHOOL.
"HELLO, GOOD-MANNERED
AND AGREEABLE CHILDREN."
HEY, EVERYBODY.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S THAT FAMOUS
ACTOR ROBERT DeZERO.
NO, CARLA.
IT'S ME--WOODY.
WOODY,
YOU HAVE BEEN
COMING IN HERE
DRESSED IN THAT
RIDICULOUS GET-UP
FOR THREE WEEKS NOW.
WHEN ARE YOU
GOING TO STOP
THIS NONSENSE?
CARLA, AS AN UNDERSTUDY,
I HAVE TO BE DRESSED
AND READY TO GO ON
AT A MOMENT'S NOTICE.
PUTTING ON MAKE-UP
LIKE THIS CAN TAKE HOURS,
BUT I WOULDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO UNDERSTAND.
WHY, BECAUSE I'M NOT
IN THE THE-A-TAH?
NO, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T WEAR MAKE-UP.
HUCKLEBERRY ALERT.
HEY, MARK TWIT!
WOODY, WOULD YOU RUN
UPSTAIRS AND GET SOME CHANGE?
ONES AND FIVES.
NEW BILLS IF THEY'VE GOT THEM.
"AH. LET US NOT
BE TOO PARTICULAR.
"IT IS BETTER TO HAVE
OLD SECONDHAND DIAMONDS
THAN NONE AT ALL."
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
MANAGE IT
WITHOUT ANY QUOTES?
"I COULD DO IT AS EASY
AS FALLING OFF A LOG."
WOODY, JUST DO IT!
"WHEN ANGRY, COUNT FOUR.
WHEN VERY ANGRY, SWEAR."
DAMN IT!
THERE YOU GO.
SAM, RUN UPSTAIRS
AND GET ME SOME CHANGE.
AW, COME ON.
THAT'S A JUNIOR
BARTENDER'S JOB.
YOU ARE
THE JUNIOR BARTENDER.
OH, RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT I'M WORKING
MY WAY UP, YOU KNOW.
PRETTY SOON I MIGHT
EVEN OWN MY OWN BAR.
- GOOD EVENING,
MA'AM.
- OH, HELLO, THERE.
OH, THANK YOU.
I'M BLIND AS A BAT
WITHOUT GLASSES.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
A BAT WITH GLASSES.
- THAT'S FUNNY.
- YEAH. I CAN IMAGINE.
I BELIEVE
IT MIGHT RAIN SOON.
"ONE OF
THE BRIGHTEST GEMS
"OF THE NEW ENGLAND
WEATHER
IS THE DAZZLING
UNCERTAINTY OF IT."
WELL, WHAT CAN YOU DO?
"EVERYBODY TALKS
ABOUT THE WEATHER,
BUT NO ONE EVER DOES
ANYTHING ABOUT IT."
MAY I HAVE A GLASS
OF WHITE WINE, PLEASE?
WINE...WHITE WINE.
UH...LET'S SEE, NOW.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF WINE
IN SAN FRANCISCO,
DON'T THEY?
OH, I SUPPOSE THEY DO.
"ONE OF THE COLDEST
WINTERS I EVER SPENT
WAS SUMMER
IN SAN FRANCISCO."
SORRY. THAT'S CLOSE
AS I COULD GET.
HA HA HA!
YOU'RE RATHER AMUSING.
THANKS, BUT I'VE BEEN
QUOTING MARK TWAIN.
I KNOW. I THINK
THAT'S AMUSING.
AND I SUPPOSE THAT
YOU'VE BEEN TOLD
THAT YOU LOOK
SOMETHING LIKE HIM.
YEAH. I GET THAT A LOT.
YOU LOOK A LITTLE BIT
LIKE EMILY DICKINSON.
SHE'S ONE OF THE AUTHORS
IN HELL.
OH, THAT'S AN UNKIND
ASSUMPTION, SIR.
ALTHOUGH SHE'S NEVER BEEN
ONE OF MY FAVORITES, EITHER.
HERE'S YOUR CHANGE,
AND, OH, YEAH, A LITTLE
SOMETHING FOR YOU HERE.
WHAT IS IT?
ONE OF THE SHRIMPS FROM
UP AT THE BUFFET TABLE.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
MY FIRST CHOICE
WAS AN OYSTER.
SO WAS MINE,
BUT I HIRED YOU.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN HERE BEFORE, HAVE I?
NO. I DON'T
GET AROUND MUCH
SINCE MY HUSBAND
LLOYD PASSED AWAY.
WE USED TO COME
BY HERE EVERY EVENING
DURING OUR WALK,
BUT LLOYD NEVER
LET US COME IN.
HE GOT JEALOUS
WHEN I WAS AROUND OTHER MEN.
I CAN SEE WHY.
OH, FOR HEAVEN'S SAKES.
I THINK YOU'RE BLUSHING.
OH, IT'S THE WINE.
ALTHOUGH,
AS MARK TWAIN SAID,
"MAN IS THE ONLY
ANIMAL THAT BLUSHES..."
OR NEEDS TO."
ALL ABOARD
THE S.S. DELMONICO,
EMBARKING AT 0900 HOURS FOR NASSAU,
SAINT THOMAS,
MARTINIQUE,
AND OTHER EXOTIC
PORTS OF CALL.
SO YOU TOOK
MY ADVICE, HUH?
YES. AS OF CLOSE
OF BUSINESS TODAY,
IT'S JUST US,
A COUPLE OF FUN-LOVING
SWABBIES LOST AT SEA.
WE'LL BE TOTO
INCOMMUNICADO.
NO BUSINESS, NO CLIENTS,
NO PHONE CALLS...
LILITH, WE PROMISED
NO BEEPERS.
I WON'T GIVE IT UP
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
YOU'LL HAVE TO
PERFORM A STRIP SEARCH.
THE VACATION HAS BEGUN!
NOW HEAR THIS!
HEAR THIS, STERN.
PREPARE TO BE BOARDED!
FOLKS, I HAVE A BIT OF
BAD NEWS THAT MAY
AFFECT A LOT OF YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA BEAT
AROUND THE BUSH.
I'M JUST GONNA
COME RIGHT OUT AND SAY IT.
LAST CALL.
WELL, WHAT THE HECK?
MAYBE
I'LL GIVE VERA A THRILL
AND GO HOME
A LITTLE EARLY TONIGHT.
ALTHOUGH, YOU KNOW,
SHE DID LOOK KIND
OF THRILLED WHEN I LEFT.
EXCUSE ME, MARY.
LISTEN.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A SECOND.
AND THEN I'LL
SEE YOU HOME.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
BUT THANK YOU.
I'VE HAD A
WONDERFUL EVENING.
WELL, I HAVE, TOO.
I'VE REALLY ENJOYED
YOUR COMPANY.
- YOU'RE A VERY NICE LADY.
- AND YOU'RE
A LOVELY GENTLEMAN.
AND MAY I ADD,
YOU HAVE THE MOST GLORIOUS
HEAD OF HAIR
I'VE SEEN ON ANY MAN
SINCE MY LLOYD DIED.
GEE, I HATE TO
DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT THIS
IS A WIG.
YES. SO WAS LLOYD'S.
UH, PARDON ME, MA'AM,
BUT THAT ADORABLE
BARTENDER OVER THERE...
- WOODY?
- YES.
IS HE KEEPING COMPANY
WITH ANYONE
IN PARTICULAR?
NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
WELL, I THINK
HE'S VERY SPECIAL.
WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S THE NICEST
WAY OF PUTTING IT.
- GOOD NIGHT.
OH, WOODS.
YOU KNOW THAT
DUST IN A DRESS
YOU'VE BEEN
YAKKING WITH?
MARY?
YOU DIDN'T,
BY ANY CHANCE,
HAPPEN TO TELL HER
THAT YOU'RE WEARING
OLD MAN MAKE-UP FOR A PLAY,
DID YOU?
THAT SORT OF THING IS
PRETTY HARD TO WORK INTO
POLITE CONVERSATION.
WITH YOUR MAKEUP AND
THE LIGHTING IN HERE
AND THOSE MR. MAGOO
GLASSES OF HERS,
I THINK SHE GOT
THE WRONG IDEA.
SHE'S GOT
THE HOTS FOR YOU.
CARLA, YOU'RE CRAZY.
SHE'S JUST A SAD, OLD
WOMAN WHO NEEDED SOMEONE
TO TALK TO.
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD UNDERSTAND THAT.
THERE'S NO WAY
SHE'S GONNA GO FOR ME,
I MEAN, IN ORDER FOR HER
TO FALL IN LOVE WITH ME,
I'D HAVE TO BE
THE BEST DARN ACTOR
IN BOSTON.
OH, NO!
I'M THE BEST DARN
ACTOR IN BOSTON.
HELLO, MON.
I'M SORRY.
LIMBO NIGHT'S TUESDAY,
MAN.
HEY, MAN, YOU STOP
WITH DE BAD MOUTH STYLIN',
OR I'M GONNA HAVE TO
BOP YOU ON DE HEAD
WIT DE BANANA BOAT, MON.
FRASIER. FRASIER, PLEASE
CUT THE CALYPSO.
ISN'T IT ENOUGH
THE CAB DRIVER ALREADY
TOOK A SWING AT YOU?
YOU GUYS LOOK LIKE
YOU HAD
A GOOD TIME.
WE HAD OODLES OF FUN,
AND WE LOST A COMBINED
11 POUNDS, TO BOOT.
YOU LOST WEIGHT
ON A CRUISE?
I HEARD THERE ARE
WALL-TO-WALL MEALS.
THERE ARE ALSO
WALL-TO-WALL WAVES.
WELL, FORTUNATELY,
AFTER THREE DAYS
OF GIVING CHEF HUGO'S
FINE CUISINE
BACK TO THE SEA,
WE WERE FITTED WITH
THESE LITTLE EAR PATCHES.
THEY SEEMED TO DO THE TRICK.
AND PUT US TO SLEEP FOR
THE REST OF THE TRIP.
SO YOU GUYS SPENT SEVEN DAYS
AND NIGHTS
SNOOZING AND BARFING
YOUR WAY THROUGH THE CARIBBEAN?
AND WE'VE NEVER
FELT SLIMMER AND
MORE REFRESHED.
WELL, WHAT SAY WE GO
AND GET SOME LUNCH, THERE,
MY LITTLE MARINE MELON?
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
JUST PROMISE ME
YOU WON'T REFER
TO THE WAITRESS
AS "SEESTAH."
* DAY-O, DAY-O *
* DAYLIGHT COME
AND ME WAN GO HOME **
YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE.
OH! HEY, WOODY,
I THOUGHT
YOUR PLAY CLOSED.
IT DID, LAST NIGHT.
SO WHAT'S WITH
THE OLD GEEZER DRAG?
I WAS WITH MARY.
ANOTHER DATE, HUH?
IT WASN'T A DATE.
I JUST TOOK HER TO LUNCH,
THEN A MOVIE,
AND THEN DANCING.
HEY, WOODY,
WOODY, WOODY, WOODY.
MAN, THIS IS CRAZY.
YOU'VE BEEN OUT WITH MARY
EVERY NIGHT THIS WEEK.
YOU CAN'T SPEND YOUR LIFE
DRESSED UP LIKE MARK TWAIN.
WHY NOT? HE DID.
OH, SAM, I--I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
I'VE TRIED TO TELL HER,
BUT EVERY TIME I DO,
SHE JUST STARES AT ME
WITH THOSE BIG, LONELY
EYES.
I MEAN,
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT
THAT MY GOD-GIVEN
ACTING TALENT
WAS GONNA TURN OUT
TO BE A CURSE?
ARE WE VOTING?
YOU GOT TO
NIP THIS IN THE BUD.
I AGREE THERE, WOODY.
FOR A YOUNG MAN
SUCH AS YOURSELF
TO BE SPENDING SO MUCH TIME
WITH AN OLDER WOMAN IS--
EH, IT'S JUST UNNATURAL.
YEAH, WELL,
HOW ABOUT YOU,
CLIFF?
YOU SPEND
LOTS OF TIME
WITH YOUR MOTHER,
AND SHE'S OLD.
MY MA'S NOT OLD,
AND SHE'S NEVER GONNA
DIE BEFORE I DO,
SO JUST SHUT UP, OK?
HEY. HEY.
HEY, WOODS.
MARY JUST CAME IN.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET HER A GLASS
OF SOMETHING.
SHE DOESN'T DRINK
IN THE AFTERNOON.
NO, I MEAN
TO PUT HER TEETH IN.
HI, MARY.
HI.
- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- I JUST WANTED
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YEAH.
CAN WE SIT DOWN?
I'D LIKE TO TALK
WITH YOU A SECOND.
- ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN. I KNOW HOW LONELY
YOU'VE BEEN
SINCE LLOYD PASSED AWAY.
OH, HOW LONELY
I WAS.
I'M NOT ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, "LONELINESS
IS HIGHLY UNDERRATED.
"IT'S ONE
OF THE FEW THINGS LEFT
THAT YOU CAN
STILL DO ALONE."
DID MARK TWAIN
SAY THAT?
WELL, NO, BUT I'M
KIND OF RUNNING OUT
OF HIS MATERIAL.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO GIVE YOU.
IT'S LLOYD'S WATCH.
I WANT YOU
TO HAVE IT.
- NO, I COULDN'T.
- OH, PLEASE.
UH, GEE, THANKS, MARY.
- WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME
FOR A SECOND?
- SURE.
OH, WAIT.
I JUST WANT TO MEMORIZE
THE WAY YOU LOOK
IN THIS LIGHT.
GO AHEAD.
SAM, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
NOW SHE'S MEMORIZING
THE WAY I LOOK
IN DIFFERENT KINDS
OF LIGHT.
AW, NO, WOODY,
WOMEN DO THAT
ALL THE TIME.
AND SHE GAVE ME
HER DEAD HUSBAND'S WATCH.
YOU COULD DO
A LOT WORSE.
LISTEN. YOU GOT
TO END THIS RIGHT NOW.
GO ON.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T STAND
THE THOUGHT
OF HURTING
SOMEBODY'S FEELINGS.
I KNOW.
CARLA, YOU'VE BEEN DUMPED
A MILLION TIMES.
WHAT'S THE BEST WAY
TO DO IT?
YOU KNOW, THE ONLY REASON I'M
NOT CLEANING YOUR CLOCK
IS BECAUSE YOU REMIND ME
OF JED CLAMPETT.
LISTEN, YOU ARE NOT
DUMPING HER.
YOU'RE LEVELING WITH HER.
NOW, IT'S THE ONLY
HONEST THING TO DO.
NOW, GO ON.
BE A MAN. DO IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SAM.
IT'S TIME I STOOD
ON MY OWN TWO FEET
AND DID
WHAT'S RIGHT.
RIGHT.
WILL YOU
COME WITH ME?
- THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU'VE GOT TO DO BY YOURSELF.
- I CAN'T.
- I'M NOT
GOING TO DO IT, WOODY.
- PLEASE, SAM. I CAN'T
DO THIS BY MYSELF.
- ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
- THANK YOU.
YOU BELIEVE
I'M JUST AN UNDERSTUDY?
UH, MARY?
YES?
WOODY WANTS TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WELL, UH,
MARY, YOU SEE...
UH, I MEAN,
YOU KNOW, UH, HOW...
I DON'T SUPPOSE
THERE'S ANY CHANCE
YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT YET.
ACTUALLY, I DO.
LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING
TO YOU, WOODY.
I'M A VERY LONELY WOMAN
SINCE I LOST MY HUSBAND.
MY FAMILY LIVES
OUT OF STATE,
I NEVER SEE
MY GRANDCHILDREN,
AND MOST OF MY FRIENDS
HAVE MOVED
OR PASSED AWAY.
SEEMS MY DAYS ARE
SO HARD TO FILL.
I SWEAR, THERE WERE
MORNINGS WHEN IT
DIDN'T SEEM WORTHWHILE
GETTING OUT OF BED.
AND THEN I MET YOU--
STOP. STOP.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
HEAVENS, NO!
I'M THREE TIMES
YOUR AGE.
- YOU KNOW
THAT I'M YOUNG?
- WOODY, I MAY BE OLD,
BUT I'M NOT STUPID.
- WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
EVER TELL ME THIS?
- WELL, I ENJOYED
YOUR COMPANY SO.
BESIDES, EVERY TIME
I WANTED TO,
YOU STARTED QUOTING
THE JUMPING FROG
OF CALAVERAS COUNTY.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
UPSET WITH ME.
OH, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M JUST GLAD I DIDN'T
HAVE TO DUMP YOU.
AND BESIDES,
YOU HAD SUCH FUN
PLAYING THE PART,
AND YOU WERE
QUITE EXCELLENT.
- YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT TO MARRY ME?
- NO, WOODY.
WILL YOU BE
MY GRANDMA?
- WELL, MAYBE
A FAVORITE AUNT.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A DEAL.
MY BIRTHDAY'S
JULY 23.
I JUST GAVE YOU
THE WATCH.
BY THE WAY,
WE'RE STILL ON
FOR POT ROAST
ON SATURDAY.
LEAVE THE WIG AT HOME.
BYE-BYE.
BYE.
WELL, I GUESS
IN A REALLY
WEIRD WAY,
IT KIND OF
WORKED OUT,
DIDN'T IT?
- YEAH. I'M STILL
A LITTLE DEPRESSED.
- WHY?
WELL, MARY KNOWS
I'M A GOOD ACTOR,
BUT NOW THAT AUTHORS
IN HELL IS CLOSED,
I'M NOT GONNA GET TO SHOW
THE REST OF THE WORLD.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, I GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU
DO IT RIGHT HERE?
HOP RIGHT UP THERE
AND SHOW THE WHOLE BAR.
AW, I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT!
GATHER ROUND, EVERYBODY.
I'M GOING TO DO
AUTHORS IN HELL.
I MEAN,
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU, MISS HOWE.
WELL, I WAS PLANNING
TO WAIT FOR THE MOVIE,
BUT GO AHEAD.
IMAGINE, IF YOU WILL,
A HUGE BOOK OPENS UP,
AND I, MARK TWAIN,
STEP OUT.
I AM SURROUNDED BY VARIOUS
TORMENTED AMERICAN WRITERS
AND SATAN.
THE LIGHTS DIM.
"PERSONS ATTEMPTING TO FIND
A MOTIVE IN THIS NARRATIVE
"WILL BE PROSECUTED.
"PERSONS ATTEMPTING
TO FIND A MORAL IN IT
"WILL BE BANISHED.
"PERSONS ATTEMPTING
TO FIND A PLOT IN IT
WILL BE SHOT."
WOODY, GO ON.
I JUST SIT HERE
AND SMOKE.
I DON'T TALK AGAIN
UNTIL THE MIDDLE
OF ACT FOUR.
translate