CHEERS IS FILMED BEFORE
A LIVE STUDIO AUDIENCE.
OH, GEORGE! GEORGE!
GEORGE...
ARE YOU REAL?
HOT BUTTERED RUM
AND AN IRISH COFFEE.
OH, NO.
NOT
IT'S A WONDERFUL
LIFE AGAIN.
HOW MANY TIMES A DAY
ARE THEY GONNA SHOW
THIS GOLDEN MOLDY?
SIX.
FROM NOW UNTIL NEW YEAR'S
ON CHANNEL 13,
IT'S A WONDERFUL MONTH.
THIS FLICK'S SO
SWEET, IT MAKES
MY TEETH ACHE.
UH-OH. STUPID ALERT.
I CAN GUARANTEE YOU
FROM MY DAYS IN ACCOUNTING
IF YOU RUN SHORT
AT THE BANK,
EVERYONE IN TOWN DOES NOT
DASH OVER, CASH IN HAND,
TO BAIL YOU OUT.
HERE COMES THE
GUSHIEST PART.
HAVE THEY NO SHAME?
OH, YECCH, YECCH,
YECCH, YECCH.
* FOR AULD LANG SYNE *
* WE'LL DRINK A CUP
OF KINDNESS YET *
* FOR AULD LANG SYNE **
COULD I HAVE
A KLEENEX, SAM?
I MUST HAVE GOTTEN
SOMETHING IN MY EYE.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
MUST BE SOMETHING
IN THE AIR.
* MAKING YOUR WAY
IN THE WORLD TODAY *
* TAKES EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GOT *
* TAKING A BREAK
FROM ALL YOUR WORRIES *
* SURE WOULD HELP A LOT *
* WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO
GET AWAY? *
* SOMETIMES
YOU WANNA GO *
* WHERE EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* AND THEY'RE ALWAYS
GLAD YOU CAME *
* YOU WANNA BE
WHERE YOU CAN SEE *
* OUR TROUBLES
ARE ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANT TO BE WHERE
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* YOU WANT TO GO
WHERE PEOPLE KNOW *
* PEOPLE ARE ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANNA GO WHERE
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME **
GOOD AFTERNOON, ALL YOU
WARMHEARTED AND GENEROUS PEOPLE.
CLIFFIE, WHAT'S
WITH THE BOX?
WELL, THE POSTAL CARRIERS
ARE HAVING A FOOD DRIVE.
IF YOU GOOD SAMARITANS
FILL THIS BOX WITH CANNED GOODS,
I'LL WIN A FREE TRIP
TO DISNEY WORLD.
IMAGINE THAT--
PIRATES OF THE CARIBBEAN,
MR. TOAD'S WILD RIDE,
AND ME.
WHO ARE
THE CANS FOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
THE POOR, NEEDY--
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THEY MAKE SUCH A FUSS
ABOUT MOTHER THERESA.
EXCUSE ME THERE, DOCTOR,
BUT DO I DETECT
A WRY NOTE OF CYNICISM THERE
IN YOUR COMMENTS?
CYNICAL, ME?
HOW COULD I POSSIBLY
BE CYNICAL LIVING
IN A NATION
IN WHICH WE CELEBRATE
THE HOLY BIRTH OF A BABE
IN A MANGER
WITH PERRY COMO
IN HAWAII?
HEY, BOSS LADY,
WHAT ARE YOU ALL
DUDED UP FOR?
- YOU MEAN WHY AM I NOT
WEARING A SWEATSHIRT
AND PLASTIC EARRINGS?
- YEAH.
BECAUSE I JUST CAME
FROM THE COMPANY
CHRISTMAS PARTY.
DID YOU CORNER MR. DRAKE
UNDER THE MISTLETOE
AND MAKE NICE?
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
* OH, REBECCA DIDN'T GET
HER CHRISTMAS GOOSE **
BUT I DID HAVE PLENTY
OF TIME TO MAKE OUT
NEXT WEEK'S SCHEDULE.
WHOA.
WAIT A SECOND HERE.
YOU GOT US WORKING
ON CHRISTMAS EVE.
THAT'S A HOLIDAY.
NO. CHRISTMAS
IS A HOLIDAY.
WELL, IT'S
A HOLIDAY EVE.
I'M GONNA PAY YOU ALL
TIME-AND-A-HALF.
NO. HEY, FORGET IT.
WE CANNOT BE BOUGHT.
I CAN.
SWEETHEART,
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE HOME
WITH YOUR FAMILY?
WOULD YOU?
GOOD POINT, GOOD POINT.
UH, WOODY!
UH, WOODY CAN'T WORK.
HE HAS TO GO BACK HOME
TO INDIANA AND BE
WITH HIS FOLKS.
NOT THIS YEAR, SAM.
I'M A BIG BOY NOW.
I GOT
COMMITMENTS IN THE CITY.
I LANDED A PART
IN OUR CHILDREN'S THEATER
PRODUCTION OF THE STORY OF SNOW.
I PLAY THE KING
OF THE FLAKES.
THAT WILL BE
A STRETCH.
WE ONLY HAVE A MATINEE
ON CHRISTMAS EVE,
SO I'D BE HAPPY TO
WORK THAT NIGHT,
ENCORES PERMITTING.
GREAT.
JUST SO YOU GUYS KNOW
I'M NOT PULLING RANK,
I'M SCHEDULED TO WORK
THAT NIGHT TOO.
NO, WAIT. LISTEN.
NO WAY AM I
PUNCHING THE CLOCK
ON ONE OF THE MOST
SACRED AND FAMILY NIGHTS
OF THE WHOLE YEAR.
WHAT DO YOU
HAVE PLANNED,
AN INTIMATE LITTLE
DINNER WITH ONE
OF YOUR NIECES?
SHE MAKES IT SOUND
SO CHEAP.
OH, JOY.
CHRISTMAS EVE.
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS,
KNEE-DEEP
IN TINSEL AND WRAPPING PAPER,
WILL HAVE UTTERED
THOSE HEARTFELT WORDS,
"IS THIS ALL I GOT?"
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
HANGING THAT THERE
FOR MY BENEFIT.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHO'D WANT TO KISS SOMEBODY
WHO'D MAKE THEM WORK ON
CHRISTMAS EVE?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
THE REVIEWS ARE IN.
WE'RE A HIT!
LET'S TAKE A PEEK.
OK.
"THE STORY OF SNOW
WAS WAY EXCELLENT.
"I THINK ANY KID IN
MISS PODESTA'S CLASS
WHO MISSES IT
IS A FULL-ON GOON."
AND THAT FROM THE KID
WHO PANNED GOLDILOCKS.
I'M GONNA CALL MY MOM
AND READ IT TO HER.
I SURE AM GLAD I STAYED
IN BOSTON AFTER ALL.
IF I WAS HOME RIGHT NOW,
I'D JUST BE SITTING AROUND
LISTENING TO
MY AUNT AND UNCLE
TALK ABOUT WHO'S DEAD
AND WHO'S SICK
AND WHO LOST PART OF THEIR HAND
IN THE THRESHER.
HELLO, MOM?
I MISS YOU ALL SO MUCH.
LOOK AT
THE POOR SLOB,
FORCED TO
HUMILIATE HIMSELF
IN SOME STUPID OUTFIT
JUST TO
MAKE A FEW BUCKS
FOR THE
HOLIDAY SEASON.
WHY DOESN'T HE JUST
WEAR A SIGN,
"LOSER FOR HIRE"?
HEY, PETERSON.
YOU'RE LATE AGAIN.
I'M NOT COVERING
FOR YOU THIS TIME.
I THINK YOU HAVE
THE WRONG PETERSON.
OH, YEAH? WHEN YOU FIND
THE RIGHT ONE,
TELL HIM NOT TO SWEAT
IN THE HAT SO MUCH.
WELL, I GUESS
I'M BUSTED.
OK, I DIDN'T MENTION
ANYTHING TO YOU GUYS BECAUSE I
THOUGHT YOU GUYS
JUST MIGHT RAZZ ME
A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT BEING
A SANTA CLAUS
OVER AT NAGELS.
THAT WAS YOU?
THAT'S WHAT
MY KID MEANT
WHEN SHE SAID
SANTA SMELLS
LIKE THE PLACE
WHERE MOMMY WORKS.
ARE YOU MAKING
THE STUFFING BONE-DRY
THE WAY I LOVE IT?
CAN'T YOU FREEZE SOME
AND MAIL IT TO ME?
NO, NOT THE GRAVY.
THAT WOULD BE STUPID.
MY MOTHER.
OH, GOD. CAN YOU
BELIEVE REBECCA?
AS LONG AS ONE
CUSTOMER STAYS,
WE ALL STAY.
IT'S 10:30. THE GUY'S BEEN
NURSING THE SAME DRINK
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
YEAH, I WISH HE'D HURRY
THE HELL UP SO WE COULD
GET OUT OF HERE.
THE PRESENTS
ARE ALL WRAPPED,
ALL THE KIDS
ARE IN BED,
AND EDDIE'S
WAITING UP FOR ME
SO THAT WE CAN
EXCHANGE OUR GOODIES
IN PRIVATE.
YOU DON'T WAIT UNTIL
CHRISTMAS MORNING TO
OPEN YOUR PRESENTS?
YEAH, BUT WE LIKE TO
EXCHANGE OUR GOODIES
IN PRIVATE.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S YOU, ME, AND WOODY
EXCHANGE PRESENTS
RIGHT NOW.
AND WHEN HE LEAVES,
WE CAN LEAVE.
GOOD IDEA.
DAD REPAIRED
THE WISE MEN?
IS BALTHAZAR
STILL BLACK?
WOODY, SOON AS YOU FINISH,
WE'RE GONNA EXCHANGE
PRESENTS.
OK, MOM,
GOT TO GO.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
HERE YOU GO, SAM.
HERE, CARLA.
OH, NO. WAIT.
THAT'S MISS HOWE'S.
YOU...YOU GOT SOMETHING
FOR REBECCA?
WELL, IT'S
NOTHING SPECIAL.
JUST AN ANTIQUE
SILVER FRAME
WITH A SILHOUETTE
OF HER FACE
THAT I CUT OUT
IN BLACK VELVET.
WOW!
I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT
'CAUSE I GOT YOU
THE SAME THING.
WELL, IT'S YOUR FACE.
YEAH, I BETTER GIVE HER
MY PRESENT NOW, TOO.
YOU GAVE
REBECCA A PRESENT?
YOU DON'T
EVEN LIKE HER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S A CHRISTMAS
TRADITION, SAM.
IT'S CALLED KISSING UP.
YEAH, I'D SURE FEEL
LIKE A DOOFUS
IF I DIDN'T
GET ANYTHING
FOR MISS HOWE
WHEN SHE GOT
ALL THOSE WONDERFUL
PRESENTS FOR US.
OH, MAN!
I DIDN'T
GET HER ANYTHING.
DON'T FEEL BAD, SAM,
JUST BECAUSE
EVERYBODY ELSE
GOT HER SOMETHING--
THE PRETZEL SALESMAN,
THE BEER DISTRIBUTOR,
THE RELIEF BARTENDER,
THAT GUY SHE FIRED
AFTER ONE DAY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ALL THOSE GUYS
ARE JUST TRYING TO
GET HER IN THE SACK.
I GOT SOME
SHOPPING TO DO.
ALL RIGHT,
HAPPY NEW YEAR,
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
HAPPY CHANUKAH.
NOW GET LOST.
- I CAN'T!
- WHY NOT?
- I'M EXPECTING FRIENDS.
- OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
HI!
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
BUON NATALE, FELIZ NAVIDAD,
JOYEUX NOEL,
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
AND SHALOM.
NOW GO HOME
AND TAKE 10
OF THESE DEADBEATS
WITH YOU.
WOULD THAT I COULD, CARLA,
BUT LADY BOUNTIFUL HERE
INSISTS ON DOLING OUT
THESE OBLIGATORY GIFTS
SO PEOPLE WILL PRETEND
THEY LIKE US IN THE NEW YEAR.
MY LITTLE SCROOGE.
IF HE DOESN'T CHEER UP,
SANTA'S GONNA GIVE HIM
A LUMP OF COAL
AND MAKE HIM SLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
MERRY, MERRY,
HAPPY, HAPPY.
WHERE'S SAM? I'VE GOT
A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR HIM.
HE WENT
TO BUY A GIFT
FOR MISS HOWE.
TOO BAD HE
DIDN'T WAIT
AROUND.
HE COULD'VE JUST
GIVEN HER THIS.
I DON'T THINK SO.
THAT'S MENTHOLATED
PRESHAVE
FOR TOUGH BEARDS.
OH.
JUST AS WELL.
THAT'S WHAT I
GOT HIM.
HE DID IT AGAIN,
DAMN IT!
THE THIRD YEAR IN A ROW
WALT TWITCHELL HAS CHEATED ME
OUT OF MY RIGHTFUL PLACE
IN THE MAGIC KINGDOM
AND HE DID IT BY
ONE LOUSY DENTED CAN OF SPAM.
CLAVIN, I KNOW
YOU'RE DYING
TO GO A PLACE
WHERE NO ONE LOOKS TWICE
AT FUNNY COSTUMES
AND BIG, FLOPPY EARS,
BUT I THINK YOU
MISSED THE POINT HERE.
A LOT OF FOOD
GOT TO NEEDY PEOPLE.
ISN'T THAT
WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT?
WELL...
I GUESS YOU'RE
RIGHT, CARLA.
MR. CLAVIN,
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
OH, THANKS,
WOODY, BUT...
WAIT A MINUTE.
CHOW MEIN
AND LITCHI NUTS?
WOODROW, THINK
VERY CAREFULLY.
WERE THESE IN THE BAR
BEFORE 4 P.M. TODAY?
YEAH. THEY WERE HERE.
I JUST FORGOT TO PUT
THEM IN THE BOX.
OH, THAT MAKES
ONE MORE CAN
THAN TWITCHELL.
I WIN!
DECK THE HALLS
WITH SUNTAN LOTION.
DISNEY WORLD,
HERE I COME!
WELL, I GUESS IT'S TRUE
WHAT THEY SAY--
CHARITY BEGINS
IN ORLANDO.
OH, YOO-HOO!
HEY, WAIT! NO!
I SEE YOU IN THERE!
HEY, COME--
PLEASE! OH, PLEASE OPEN!
AW!
HEY!
PLEASE OPEN UP!
EXCUSE--
OH, GREAT, LISTEN, UH...
IS THERE ANY STORE
OPEN AROUND HERE
THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
OH, GEEZ.
OHH!
OH, BLESS YOU, SIR.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU
FOR BEING OPEN.
SORRY. CLOSED.
OHH!
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NO...NO.
I'M TRYING TO GET
A GIFT FOR MY BOSS,
EVERYTHING'S CLOSED,
I'M COLD, IT'S WET,
AND I'M MISERABLE.
I'VE GOT
PLENTY OF PRESENTS HERE.
MAYBE YOU CAN USE
ONE OF THESE.
WHAT? YOU MUST
BE AN ANGEL.
YOU DON'T HAVE WINGS
UNDER THERE, DO YOU?
MM-HMM.
WHAT?
I'M A STEWARDESS.
OH, OH, GOD!
OH, BLESS YOUR HEART!
WELL, LET'S SEE
WHAT I'VE GOT.
OH, THANK YOU.
OK.
AH, WELL, WHAT'S
THIS ONE RIGHT HERE?
THOSE ARE EAR MUFFS.
YOU DON'T WANT THOSE.
THEY'RE TOO IMPERSONAL
AND BORING.
THEY'D BE PERFECT
FOR HER.
YOUR BOSS IS A HER?
YEAH. WELL,
RUMOR HAS IT.
I'VE GOT SOME THINGS I BOUGHT
FOR MYSELF SHE MIGHT LIKE.
NO,
THE EAR MUFFS
ARE PERFECT.
LET ME JUST
WRITE YOU OUT
A CHECK HERE.
HOW ABOUT
A NICE SILK TEDDY?
I LOVE TO LOUNGE
AROUND IN MY HOUSE WITH THIS.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT ELSE DID YOU BUY
FOR YOURSELF IN THERE?
A BLACK LACE
GARTER BELT.
TRUST ME. YOU CAN
NEVER HAVE TOO MANY
OF THESE.
MMM.
MM-HMM. LET'S SEE.
WE HAVE BABY DOLLS
AND A SHORT KIMONO...
MERRY CHRISTMAS, SAMMY.
AND SATIN CAMISOLE.
EVENING, EVERYBODY.
NORM!
SANTA, WHAT
CAN I GET YOU?
FINALLY, SOMEONE WANTS
TO GET ME SOMETHING.
I AM SO HAPPY
THIS HOLIDAY SEASON
IS OVER WITH.
THE WHINING, THE CRYING,
THE SCREAMING,
THE TEMPER TANTRUMS...
OK, I WASN'T
YOUR TRADITIONAL SANTA CLAUS.
RIGHT OVER THERE.
I'LL GET YOU SOME BEERS
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE BOWLS
FULL OF JELLY?
JUST HAVING A LITTLE
GET TOGETHER
AFTER WORK,
KIND OF A CLASS REUNION.
WOW.
YOU GUYS ALL WENT
TO THE SAME SCHOOL?
SANTA SCHOOL.
IT COVERED ALL THE BASICS--
THE HAIR, THE MAKE-UP,
HOW TO TALK KIDS INTO
ASKING FOR BIG-TICKET ITEMS.
HO HO!
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
OH, NO! WHAT IF
A LITTLE KID WALKS IN HERE?
SWEETHEART,
IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT
CHRISTMAS EVE.
WHAT A TIME
TO FIND OUT.
WHY DON'T YOU
GRAB A SEAT RIGHT HERE,
AND I'LL GO GET US SOMETHING
HOT FOR OUR TODDIES.
THANKS, SAM.
HEY, CARLA,
I GOT A PRESENT
FOR REBECCA.
I SEE YOU PICKED UP
A LITTLE PACKAGE
FOR YOURSELF, TOO.
HEY, WHY NOT?
I'VE BEEN A GOOD BOY.
IT'S WHAT I ASKED FOR.
SAM, PLEASE ACCEPT
THIS MERRY CHRISTMAS
FROM FRASIER AND ME.
OH! HEY, WOW!
THAT'S GREAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
LISTEN,
I GOT YOU SOMETHING, TOO.
I LEFT IT OVER AT, UH,
MY OTHER APARTMENT.
CAN I GET IT FOR YOU
NEXT WEEK?
OF COURSE,
WHATEVER YOU LIKE, SAM.
OR WHENEVER YOU GET
A CHANCE TO BUY IT.
IGNORE HIM, SAM.
HE HAS A BUG UP
HIS CHIMNEY.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
LET ME HAVE
THE EAR MUFFS.
THAT'S MY BOSS HERE.
WOODY,
CARLA, SAM.
THESE ARE JUST
LITTLE TOKENS
OF APPRECIATION
FROM ME TO YOU.
OH, MY!
YOU GOT US
PRESENTS!
OH, WOW!
THERE WERE
SO MANY CHOICES,
BUT I THINK
I DONE GOOD.
A COFFEE MUG
WITH THE CORPORATE LOGO.
A NIGHTSHIRT
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME,
AND I DON'T
EXPECT ANYTHING
IN RETURN.
OH, WE GOT YOU GIFTS.
YAY!
WHY DON'T YOU
OPEN MINE FIRST?
"TO REBECCA FROM SAM."
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
GONE TO THE TROUBLE.
JUST A LITTLE
SOMETHING TO KEEP
YOUR EARS WARM.
OH, MY GOD!
DIAMOND EARRINGS!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
I DON'T EITHER.
I THOUGHT
I WAS A KISS-UP,
BUT SAMMY WINS
THE PUCKER SWEEPSTAKES.
HEY, IF HE GOT HER DIAMONDS,
I WONDER WHAT HE GOT US!
YEAH!
AW, BIG WHOOP,
A WALLET.
THANKS FOR
THE SOAP, SAM.
OOH, AND
IT'S PINK, TOO.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY
ABOUT THE MIX-UP HERE,
BUT MY BOSS SEEMS
TO REALLY LOVE
THE DIAMOND EARRINGS.
CAN I BUY THEM FROM YOU,
MAYBE?
THEY WERE FOR MY MOTHER.
THEY COST $500.
$500? I'LL BE RIGHT
BACK. REBECCA?
SAM, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
I'M REALLY OVERWHELMED
BY YOUR GENEROUS GIFT,
BUT I THINK
IT'S INAPPROPRIATE.
YOU MEAN,
YOU'RE GIVING IT BACK?
YOU DON'T
WANT TO KEEP IT?
I THINK I SHOULD.
OH, WELL...
IF THAT'S THE WAY YOU FEEL,
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I WOULDN'T HAVE BOUGHT
THESE FOR YOU
UNLESS I WANTED YOU
TO HAVE THEM.
WELL, THEY
ARE PRETTY.
THANK YOU.
IS THAT THANK YOU YOU'RE
GIVING THEM BACK TO ME
OR THANK YOU
YOU'LL KEEP THEM?
I'M AFRAID THAT
I'VE MISJUDGED YOU.
YOU'RE VERY SWEET.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO COME OVER
MY HOUSE TONIGHT
FOR A LATE SUPPER?
WELL, THAT SOUNDS
VERY INVITING.
AND I'LL WEAR
MY NEW EARRINGS.
AND VERY LITTLE ELSE.
DAMN! THAT WITCH IS
GONNA MAKE ME WORK
TONIGHT.
AFTER I GAVE HER
THE EARRINGS, TOO.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
OH. GUESS THAT MEANS
THERE'S NO LINGERIE
FASHION SHOW THEN?
WELL, MAYBE WE COULD
DO IT SOME OTHER TIME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I DON'T KNOW.
JUST SEEMED LIKE SUCH
A CHRISTMASSY THING TO DO.
OH, WELL,
JUST WRITE ME A CHECK
FOR THE EARRINGS,
AND I'LL BE GOING.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT WAS $500,
AND SHE BETTER
BE FANTASTIC.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
YOU'RE SURE
YOU'RE NOT UPSET
ABOUT THIS?
NO. I'M JUST GONNA GO OVER
TO MY MOM'S HOUSE.
SHE'S PROBABLY STILL UP,
GETTING EVERYTHING
READY FOR TOMORROW--
YOU KNOW, BAKING THE BREAD
AND ICING THE COOKIES
AND STUFFING THE TURKEY.
STUFFING?
OH, YEAH. MY MOM
MAKES IT FROM SCRATCH.
GEE, SO DOES MINE.
YEAH, BUT DOES YOUR MOM
MAKE IT BONE-DRY?
YOU COULD GAG ON IT.
HEY, DON'T TELL ME,
DO YOU HAVE
A MANGER SCENE
ON YOUR FRONT LAWN?
THE BIGGEST
ON OUR BLOCK.
OH!
THE WISE MEN
ARE MY FAVORITE.
OH! I LOVE BALTHAZAR.
BALTHAZAR'S GOOD,
BUT MELCHIOR'S THE BEST.
LISTEN,
I'D INTRODUCE YOU TWO,
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME
YOU'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR YEARS.
YOU DRIVING, CARL?
NO WAY, B.J.
I'M OVER MY LIMIT.
DON'T ASK ME.
I'LL GONNA SLEEP
WHERE I FALL.
DOESN'T THAT
JUST EPITOMIZE
THE SPIRIT OF CHRISTMAS
IN THE EIGHTIES--
A GAGGLE OF PIE-EYED
SANTA CLAUSES
ALL TRYING TO FIND
A DESIGNATED DRIVER
FOR THE SLEIGH RIDE
HOME.
WELL, I HATE TO LEAVE,
BUT I'VE GOT
A BUSY NIGHT
AND A LONG HAUL
AHEAD OF ME.
ANYONE REMEMBER
THAT GUY FROM CLASS?
BEATS ME. I THOUGHT
HE WAS YOUR FRIEND.
NO, NO.
HE CAME IN YOUR CAR.
I'D SWEAR HE CAME--
WAIT A SECOND NOW!
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE...
[MUFFLED SOUND]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
I SUPPOSE IT COULD BE
THE WIND,
BUT IT SOUNDED
LIKE SLEIGH BELLS.
OH, COME ON, GUYS.
SERIOUSLY,
THERE MUST BE
SOME EXPLANATION.
OH...
YOU THINK
THERE ACTUALLY
COULD BE A...
MY WIFE'S
GOING TO KILL ME.
I LEFT THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE STATION WAGON AGAIN.
CAN ONE OF YOU GUYS
GIVE ME A JUMP?
LILITH,
THAT WAS A MIRACLE.
SNOWBALL, YOU'VE HAD
TOO MUCH SCHNAPPS.
NO, NO. I'M STONE SOBER.
I KNOW THAT'S JUST
SOME FAT OLD GUY
WITH CAR TROUBLE.
BUT FOR A HALF-SECOND THERE,
I ACTUALLY BELIEVED
IN CHRISTMAS.
THAT HASN'T HAPPENED TO ME
SINCE I WAS...
BORN.
COME ON! LET'S SING
SOME CHRISTMAS CAROLS,
ROAST SOME CHESTNUTS,
AND ALL THAT TREACLE.
* DECK THE HALLS
WITH BOUGHS OF HOLLY *
* FA LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA *
* 'TIS THE SEASON
TO BE JOLLY *
* FA LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA *
SAMMY, I DON'T WANT
TO BE UNGRATEFUL
OR ANYTHING,
BUT THIS SOAP
SUCKS WIND!
YOU BOUGHT
MISS HUMBUG
DIAMOND EARRINGS.
COME ON, NOW, THERE WAS
A REASON FOR THAT.
SHE HAS INVITED ME OVER
FOR AN INTIMATE
LATE-NIGHT SUPPER.
YEAH, YOU, ME,
AND HALF THE PEOPLE
IN THIS BAR.
DON'T KID AROUND
WITH ME.
I'M IN FAR TOO FRAGILE
A CONDITION.
YOU MEAN, YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA BE
THE ONLY...
I WASN'T TOO THRILLED
ABOUT THE SOAP,
BUT THIS
MAKES UP FOR IT.
* ...LA LA LA LA **
HEY, LOOK
IT'S A WONDERFUL LIFE
IS ON AGAIN!
IT'S THE VERY BEST PART.
TURN IT UP, SAM.
* SHOULD OLD ACQUAINTANCE
BE FORGOT *
* AND NEVER BROUGHT... *
I'M GLAD I CAN FINALLY
SAY THIS TO YOU
WITHOUT HAVING MY HEAD
BITTEN OFF--
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
FRASIER.
IT IS, ISN'T IT?
WE HAVE EVERYTHING
THAT MATTERS--
WE'RE TOGETHER,
OUR LOVED ONES
ARE SAFE AND HAPPY.
THIS JUST IN
TO OUR NEWSROOM--
BOSTON AIRPORT
HAS BEEN TEMPORARILY CLOSED
DUE TO THE PRESENCE
OF A BERSERK MAN ON RUNWAY SIX
CHASING AN
ORLANDO-BOUND PLANE
AND THROWING WHAT APPEARS
TO BE CANS OF CHINESE FOOD.
STAY TUNED
FOR FURTHER DETAILS.
AW, CLIFFY,
CLIFF, CLIFF, CLIFF.
* WE'LL TAKE
A CUP OF KINDNESS YET *
* FOR AULD *
* LANG SYNE **
[WOODY]
GOD BLESS US, EVERY ONE.