"CHEERS"IS FILMED BEFORE
A LIVE STUDIO AUDIENCE.
HEY, HOW ABOUT
A COUPLE OF BEERS?
I'M AFRAID I'M GONNA
HAVE TO SEE SOME I.D.
ALL RIGHTY, THANK YOU.
NOW IF I COULD SEE
YOUR, PLEASE?
WHY DON'T WE
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT?
LET'S JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
GUYS, BEFORE YOU RUN
SCREAMING FROM HERE,
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
THIS FRIEND OF MINE
IS HAVING TWINS.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S ME.
NOW I DON'T CARE
IF THEY CALL EACH OTHER
CUTE LITTLE NAMES,
LIKE CHIPPER AND SKIPPER,
OR IF THEY PRETEND TO BE
EACH OTHER,
MAKE THEIR TEACHERS' LIVES
A LIVING HELL.
BUT, SEE,
WHAT WORRIES ME
IS THAT THEY'LL HAVE ESP,
AND THEY'LL COMMUNICATE
SILENT, EVIL THOUGHTS,
AND I WON'T KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE SAYING ABOUT ME.
YOU THINK THAT'S WEIRD?
- WELL?
- WE'RE DISCUSSING IT.
* MAKING YOUR WAY
IN THE WORLD TODAY *
* TAKES EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GOT *
* TAKING A BREAK
FROM ALL YOUR WORRIES *
* SURE WOULD HELP A LOT *
* WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO GET AWAY? *
* SOMETIMES
YOU WANT TO GO *
* WHERE EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* AND THEY'RE ALWAYS
GLAD YOU CAME *
* YOU WANT TO BE
WHERE YOU CAN SEE *
* OUR TROUBLES
ARE ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANT TO BE WHERE
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME *
* YOU WANT TO GO
WHERE PEOPLE KNOW *
* PEOPLE ARE ALL THE SAME *
* YOU WANT TO GO WHERE
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME *
HEY, LISTEN UP, EVERYBODY.
CLIFFORD CLAVIN HAS DECIDED
TO MAKE A MAJOR LIFE CHANGE.
DON'T BOTHER. YOU'D BE
A DORKY WOMAN, TOO.
YEAH, THAT'S
A GOOD ONE, CARLA.
ALL RIGHT, CLIFFIE.
WHAT'S UP, BUD?
THERE'S A NEW CONDO
COMPLEX GOING UP ON MY ROUTE.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THOSE
PLACES FILLED WITH, UH,
BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE HAVING
THE TIME OF THEIR LIVES.
I SAID TO MYSELF,
"CLIFFORD C,
"YOU'D TAKE TO THAT PLACE
LIKE A FISH TAKES TO WATER."
ALL SLIMY AND WITH YOUR
EYES BULGING OUT?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE SQUATTING
IN A FIELD SOMEWHERE, CARLA?
WELL, TO MAKE
A LONG STORY SHORT,
I AM BOSTON'S
NEWEST HOMEOWNER.
I BOUGHT A CONDO.
WAIT. THAT MEANS
YOU'RE MOVING OUT ON ME?
NORMIE, I CAN'T LIVE
WITH YOU FOREVER.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WHO'S GONNA MIX
VERA'S COCOA?
WHO'S GONNA
RUB HER FEET?
TALK TO HER?
NORMIE, I'M AFRAID
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO, UH,
HAVE TO PICK UP THE SLACK
NO!
NO, NO, NO.
NOT ME.
MAYBE I CAN
HIRE SOME
HIGH SCHOOL KID.
DID EVERYBODY SEE THAT?
YES, I'VE STARTED
SMOKING AGAIN.
I'VE BEEN UNDER
A LOT OF PRESSURE,
AND I NEEDED SOMETHING TO
CALM MY NERVES, ALL RIGHT?
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANY STUPID REMARKS
ABOUT YELLOW FINGERNAILS
OR KISSING ASHTRAYS.
AND IF YOU USE THE PHRASE
"COFFIN NAILS,"
YOU BETTER BE
A MORTICIAN.
ANY QUESTIONS, COMMENTS?
SNIDE REMARKS? NO? GOOD!
WELL, IT CERTAINLY
HAS CALMED HER DOWN.
UH, EXCUSE ME.
YOU KNOW, I OUGHT
TO APOLOGIZE.
I FEEL LIKE THIS
IS MY FAULT.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY YOU STARTED
SMOKING AGAIN
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT
SOME SORT OF
PENT-UP SEXUAL FRUSTRATION
GOING ON.
AND I DON'T THINK
WE HAVE TO TELL EACH OTHER
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR THAT,
NOW, DO WE?
HEY, COME ON, I'M JUST TRYING
TO HELP HERE, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU OUGHT TO DO
IS YOU OUGHT TO
COME ON OVER TO DR. SAMMY'S
STOP SMOKING CENTER.
TODAY'S SPECIAL
IS A FREE CHEST EXAM.
SAM, IS THIS ONE OF
THOSE TWO-WEEK PROGRAMS
WITH A SIMPLE
TWO-DAY FOLLOW-UP?
AW, THOSE GUYS.
COME ON IN.
WHAT A SURPRISE,
YOU GUYS.
WELCOME TO CHEZ CLIFF.
SOUNDS LIKE
PARTY CENTRAL
OUT THERE.
WELL, I JUST HOPE THAT
THEY CAN KEEP UP
WITH THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE BROADS.
HEY, CLIFFIE,
I BROUGHT YOU
THE TRADITIONAL
HOUSEWARMING GIFT.
- OH, A SIX-PACK.
- UH, THE FIVE-PACK.
WELL, SO, YOU GUYS READY
FOR THE GRAND TOUR?
OK.
YEP. RIGHT HERE
WE HAVE THE LIVING ROOM.
RIGHT OVER HERE
IS THE BEDROOM.
HEY, SLOW DOWN. LET ME
CATCH MY BREATH HERE.
WHOA!
I ALMOST FORGOT
THE KITCHEN.
I THINK THE BUILDER
DID, TOO.
LET ME PUT THESE BEERS
ON ICE HERE.
YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
IT'S NOT TOO COLD
IN HERE, BUDDY.
YEAH, YEAH,
I NOTICED THAT,
NORMIE.
I THINK IT'S THE
AMALGAMATOR VALVE.
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO STRIP IT DOWN,
CHECK OUT
THE ENGINE,
YOU KNOW,
I THINK
I BETTER PUT IN
SOME MORE FREON
IN THE REGULATOR,
TOO.
OR ELSE YOU CAN JUST TURN
THIS LITTLE DIAL TO "COLD."
WELL, YEAH,
IF YOU WANT TO TAKE
A STOPGAP APPROACH.
- DID YOU NOTICE THE POOL
ON YOUR WAY IN?
- YEAH.
YEAH.
SO WHEN SUMMER ROLLS AROUND
AND ALL THOSE GIRLS
ARE OUT THERE IN THEIR
FRENCH-CUT BIKINIS,
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
WHERE I'LL BE.
- STANDING RIGHT HERE WITH
A PAIR OF BINOCULARS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
BOY, OH, BOY.
HEY, THANKS FOR COMING BY,
GUYS, BUT...
YOU KNOW, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE RUDE, BUT...
I GOTTA ASK YOU
TO SKEDADDLE.
I'VE GOT SOMEBODY
SOFT AND SWEET,
WITH A VOICE LIKE
A NIGHTINGALE
COMING OVER.
THE BUSBOY FROM MELVILLE'S
IS COMING OVER HERE?
NO, WOODY.
REUBEN'S NOT COMING
OVER HERE.
IT'S ONE OF THE WOMEN
IN THE BUILDING.
WAIT A MINUTE,
CLIFFIE.
ARE WE ACTUALLY
TALKING A FEMALE?
I MEAN A REAL, LIVE,
BREATHING WOMAN?
THREE-DIMENSIONAL?
NO POSTERS,
NO POLYURETHANE?
NO, NORMIE.
SALLY IS THE REAL McCOY,
AND SHE'S ONE
GORGEOUS BABE TO BOOT.
ALL RIGHT. THIS I GOTTA
SEE, CLIFFIE.
YEAH, MAYBE WE COULD
STICK AROUND
AND MEET YOUR
LADY FRIEND.
YOU KNOW, I, UH...
GUESS I...
I REALLY DON'T THINK
THAT'S A VERY GOOD IDEA.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
BRING HER BY THE BAR
OR SOMETHING?
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO GET THE WOMAN
TO GO OUT, NORMIE,
BUT SHE JUST WANTS
TO STAY HOLED UP HERE
IN HER LITTLE HIDEAWAY.
I GUESS I'M HER
LOVE HOSTAGE.
THAT'S SOMETHING
I DEFINITELY
DON'T CARE TO SEE.
GOOD TO SEE YOU,
GUYS.
HEY, IF I'M NOT
DOWN TO THE BAR,
SEND OUT A MISSING
SWINGER'S REPORT.
HI.
HI, SALLY.
GUESS WHAT?
I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
I WAS NAMED
"EMPLOYEE
OF THE MONTH"
AT THE YARN BARN.
WELL, I TIED.
THAT'S REALLY
GREAT NEWS, SALLY.
I'M REALLY HAPPY FOR YOU.
SO I WAS THINKING
MAYBE TO CELEBRATE,
WE COULD GO OUT.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE JUST STAY IN?
OH, CLIFF,
WE'VE DONE THAT
EVERY NIGHT THIS WEEK.
I WAS THINKING MAYBE
WE COULD GO TO THAT BAR
YOU'RE ALWAYS
TALKING ABOUT.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT DIVE?
YOU KNOW, SALLY,
I SPEND ALL DAY
WALKING AROUND OUTSIDE,
AND AT THE END OF THE DAY,
I JUST LIKE TO COME BACK
TO MY OWN LITTLE
APARTMENT HERE
AND JUST SORT OF RELAX
AND TAKE IT EASY AND, UH...
GET MY TENSIONS RELIEVED,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YES, I KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
I'LL GET THE LIGHTS, HUH?
FINE, I'LL JUST
GET COMFORTABLE.
- AND I'LL MEET YOU
ON THE SOFA IN
ABOUT 5 SECONDS.
- ALL RIGHT.
HAVE YOU GOT THE...
YOU KNOW?
OH, YEAH.
AND NOW, HERE IS
THE HOST OF JEOPARDY!,
ALEX TREBEK!
THANK YOU, AND WELCOME
ONCE AGAIN TO OUR SHOW.
WE'RE ARE DELIGHTED OF
COURSE TO WELCOME BACK
OUR RETURNING CHAMPION,
THE LADY FROM
BOCA RATON, FLORIDA...
UH-OH. HERE COMES
MADAM NICOTINE.
I'VE JUST HAD
THE MOST DISGUSTING
MORNING IN MY LIFE.
OOH. CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR ABOUT IT.
I JUST SPENT
THE LAST HOUR
AT A "NO SMOKING" CLINIC
LOOKING AT PICTURES
OF UGLY ASHTRAYS,
ROOMS FILLED WITH SMOKE,
PEOPLE COUGHING.
AND THE WORST ONE
WAS A CIGARETTE
SNUFFED OUT
IN THE YOKE OF
A FRIED EGG.
AND THAT STOPPED YOU
FROM WANTING
A CIGARETTE, HUH?
NO, BUT I THINK IT'S PUT
ME OFF EGGS FOR GOOD.
I'LL BE IN THE OFFICE
CHEWING ON MY HAIR.
THIS IS
GONNA BE FUN.
CARLA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM GOING TO
TORMENT HER
WITH THIS FRESH PACK
OF CIGARETTES.
NO, CARLA, YOU MUSTN'T!
CARLA, NOW GRANTED
SHE'S BEEN IN A RATHER
A FOUL MOOD LATELY,
BUT REBECCA HAS MADE
A SERIOUS LIFE DECISION.
AND WHAT SHE NEEDS NOW
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE
IS ENCOURAGEMENT
AND SUPPORT.
AND I, FOR ONE,
AM NOT GOING TO FAIL HER.
- OH, REBECCA?
- WHAT IS IT, BONE-DOME?
HERE, TRY THESE.
THEY'RE MENTHOLS.
NEXT CASE.
DR. CRANE...
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I THINK I'M JUST
A LITTLE ON EDGE.
LOOK, I APOLOGIZE, TOO.
I BEHAVED VERY
UNPROFESSIONALLY.
IT'S JUST THAT
I'M REALLY FRUSTRATED
BECAUSE I CAN'T SEEM
TO KICK THIS HABIT.
LISTEN, MAY I SUGGEST
SOMETHING
THAT HAS SEEMED TO WORK
FOR MANY OF MY PATIENTS?
CHANGING DOCTORS?
THANK YOU, CARLA, NO.
YOU'RE ENGAGED RIGHT NOW
IN A PSYCHOLOGICAL
BATTLE WITH YOUR WILL.
NOW YOU'VE GOT BRING
TO THE FOREGROUND
EVERY WEAPON AVAILABLE.
PROMISE YOURSELF THAT IF
YOU SMOKE ONE MORE CIGARETTE,
YOU'LL DO
THE MOST DISGUSTING,
REPULSIVE THING
YOU CAN IMAGINE.
DR. CRANE,
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE--
SAM MALONE,
IF I SMOKE
ANOTHER CIGARETTE,
I'LL GO TO BED
WITH YOU.
DARN THING'S
ON THE BLINK AGAIN.
EXCUSE ME, REBECCA.
WHAT?
THERE'S A PROBLEM I'D LIKE
TO TALK OVER WITH YOU.
I'M REALLY
TRYING TO QUIT!
NO, NO, NO,
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
I MET THIS GIRL.
AND...
OH. PEOPLE
USUALLY STOP ME
AT THAT POINT.
ANYWAY,
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT,
I KEEP BEGGING HER TO
COME DOWN TO THE BAR
TO MEET THE GUYS,
BUT SHE JUST WON'T COME.
SHE JUST WANTS
TO STAY HOME
AND WATCH "JEOPARDY!"
I THINK THAT MAYBE
SHE'S A LITTLE...
A LITTLE BIT ASHAMED
ABOUT THE WAY SHE LOOKS.
SHE'S AFRAID SHE MIGHT
EMBARRASS ME.
SO, UH, YOU GOT ANY
SUGGESTIONS?
WHAT CAN I DO?
LET ME SEE, HERE...
UM...
OH! HAVE YOU EVER SEEN THOSE
BEAUTY MAGAZINE MAKEOVERS?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
SURE. SURE.
WELL, THEN WHAT ARE
YOU BUGGING ME FOR?
WAIT A MINUTE.
IF YOU EVER SEE ME
WITH A CIGARETTE
HANGING OUT OF MY MOUTH,
WILL YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
WHAT'S THAT?
KILL SAM.
DID YOU, UH...
DAB LIP GLOSS
ON YOUR EYELASHES
SO THEY
"SPARKLE LIKE
THE NORTH STAR?"
YES, CLIFF.
I'M COMING OUT NOW.
OK.
LISTEN, DON'T STAND
TOO CLOSE, OK?
TRY ME FROM
A DISTANCE, FIRST.
OK. ALL RIGHT,
I'M BACKING UP.
ALL CLEAR!
- WOW.
- GEE, THANKS, CLIFF.
OH, ISN'T IT ABOUT TIME
FOR"JEOPARDY!?"
HUH?
"JEOPARDY!"
WHY DON'T WE GO OUT?
REALLY, CLIFF?
SURE.
GREAT. OK.
I'LL JUST GO DO A LITTLE
MORE BLENDING,
AND THEN WE'LL GO.
I'LL JUST, UH...
BE OUT HERE
ON THE FRONT PORCH
AND CATCH A LITTLE BREATH
OF FRESH AIR.
I GOT A FOX!
CARLA! CARLA! CARLA!
CARLA! CARLA!
LADIES ROOM!
LADIES ROOM, PLEASE!
I'M NOT FOLLOWING HER
IN THERE AGAIN, SAM.
I'M ONE PUFF AWAY
FROM PARADISE.
COME ON, PLEASE.
THERE IS ONLY SO MUCH
POLITE CONVERSATION
YOU CAN MAKE YELLING
OVER A STALL.
CLIFF...
THIS ISN'T A DIVE.
WELL, NO, BY A DIVE
I MEANT THAT, UH,
IT WAS BELOW
STREET LEVEL.
OH, RIGHT.
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO MY CRONIES.
BUT I GOT TO
WARN YOU FIRST,
THEY CAN BE
A LITTLE BIT CRUDE,
ALL RIGHT?
HEY, GUYS!
VA-VA-VA-VOOM, HUH?
HELLO.
I THOUGHT WE MET ALL
OF CLIFF'S COUSINS.
- OH, I'M NOT HIS COUSIN.
- SHE'S MY DATE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A LITTLE
SEAT HERE?
I'LL GET YOU
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
LIKEWISE.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU,
SHE'S WHAT GUYS BACK
DOWN ON THE FARM
WHERE I COME FROM
WOULD CALL "ETHEREAL."
WOODY...
WHERE EXACTLY
WAS THIS FARM?
EH...A COUPLE
OF BEERS, WOOD MAN.
YOU GOT SOMETHING
ON HER, DON'T YOU?
YOU FOUND SOMETHING
INCRIMINATING IN HER MAIL.
FOR GOD SAKE, CLIFF,
JUST ASK HER FOR MONEY.
DON'T BE VICIOUS.
LOOK, IS IT SO HARD
FOR YOU PEOPLE,
AND WHATEVER
YOU ARE, CARLA,
TO BELIEVE THAT, UH....
THIS BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
WOULD GO OUT WITH ME
ON HER OWN ACCORD?
NO, OF COURSE NOT, CLIFF.
I CAN THINK OF ANY
NUMBER OF REASONS
WHY A WOMAN MIGHT
BEHAVE THAT WAY.
- YOU CAN?
- WELL, OF COURSE.
BUT REMEMBER,
I'M A PSYCHIATRIST.
SO, WH--WHERE'S SAMMY?
I WANNA SHOW HIM ONE
GORGEOUS BOSTONIAN
THAT SLIPPED THROUGH
HIS NET.
HE'S OVER THERE
HAULING HER IN.
WHOA! WHOA!
SAMMY! HEY, HEY, HEY.
HEY, SAMMY.
WHOA, YOUNG FELLOW,
WHOA, BOY.
DO YOU KNOW EACH OTHER?
OH, YEAH.
CAN I HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU, SAMMY?
SEE, SHE'S WITH ME.
OH, OH.
UH, EXCUSE US, SALLY?
- HEY, SHE'S ONE
VERY PRETTY LADY.
- THANK YOU, SAM.
ANOTHER ONE
OF YOUR COUSINS?
SHE'S MY DATE.
REALLY?
IS SHE, UM...?
WE THINK SO.
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
LISTEN, SAMMY, ABOUT THAT
OVER THERE--
I'M SORRY.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE IF
I WAS OUT OF LINE THERE,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
YOU HAVE TO EXPECT
THAT KIND OF THING
HAPPENING FROM NOW ON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, SHE DEFINITELY
A MAJOR-LEAGUE LOOKER
THERE, CLIFF.
I MEAN, GUYS ARE
GONNA BE HITTING
ON HERE ALL THE TIME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THAT, SAMMY.
SALLY IS
A ONE-MAN WOMAN.
YOU BETTER CHECK
YOUR ARITHMETIC THERE.
HEY, SALLY.
CLIFF, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S JEFF--
FROM 325.
HEY, I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE THE GUY
WITH THE BINOCULARS.
UH, SALLY, I THINK
IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE VAMOOSE OUT OF HERE.
"JEOPARDY!" IS
GONNA BE STARTING
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
LET'S GO, SALLY.
JEFF JUST GOT
A NEW PORSCHE TURBO,
AND HE WANTS TO
TAKE ME FOR A RIDE.
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
WELL, UH--
WE'LL JUST BE GONE
A FEW MINUTES.
- YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
- OH, NO.
NO, I DON'T MIND.
HA HA!
YEAH, IT'S FINE.
I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
BEER HERE, WOODY.
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT WAS THAT LADY
DOING IN THERE?
OH.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NO, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WE HAVE THIS LITTLE
BET BETWEEN US.
LET ME--
LET ME EXPLAIN.
SEE, I GET TO GO
TO BED WITH HER IF SHE--
JAMIE, KELP IS
A CORRECT RESPONSE,
BUT YOU FORGOT TO PHRASE THAT
IN THE FORM A QUESTION.
BEER, SAM, PLEASE.
ARE YOU OK, CLIFF?
"JEOPARDY!" USED TO BE
OUR SHOW, NORMIE,
IT'S JUST NOT THE SAME
WATCHING IT BY MYSELF.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF
I CAN GO ON WITHOUT HER.
SHE'S ONLY BEEN GONE
FOR 10 MINUTES.
YEAH, I HAD TO MAKE HER
BEAUTIFUL, NORMIE.
I'VE CREATED A BEAUTIFUL
MONSTER. WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHAT IS PARAGUAY?
YEAH! ALL RIGHT!
WELL, THANKS A LOT,
NORMIE.
WHAT IS NOTRE DAME?
...NOTRE DAME?
OOH, YEAH!
HEY, CARLA.
DO YOU SMELL SMOKE?
COME HERE.
OF COURSE I SMELL SMOKE,
YOU DINK.
IT'S A BAR.
I ALSO SMELL BEER,
SWEAT, AND LOUSY TIPS.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO.
SHE'S SMOKING IN THERE.
I KNEW SHE COULDN'T
LAST THIS LONG.
HEY, WHERE'S THE POOL TABLE?
WRONG ROOM.
I KNEW IT, I KNEW IT,
I KNEW IT! HA!
I'M GOING TO SAY I KNEW IT,
BUT I KNEW IT. I KNEW IT.
NOW THIS WAS
YOUR IDEA, TOO.
I DID NOT
COME UP WITH THIS.
THIS IS YOUR IDEA.
WHAT A GREAT IDEA! OH!
WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SHALL WE STRIP DOWN
TO OUR SMILES HERE
AND SHOW THE COUCH HERE
A GOOD TIME?
NO.
WE'LL GO TO MY PLACE.
EXCUSE ME?
WHOA. YOU'RE REALLY GONNA
GO THROUGH WITH THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
- YES, I AM.
BUT I WANT TO GET
ONE THING STRAIGHT.
- YEAH, YEAH.
MY SMOKING
HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH SEXUAL FRUSTRATION
OVER YOU OR ANYONE ELSE.
IT'S JUST
A STUPID HABIT.
BUT I MADE A PACT.
SO NOW I'M GOING
TO SUFFER
THE CONSEQUENCES,
NO MATTER HOW VILE OR
DISGUSTING THEY MAY BE.
LET'S GO.
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT
TO DO THIS, DO YOU?
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST CLOSE MY EYES AND
IMAGINE SOMEONE APPEALING.
BESIDES, I HAVE A FEELING
IT WON'T TAKE LONG.
GEE WHIZ, IF YOU'RE
NOT GONNA GET IN THE
SPIRIT OF THIS,
THEN I JUST
DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
NO, COME ON. COME ON.
A DEAL'S A DEAL.
NO.
LOOK, I MADE A PACT.
I JUST WANT TO
GET IT OVER WITH.
NO.
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE
SOME PRIDE.
I HAVE SOME DIGNITY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO DO YOUR DIRTY WORK.
THIS WILL TEACH YOU
TO MESS WITH SAM MALONE.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- SHE ASKED ME TO
GO TO BED WITH HER,
AND I SAID NO.
OH, CLIFF!
I'VE NEVER DRIVEN SO FAST
IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
I HAD THE BEST TIME.
OH, GREAT, GREAT.
SO DID I.
CLIFF, IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER?
NO.
NOTHING'S THE MATTER.
WHAT COULD BE
THE MATTER?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
LITTLE MISS PORSCHE.
TRY TO DO A GIRL A FAVOR,
HELP HER BECOME
A LITTLE BIT MORE ATTRACTIVE,
AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
SHE'S OUT THERE...
ATTRACTING PEOPLE.
IS THAT WHAT'S
BOTHERING YOU?
THIS MAKEUP?
IS THAT WHAT ALL
THIS IS ABOUT?
WELL...
HEY, YOU GOTTA ADMIT
BEFORE YOU PUT IT ON,
YOU WERE A...
A SWEET THING WHO, UH...
MORE CONTENT TO SIT
BY A DEAR FRIEND'S SIDE
ON AN EVENING
AND WATCH A ROUSING,
WHOLESOME GAME
OF "JEOPARDY!."
SO ALL I HAVE TO DO
TO MAKE THINGS
RIGHT BETWEEN US
IS TAKE OFF ALL THIS
SILLY MAKEUP
AND GO BACK TO BEING
THE WAY I WAS?
YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
NO WAY.
I LIKE THE WAY
I LOOK IN MAKEUP.
WAIT TILL THEY GET
A LOAD OF ME AT THE YARN BARN.
IT MAKES YOU LOOK...
LIKE A...
COVER GIRL.
I'M SORRY, CLIFF.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
STUCK WITH.
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO LEARN TO LIVE WITH IT.
WELL...
I GUESS I'M...
BIG ENOUGH
OF A PERSON
NOT TO LET
YOUR APPEARANCE
GET IN THE WAY OF
OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I'M GLAD.
- BESIDES, APPEARANCES
DON'T MATTER AT ALL.
- OF COURSE THEY DON'T.
LIKE, IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME
THAT YOU WEAR THOSE
FUNNY WHITE SOCKS.
OF COURSE IT DOESN'T.
OR THAT IT LOOKS AS IF
YOU TRIM YOUR MOUSTACHE
WITH A BUTTER KNIFE.
ANOTHER FINE EXAMPLE.
CLIFF, HAVE YOU EVER
CONSIDERED JOINING A GYM?
HAVE YOU EVER CONSIDERED
WEARING FLATS?
I CAN HELP YOU WITH
THAT SMOKING PROBLEM.
translate