Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
No, no, it's
a well-documented fact
that the female of the species
is irresistibly drawn
to men in uniform.
Yeah, just yesterday, some
lonely, frustrated housewife
saw me coming
up the garden path,
you know, peeking
through the window,
and she tries
to coyly titillate me
by pulling down the shade
so I wonder what's
going on behind it.
Let me dispel the mystery.
She was puking.
Carla,
don't you get bored just
hanging around here all day
waiting to take
cheap shots at me?
Yeah, I should get a beeper.
All right, look. That's it.
I am sick and tired
of being your whipping boy.
Today the worm turns.
You are not going to insult me
any longer,
because I am not going
to give you the chance.
As of from right now,
I am shutting up,
zipping my lip.
And my friends support me.
¶ Making your way
in the world today ¶
¶ Takes everything you've got.
¶ Taking a break
from all your worries ¶
¶ Sure would help a lot.
¶ Wouldn't you like
to get away? ¶
¶ Sometimes you want to go.
¶ Where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ And they're always glad
you came ¶
¶ You want to be
where you can see ¶
¶ Our troubles
are all the same ¶
¶ You want to be where everybody
knows your name ¶
¶ You want to go
where people know ¶
¶ People are all the same.
¶ You want to go where
everybody knows your name. ¶
You know something, chaps,
I had a particularly fascinating
session this morning.
No, honestly.
Someone I was seeing
for the first time.
Extraordinarily beautiful,
young woman,
who's uh, rather unique malaise
is to be aroused
with sexual frenzy by...
Oh, good Lord.
Excuse me. I don't really think
I should be discussing
my patients here.
Uh... how about
discussing them over here?
Well,
I suppose it wouldn't violate
any doctor-patient
confidentiality
if I don't use names.
Pour the beer, Woody.
I thought you weren't going
to use any names, Dr. Crane.
Woody...
Well, it seems this woman
has her passions inflamed
by men who dance.
Wait a minute, Wait a minute.
Men who dance?
That's weird.
What's even more bizarre,
is that she will catapult
herself compulsively
into the arms of any man
in tights or tap shoes.
Fascinating fixation.
Ooh, geez. I've got
to go. I'm sorry.
Where you going?
My ballet class.
No, no,
lunch, lunch.
That was a little psychological
humor.
You know, as my old
professor used to say,
if you can't laugh
at your patients,
what fun are they?
See you later.
Norm.
- Morning, everybody.
- Norm!
Can I pour you a draft,
Mr. Peterson?
A little early, isn't it, Woody?
- For a beer?
- No, for stupid questions.
Pour.
Would you believe the board
of directors is asking
for a breakdown
of projected earnings
for the next six months?
Yes.
Rebecca,
I started painting
Mr. Drake's house.
I want to thank you
for that recommendation.
Oh, it was my pleasure, Norm.
How's it going?
Great, great.
He's out of town for a few days
so, uh,
I thought it'd be a good time
to get started in his bedroom.
I was doing a little prep
work over there this morning,
and I must say, that's
a cute photo of you
he has next
to his night stand there.
- What?
- Just kidding.
I will kill you, Norm.
You know, uh,
I am over there all by myself,
so if you want
to drop by and, uh,
check any of the house out,
I can get you in.
No... I can't.
Oh, go on.
You're dying to look
in his drawers.
That's right, he won't be there.
The last thing on my mind
is Evan Drake
and where he sleeps.
No, I don't want
to be distracted.
I've got to get these figures
into the bed of directors...
board of directors.
- Shall we say in one hour?
- I'll be there.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for Dr. Crane.
He mentioned he'd be here.
Oh, I'm sorry,
you just missed him.
Oh, darn.
I had a session earlier today
and left a package
in his office.
When I went back, it was locked.
Gee, I don't know
what to tell you.
But then again, I don't know
what to tell most people.
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, you had a session with him?
Are you a patient of his?
- That's right. Why?
- Oh, just curious.
Well, it's not that important.
I just thought if I caught him,
I could still
get my package back.
I understand perfectly.
Well, I'm out of luck, I guess.
I'll just have
to stop by tomorrow.
¶ Gotta dance, gotta dance... ¶
- Why are you doing that?
- This? Oh...
I guess it's kind of an
old reflex with us hoofers.
Oh. You're a dancer?
Well, kind of.
Yeah... my name's Sam Malone
but people call me Bojangles.
- Jennifer McCall.
- Jennifer McCall, whoo...
That's a beautiful name
for a beautiful girl.
Well, thank you.
I have to be going.
Well, at least let me,
uh, waltz you
to the door here, all right?
I know I'm not
very sophisticated,
but I don't think
what Sam is doing is right.
Well, look,
don't you put yourself
down with me,
and I happen to agree with you.
I mean, standing around
tending bar all day
is like the worst thing
a dancer could do
for his calves.
Speaking of calves, Woody,
was it painful when the cow
kicked you in the head?
You get used to it.
Why don't I stop back
and um, we'll go to lunch.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it
already.
Ow, got a cramp. Oh, God...
Ow, Woody...
And, uh, here's his bedroom.
I feel kind of queasy.
Like I don't belong here.
Like I'm doing something wrong.
I know... that's how I feel
in my bedroom.
I just feel kind of like
I'm trespassing.
Like I'm invading his privacy.
This is not right.
I should not be doing this.
I shouldn't.
I shouldn't, I shouldn't.
Would you like to be alone?
Sorry.
Well, as long as I'm here,
I guess it wouldn't hurt for me
to just look around
a little bit.
Sure.
Now, I suggested Navajo white,
but he went with sandstone.
What do you think?
This is where he keeps
his clothes, isn't it?
Do you think anybody heard that?
- Like who?
- I don't know. I'm just nervous.
God, there's no way I could
explain it if I got caught.
How are you going to get caught?
Because people always get caught
in this situation.
- What if Evan comes back
unexpectedly.
- Look, he's in Europe, okay?
You don't come back
unexpectedly from Europe.
You come back unexpectedly
from the movies or shopping.
But you don't come back
unexpect...
What? What?
Oh, my God, it's Mr. Drake!
He's back unexpectedly
from Europe!
Oh, I have to get out of here.
Norm, are you here?
- Uh, yes, sir.
Be right down, sir.
No, that's all right,
I'm coming up.
For the love of...
Go, go, go, go, go.
Norm...
- Oh, oh, right, right.
- Okay.
- Ah, Norm... there you are.
- Hi, sir.
What are you doing here, sir?
Oh, I wound up everything
in a marathon session.
I haven't slept for three days.
Three days.
Let me take you out
for a cup of coffee, sir.
No, no, no.
All I want to do is
sleep for about a week.
Should I get your pajamas, sir?
No!
- No?
- No.
Oh, I thought you meant
my pajamas.
No, they're, uh, they're
too far away from here
and I don't even think
they'd fit Mr. Drake.
Actually, I think you'll find
a clean pair of pajamas
in the bag.
I thought you were
going to fix that.
Oh, yeah, that squeak.
I'm going to fix that squeak,
sir.
You should go to another room.
I may need to use
the jaws of life.
Uh, no, just leave it, will ya?
As a matter of fact, forget
the painting thing, too.
I'm a light sleeper,
and I don't want to hear you
rattling your paint cans.
Well, that's one thing
I've never been accused of, sir,
is rattling my cans.
Please, I mean it, Norm. Scoot.
- Huh?
- Yes, sir.
So you're a really light
sleeper, sir?
Yes, but I have
excellent hearing, Norm.
Yeah, most light sleepers do.
That's what makes them
light sleepers.
So you just left her
in the closet?
Believe me, I did
everything I could
to get the guy out of the room
for like one minute,
but he wouldn't budge.
So you just left her
in the closet?
There was nothing else
I could do, okay?
So you just
left her in the closet?
Carla, it wasn't
my fault, all right?
It's been at least an hour.
She should have
snuck out by now.
Oh, come on.
She'd be here
if she'd gotten away.
You gotta get her out of there.
Hey, look.
You, uh, you think of it
as an adventure.
She's the damsel in distress
and you are the knight
in shiny white armor,
leaping upon your steed.
And driving it into the ground
up to its knees.
No, no, no, no, and
saving a damsel.
I guess you're right,
you're right.
I gotta go do this.
Listen, uh, Cliffie,
if I'm not back in an hour,
go ahead and finish my beer.
This is your beer.
Sammy, I hear you got
a sure thing lined up, huh?
Mm, no, I never like
to use the term "sure thing."
I prefer the term "in the bag."
What? What?
Ah, Sammy, come on.
Isn't this, you know,
pretending to be a phony-bologna
dancer a little bit beneath you?
I mean,
when I go picking up girls,
I don't need all that stuff.
All I need is a wink
and a smile.
And a rag doused
with chloroform.
I don't know, Sammy.
It looks to me like you're
getting a little desperate.
What are you talk...
I'm not desperate.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Ready, Sam?
Oh, hi, Jennifer.
I'll be right with you.
See you guys later.
Ready to go? Mm-hmm.
Mr. Drake!
Mr. Drake, sir!
Sorry, sir, but Mr. Peterson
said it was an emergency.
What? Emergency?
Yeah, structural, Evan.
It's just a damn good thing
I went back
and checked those blueprints.
This ceiling could go
at any second.
- Ceiling?
Yeah, it's a crack, sir.
It extends all the way
into, uh, here.
Get me out of here.
What crack?
There's nothing wrong
with that ceiling.
I'm only thinking
of your safety, sir.
Now, I'd feel much better
if you slept
in a different room.
Peterson, get out.
And close that closet door.
Well, wait a minute.
Many people prefer to sleep
with the closet door open.
Is there something wrong
with you?
Yeah, it's, um,
it's the paint fumes, sir.
They make me giddy.
Really.
And, uh,
I'm afraid they can be hazardous
to your health, sir.
Oh, nonsense.
No one was ever killed
by paint fumes.
But, uh, they can cause
brain damage.
Evidently.
Now get out of here.
Sir, I have some paint cans
in the closet there.
I'd feel much better for you
if I tightened those lids.
Whatever, just do it,
get out of here.
Norm, I'm so glad to see you.
- You gotta get me out of here.
- Okay.
Every time I open the door,
it squeaks and he
starts to wake up.
If he finds me here
in the morning,
he will fire me, hate me,
and he is never, ever going
to want to be my boyfriend.
Norm, are you talking
to your paints?
Uh, yes, I am, sir.
Come on, come on. Just,
just calm down, all right?
Calm down. Calm down.
Okay? Everything's going
to be fine.
I'm going to get you out of...
Whoo, cashmere.
Here's my plan, okay?
I'm going to walk out of here.
I'm going to leave
the closet door
yea bit open, right?
So it won't squeak.
Now you wait until he's good
and sound asleep,
and then you just walk
on out of here, okay?
Okay.
If you're hungry,
I brought you some chips.
Cajun style?
Never mind. Just go ahead.
Okay, all right.
Good luck.
Is he asleep?
Get lost.
Getting lost, sir.
Oh, like an open door would
really kill you, Greyson, huh?
So you just left her
in the closet?
I had a foolproof plan
to get her out of there
and the whole thing got spoiled
by this anal-retentive butler.
Mr. Peterson,
you gotta get her out of there.
Oh...
How did I get myself into this?
I should have never become
a house painter.
I should have listened to my
mother and become a matador.
You know, Norm, you are
probably too logical.
What?
Yes, you see, it's an
established psychological fact
that the more outrageous a lie
one tells,
the more readily
will the victim believe it.
You see, if you told Mr. Drake
a sufficiently outlandish story,
odds are he'd buy it.
No, that's impossible.
No, Woody, it's a
stroke of genius.
Frasier, you're brilliant.
That is one of the most brilliant
ideas you've ever had.
And you've had a lot
of brilliant ideas.
Thank you, Carla.
See, Woody? It works.
Bonehead bought it.
All right. All right.
All right, I guess
I just gotta go do this.
I've got to do it.
If it doesn't work out,
tomorrow I'm going to be
shopping for toreador pants.
Hey, where you going?
I gotta get Rebecca
out of the damn closet.
You just left her in the closet?
Where's Frasier, man?
I gotta talk to him.
Where's your date?
She's at my apartment.
I told her I was going out
for some ice.
I don't know,
something's wrong here.
I've been dancing my brains
out and nothing, zilch.
Frasier, you know that,
that beautiful girl
you were treating this morning?
I treated two beautiful women
this morning, Sam.
Which one?
The one that had the hots
for the dancers.
Yes, why?
Well, uh, you didn't cure her,
by any chance, did you?
You don't just "cure" someone
overnight.
Most patients require dozens
of costly sessions
to make even minimal progress.
God, I love this profession.
Well, I don't know.
Something's wrong.
Maybe it's my dancing.
You treated two beautiful girls
this morning?
What did you treat
the other one for?
Um, pyromania.
Pyro... pyromania. Pyro...
What?
Stop! You can't go in there!
Up, sir! Up quick! Bees!
Killer bees are coming
this way from Mexico
and they're hopping mad, sir!
Bees?
Yeah, those suckers could swarm
through here like a buzz saw.
Sir, you don't have any honey
in here, do you?
Peterson, get out of here.
And if you come back
in here again,
I'm going to have Greyson use his gun.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Hey, he was talking to me,
okay, Greyson?
Look, sir, let me just get
your robe.
I'm very concerned
about these bees.
Well, never mind.
They've gone.
Yeah. There they go.
They're headed up
to Canada or someplace.
What is it?
Bee sting. They're back, sir.
Peterson, what the hell
is going on?
Sir, I'm sorry. I...
I didn't want to have
to tell you this, but...
you're forcing me to.
Oh, please, tell me quickly.
If I don't sleep, I'll die.
And I'm gonna take you with me.
It's, actually,
it's kind of personal.
Do you mind, Greyson?
Sir?
Whatever. Anything that
will get him out of here.
Sir, to begin with, when I was
a little boy, I was very poor.
Peterson, I'm not going
to survive any story that begins
with when you were little.
Oh, right.
Sir, I've had this fantasy
that's haunted me all my life.
At night, when I'm lying in bed,
it comes and torments me.
Oh, I know the feeling.
Yes, sir. Of course you do.
Anyway, this is my fantasy, sir.
It's a little outrageous.
So, uh, just stay with me.
Even though I was born poor
and I'll never be a rich man,
somehow, it wouldn't make any
difference if one time, sir,
just one time,
just one darn time,
I could do something symbolic,
like...
carry a rich man across the lawn
in his pajamas.
Come here.
I know, I know, I know,
it sounds crazy, I know.
Sir, no... sir,
I don't have a fever.
No, I know that.
I'm feeling
for the lobotomy scar.
Sir, sir, please.
Sir, please, please...
All right, all right,
all right, all right!
Look, if I actually
let you do it,
Uh-huh.
Would you promise me,
would you swear on
your mother's grave
that you would let me sleep?
Yes, sir, I swear. I prom...
No, no, no, no, no.
You've got to do
more than promise.
You've got to give me
your solemn oath
as a crazy person.
My oath, my vow, my pledge.
I promise you.
All right, okay.
Thank you so much, sir.
All right.
Thank you, thank you
very much, sir.
Thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you so much, sir.
You know, sir, I don't mean
to flatter you,
but you're very firm
for your age.
Thank you very much, sir.
It was everything
I dreamed it would be.
Whoa, hey, whoa,
who made the bed?
I did, sir.
When?
The instant Mr. Drake
vacated the premises.
You mean you came in here
the instant we left
and you haven't left since?
Aw, sir.
Sir.
Sir?
I don't know quite how
to tell you this, sir.
We've got to own up, sir.
I've got to tell you the truth.
Now... ow!
What? What?
Ah! Ah!
Ahh! You should do that
before you go to sleep.
It clears the lungs.
Ahh!
You'll sleep much better.
Sweet dreams.
Hi, sir.
Oh, I knew it, I knew it.
You broke your word.
No, no, no.
You lied to me, Norm.
No, no, no, sir.
You see, I went back to the bar
to tell everyone
about my dream coming true.
And since none of their dreams
have come true,
they wouldn't believe mine.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
Sir, my dream
is to have people know
that I carried a rich man
across the lawn in his pajamas.
You're going to hurt me.
No, sir. I just need witnesses.
I've got several
lined up outside.
Greyson would fill out
the troop nicely, sir.
Just a couple minutes,
This is a nightmare.
Then it'd be all over, sir.
You can sleep, I promise.
This isn't happening to me.
This is a nightmare.
Don't worry about it, sir.
We're going out now,
but only for a minute!
Will there be any more bees?
Oh, no, no, no, sir.
You shut your eyes now.
All gone, all gone.
Hey, guys, here they come.
Here they come.
They're coming, they're coming.
He's got Drake.
Oh, here they come.
Yes, Norm.