Cheers is filmed
before a live studio audience.
Boy, oh, boy, oh, boy. Yep.
Woody's wedding was quite
an event, wasn't it, Norm?
Oh, man. Huh, huh?
Boy, what a night
that was. Yeah.
Yeah, the priest dying. Yeah.
Carla being caught
in a dumb-waiter.
How about that German guy
trying to kill Sam?
"Du, dort!"
Remember that?
Yeah, oh, golly.
Oh, yeah, but all that
was nothing
compared to the
wedding itself. Yeah.
Oh, now, there
was a comedy of errors.
Hey, it's not quite 2:00.
What do you say we, uh,
stop off at Cheers, huh?
Won't, uh...
won't Vera be angry?
- She'll never know.
- Yeah, well, I guess not.
She... she sure put away
that champagne at the wedding.
Yeah, she's a big girl.
Yeah, she's still out cold, too.
Okay, just don't slam the
door when you get out.
And remember... crack a window.
You're a good husband,
Norm Peterson.
♪ Sometimes you want to go ♪
♪ Where everybody
knows your name ♪
♪ And they're always
glad you came ♪
♪ You wanna be
where you can see ♪
♪ Our troubles
are all the same ♪
♪ You wanna go where
everybody knows your name. ♪
Okay, Sammy, I'm going home.
I put away all the glasses.
The, uh, bottles
are in the storeroom,
and all the rest of the garbage
from the wedding's
in the office.
Thank you, honey, I'll lock up.
- Where's Rebecca?
- Just told you,
she's in the office.
Hey, Norm, uh, you mind
if we make a stop or two
on the way home?
I, uh, forgot
to finish my route.
Cliff, no.
Eh, all right.
I'll do it tomorrow.
- Hey, Rebecca.
- Hi, Sam.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just thinking,
you know.
Weddings always make me do that.
I have nothing
to show for my life. Oh, come on.
You're being a little harsh
on yourself, aren't you?
I mean, come on,
take a look at today, right?
The wedding started
to fall apart.
You pulled the whole
thing together.
Yeah, I sort of did, didn't I?
You bet you did.
You know, you know,
I used to think
that if I married a millionaire
or if I had a baby,
I'd be a better person,
but now I realize
that the only thing
that's gonna make me
a better person is me.
Boy, as scary
as that sounds, it's true.
In fact, you see this cigarette?
This is the last cigarette
I'm gonna smoke forever.
This is gonna be my...
my symbol of change,
you know, the old Rebecca
burning away.
And I'll tell you
something else.
Starting tomorrow,
there's gonna be no more whining
and no more complaining.
I am gonna be the best manager
in the whole world.
Okay, good night.
I gotta get my life together.
No more screw ups.
No more mistakes.
Good-bye, old Rebecca.
Well, I think we've got this one
pretty much under control.
You get hold of the owner?
Yes, sir, should be
here any minute.
Engines 28 and 30 can head back.
oh, my God.
Mr. Malone.
Everything's under control.
The fire's out, no one was hurt.
It was basically confined
to this end of the bar.
oh, this is terrible.
How did...
This is my bar.
Oh, man.
Oh, oh, yes, wait a minute.
Oh, thank God!
This is great.
This is really good.
I'm sorry?
Gary, you know, from
Gary's Olde Towne Tavern?
Oh, we're doing...
always doing pranks
like this, you know.
First, he makes the bar
look like it burned down,
and then he gets you guys
to go along with it.
You are very good.
Come on, lighten up, will you?
Come on, Gary!
Come on out.
Hey, you know,
time to push the button,
make everything
go back together again, Gary.
Gary!
It's not Gary, is it?
Sammy, this is terrible.
You know, it just hurts me
just to look at this place.
I know, I know.
But I'll tell you something.
As soon as the
insurance kicks in,
we're gonna get this place
back on its feet
in a couple of weeks.
I just wish I knew
how it started.
Hold it right there.
What are you saying, Sammy?
That a Tortelli kid
would torch his mother's
place of business
just for spite?
No, I'd never think that.
Why not? It's plausible.
Listen, just...
just start cleaning up.
You know, we're gonna...
all gonna feel better
if we just start cleaning up.
You know, I gotta say, Sammy,
you're taking this whole thing
pretty darn well.
Not like some people.
Oh, the humanity.
Norm, I wish you'd
stop saying that.
You've got to get a
hold of yourself.
I'm sorry, I... I just...
This place means
so damn much to me.
It's my home.
Hell, for the last few years,
it's been my life.
And the thought of living
without it, Sammy...
Oh, buddy.
Now, I'm gonna be over at Gary's
for the next few days, okay?
I want you to give me a call
when it looks decent, all right?
Somebody said
there'd been a fire.
Oh, my God,
I had no idea it was this bad.
Sam, what happened?
We don't know yet, sweetheart.
But don't worry,
everything's gonna be fine.
I've already called
the contractor,
phone company,
the electric guy.
I think that's everybody.
Sam...?
Well, almost everybody.
Well, Sam, I see you monkeys
have discovered fire.
Would you like to come upstairs
and see the damage
at Melville's?
You know, why not?
It might even cheer me up.
Hi, everybody.
What happened here?
Woody, we had a fire.
Oh, no.
This is terrible.
This is Cheers, my home
for the past seven years,
the place where I grew
up, and now look at it.
You ought to see the pool table.
It actually fused to the floor.
Really? Cool.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Cliff, was that
undelivered mail?
Oh, yeah, it was, Doc.
my sweet Lord,
what a catastrophe.
I mean, there could be letters
from mothers to sons in there.
Social Security checks,
wedding invitations.
Well, there's only one thing
left for me to do now.
What's that, Cliff?
Get up early tomorrow
and stage a Jeep accident.
Well, it's a good thing
this fire didn't spread.
It could have been
like that fire
my great-grandmother's
cow started.
Darned thing kicked
over a lantern,
burned an entire city
to the ground.
Yep.
The shame was so great,
the family had to move to Ohio
and change their last name
to Wilkins.
But, Woody, you're from Indiana,
and your family name is Boyd.
Oh, well, some stuff
happened in Ohio.
Come on, Woody, we've got
to get to the airport.
You know,
when these things happen,
it really makes you
stop and think.
Bye, everybody.
Next time you see us,
we'll be tan.
Bye, Woody.
Well, I discovered
the cause of the fire.
Same old story.
Some idiot tosses a cigarette
into a trash can,
and the whole thing goes up.
Are you sure?
Yeah, seen it 100 times.
When are people gonna learn?
Are you all right?
Uh-huh, I'm fine.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
You know, I couldn't help
overhearing that conversation.
Wild guess: Your cigarette?
No.
Rebecca, you burned down
the bar, didn't you?
What, am I wearing a sign?
Are you gonna tell Sam?
Could you?
I don't really think
it's my place.
No, I mean, could you tell him
you did it?
Rebecca, you have a very
difficult choice to make.
My advice to you is to
simply tell Sam the truth.
He's gonna find out
about it in any event.
You're right.
He will.
All right, I'll tell him.
And I mean,
he's a friend of mine,
and it was an accident.
He'll understand, won't he?
Okay.
Thank you, I feel better.
Sam?
Could I talk to you a second?
Yeah.
Sam, we found out how
the fire got started.
You're kidding. No, and-and...
the guy said, you know,
he's seen it happen
100 times, so he's
seen it a lot.
How did it happen? What...
I-I'm getting to that, it's
just sort of hard to say.
Please tell me.
All right, all right, I-I'll...
The fire was started by...
Faulty wiring.
Faulty wiring?
Been meaning to take care
of that for years.
My God.
I burned down my own bar.
Oh, Sam. Oh!
It's gonna be okay.
We all make stupid mistakes.
No.
Okay, guys, I got
the plastic bags.
You can start bagging the soot.
What happened to you?
Uh, a little Jeep accident.
Nice of you to, uh...
join us, Norm. Well...
Thought you were gonna
wait it out at Gary's. Well, I was,
but then it... I
came to my senses
and realized my place was here
helping Sammy.
If we all pitch in,
we'll have this place
back together in no time.
Gary wouldn't run you
a tab, huh?
No, he was a real
jerk about it, too.
Rebecca? What?
Have you told Sam
how the fire started?
Oh, yeah, I told him, and, uh,
he kissed me, and he hugged me,
and he-he told me what
a big person I was to tell him.
You didn't tell him, did you?
Of course not, you moron!
Rebecca, don't
you realize
that unless you tell him,
your guilt will get
progressively worse?
You'll start to shake.
You'll get the cold sweats,
insomnia, nervousness.
Suddenly one morning,
you'll wake up,
and you'll be paralysed
from fear and guilt.
I can live with that.
It'll just be like
every other Monday.
Well, I called
the insurance company.
We're not getting a penny.
What?!
Well, it turns out
that my insurance policy, uh,
had a $25,000 deductible.
Isn't that rather high, Sam?
Yes, it is,
Mr. Where The Hell Were You
When the Agent Was
Talking a Mile a Minute?
God, man, I'm, um,
in a lot more trouble
than I thought I was.
Rest easy, my friend.
I'm gonna take out my cheque book,
and I'm going to write,
"Pay to the order
of Sam Malone."
Then I'm going
to fill in an amount
that will be more than adequate
to bring Cheers back
to its former glory.
There. I've signed it.
Now all we need is the signature
of Lilith Sternin-Crane.
Oh, she'll put up a fight,
the little badger,
but this is important to you,
so it's important to me.
I'm simply gonna go home
and demand that she sign it.
Yes, demand!
I don't care what she says.
She will sign it!
Thanks, Fras.
Uh, you know, I'll
probably just go
to a bank or
something, you know?
Oh, thank you, Sam, thank you.
There was... no way.
You understand.
Your monthly cash flow is,
uh, this figure here?
And now you want us
to grant you a loan?
Yes, please, and by
the end of the day, too.
Thank you. Uh-huh.
Am I on one of those programs
with the hidden camera?
Oh, no, I-I'm afraid you're not.
I know I'm not.
I was making a point.
Mr. Malone,
there is no way
we can grant you a loan.
I've been to every bank in town.
They've all said no.
Listen, oh, come on, you know,
you're supposed to
be the friendly bank.
Remember, you know...
♪ We're the friendly bank... ♪
Mr. Malone...
Oh, come on. I've seen
the commercial. You know,
you-you're supposed to sweep
everything off your desk here
and offer me a cup of coffee.
You don't even have
any coffee here!
Mr. Malone, good afternoon!
Oh, please. Don't you
remember? You know...
♪ You and us ♪
♪ Working it out together... ♪
Doris, do send in Security now.
You know, ♪ You and us ♪
♪ Making the world better... ♪
Sam...
I burned down the bar.
And, you know, see,
speaking of bars burning down,
guess what I did?
Hi, Sam. Did you get the loan?
No.
It's all right,
though, you know.
It's not the end of the world.
Yeah, I've been
thinking long and hard.
I got a plan here.
You know, I figured
that if I, uh... if I cash in
my baseball pension, you know,
max out my credit cards
and maybe move
to a cheaper apartment,
and...
well... sell the Vette.
A neighbour of mine, Kirby, uh,
had his eye on it
for a long time,
and, uh, he's upstairs right now
taking a look at it.
No, no. Sammy, your Vette?
Well, I... You know,
it'll be all right, um...
she'll come back to me.
She'll-She'll find me.
Like...
Lassie?
All right, Sam,
you got yourself a deal.
All right, okay.
There's the check. Yeah, thanks.
Thanks, Kirby. That's great.
The, uh... the
title and the, uh,
registration are in
the glove compartment. Yeah.
Okay. Great.
Well, uh, so I guess
all I need now are the keys.
Sam, the, uh, keys?
Thanks.
No, no! Wait! Wait...!
Please.
Listen, there-there's
another way.
I just thought of another way.
See, I can get this money.
All I have to do is, uh, come up
with a simple product
that America needs.
What?
No. Listen to me. You know,
like-like the Pet Rock.
Or the, uh... You know,
the vacuum thing
that-that cuts your hair
at the same time.
Or-Or maybe even,
you know, the-the toilet duck.
You-You know, just throw
it together from scraps
around here, you know,
and-and sell millions of 'em.
You know, why didn't I, uh,
think of that before?
Sam, you're just making
this harder on yourself.
Yeah. Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, they, uh,
stole that toilet duck
idea from me.
Yeah. Yeah, you see, uh,
in my original sketches,
I had it as a goat.
Look, uh, Sam,
if you don't mind, uh,
I'm ready
to drive my Corvette home now.
Sorry, Sammy. Oh.
Thanks.
Kirby, take care of her.
This is a day
I never thought I'd see.
Yeah, me, too.
You know what makes it worse?
This is all my fault.
You know, I'm the one
who did this to myself.
If I'd checked the wiring,
you know?
That's a stupid mistake
I'm gonna live with
the rest of my life.
Oh, come on,
what is it now, Rebecca?
I have something
I have to tell you.
Sam, the fire wasn't your fault.
I was smoking a cigarette,
and I burned down your bar.
You did this?
You did this to me?
Yes, yes, of course.
Why didn't I figure
this out earlier?
My bar burns down,
you're within 50 miles...
it all fits.
Sam, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, what-what...
what were you thinking?
Huh?
You tired of screwing
up your own life?
You start to pick on mine?
You know, of all the stupid,
stupid things you've done
in your useless life,
this is your masterpiece!
I'll tell you what. Why...?
Get out.
Get out of my bar.
Sam, it was an accident.
She had it coming.
Nobody had that coming.
I don't want anyone
to defend her.
She's gone. Case closed.
Let's just get back
to work here.
I'll give you a hand.
Well, I guess we've seen
the dark side of Sam Malone.
Hmm. You want to see dark sides,
you ought to see Ma
when you leave
the shower curtain
on the outside of the tub.
That's something
you don't do twice.
I know you don't want me here,
and I'm going.
I just wanted to drop this off.
I cashed in my checking account
and savings,
and, uh, everything
I could scrape together.
I owe you this.
Good-bye, Sam.
Rebecca, wait-wait a minute.
No.
Sam, look, you and I don't have
anything to say to each other.
You said some things today
that you cannot take back,
and you really hurt me.
And I know
that what I did was terrible,
but what you did was worse
because you did it on purpose.
I don't want to ever
see you or this bar again.
Good-bye.
Do you want your job back?
Yeah, I really do!
I'm sorry.
Listen, uh,
why-why don't I, uh,
get my jacket
and drive you home?
Or maybe, uh...
maybe we'll take a walk.
It's such a nice, nice evening.
Sam, uh, just out of curiosity,
why are you taking me back?
Well, I...
I remember that five years ago,
after I had sold this place,
I came back to the bar,
and, you know, my boat had sunk,
I didn't have a dime,
I didn't have a job,
and I needed someone to give me
a break, and you did that.
And I owe you one.
Sam...
Hey, listen, uh, this
is very important.
We're even now.
Yeah. All right.
You want to go out and
get a pizza or something?
Sure. All right.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Um, I don't have any money.
Oh, that's okay.
We'll-We'll just
take it out of my life savings.
All right.
This should just about cover it.
translate