-Dude, I cannot believe
Amy Poehler's here.
-I know. it's crazy.
She's such a legend.
-Hey.
-What's up, Amy? How you doing?
-Uh-oh. Here comes trouble.
Don't hit me.
-I'm Veronika.
-I know who you are.
You are always
sticking it to the man,
giving him hell.
-It-- It's my s-second week.
-There's my guy.
There's my man.
God, remember when we used to
tear it up back in 2005?
-Lower East Side?
Bartenders kicking us out?
Mr. Pizza Sticks.
-Nah, I don't --
I don't think that was me.
-[ Normal voice ]
I'm pretty sure it was you.
-I was 6.
And this guy.
-Me?
-The classic
"will they, won't they?"
The old slow burn.
It's nice to see you again.
-You have no idea who we are,
do you?
-I don't. No, I'm sorry.
I thought I was coming into this
building to get a mammogram,
and it turns out I'm hosting.
Oopsie.
So I'm -- I'm nervous.
I'm very nervous.
And when I'm nervous,
I make things up
and I get face blindness
and I point my fingers
around a lot.
This guy knows what
I'm talking about.
-That's a plant.
-It is.
Okay, I'm gonna head out.
I'm gonna hit the lobby.
Great meeting you guys.
-Do you think she's okay?
Oh, that's a closet.
-You kids are hilarious.
-Hey, this place is strange,
man.
-Lorne Michaels' office, please.
-I think we just leave her in there, right?
-Yeah.