-With the rise of RFK's Make
America Healthy Again movement
and his recent announcement
connecting Tylenol to autism,
many doctors say
health misinformation is
at an all-time high.
Here to set the record straight
is manosphere health podcaster
and biohacking pioneer
Chuck Spyro.
-Yeah. Alright.
What's up, Che?
-What's up, Chuck?
-Can I just say you're
funnier than ever
and you're looking great?
-Well, thank you, sir.
So what's the deal with
all this health misinformation?
-You know,
there's a lot of BS out there.
Fad diets, bunk supplements.
Sometimes you want to say
vitamin F off, man.
-Alright, well, let me guess.
You know the secret.
-Look, Che,
I used to be like you.
A successful guy who just wasn't
reaching his full potential.
-I think I'm doing alright.
-Just an angry, unmotivated,
eating like crap,
drinking like crap,
more likely to walk off a bridge
than jog a single mile.
-Alright, buddy, relax.
-Okay.
That's when I discovered
the benefits of biohacking.
After reading this book, "The
One Hour Guru" by Chuck Spyro.
-I mean, isn't that you?
-And my life changed
overnight, Che,
by following a simple
daily routine anyone can do.
-Okay, well, let's hear it.
-Here's what I do.
Every morning I snap
awake at 4:30. No alarm.
Dissolve 40 grams of rock salt
in piping hot water and chug.
Then I strip nude
and make a beeline for sunlight.
That's very important.
Got to get in that sunlight
as quickly as possible.
There I eat papaya, rice powder,
and a gallon of iodine.
-A gallon?
-Then I make a beeline
for my subzero shower.
That's where I journal,
reflect on my goals,
and lower my body temp
to 65 degrees.
Then I make a beeline
for sunlight again,
assume a reverse lotus pose
and blond my perineum.
45 minutes later,
I somersault back inside
and I make a beeline
for my cryo chamber.
-Are you just sprinting
around your house
butt naked for two hours?
-Then after scream therapy,
I lie on my couch,
order a catering tray
of Chick-fil-A nuggets,
and swipe on Raya
for four hours.
And I feel great.
-I mean,
see, this is the kind of thing
that seduces people
and it's mostly fake.
-Oh, yeah? Would something fake
have this kind of music?
Che, I used to be just like you.
Steak 'n Shake for breakfast,
Red Lobster for dessert.
More likely to put a gun in
my mouth than a piece of fruit.
-Whoa! Take it easy, man.
-I was 300 pounds, 6'10",
soaking wet.
-You lost weight and height?
-Then I started taking
mitochondrial fluoride
and running 16 miles
three times a day,
three times a night.
-How many miles is that?
-Che, I lost over 400 pounds
in a month.
I worked my way to the top
of the biomedical tech space.
Did a couple of years
in max-security prison for fraud
and got out,
married a brilliant,
soulful 19-year-old.
And here I am,
27 and on top of the world.
-27?! You're fully gray.
-Thanks, man.
-No.
-And if there's one thing
to take away from this,
remember this.
You can always refuse to die.
Ow. Sorry, Che.
My Neuralink just went off.
Time to get my 16 miles in.
-What? You're going to run now?
-That's right.
See you at JFK. Stay healthy.
-Chuck Spyro, everybody.
For "Weekend Update,"
I'm Michael Che.
-I'm Colin Jost.
Good night.