-My wife blew up the bathroom.
Now I slammed my head
on this stupid mic.
My life [laughing] sucks.
I just need a minute.
Who put that there?
-We are shooting
a very funny trailer
for a fake true-crime show
called "Gone Without a Trace."
And it's about
these three doofus husbands
that spiral when their wives
leave for like 30 minutes.
-What the hell is this [bleep]?!
-We have a lot
of found footage,
a lot of, like, Ring cameras.
There's a lot of body cameras.
We have six GoPros today.
We're kind of
picking and choosing
from different types
of true-crime documentaries.
-My wife is missing, man!
-Bring it up!
Got to go, got to go, got to go!
And action!
-Megan!
-Miles is hilarious.
Feels like he related to this
a lot, too.
-Bring her back!
-As soon as he heard the idea,
he was like, "Yeah. Yes."
-It's about sort of a group
of dumb guys.
-Which is kind of what all my
sketches are about these days.
-Definitely.
Where do you pull that from?
-Yeah. Can we move on,
Ben Fincher?
-Hey, man, this is my art.
-Come on!
-This group --
Jake, Dietsch,
Ceara, Jimmy --
they call themselves Claudette.
And I asked if Claudette
would want to write it with me.
-There's a lot that I relate
to these three men.
This is right in my wheelhouse.
-What do you eat?
-I have a husband,
and he never knows where I am.
-I never know
where my boyfriend is.
So I don't totally listen.
-I was literally
in the bathroom,
dumping, if you must know.
-What is this?
-No!
-That's a wrap.
-Thank you. Love you.
-I hope
there's anything there.
-That was not usable.