Well guys, a new study was just released
that found
that people go on the highest number of dates in the fall.
Here to
comment on this is Jane Wickline.
Hi, Colin.
Hi. Hi, Jane. So, how was your night
last night?
Well, let's just say I'm wearing what I
wore yesterday.
Yes. Yes. But you also wore it the day
before that.
Well, let's just say the first two days
were because I thought it looked nice.
But this is the third day.
Okay. Okay. So, you're saying that you
did a walk of shame?
I'm not on a walk of self-regard.
And I And I hear that you have a song
about that.
Yes. Okay. This is a song about those
classic late night texts you send.
And
it's called I just texted. Can I come
over?
Take it away.
You start typing back right away.
Oh my god. Amazing. I'm going to get
laid.
You type for an extremely long time.
What is on your mind, babe? What is on
your mind?
And then my phone dings
like the bell of an angel getting its wings.
And I read the sexiest 104 words known to man.
You're like, "Oh, I guess that's fine.
I've been feeling kind of off today
and I might go to sleep right when you get here,
but you can come if you're okay with that.
I'm seriously feeling so off today.
I think I might be coming down with something.
I tested negative for covid, so that's good.
It must be some kind of bug.
But you can come if you want,
but I might give you this bug.
And I'm not going to be fun.
I'm gonna go to
sleep right when you get here.
It's up to you.
Doesn't Doesn't sound that enthusiastic.
I guess
I write back something non-committal.
Haha. Okay, I'm coming over now.
You think I'm scared of a cold? Here's
what I have to say to that.
Baby, you can get me sick.
I don't have anything
coming up.
You You have work.
Just work. And my sister's wedding is
tomorrow.
Baby, you can knock me out.
I'll cancel my whole month to hook up one time.
I want to see what you got going on under
those 10 blankets.
I walk into the room.
Tissues are strewn
on your bed like rose petals.
You're in the bath already, saying,
"Did you bring
my soup? Don't come in here.
You are sicker than I thought.
I brought you champagne and oysters and Ferrerero
Rochair.
Yes, I'm sick. You're sick.
So, can you please get my soup?
And when while you're out, can you swing by CVS?
I say yes, baby. I know what you want.
A bunch of plan B and more Ferrer
Rocher.
Baby, you can get me sick.
I have no plans.
Again, Jane, you have work.
All I have is work that I can sherk
and a brisk that I can miss.
And
oh no, a symptom.
I'm already getting sick.
You have some crazy power over me.
I wouldn't be surprised if this thing is
covid.
What?
Baby, you can get me sick and I'll still go to work
cuz I'm pulling my sick days
so we can't hang out.
Do you have covid?
It's like they say, if you don't test,
then you don't have it.
I'm definitely sick.
I text you, maybe
we can quarantine together.
And you're
like, I'll think about it.
Well, think
about this. I love you,
Jane Wickline. Everyone
update. I'm Colin Jo.