-Hey, guys.
Thanks for taking the time
to meet with me.
-Yeah.
-Of course, dude.
-Um, so you have
a sketch idea for us?
-Yeah,
I was thinking I would play,
like, a cool pope
doing baptisms in a hot tub
and just, like,
cool stuff like that.
That's good.
Yeah.
-Sorry, is Jeremy listening?
-Oh, yeah.
Jeremy's, um, training
for the big
hot dog eating contest.
July 4th is
right around the corner.
But, yes,
I promise he's listening.
-Are you sure?
Because he seems really
locked in on those hot dogs.
-Oh, Jeremy's the best listener
on the cast.
-Okay. So, yeah, like,
the cool pope
would do communion,
but instead of drinking wine...
Anyway, I was thinking
he's, like, a mobile pope.
He's got a cool --
-It's not wet enough.
I feel bad. I feel bad.
-Miles, are you okay?
-Yeah. I'm sorry.
I just lost my train of thought.
-Okay, guys,
don't worry, I got this.
The sketch is "Cool Pope."
Your robes are made
out of jeans.
The popemobile is a skateboard.
And for communion,
instead of wine and bread,
you're eating pizza
and drinking...
Both: A tallboy
of ice-cold malt liquor.
-Oh, my God.
-You really are
a good listener, Jeremy.
-I know. I'm the best.
-Jeremy? Jeremy!
-Oh, Jesus.
-Oh, my God!
-Give him mouth-to-mouth!
-Help!
-Medic!
-Mouth-to-mouth!
-I don't want to.
-No, you have to!
Mouth! Mouth!
-Can someone else --
-Mouth him!