-This was actually my dream.
I said I'm living my dream.
-Okay, here we go.
And action.
-♪ I miss my ex's dad ♪
♪ Oh, Gary and Dr. Mike ♪
-Hey, we're on the set
of "Country Music Breakup Song,"
aka "My Ex's Dad."
-Very nice, Tommy.
-Written by Ben Marshall
and Tommy Brennan and Dan Bulla.
-Cut. Lights on.
"Your boyfriend kissed me."
-Your new boyfriend
tried to kiss me.
-I didn't try
to kiss your back.
-Is he usually like this?
That's so embarrassing.
Those were the shoes
I just wore around
until I got laughed at too hard
from the rest of the cast.
Two in a row songs is, um,
not what I thought
I was going to be doing, but...
♪ And I'd give up forever
to touch you ♪
It's fun as hell.
Sang in my audition.
♪ There's a sexless vibe
in Washington ♪
♪ That I've been trying
to articulate ♪
And no one was casting me
in songs
for the first couple weeks,
so I said,
"Guess what?
I'm gonna start writing them."
We have, like, savant musicians.
You send them
like a little voice note
with like a "This is
kind of what I think it is,"
and then they have
like a chart-topping hit
for you in 20 minutes.
Glen's got an incredible
country music vibe.
How do you not write
a country song with this guy?
He's so good.
-♪ He's proud to be ♪
♪ Your ex's dad ♪
-No one knew I sang
for the first time.
- No. It's a hell of a twang.
-Midwestern boy.
-Texas approved.
-Hell, yeah.