Green
-Okay. No guys' favorite movie
is "The Notebook."
-Come on.
Just gets me every time.
Uh, your coat?
-Thank you.
Wow.
You said you run a nonprofit?
-Yeah, I run a small group
of animal shelters,
but this is from
my previous life in finance.
-You know,
I've never gone home with a guy
after a first date.
-What made
this time different?
-You're just...all green flags.
-Should I give you the tour?
-I'd love that.
-So this is the dining room.
I'm basically addicted
to hosting dinner parties here.
-I'm basically addicted
to food.
-This is my office.
I, like, never use it,
but I wanted to get
a second room in case
my mom ever has to,
like, move in.
-Aw, that's so sw--
-And this is my living room
where the magic happens.
Can I interest you
in my famous martini?
-Why do you have a 3-foot
LEGO statue of Bugs Bunny
proudly showing off his ass?
-I don't -- I don't have Bugs --
-I'm staring at it right now.
It's on your desk.
He's popping his booty and
he's looking back at me like,
"Do you want this thing?"
-Can I interest you
in my famous martini?
-Okay, you know, that's way
too much vermouth, by the way.
Sorry. Why does it look
like he's about to bottom?
-Alright,
if he was about to bottom,
then why would he still have
his little red panties on?
-Okay,
this feels like a red flag.
-But can we please continue
with the tour?
Because next up is the wall
of Woofs.
-The what?
-My wall of Woofs.
Photos of all the dogs
I've fostered over the years.
This one's my favorite, Scooby.
-Oh. So cute.
Oh, my God! LEGO Porky Pig?!
What is he doing to himself?
And what is in this martini?
Oh, okay. I'm leaving.
Happened
Well, then you might need
Rent-A-Roommate.
So now
when you bring a date home,
you can blame your
LEGO collection
on one
of our professional
fake roommates.
-You have a roommate?
-Yeah.
-Why does he have that thing?
-I don't know. It's his.
-So weird.
-Well, it's not that weird.
-How dare you insult my...
-What is your penis doing out?
-Put it away.
-I'll put it away.
-I'm leaving.
-Why?
Just 'cause my favorite
movie's "The Notebook?
Written