Delta base, come in. Delta base.
Delta base, this is Zeus research team.
Come in. Do you hear me?
My leg feels better, Charles.
It's good, Renee. It's really good.
- How is she?
- Her femur's broken. She
can't feel it because of the frostbite.
This can't be happening to us, man.
Sir, the radio's dead.
Well, I guess that settles it then.
We'll all be dead by morning.
Not if we make it to the dome.
How? The dome is 40 miles away and all
the sled dogs are dead.
Not all the sled dogs.
We still have Mochi.
The runt.
We should eat him now while we still
have the strength.
How can you say that when you have dog
blood in your veins?
That's a myth. Just the deranged
prophecy of an Inuit shaman.
To make it
to the dome, Mochi would have to pull
Renee through 40 miles of ice.
It's impossible.
Guys,
look.
Well, I'll be damned.
Conserve your strength and do not fall behind.
We have to stick together if we
want to survive.
Yeah. And also, have you guys seen Mochi's face?
He looks really cute right
now.
Can we please stop talking about Mochi?
We have to focus.
Thomas is right. We have to Oh,
his femur is broken.
Mochi will have to pull both of them.
Come on.
In case I don't make it, I just
want to say
I think MoJi's frozen face
is extra cute.
He's so serious right now. Someone's got
an important job.
He does have an important job.
Now, please just watch what you're doing so
nobody else gets hurt.
Good boy, Thomas. Can't afford to
I broke my femur.
I also broke my femur.
I broke my femur. Come on.
To get to the dome, we'll have to cross the Aymong
plain.
Legend says the Pulaga lives there.
A monster with teeth like needles
and hair like rubber tubes.
What's wrong, boy?
What is that?
My god, it's the paga.
What do we do?
We have to kill it before it kills us.
Here's the plan. I'll take the flare.
Mochi,
- wait. They're coming back.
You made friends with it?
What's he saying, Renee?
I don't fully understand the language,
but I think he's saying his baby's fever is broken.
God damn it.
Wait, what's that sound?
Oh my god, the ice is breaking.
Faster emoji. Faster.
My god, it's the dome.
You did it, Moi.
Moi.
Moi,
what's wrong with him?
His heart gave out.
He's He's dead.
Do something, Charles.
Nothing I can do. He He's lost too much
blood.
Then I'll give him mine.
But we don't have the equipment for a
transfusion.
Yes, we do.
teeth like needles. You're like rubber
tubes.
She does have the glut of a dog.
God damn, you look so cute right now.
Let me take over. Let me take over.
Come on, Mochi.
It's no use. There's still no
heartbeat. We're going to lose him.
Damn it.
Please, Mochi.
The world needs you.
I need you.
Moi,
he's alive.