-Picture this.
It's Christmas morning.
Your family's coming
to your house any minute,
but you still don't have a tree
'cause you done blew it.
-And if you done blown it,
you come down to the Rob & Pop's
Last-Stop Christmas Tree Shop.
-And whatever we got,
that's what you're gonna get.
-And what we got is stuff
like this.
-Hey, come on.
Bring it out, Spike.
Listen. Is it tall?
-No.
-Is it nice?
-Does it kind of look like
what the Grinch
would, like, leave behind?
-Yes, it yabba-dabba do!
-But you're in no position
to turn down what we got.
-It's Christmas Day,
and this is what we got left.
-You're the one who forgot
you had custody this weekend,
you junkie.
And we're the only tree store
left open in town.
So, you're gonna get
what we got going on.
-And what we got going on
isn't the best getting
ever to be gotten.
But you got to be getting
whatever we're gonna
be giving to you.
And that's why our motto is,
"You're gonna get what you get
because what we got
is all we can get.
So that's what's gonna
be gotten to you.
And you're gonna get
what we got
because you got to,
and we got you.
-And that's a...
and that's a promise, weirdo.
-Hey, Spike, we told you,
don't smoke by the trees.
-Let me live my life, Dad!
-Put it out.
We got a customer.
-Hey, I know this is
insanely last-minute,
but do you guys happen
to have any trees left?
-Yeah, we got this.
-Yeah, we got this one,
and this one's got a full bush.
-Sorry. Was one of those
just a pineapple?
-Hey, you're a pineapple,
waiting so long to get a tree!
-I work at the ICU. I'm busy.
-"I see you" making excuses.
-And if you were my wife,
I would never, ever blow it.
You understand me?
I would treat you
like Cleopatra.
-Okay.
Do you have any better trees?
-You're gonna get what you get
because when the getting's good,
you better get it
while it's good to be gotten.
Got it, weirdo?
-Did you just have a stroke?
-Hey!
-I'll stroke you if you...
[ Laughs ]
If you don't get gone,
I'll stroke you!
-Yeah, yeah.
And now our stock's
running pretty low.
But we still got trees,
like this mixed-race tree.
-Yeah.
And this one's just peeing sap.
-Oh, oh! Hey!
-And this one is
a Verne Troyer memorial cactus.
Ouch!
-And, uh,
you've heard of the Giving Tree,
but we call this one
the taking tree,
because
this tree will take your life.
-Yeah.
-Oh!
-And if you think
you deserve better, you don't.
-Because our motto is...
-You're gonna get what you get
because when you get
what we got,
we get all
of what has got to get.
And you better be getting
what we're getting at.
Got it? So get this.
You gotta get, got,
the got it to the get it
to the bang bang,
boogie the tree.
Now git!
Spike, what did I say
about the smoking?
-What are you talking about?
He started smoking, not me.
-All right, call now
and get our free
last-minute menorah.
-Got your ass.
-Hey, hey, hey!
Good one! Hey!