-It is a Christmas show,
and we're on the set
of "Home Alone"
with Ariana Grande.
It is a delight.
It is violent as hell.
-It's "Home Alone,"
the horror movie.
-This is the fifth
of the sick, twisted series
that Mikey and Colin like to do.
-Colin and I
have done a lot of violent ones.
A lot of heads
getting chopped off.
We obviously love "Home Alone."
-We wanted to have a mix
of the real booby traps
from "Home Alone,"
and then we were
under the assumption
that Kevin McCallister
had set up other,
perhaps even more violent traps
that we never got to see.
And now we do.
-You have Ariana
as Kevin McCallister.
-Luckily, she was really into
being sprayed with blood.
-Ariana was like, "I want
as much blood as possible.
I want to look like Carrie
by the end of this thing."
-I'm Kate McCallister.
I just love Catherine O'Hara
so much,
and she plays it so earnestly.
You know, it's just...
this made me want to be
in a Christmas movie.
This is my audition.
-What's up, dorks?
I'm playing the role of Buzz.
Colin texted a picture of Buzz
and said, "Should I play buzz?"
And it was immediately like,
"Yes."
This actually looks like me
in eighth grade.
-It's wild to work with him
or look at him
when he's dressed like that.
It makes work impossible.
-Hey, barf nuts.
-I'm about to be bullied
by this dude.
-"Home Alone" --
it's a classic, it's iconic.
The pressure's on
to get it right.
-So it's really important
that we match up everything
as close as humanly possible.
We tried to match
the camera movements,
shot for shot,
like when Kevin's
coming down the stairs
and, like, looking out,
and then his mom
kind of peeks out
from behind the wall there,
and it's like we're doing
that exact same shot
with the exact same set.
We have this, like,
one-to-one replica of the house.
-For the house, it's about
getting the wallpaper right.
So the graphics department
had to, from scratch,
recreate all of the wallpaper.
-All the wardrobe is, like,
custom made.
-There's always something
that gets you.
For most of the scene,
Kevin wears a green robe.
For some reason,
no one has that robe this year.
So I went to a fabric store,
got the last
two and a half yards
and was like, "Please, Sam,
please make a robe."
-There's choreography,
there's stunts.
-There's a lot of VFX,
a lot of tricky, finicky
practical effects
mixed with digital effects.
We have the best team working
to throw this all together
in a not-ideal amount of time.
It takes a village
to make Bowen's arm fly off
and spray blood everywhere.
At this point, we know
that this is
Bowen's last episode,
and it is a beautiful thing
that his last shot on Film Unit
is him getting
his arm ripped off
and spraying blood everywhere.
It brought a tear to my eye.
-That is a wrap on Bowen!
-It's crazy that we're able
to pull all this stuff off.
This is, like, my fifth season,
and it's still mind-blowing.