The only movie that matters this awards
season is
Kpop Demon.
One battle after another.
You guys have seen that.
Hi, welcome to the set of toy
commercial.
I'm Streer. This is Mikey.
We wrote it.
Hey, it's an Ashley Padilla sign.
Look, Ashley Padilla's. She's mad she's
not involved.
We're taking Paul Thomas Anderson's
masterpiece
and we made some toys
reflecting the characters.
We thought it would be funny to hear kids saying
some of the very
inappropriate lines from that movie.
I love them.
- It's inappropriate for children.
- I would say
No, no, no.
For this commercial, we have like six
unique characters that are from one
battle after another.
Those obviously
don't exist. So, we reached out to Monkey Boys,
which is usually our
special effects prop manufacturing house
at the show.
Our first time on SNL was season 40.
They kept asking us, "Could you make
stuff like this really quickly?"
And we
said, "Yes, of course, we can make stuff
really quickly.
Can you make that? Can you make that?
Could you make that?"
It was a lot of yeses.
Wednesday evening, we got uh kind of a a
heads up that this sketch might get picked.
We usually make a sketch and or
send reference images
and just go to work.
It's such a quick turnaround.
We
do a lot of 3D printing at our shop
and
the head for Leo was sculpted digitally and then 3D printed.
They come out, they
get cleaned, they get painted.
For the cardigan, one of our fabricators
laser cut a stencil
which Killian then
used as a a way to get that specific
black patterning.
Yeah,
we tried to pick out the items that were keyed
to your eye when you're watching
the movie.
We did actually build the bed.
Um, we built a couple pieces of furniture over
there.
We took the liberty of putting the
trapoor into the apartment set.
We get, you know, maybe 24 hours at the
most to to actually build stuff.
It takes a lot of a lot of attention to
detail and a lot of tedious work,
but
the team did it. They're amazing.
It's really insane how quickly they make
something to such detail.
Action
of Beverly Hills.
Welcome to the revolution, kids.
Siana Taylor got right back into character as
Perfidia Beverly Hills.
Her Academy
Award nominated character
is a little intimidating being around
Preridia.
She was nominated yesterday.
I don't think I've ever worked with someone
nominated for an Oscar less than 24 hours.
She was lovely. She was like
improvising some conversation
between
her and Loftjaw with the toys and just
kind of playing house.
And it was really
fun to see her be a little silly.
Cutting air. That's a wrap on our hugs.