-Okay, Mom, thanks so much
for lunch.
I gotta bounce. I love you.
-Wait, baby.
I never showed you
that photo of the kitten
following me outside
the grocery store.
Just text it to me, Mom.
The boys are already here.
-No, baby,
it'll just take a second.
Come here, come here.
-Where was it?
No, that's not it, baby.
That's not it.
-Hey. Welcome in.
-Let me guess.
Mom was trying to locate
a picture from last week?
-Yeah.
That's gonna take a while.
Get comfy. We got you.
-Take a stroll through the
endless wonderland that is...
-Your mom's camera roll.
♪ We got 32 of the same
blurry sunset shots ♪
♪ And a selfie with the guy
who she thought was the Rock ♪
♪ And a photo of a photo of
a photo of your childhood dog ♪
♪ And the pics from the beach ♪
♪ Where you see
your old man's hog ♪
-Hey, yo!
-♪ 10,000 photos on her phone
not backed up to the cloud ♪
♪ She wants to show you
every one ♪
♪ And it has to happen
right now ♪
♪ Your mom's camera roll ♪
♪ No place like your mom's
camera roll ♪
-Uh-oh!
It's the back of the router.
-♪ Has she ever deleted
a single pic? ♪
♪ Hell to the no ♪
♪ It's your mom's camera roll ♪
-♪ A blurry pick of a flower ♪
♪ And what I would guess is
the moon ♪
-♪ What the hell is that? ♪
-♪ And every 10th photo is
a baby picture of you ♪
-That's my baby!
-♪ And a thumb and a thumb
and a thumb and a thumb ♪
♪ And a shell that she found ♪
♪ And a paper with the passwords
to all of her accounts ♪
♪ Accidental pictures
where she looked so beautiful ♪
♪ And a selfie with the body
at a funeral ♪
♪ It's your mom's camera roll ♪
♪ Strolling
through your mom's camera roll ♪
-Damn, this lady loves birds.
-♪ Are any of them in focus? ♪
♪ Hell to the no, no, no ♪
♪ It's your mom's camera roll ♪
-Okay. Since you all
seem so interested,
here's a look at my process.
♪ I see something cool,
so I pick up my phone ♪
♪ I put on my reading glasses
on the tip of my nose ♪
♪ I open up an app,
but it's the wrong app ♪
♪ I don't know how to get out,
so I have to ask ♪
Baby, how do I get
to my phone camera?
Trapped in my settings again.
-Mom, why your flashlight on?
-My phone just does that.
-That's easy. All you gotta do
is come right here.
-Okay, well, while we're at it,
let's see what's in your--
-Wait, wait. No, no, no.
Mom, Mom, Mom!
-♪ Bitches and some bitches
and some bitches ♪
♪ And some bitches
and some
bitches and a progress pic? ♪
-Mom, stop!
-♪ Bitches and some bitches
and some bitches ♪♪ And some bitches
and a problematic meme ♪
-♪ It's your son's camera roll ♪
♪ Watch out for your son's
camera roll ♪
-I created a monster.
♪ A version of my baby boy
that I don't wanna know ♪
-♪ Stick with your mom's
camera roll ♪
♪ Your mom's camera roll ♪