Well, good morning.
And can I just say thank you for last night.
In the words of Hosier, you took me to church.
- Oh, it was mutual, baby.
- Yeah,
you wouldn't know by looking at your naked body.
But you are an incredible lover, dear.
Married for 3 years, but last night may have been our most perfect.
Well, almost perfect.
I still can't believe Benny accidentally walked in the door.
Oh, it's fine.
Benny was asleep.
I just really want to be a good stepmom.
- You sure he didn't see anything?
- I'm positive.
Well, speak of the devil.
Morning, Benny.
Hello, father.
How you doing, sweetie? What you want for breakfast?
Could I have a bowl of nothing?
For some strange reason,
I've lost my appetite forever.
Under the weather, huh? Well, have some OJ.
That vitamin C will get you back on top.
On top.
I can get on top.
The girl can go on top?
To quote Mario, here we go.
I'm going to go take a shower now.
Are you sure, Benny?
You've already taken three showers in the middle of the night.
Yes.
And yet I still feel so unclean.
Hey, uh, anyone want a smoothie? I'll take one.
Hey, do me a favor and throw that little weird banana in there.
Throw that weird little banana in there.
Are you sure? I don't want to hurt you.
That thing ain't hurting nobody, baby.
Never has, never will.
Hey, uh, Benny, shouldn't you be getting ready for school?
School? What need have I for school
when I have nothing left to learn?
I'm telling you, honey, something's definitely off with Benny today.
Oh, listen, honey.
Neither of our kids saw us having sex.
Speaking of, uh Oh, hey, Eric.
Morning, bud.
Hey,
honey.
What are you doing with that toaster?
Taking a bath.
Goodbye.
See, both our kids are completely fine.
If anyone saw something, it would have been the dog.
And he's as normal as ever.
He looks shell shocked.
Well, he always does.
That's just that doggy style.
Doggy style.
Doggy style is normally performed with the man behind, right?
- So, you want to switch places?
- Well, I didn't say that.
Here we go.
Oh, Benny's back.
Hey, Benny, did you change your clothes?
Yes.
I've decided to commit my life to God.
Are you sure you don't want any breakfast, honey?
Yeah. Your mom's done with her toast.
Uh, have her piece.
Have herpes.
It might be strange to disclose this 3 years into our marriage,
but I have a herpes.
Never mind.
There is no God.
Oh no, I just realized our blinds were open all night.
Do you think Neil saw us?
Oh, our our neighbor Neil Degrass Tyson.
No, he's always too busy looking into that telescope of his.
Oh, I wonder who that could be.
Oh, hi, Neil.
Oh, hello.
I just wanted to give you my trusty telescope.
I won't be needing this anymore.
Oh, yeah.
Why not, Neil?
Let's just say that I was gazing into it last night and I caught a glimpse of Uranus.
And in addition to the planet, I also saw both of your bee holes.
Good day.
Oh, honey, what a strange, weird person.
Yeah, it really was a night to remember
and one I wish I could forget.