-This is really funny.
-Alexander Skarsgård
has only been here a few days,
but he's already
fitting right in.
-Alexander brings so much
to the table.
Like, he can do things
no one here can do.
-Both: ♪ Sheriff is dead ♪
-Yes! That's awesome.
-All right.
-Alexander's, like,
the total package, dawg.
He makes everything around here
just...easier.
-Much easier.
-Like, so much easier.
Oh! My pen.
I can't reach it.
I'm so little.
-Do you mind if I...?
-Oh, uh,
that would be so nice of you.
-There you go.
-Thank you.
-So then I do
a little solo dance
and it's like, wahhh pa-pa!
-I really don't like that.
-Yeah, it actually looks, like,
a lot better with my hat.
-Do you want your hat?
-Yeah, that'd be great.
Thank you.
-Since you're grabbing stuff,
my football is also up there.
-Do you want me to, uh...
-If you could.
-Thank you so much.
-Oh, you're welcome. No problem. No problem.
-He tall.
-I'm just so stressed out
about this choreo, man.
I need, like,
some fresh air or something.
-Get up, little guy.
-Wait, really?
-Really.
This is a dream come true!
I'm so tall!
-It is a dream come true,
isn't it?
-Me next! Me next!
-Uppies, please! Please!
-All right. Kids, kids, easy.
One at a time.
-Ready for a little spin? Yeah?
-Ohh!
-Guys, I'm tall too.
I can help you reach stuff.
-Go away!
-Get lost, beanstalk!
-Shut up, stupid!
-Get out of here!
I don't see you moving! Go!
-I'll catch up with y'all.
-No, you won't.
-Okay.
-Who was that freak?
-I have no clue.
-Yeah, we don't know
who that guy is.
-Problematic energy.
I love my life!