You're watching channel
four KOMO news in Seattle.
KOMO se dice news us
still working on that.
Good evening.
I'm Jones, Earl James.
and I'm P. Henson. Taraji.
Later in the program,
our beloved
Seahawks are headed
to Super Bowl 60.
But how will they get there?
The answer won't surprise you.
A plane.
and what's black
and white and red all over?
A biracial man who ate fireworks
and exploded in blood.
Sorry. Thought that was
going to be a silly one.
All that, plus Jake Resnick
with our five day AccuWeather
forecast.
Let's just say I'm going
to need these sunglasses for
to keep my eyes dry.
But first, we're joined
by one of the leading biologists
from the University
of Washington
who has an alarming
announcement.
Doctor Wesley Simmons,
thank you for joining us.
Thank you
for having me. Oh. Thank you.
I, I just wish
I was here with happier news.
Well, this is important for the world to know,
so please go ahead, doctor.
Thank you very much.
You know,
my team and I have been studying
some of the most common everyday
viruses.
And unfortunately,
we've discovered
a new strain of Epstein-Barr.
The the Epstein-Barr virus.
A new strain of it,
I'm afraid. Yes.
Can you give us
any more details?
Yes. Of course.
I'm not hiding anything.
I want everyone to know.
And how is this new strain
different than the original?
Well, it's more aggressive,
for sure.
I can tell you that.
MORE
And the virus does
not discriminate.
You know, it targets
the young as well as the old,
men, women, boys and girls.
And I
have a family practice as well.
So I have seen Epstein Barr
prey on many of my patients.
And I'm so sorry.
I just
saw myself in the monitor.
I think there's some kind of
issue with the graphic under me.
I'm worried. It makes me seem
like I'm the new Epstein.
Well, we'll get that cleared up
right away.
Now, doctor, what is your advice
for avoiding this virus?
Well, you know, unfortunately,
there's no vaccine available.
We're discovering
that it's actually better
to be exposed to it
when you're young.
And, And if anyone is worried
they're a victim of this
new strain.
If you have any rashes,
you know, feel free
to send photos
so we can properly diagnose it.
And I am sorry, I'm seeing the
graphic is still a little wrong.
Can you just
can you just make sure
that whenever it says Epstein,
there's a bar as well?
Absolutely.
We'll make sure there's a bar.
Have you discovered anything
else?
Yes. Well,
I went back through my files,
and I, discovered some things.
And I
will be sharing all my results
with the public shortly,
I promise.
So check, check that
Okay.
And so I think
they they had an actual bar.
Not the word bar, which I think
makes it look even worse.
We're going to get
the graphic sorted out.
Doctor,
are you, like,
just skeptical?
I was about to explain
how the strain of the virus
has a much larger viral load,
but until they fix the graphics,
I might.
I might just drop it. So.
Okay,
guys,
how do you get to that?
Come on.
I'm told they're working
on the graphics right now.
In the meantime, we're joined
by the first patient
who discovered
who was carrying the new strain
of the virus, bill young.
Thanks for having me.
You know, when Doctor Simmons
first diagnosed me with
a new strain of Epstein-Barr,
he warned me that no one would
believe me.
Okay. Well, okay.
Oh, God.
Oh my God. His name.
His name is young. Oh.
He told me to hydrate
like crazy.
Keep pounding fluids. His word.
That's not. And,
that's not right.
And he told me to isolate myself
from my family.
Almost like I was on an island.
That's what he said.
But not the actual island.
I knew people would be skeptical
at first.
That's why I said it.
Eventually there'll be more data
to back me up.
But right now, it's hard.
NEW
I'm hard, guys
These graphics
are making me
look really bad.
A lot of people
are probably watching
this on mute in the airport.
I'm sure it's fine.
Although
our phones are lighting up.
I don't think we've gotten a
call on a landline
in, like 15 years.
Oh, and we're getting a ton
of response online.
The National Center
for Victims of Abuse
just tagged Doctor Simmons and
wrote all caps monster.
And yeah, and I
agree with them on this, Taraji.
This virus truly is a monster.
Okay, can I can
I please clarify something?
Yes. Go ahead, Doctor Epstein. Doctor
Simmons.
Doctor Simmons.
Look, I'm not the only one
working on this virus, okay?
ALONE
You know, we have elite doctors
all over the world
who are
supporting us in this endeavor.
And we are so grateful
to the Gates Foundation
for funding all of our research.
And. Yeah,
and I've been in constant
communication
with the government
all the way up to RFK
Jr and the president
of the United States.
We're in constant communication,
and I'm only one
member of the team.
Can we please just show
a group of our research?
So the whole group.
Oh, absolutely.
Let's show the team.
Unfortunately,
we weren't able to get any of
their permission
in time for the broadcast.
No, I would if you could.
It clear. Why would you show it?
Yeah, I'm
noticing a jungle as well.
- Was that photo taken on your
island?
- I don't have an island.
It was a business lunch.
We went to the Rainforest Cafe.
Hey, Dr. Epstein is this your
phone, Cause it■s smoking.
I think you got, like,
10,000 texts now.
I'm sorry.
What is happening?
Did I, like,
have sex with a graphics
guy's wife or something?
YES
Oh, yeah. All right.
Okay, well, that explains a lot.
Why don't we take a break?
When we return, we'll meet two
very different Menendez
brothers.
That's right.
These two killed their dad.
Wait. Sorry, I read that wrong.
They're going to teach us
how to grill ham.
Sorry.
Not even that close.
No. It happens.
No. It
happens. It's interesting.