-Oh, my God.
And so by the finale,
-I was completely dehydrated.
-You're welcome.
-And by the way,
the Russian accent was awesome.
-Thanks. Yeah. Um, I actually
do all kinds of accents.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Did someone
say all kinds of accents?
Well, I reckon this here show
ain't big enough
for the both of us.
-[ Southern accent ]
I reckon it ain't, partner.
-It's an accent duel.
Come on,
let's get out of the way.
-Y'all ready?
-Call 'em out.
-German!
-Oh, das ist easier than
drinking ein Hefeweizen, ja?
-Cajun!
-[ Cajun accent ] I was taking my fambo down there
Lake Pon-char-chon Way.
-French.
-[ French accent ] But what do
you mean, everyone wears Croc
to the airport?
-Shakespeare!
-To be or not to be?
-That is the question.
-Now Shakespeare but bad.
-[ British accent ] To be or
not to be. That's the question.
What's up with this guy,
am I right?
-Jamaican.
-I feel like guys like us -should probably not --
-Yeah, that's not --
I don't think
that's a good idea.
-Okay. Sorry. What about
a Na'vi from "Avatar"?
-[ Jamaican accent ] I seeing ya
clear as Mother Eywa, mon.
-Shrek!
-Get out my swamp, Donkey.
-Italian!
-[ As Mario ] Here we go!
-Russian!
-[ Russian accent ]
When you get to hell,
tell them Rosanov sent you.
You got me.
-Yay!
-I won. I won.
-Good job, man. That was great.
-Is he okay?
-James!
-James.
-Ja-- He's not breathing!
-You okay?
-You killed him!
-Uh, medic?!
Can we get a medic?!
-Stop. Relax. Stop!