-How dare you?!
-How dare you?
-Hello. Welcome.
-This is the set of
"Victorian Gentlemen."
Streeter Seidell and I wanted
to do a sketch
based on the taking off a glove
and slapping someone.
-Oh, sorry.
-That one was my bad.
Connor Storrie is a dreamboat.
-How dare you?!
-Very committed to character,
very game to be silly.
Look at your hat, Fettington.
-Chapeau on.
-And he's very good actor, too.
-How dare you?
-Are we done with this shot?
I hate it.
-Marcello's getting punched.
-Nice.
-Connor's getting punched.
-Oh, I'm getting punched.
-You're getting punched.
Everybody's getting punched.
-We rented a dummy,
and wardrobe gave us
a second set of clothes,
and so we were able to
not have to injure the real boy.
-We get slapped by a dog
in this.
No, my mustache
was falling off from moment one.
Mustaches are annoying.
How dare you?
Mama!
That's it.
-Good luck, everybody.
-I would like the team
to approve.
-Thank you so much.
-And the hat stays
on your head.
-Connor Storrie!