The art of looks maxing when young men
go to extreme lengths to improve their appearance
is taking the online
manosphere by storm.
Here to tell us how
to achieve the peak male form
is
21-year-old looks maxing influencer Chad
Maxington.
What's good? What's good?
And can I just
say Colin, you're brave
to sit next to
me on live TV, bro. That's awesome.
I'm brave. Why? Why am I brave?
Uh because I'm absolutely framemogging
you into oblivion right now, dude.
Check
it.
Frame mogged.
I'm sorry. Wait, what is frame mogging?
dude, Are you like a hundred, bro?
It means my frame mogs yours.
Like, no. No
offense, but you're sitting there
gesture gooning like a subhuman beta cuck.
Meanwhile, I'm out here oramaxing
like an S tier gighat.
Speaking of English, Mud.
Yes, I actually do speak English. And
that's not it.
Let me let me explain Max for you for
you dork.
Watch it.
All right. I'm like the rock and you're
like the crumb. Okay.
Check me out, bro.
A blood pressure cuff hates to see me
coming.
You're not You're literally not even
that much bigger than me.
I am though. And check the angles, bro.
Jawline.
See that is call?
My jawline literally
goes from my ear to my ass crack.
I'm chiseled as hell. Literally chiseled.
What are you doing? Stop doing that.
No, I'm bone smashing to promote bone
growth, dude.
And you can do some, too.
Okay, just stop. Stop it. Okay,
this is serious news. Okay, it's a new serious
news program.
You're just doing all this to get in
shape. Is that the deal?
Uh, yeah. To get into a shape square
with veins.
All you got to do is protein max,
steroid max, and methax.
Jaw
Then in one
day, you too could look like
the big
gray block from Mario 64.
Okay. Well, contrary to popular belief,
I don't use steroids,
dude. Why not?
Okay, I'm on so many roids,
my nuts receded so far up into my body
that I have a second Adam's apple
now. Look.
Necknut
Oh my god. Why are you
Why are you hurting yourself, man?
You're young.
Stop. You have your whole life ahead of you.
I just want to pull mad chas, bro.
Okay. And has this been working?
Not sure. I technically haven't spoken
to another human being in a year.
Okay. Well, let's give it a shot. Ladies
and gentlemen, a girl.
Hey,
want to see my neck nut?
Oh my god, that was horrible.
- Shoot.
- Let Let me show you how it's
done, bro. Okay.
- Hey.
Do you want to see my throat scrub?
Calling everybody.
Hey, don't update mom me.
My throat's gross.