I was recently diagnosed
with sleep apnea.
-My snoring was so loud, I
couldn't even live in the city.
-I tried mouth guards
and nose tape,
but nothing worked.
Then my doctor suggested
I try a CPAP machine.
-With the CPAP's
constant airflow,
I'm getting better sleep
than ever.
-I feel like myself again.
-My sleep apnea is outta here.
But now I have
a whole new problem.
-Honey, where's
my good-night kiss?
-Right here, babe.
-Oh. Never mind.
-That's why I put down
the CPAP machine
and picked up the CoolPAP.
Now, how about
that good-night kiss?
-Wow!
-Say goodbye to awkward
medical equipment
and hello to the sleep mask
of your dreams!
-Normally, I'm too embarrassed
to let romantic partners
stay the night,
but thanks to CoolPAP,
that's all in the past.
-Is that a CPAP machine?
-No! I'm a pilot! Good night!
-The CoolPAP works
by delivering pressurized air
through custom masks like...
"V for Vendetta," surgeon,
pillow, Master Chief,
and DJ series with
deadmau5 and Marshmello.
-And thanks to CoolPAP's
custom designs,
no one will ever even know
I have sleep apnea.
-Oh, babe, one more thing
about tomorrow.
-Yeah?
-Oh, my God!
-It's just my face!
It's just my face!
-Why?!
-Six years into our marriage,
the last thing I needed
was bulky medical equipment
ruining our love life,
but with CoolPAP,
my husband does not mind.
-Yeah. I could get used to this.
-If you're worried
about traveling
with that lame CPAP case, heh,
let's just say the travel bag
is a little more cool.
-He's got a bomb!
-So stop snoring
and start scoring...
with the CoolPAP!
-Good night, honey.
-Good night.
-Ohh!
-CoolPAP. From the makers
of the Coolostomy Bag.