I was recently diagnosed
with sleep apnea.
- I'm sorry.
That was funny.
-It was too good.
It was too f--
-Resetting.
-Oh, hey, we're "SNL" and
welcome to "CoolPAP BTS."
-At the mark.
-All right, here we go.
-Look at that CoolPAP.
-Me and Jack's first pre-tape,
so yeah,
let's hope it goes well.
-Well, I'd spied on Jack Black,
and I saw he did an interview
with Mrs. Amy Poehler
that they both
had CPAP machines.
I recently started using
CPAP machine, so I thought,
why don't we create art
out of this?
-Let's just say the travel
bag is a little cooler.
-I snore really bad
and choke in my sleep.
And I got tested for sleep apnea
and they said it was false.
-We had to make
two different masks this week.
One was a faux beard
with sunglasses for the host,
and the other was
not quite a mask,
but something for Sarah to wear,
which inflates.
-Thanks, CoolPAP!
-It's very freaky
to see your own face projected
into a weird version
of your face.
When I saw it, I went,
"This looks nothing like me."
And then I saw it on Chloe
and I went,
"Oh no, it looks
exactly like me."
Ya boy ugie!
-But I got to kiss
Jack Black today.
He's literally the best dude
in the world.
-He'll lift one eyebrow.
Hilarious.
-Action. Eyebrows.
-Like what you see?
-Turns out Andrew has
a huge noggin.
-We had to stop down
for almost an hour
because his head was too big.
-All right,
that's a wrap on home.
-Good wrap up, Chloe.
-We did it!
-Yay!
-It got cut.
-Yeah, we're not
even upset, man.