Simon's life
-My adult cousin on my dad's
side has trouble making friends.
His name is Simon.
He has difficulty connecting
with new people.
-Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Do we know each other?
-Oh, not by name.
It's just not every day
I meet a fellow childless adult
in the Nerf gun aisle.
-This is for my nephew.
Are you hitting on me?
-No, don't worry.
I'm not trying to get you
into my bed,
which is shaped like a car.
-What is going on?
-The name's Simon,
but you can call me El Tigre.
-Okay.
Your hand looks really wet.
-Perhaps he has trouble
connecting
because of how he dresses.
-I'm pretty sure
you're not wearing pants.
-Pretty sure?
Allow me to make you certain!
-Oh, my God!
-Somehow, Simon is a member
of something called a polycule,
as we found out when he
brought all of his love partners
to my grandma's Easter dinner.
-Okay. I'll start.
I'm Crystal,
I'm asexual,
but I'm always horny.
-I'm Pennywise,
I'm a Taurus, and I'm queer,
but only in the sense
that I'm unusual.
-And I'm Chobani.
I'm a queer,
non-binary person of interest
in the murder of Kathleen Durst.
Did?
-Simon gets that from his mom,
who also brings weird
new boyfriends to Easter dinner.
So, Lucas,
what do you do for work?
-I work for a little company
called Brian's Secret.
-When it comes to lingerie,
why let women have all the fun?
-Introducing lingerie for men.
-From Brian's Secret.
-I don't understand
Simon's life,
but maybe I'm just jealous.
Simon has community,
and I don't have anyone anymore,
after what happened with us.
You'll never believe what --
-It's not what it looks like.
-Hello.
-Are you cheating on me
with Jack Black?
-It's not her fault.
No one can resist.
-What?
-No one can resist the power.
-The power of what?
-The power of my --
...lingerie for men.
Bedroom
Can
For men
Thanks, Brian's Secret.