- Where is our waiter?
- I know it's taking forever.
First the
war in Iran, now this.
Circle the way you guys.
Oh, I I I guess that's her.
Yeah, Applebee's wishes it was this
slammed, right, babe?
I don't even know what to say to that.
Hello. How are we doing tonight?
My name is Crystal. Like the meth.
Okay. Have we done with this before?
Uh, nope. This is the first time.
Oh, well, welcome back. Welcome back.
Okay. So, sorry for the way you guys.
I'm sorry we're a little bit slammed,
but I promise you, you are in amazing
hands. Okay, I've got you covered. All right?
So, are we celebrating anything
special tonight?
Um, yeah, it's actually our anniversary.
Oh my god. Well, happy birthday.
Okay. Can you get yourself some water?
Spring.
Oh, what? Uh, what?
Spring time, by the way.
Um, oh, half is fine.
Okay. Okay. Amazing. All right. Well,
um, so here is a menu for you guys.
And
of course, a kids menu for the little
guy.
What?
Ooh. Should we get started with some
drinks?
Um. Ooh. Yeah. Margaritas.
Margaritas. Oh, okay. I'm fine. Okay.
It's a fun table. Okay. I like you guys.
Yeah, you guys are fun.
Okay. Um, so I'm
Okay. Well, she's a character.
Yeah. Sounds like she's maybe had dental
surgery recently,
but whatever. Would
still smash.
-It's our anniversary.
-Sorry.
Hi guys. I'm the manager.
Just checking in to make sure everything going.
Have a
good time. Having fun. I know you're
hungry. So, all is going to make sure
that you get some food.
I make up for the weight. We got you
some complimentary tableside guac.
Ooh, we get the big show.
Let's give him something guac.
There we go. And I heard it's a birthday in the house.
A happy birthday, little man. How fast.
Ow. So strong.
He is not a child.
Yeah. If I was a child, would I be doing
the maze on the menu with a pen?
No.
Okay. care the drinks for you guys. Have
we had a chance to look at the mans?
Cuz
I really recommend this steak. Okay.
Amazing.
It's amazing. I have it like three times
a day. I literally do.
You eat three steaks a day
and I'm obsessed with the chili chipotle
cherries. The choppers are so good.
Yeah, they are. He eats them like all the time.
- So, it's she knows.
- I know. I know.
Okay. Okay. I'll get the steak.
excuse me.
I mean, I'm in a red. I
suggest medium rare down.
I
I I guess medium rare done.
Okay. One straight rammer and I'll go
for the little guy.
I'm a grown man. Okay.
Um I'll have the
buttered noodles.
I found nachos.
There's quesadillas.
That is not a word search. It's a list
of appetizers.
Hey guys, under
like a fun table.
So fun. You guys want to tell over the margarita?
A little bit of margarita.
Hey, that's
okay. What about the song? Let's all for
you guys for you guys.
Dude, dude, we're good on the song.
Okay, guys. You guys have been so
amazing. So nice to talk to you.
It's
nice to be with you guys and we're
letting you guys and I want to say to you
happy birthday.
He's He's my least favorite one.
It's no one's birthday.
It's happy birthday. It's a happy
birthday.
Happy birthday, little boy.
For the last time, it is not his birthday.
It is our anniversary.
It's your anniversary.
You're celebrating at a chill house.
Anyway, here's a trick for you.
- Please take your time.
Happy birthday.
Thank you so much.