-A new "Forbes" poll indicates
dating-app fatigue
is growing
among many U.S. singles,
with many seeking
to meet partners offline.
Here with more on this
are a guy
and his girlfriend
who's always cold.
-Hey.
-Wow. So people are experiencing
dating-app fatigue?
-Yeah, exactly.
Now, obviously you know nothing
about dating apps
'cause you ain't meeting a dime
like your wife on Bumble.
Am I right?
Pound that, dude.
That's incredible.
Incredible. Incredible!
-Yeah. So, uh, cool.
H-How did you guys meet?
-Oh, we actually met
through the ancient art
of mutual friends,
but I honestly think
that's why we're still together
after a year.
It's 'cause
our initial connection
came from a real place.
-Yeah.
-It's freezing in here.
Right?
-Yeah.
I told you to wear a
jacket, but you didn't want to.
-'Cause I like my outfit.
Sorry. It's, like, so cold.
-Alright. Here. Take my jacket.
I asked.
I said,
"You want to take a jacket?"
-Are you sure?
-And you said, "No." Yes, yes, I'm sure.
-You're gonna be so cold.
-I'm not gonna be cold!
'Cause it's not that cold.
Just take my jacket, please.
Take my jacket, please.
-Thank you!
Is that better?
-Yeah.
-Alright. You're not cold?
-No.
-Alright. So, people lie
on their profiles.
They use filters
on their pictures.
-I'm cold.
-Alright. Here!
Take my hoodie.
Take my hoodie!
Sorry. Sorry.
I do this every day.
I do this every single day!
I do this every day!
-It's really cold.
-Sorry. Sorry.
-Thank you. Good.
This is what the people
on the "Titanic"
must have felt like
in the water.
-It's not at all like that.
Not at all like that.
-No, it is.
Look. No. Look.
-You can't--
-You can see my breath. Look.
-You can't.
-Watch.
-You can't see your breath!
-It's like I'm smoking.
-Are you still cold?!
Do you want my shirt, too?!
-Yeah.
-Fine. Oh, this is awkward.
I have a tattoo of your wife,
and I'm sorry.
I'm a fan. I'm a fan.
I got it
before you were married.
-He's a huge fan.
-I didn't know I'd be
taking my shirt off, baby!
-I'm really cold!
-Just take my shirt!
Look at me!
How are you still shivering?!
-I'm cold.
-With more layers! I can't do it anymore.
-My feet.
I'm going crazy.
I love you,
but you're never not cold.
-Sorry.
-Heat. Heat at max!
Any room we sleep in.
Any season.
Any region. Any climate!
I'm so hot at night!
-Just, like, literally--
literally feel my hands.
They're like icicles.
-Oh, my-- I can't do this.
We have to break up!
But she's so pretty!
I'll never do better than her!
Alright. Fine. I can't leave.
I can't leave her.
-Sorry. I'm not crying.
It's just my eyes water
when it's, like, really cold.
-Okay. What else do you want?!
You want my pants?!
It's all I have left!
I'm gonna take off my pants
in front of Colin Jost
and Michael Che!
Don't look at me!
-Hurry!
-This is my life!
-Thank you.
It's like my butt's cold.
See? You are cold!
-A guy and his girlfriend
who's always cold, everyone.
-What do you want from me?!
For "Weekend Update,"
I'm Colin Jost.
-I'm Michael Che. Good night.