-White rapper Jack Harlow
recently made headlines
for describing the sound of
his new album by saying,
"I got blacker."
Here to explain himself
is Jack Harlow.
-What's poppin'?
Brand new whip
just hopped in.
Remember that Shay?
-I mean, kind of.
How you doing, Jack?
-Spectacular to meet
your acquaintance.
Dap me up, my brother.
-Alright.
-Hey! Oh, no. No.
That's not how you do a dap.
-Can never get
that one right.
-Alright, man. Well...
you're here to tell us
about your new album.
So what was the songwriting
process?
-Yeah, basically, man,
I was at home for the holidays with my fam,
asking myself like,
"What's my new sound?
What's my new sound?"
It was stressing me out,
man.
Damn near ruined
my Kwanzaa.
-Uh, sure. Jack. Yeah.
-Yo, so I went to sit outside
the liquor store with my OGs.
-Okay.
-Like I do every day when
the UV isn't too high.
-Let's just move on.
I don't know if you've seen.
But some people have been
clowning you online.
-Alright, alright.
I've seen it.
I've seen all the clever
little nicknames, you know?
Mos Def-initely not.
L.L. Cool Whip.
D Anglo.
-That's good.
-That one's good.
That one is good. Yeah.
-That's really good. -That's a good one.
Jay ZZ Top.
-I like that.
-Lil' Wayne's World.
You gonna like this one.
Kan-ye it's Friday!
You know I'm cool with it man.
'Cause that's what we do, Che.
We roast each other, man.
Then we rub our hands together
like an otter in the river.
-We don't do that.
-That's what we do, man.
-No, we don't.
-And I just like to create,
bro.
Hell, I'll freestyle right now
off the top of the dome.
-All right, go ahead.
-Alright, alright.
Alright. Yeah. Mm.
-Alright.
You don't gotta do this.
-Good, man. Good.
-Good. I did not want to, man.
I did not want the album.
-Let's get back to the album.
It's titled "Monica."
-Yeah.
-Which some people
are suggesting
is just a clever way of saying
the N word.
-I don't hear it like that,
man.
It doesn't hit my ear that way.
-Come on, man. Mo-ni-ca.
-Whoa!
-You said that, not me.
I just love the name Monica,
man, always have.
Ever since she topped off
my favorite president.
-Oh, Jesus.
-He's not your favorite?
-So the genre of your new
album is listed as Neo Soul.
What made you want to go
in that direction?
-Because on this new album, I
wanted to challenge myself, man.
I thought,
what's blacker than rap?
R&B?
And to me, R&B stands for...
Rhyming
-No.
- Rural
-No!
-Yeah.
Real
-Wrong again, no.
-Know what I'm saying?
Raised
-That sounds about right,
my nigga.
Jack Harlow, everybody.
-We gotta stick together, Che.
That's the "Weekend Update."
I'm Michael Che.
I'm Colin Jost. Good night.