-Maybe if you're
in a funny wig.
-I feel like we've done that.
-God, I don't know.
What if it's a commercial?
-Hm, maybe.
-Hey, what are you guys up to?
-We're trying to figure
out the perfect SNL sketch.
Experts have been trying
to crack this for years.
-Yeah, Ferrell got close once,
but ultimately,
it drove him insane.
-Yeah,
I see you guys are doing like,
a "Good Will Hunting" thing
with the chalkboard.
You guys know that movie's
like, 30 years old, right?
-Never seen it, dude.
-Yeah, I grew up in a cult.
I've never seen a movie.
-This is hopeless anyway.
-Yeah, it's getting late. Why don't we call it?
-Yeah.
See you, Matt Damon.
-See you, guys.
-Oh, my God.
-Who did this?
-Wow.
Looks like someone
finally cracked it.
-No, not even a little bit.
Somebody just wrote
"Bisexual cigarette talk show.
Black Snape as host.
No guests."
-Then they drew stoner carrot
checking into a casino hospital?
-Yeah.
-Matt Damon, did you do this?
-No.
-Matt.
-No. I was cleaning.
-Yeah, you're holding the mop
upside down, buddy.
-Matt Damon,
I think you did it.
-Nope.
-You definitely did this.
You're not getting anything.
You're just making marks
on the ground.
-No, I'm not. I'm cleaning.