Making amends
-Son.
-Hey, Dad.
I heard about your heart attack.
-Didn't expect you to come.
Wasn't much of a father.
-Weren't really a father at all.
We haven't talked in...
-24 years.
-Well, for a second there, um...
I was worried we were gonna
have to say goodbye.
Bar savior
-Your sister tells me
you have a son of your own now.
-I do.
I don't know.
It's got me thinking.
-About what?
-All the things
I almost didn't get to tell you.
-This bar sucks!
It sucks!
-Suck my [ bleep ].
-Oh, yeah?
-I just realized I hold
a lot of anger towards you.
-You know how you can help me?
By sucking my dirty [ bleep ]!
-Okay. Just one --
What is this?
-Oh my god!
How is there so little cheese
on that?
-Vagina boy.
-Uh, sorry. Sir.
-Yes?
-You mind just turning down
the volume a little bit?
-Absolutely. I'm sorry.
-Great. Thank you.
Dad, I hated you for leaving.
-You fat [bleep] bitch!
-I'm not fat.
Yo mama's a fatty.
My momma is a model.
-For what? Mobility scooters?
-Son, I'm listening.
Just say what you have to say.
-Um, when you walked out on us,
I never wanted to see you again.
-What even is the theme
of this place?
Hawaii in space?
-But now that I have a son...
-The theme is just Hawaii.
-...I just wish I knew you.
-Then why with the Avatar stuff?
What are the Na'vi doing
in Hawaii?
-Exactly.
-Okay, sir. What is wrong with you?
-I got stabbed.
-Oh my God!
I don't think
you should be drinking.
-Okay. Your son sucks, man.
Hats off for leaving him.
-Thank you, Thomas.
-Why would you hang that up?
Why?
*casey anthony*
-It's the day the bar opened.
-Nobody wants to think
about that.
-Dad, when you left us --
-I'm the host.
-I don't do this.
I've never done this in my life.
You know what?
-Don't. Oh, great.
You just woke up my chef
from his nap.
-What is he wearing?
-His uniform!
-There's too much bush!
-I don't think there's
enough bush!
-I like the bush.
-What was that?
-I said, being a father is hard.
-Yeah, I get that.
-This bar suuuuuuuuuuucks!
-Suck my [ bleep ]!
-Stop saying bad words
on my show.
-Do you know what?
You still should have been there
for me.
-[ Bleep ] isn't a bad word.
-Well, it sure as [bleep, bleep]
ain't a good word, sister...
-I was just a little kid.
You still should have been
my dad.
-I know, son. I'm sorry.
-I've always wanted
to hear you say that.
-I will [bleep] end your life!
-Everyone relax now!
-Can you forgive me?
-I don't know, Dad.
-Shoot.
Do it! Do it!
-Wait! Wait!
I'm not even the owner,
I'm just the manager.
-I'm the chef.
-Son.
-I'm gonna find whoever owns
this place,
stab them in the neck,
and then I'm gonna go to
the hospital and finish the job!
-I love you, Son.
-I love you.
-You!
Written