-Can you believe it, kids?
First, a Juicy Toobin concert,
then a meet-and-greet?
Just a 5-hour drive
for a 30-minute show.
I ain't mad.
-Okay, guys, my name is Craig.
I am the human helper
on the Toobin tour.
Now, who's ready
to meet the Juicy Toobins?
-Me!
-When I say, "Juicy,"
you say, "Toobin."
-Juicy!
-Toobin!
-And when I say back up,
you back the hell up.
You back the hell up.
I'm security.
You don't need to know my name.
Listen closely.
If you want to meet
the Toobins,
you got to follow the rules.
-Um. Sure, man. Yeah.
Whatever.
-One, the Toobins owe you
nothing.
They don't owe you a picture.
They don't owe you a hug.
And they certainly don't
owe you a Toobin Tango.
Two, keep in mind,
the Toobins are exhausted.
They are performing
three shows a week.
They are spent.
-It's like barely any shows.
-And three, if you move
too quick on a Toobin,
I will kick you
all the way to Guam.
Do I make myself clear?
-Yeah.
-I said,
do I make myself clear?!
-Yes!
-Good.
-Hey, man,
it's a children's concert.
Maybe just take it down a notch?
-What'd you say, fella?
Huh?
-I'm just saying, man.
-What are you doing?
-...your kid
gets a Toobin Sleeve.
-What? Oh, my God!
-That's not my kid.
-If you guys think I'm playing
around, I assure you I am not.
-Stomp, stomp, stomp.
Who could that be?
It's Mama Toobin
and her famous cinnamon rolls!
-Hi, kids.
Good thing
I wore my boogie shoes.
Come here, kids. Let's dance.
-Back up, back up!
Back up, back up!
-Back up! Step to the side!
-Everyone say,
"Bye-bye, Mama Toobin."
-Bye-bye, Mama Toobin!
-All right,
we've established one thing.
You kids don't listen.
What's your name?
-Adeline.
-Adeline, you are at a 10.
I need you to take it down
to a 4.
You, what's your deal?
-I'm Josie.
-You're a vulture, Josie.
Yeah. You're a little vulture.
I can smell it.
You take and you take until
the Toobins have nothing left.
-Hey!
-You, Josie!
-No.
-Vulture!
-Look. They were just dancing
with her, man.
-Oh, hey. Yeah, buddy?
One man's dance party is
another man's stampede.
I learned that serving in Iraq.
-You served in Iraq?
-Yes. I was a server in Iraq.
-Oh.
-I served at
the Baghdad Cheesecake Factory.
Number-one Cheesecake Factory
in the Middle East.
That's where I cut my teeth
in crowd control.
-What are you talking about,
man?
-Stomp, stomp, stomp, kids.
Here comes Papa Toobin.
-Who's ready to shake,
shimmy, and do the Toobin Tango?
Come here, friends.
-Back up, back up,
back up, back up!
-Hey, you little kid.
You're like a little mosquito
on there.
You get off!
-Oh, my God!
-Hey!
-Put him down! Put him down!
-I wasn't gonna throw him.
I know how
to safely throw a child, okay?
I was not gonna throw him.
-Everyone say,
"Night-night, Papa Toobin."
-Night-night, Papa Toobin!
-Well, that was hell.
Adults in the room, you guys,
I'm sure a big chunk of you
are on the spectrum.
-You what?
-Excuse me?
-And I can assure you,
I am on the spectrum, as well.
I'm on the spectrum
of having it to not having it.
Except instead of a spectrum,
it's a switch.
And, honey, you just flipped it.
-Dude, relax.
For the last time, relax.
-Relax?
Boom!
-Oh, no!
-Toobin Sleeve.
Toobin Sleeve.
-Hey!
-Watch it, sister. At the
Baghdad Cheesecake Factory,
I was doing four
to five Toobin Sleeves a day.
-Okay. If you were using them
in Baghdad,
then why are they called
Toobin Sleeves?
-Bitch! I know you ain't poking
holes right now.
-Okay, okay.
Okay, kids, this is the moment
you've all been waiting for.
He's cute, he's cuddly,
and he loves asparagus.
It's...
-Hold, hold, hold, hold, hold.
Baby Toobin is about
to come out.
And I know you feral, little
effers want to go nuts on him,
but that will happen
over my dead body.
-Everyone, give it up
for Baby Toobin!
-Hi, kids.
Who wants a Toobin toy?
-Me!
-Here you go!
-Hey! Stop it!
Do not feed the beast!
Dear God!