-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Oh, my God.
Oh, I am so dang lucky.
This is what birthdays are
about, huh?
I got my wife.
I got my beautiful son.
Huh? My boy.
Oh, and John,
it is so nice you came. Wow.
-Yeah.
Dennis hasn't shut up
all day
about
how his cool young boss was
coming to his birthday party.
-Oh, God. Not all day.
Not all day.
-No. It's true.
It's true.
-You know, I thought
that more people
from the office would be here.
-Oh. Me too.
-Alright,
I'm going to Brandon's.
-Oh. Uh, not yet. Gabriel.
Alright?
We're gonna eat some cake first,
and then you can go off
to Brandon's.
Right? They always
want to go to Brandon's.
-I'm done with this.
I want to go to Brandon's.
-Buddy, it's my birthday,
and I want to have
some cake with my son.
-Why?!
-Because it's my birthday,
pal.
Right?
-Damn you! Damn you!
-Yeah.
Kids, right?
-Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
-Uh-oh, don't tell me
your boys are little angels
or I'm gonna be jealous.
-Yeah, I think John's
just a little stricter
with our boys than that.
-Our kids would
never get away with that.
Hey, Gabriel.
You're not going to
Brandon's tonight, buddy.
-What?! Why?!
-Because you talked back
to me,
and we don't let that slide
in this house.
-Yes, we do.
-No. No, we don't.
-What the hell's going on?
-Gabriel.
What's going on
is that you're staying home.
That's the end of the story.
Sorry.
-I'm -- I'm going to Brandon's!
-Hey.
No, you're not, alright?
Sorry.
-Yes, I am!
-Well, okay.
Well, now I'm pissed.
It's not gonna be a sleepover,
I'll tell you that much.
-Yes, it is.
-Well, then,
bring your toothbrush, Mister.
-Hell no.
I won't bring my toothbrush.
-Okay. You win.
Oh, sorry you had to see
that side of me, guys.
-So, John,
are you liking the new job?
-Yeah. It's great.
Everyone's been
really welcoming,
especially Dennis here.
-Oh! Because I like people,
I like people.
-This cake tastes like balls.
-Gabriel.
-What?
-We don't say "balls," right?
-There's, like,
jelly in the middle. Yuck.
-Gabriel, it's my favorite cake.
Okay?
We're just being nice.
-No! I'm going to Brandon's!
-Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop it, stop it!
-I'm going to Brandon's!
-Okay, okay, okay.
Dang. I had to put
the parent hat on. Right?
Gabriel, go to your room.
-No!
-Oh! Hey, Gabriel.
Gabriel...go to your room.
-Shut up!
-Okay.
Okay. Well, countdown time.
Right?
'Cause that's
what we do in this house.
Gabriel, you're gonna
go to your room in one...
...two...
Please go to your room.
-No!
-Okay. Alright.
That's it. Fine.
Then I'm throwing him
over my shoulder.
Right? 'Cause that's
what you gotta do as a parent.
Alright, come on. Come on.
You're going over my shoulder.
Stop it!
I'm taking him to his room.
I'm sorry
you guys have to see this.
Okay. I can't do it.
I can't! Hey!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Stop! Stop!
You know what?
Alright,
I'm throwing him over.
Stand up.
Right? 'Cause I gotta do this.
That's being a parent,
and it's ugly.
Jesus Christ.
God, why are you so big?
-I'm small for my age.
-There's no way.
-What is his age?
-Alright, over the shoulder.
Let's go. Come on.
Okay.
You're going over the shoulder.
Alright, you know what?
Da-- Okay, okay.
I'm gonna have to hit him
where it hurts.
Right?
Allowance.
You get none.
-I want it.
-Fine.
You can't bargain with that,
right?
And I'm sorry that you
had to see me lay down the law.
-Yeah, I think you just
kind of let him push you around
and ruin your cake a bunch
of times.
That's because...
I didn't want to have to
do what I have to do right now.
This is the ugly side
of parenting.
Alright?
We're doing belt, huh?
Because we have to hold...
-Dennis!
-You're not gonna do the belt.
-This may be, uh,
hard to believe,
but this was not what
I planned on happening today.
-You know what, Dennis?
It's -- I get it.
It's tough being a dad, okay?
Especially for you.
Because your son is gigantic.
Way too big.
He looks like Will Ferrell
in a kid wig.
-Hey! Shut up! You shut up!
-Buddy, buddy...
He's my boss.
Thank you
for saying all that.
I'm gonna reprimand him, and --
and I'm gonna take him
to his room. Okay?
You're going
to your room, bud.
You're going to Brandon's.
-Thank you.
-Okay. Let's go.
-Ow! I'm not ready.
-Bad boy, right?
-Don't push me.
-Don't bump me!