-Iran paralyzed
commercial shipping
through the Strait of Hormuz.
-The Strait of Hormuz,
-Strait of Hormuz.
-The Strait of Hormuz
remains closed
to any ship trying
to get through.
-Except mine!
I'm Hormuz Jeff.
And if you got something
you need shipped through the
Strait of Hormuz, I'm your guy.
I've got the only boat
going through the Strait
of Hormuz right now!
How am I able to do this?
Simple.
I have nothing to lose.
Family
Friends
Best of all...
Die
Six years ago, I dove into the
shallow end of a swimming pool
and pancaked my head.
Since then, I don't feel fear!
I'm like that Free Solo guy,
except I promise
I've gotten a thousand times
more panoony than that nerd.
What?! What?!
You met me.
Now meet my boat,
the Hormuz Hornet,
a 22-foot party pontoon
outfitted with not five,
but six Yamaha racing motors
illegally welded to the back.
Now, that's fast,
Ain't it, ladies?
-Oh, yeah.
-Hey, what did I say?
If you're gonna cough,
do it off camera!
-Whoa!
-And she fell off the boat.
Ship
Anything
Don't ask
And neither does my first mate.
-I don't need to know [bleep]
-Just listen to
this satisfied customer.
I am pleased.
-The only thing
we don't ship is animals.
They crap in the boat
and can't handle the speed.
I drive fast.
After all, it's called "Iran,"
not "Iwalked."
-I just shot a fish.
-No, you get off my ass!
Hey, don't let a war stop
your shipment.
Contact
-You have to use text-o, though.
-Right, right.
You have to contact me
using text-o.
It's not
on the normal app store.
It's a third-party alt-web
secure messaging service
only available via Peelr.
-Yeah, you gotta download Peelr
first, man.
-Peelr is a phantom browser.
Just go to
www1.Bananapeelr.zox,
then install
Peelr-Installer.XLE.
Once Peelr is installed, then
download text-o through Peelr.
-Yeah,
you run text-o through Peelr.
-All communications with me.
From messages to payments,
everything has got
to go through Peelr.
-Never do it normal.
Always do Peelr.
-Always.
-Gotta use Peelr.
-Got to.
The only way your shipment
won't be completed is
if we get blown up.
But we take precautions
to ensure that won't happen,
including driving top speed
in a wild zig-zag
and blinding recon drones
with a paintball gun.
So when it absolutely has to get
through the Strait of Hormuz,
contact Hormuz Jeff
on text-o
through Peelr today because...
-He doesn't care if he dies!
-She's coughing again.
-Fish!