-As you know,
tonight is the season finale.
Here to reflect on Season 51
is The Hunchback
of 30 Rock herself,
Sarah Sherman.
-Hey, Colin. You know,
this season has made
me finally accept
something
I've been fighting for years.
My haters are right --
It's bad.
-Your acting in sketches?
-No. Hey!
My haircut.
I mean, look at this thing.
Vegan in the front.
Pronouns in the back.
I actually copied this hair
from Paul McCartney's Wings era.
I told him
that in the hallway earlier,
and the strangest thing
happened.
He killed himself.
-Okay.
Sarah, why don't you just cut
your hair then?
-I try, but it always
bounces right back
into this Smollett.
-Smollett?
Is that like a small mullet?
-No, like a Jussie Smollett.
Because it's a hate crime
I did to myself for attention.
-Really good. Really good.
I have to ask --
Who cuts your hair?
-Obviously
Parkinson's Scissorhands.
This haircut's, like, a thing.
It's very popular
with annoying people.
Sorry. I mean
bisexuals in my neighborhood.
By the way, I'm "bye-sexual."
As in "Bye, sex.
You'll never see
me having that with a woman."
-What...
What neighborhood do
you live in?
-The part of Brooklyn
where all the white people
do land acknowledgments,
like, "I acknowledge that
I've landed an awesome apartment
that used to belong to
a Puerto Rican family."
-Well, I will say, Sarah,
you look much better
in a wig.
Every time
you're blond in a sketch,
I get more bricked than
the third little pig's house.
So then I hit the bathroom,
and I huff and puff
and I blow my own back out.
-Jesus, Colin.
God.
Listen, I can put on a wig,
but I still have
a resting mullet face.
And to prove it,
here's a compilation
of men pulling away
from my unscripted kisses.
Damn.
Don't clap.
Pathetic. Do not clap.
Matt Damon dodged me
like he was George Bush
and I was the shoe.
-Oh, my God.
Well, timely reference.
You know, Sarah,
you have to stop being so hard
on yourself, you know?
-You're right, you're right.
I'll keep my hair the way it is.
Oh, shut up!
And, hey, thanks for being sweet
to me, Colin.
How about we end this season
with a kiss?
Oh! Pepper...
Pepper spray!
-Sarah and her mullet,
everyone.
Get the hell out!