speed
going to meet for about three minutes
then you're going to hear this buzzer
okay and when that goes off we're gonna
move to the next table
ready to find
some love
Tana
what are you doing here
I was asked to
speak at this hotel
it turns out there's
some type of [ __ ] banquet going on
you
know one second just give me a second
[ __ ] you you [ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
ugly fat orange buck
social media
they had to take it away I
was too good
in fact go ahead put it
back up put it back up
people say I've
got bad makeup
Donna looks like someone
painted her face like a clown
that's
what we're gonna call her Tana It the clown
she looks like him she looks like
she should be in a sewer
bothering children
you are utterly disgusting
I'm disgusting I saw you walk in I said
who's this
is this a pig I didn't know
they were letting pigs in
you're a dictator
old sage what a loser what a
loser she was
somebody needs to tell her
that her [ __ ] stinks
when you walked in
I could practically smell you your
vagina stinks
smells no one here is
gonna go on a date with you
there'll be
no problem there I'll get a day
there's
gonna be so many dates people whoa this
guy has so many dates
you none
I don't even need a date but I'll get a date if
I want a date
you can go on Tinder have
you heard of this there's Tinder
you go
beep boop pop and there's [ __ ]
this is pretty exciting I've never been
on a date with a white guy before
hit the buzzer
I mean I'm just wondering
what it would be like with something a little smaller
let me stop you there
I don't know who sat in this chair before
me but it stinks
I told her
any interest
you're gay hey blame the
dairy industry
I would never suck a guy's dick
but if I did it'd be one of
the best sucks he's ever had
a few years
ago women would have the flat butts not
you you've got a very nice one
thank you
you know I did I pulled very
well with the blacks how am I pulling
with you
I saw you come in I said that's the one
the bell of the ball
you're the prettiest one
I'm gonna be
completely honest with you here I'm not
that interested
you're the ugliest
do me a favor could you take your gigantic
perfect tits and leave
I don't recall
saying I would get a date here
but if I
did say that maybe I will
oh my God hello
oh my God
you like my shirt I gotta dye
the special the
there's a
two for one at the tackle
at the tackle
shop The Bait and Tackle
I can get you
one it's two for one wow
how are you Mr
President
well I'm great especially since you
since you expose all the all the Jews
that were put in 5G in my brain that
wanted the meth
how are you at oral sex
pretty good to
be honest my teeth come out
Siobhan
how would you like to go on a date with
Donald Trump
yes finally oh my God I won
did I win
I got ahead