What's up gang? I'm Toby Pictar
and not only am I a military vet, but I'm also a
grilled meat connoisseur.
I went through
hell and back to defend this country.
Now I'm traveling all over it to find
the best greasy grub.
When I was in war, I went through a
pretty traumatic experience
that left my memory fragmented,
but my taste buds
perfectly intact.
And sure,
sometimes
[ __ ]
Whoa. Not cool, gang.
But I'll never forget these tasty flavors.
So, join me while I'm trying to
remember who I am with some
unforgettable food.
I am the grill
sergeant.
I'm here at Haruto's hot house where I
hear he's got a spicy chicken dish that's hotter than nap.
Let's check it
out, gang.
Hey, nice pork job, [ __ ]
Hey, I'll beat the [ __ ] out of you. I'll bust your
ass, boy.
- It's too spicy.
- You don't [ __ ] with me.
What's up, guys? I'm here with Herudo,
and this is his world famous spicy chicken.
Herudo, what's your secret to
this stuff?
Well, I tell you what, Toby, it's all
about the spices.
Ain't that true, brother? Back in the
military, we used to have a saying.
Oh, where's his leg? [ __ ] He's gone.
Tell me about these spices, Harudo.
Yeah. Uh so we're just going to slide in
some uh cornstarch right there.
That's cornstarch.
And then a little bit of uh garlic
powder. Super important.
Garlic powder.
And then a little bit of a cinnamon.
Cinnamon.
crazy.
It is crazy. It's really going to make
the flavors explode.
Drizzle it in real smooth. Because if
you do it with a machine, it might be too powdery.
It's not going to fry too
as good.
Okay,
you [ __ ]
I just love the crunchiness on the
outside.
- I know what you did, you son of a [ __ ]
- What?
Juicy chicken on the inside.
I'm so sorry.
I don't really like the Chinese [ __ ] on
the walls. That's why I don't wear my glasses.
This chicken is unreal.
Jesus Christ.
It's okay. Hey, he's just having a
flashback. You're doing great.
Talk a little bit more about the spices,
the cinnamon.
That's a little goofy,
huh?
You know what I love about this
restaurant?
They play a loud music in
the bathrooms.
What the [ __ ] man?
Okay.
Can you get back to the chicken? Can you
get back to the chicken?
Wow, that chicken's not half bad.
Hey, Herudo, you can really taste that cinnamon.
- You want a bag of ice?
-  Yeah, a
bag of ice might help.
You dinged me up
pretty good back there, Herudo.
Also,
the spice is getting into the wounds
pretty bad.
That's it for Herudo spicy chicken. Wow,
that stuff had a kick.
Coming up next
week, we're headed to Denver to check
out
Jesus Christ. Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm driving around a convertible
eating [ __ ] and sandwiches for a living, [ __ ]
[ __ ] you. Suck my dick.
[ __ ] you. [ __ ] is your problem?