hello
i have your son
what
who is this
let's just say they call me
the sparrow
and is that like a black
name
what no it's not even my real name
shut
up you shut up
hey i have your son
steven yes
okay
and i want 25 hundred dollars
25 000
what are you buying the lakers
you have
30 minutes to hand deliver
that's way too hard he's never gonna pay
it number seven in the league and hitting
got this
what did you not hear what i said
keep him he's a pain in my ass
um well what about his ma
what would she think it's his mother
yeah she's out
tell you what if you want
to swing by and pick her up too
be my guest
but you might need a [ __ ]
forklift
come on man he can't be that bad
how this place stinks put that back on
my mouth
but cover my nose this is utterly
disgusting
christ dad
pick me up
don't worry bud
hey hey don't lay on my
bed like that
i have no other
oh christ you here
that's got to be months old
oh you're right this kid
sucks
can you turn on the news or something
all the kid talks about is news this
news that
vaccines and mass
yeah we need to get to
hurt immunity before we can fully open
up the economy
i'll come down there and give you herd immunity
you tell him i wish he would
tell him i wish you would
- take me off to your bluetooth
- in your dreams dad
help hey both of you shut up
listen you hear how much of a [ __ ] this kid
is
all right damn i'll just bring him back
oh no no no no no you don't have to do
that let's pump the brakes on this
2500 oh i'm bringing back your son
40. 2 000 or i'm bringing the kid back right now
alexa play the beach boys
why ain't i no damn alexa
now shuffling songs by the beach
boys
alexa down
i assume the answer is no but
do you have a yankee candle
alexa
steve
i knew it
tell you what
i'll give you hundred dollars
you
babysit them for the weekend
we have a deal terrific
uh he making this weird face right now
face that means he's hungry
oh it ain't no problem ain't no problem i'll
pick him something
he alerts anything yeah [ __ ]
that's not funny is that funny
man you're great
oh