well
jerry's dead
gonna miss him
he was a good brother i served with him
he fought alongside me at the costco
in virginia
we're blocking looters you know
a lot of us were there
some of us had to work
i did i had to work
you couldn't take a vacation
no i used them all
or what
well as you recall i came down with
mononucleosis
and that took me out for about five days
i passed it to my wife cheryl
and she's big so when she gets sick she
gets sick
shut up glenn
i know why you keep
bringing it up i thought we covered it
i want to thank matt
for putting together this fine casket
american-made
made it out of [ __ ] wood he found
around here in america
one thing jerry
hated the most and he said it to me
before he passed
he said make sure my
casket's not made out of chinese [ __ ]
i said i [ __ ] promise
jerry's fine ass wife terry is in attendance
as is custom
we'd like to present the wife of a
fallen soldier with a holded american flag
bring that to me no it's
the top corner keep it in there there
you go and then this one
under yeah bring that under i'm coming on
this one goes under i'm coming under
there to meet you
jerry sit here and cry
while you're sitting in applebee's
with god in the sky
it's out of tune
it's always at wednesdays and endless pints
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
stop enough excuse me
what's up you shut the [ __ ] up please
turn it off or i'll shut it off
we're in the middle of something
but there's some type of play
what's this a play no
what do we look like [ __ ] lesbians to you
yeah you actually do
no this is a service for a fallen troop
oh we're doing the same thing our buddy
smashed into this tree yesterday
now what you guys are doing is a lot
different this is troops
what's up
military
yeah i mean yeah pretty much pretty much
i was in the navy for a
couple weeks
they tossed me out though because i
couldn't swim
i tried to join the air
force
they there were psychological issues
that i was running into a couple walls
and then uh i got catfished by isis
what was your what was your question
troops yes bomb troops
man y'all gang man
yeah right
we're not gang this is troops
the government give you those guns
no yeah because you're a gang
exactly where do y'all even meet
we used to meet over at jerry's but
we're gonna have to switch out probably
like glenn's
probably glenn's garage or something
oh wait a minute my trains are in there
all  right glenn maybe it's time to move your
[ __ ] train set it's embarrassing
you're a gang you're a gang
you're a
gang how can we be a gang we're white
it is what it is this is a
well-regulated militia
we're the free men of mechanicsburg
sometimes
boys chill no no
we're the turtles
these are the turtles that's cute
the turtles oh cool man
are you laughing at fat matrix
oh now you got them started that was the
last thing you wanted
are you making that noise with your mouth
yeah you want to [ __ ] talk [ __ ]
damn i thought that casket was [ __ ] up
but who did you hair
this haircut's more
than your [ __ ] life [ __ ]
nice bowl cut chuckie you make fun of my
hair from my friends
i'll [ __ ] kill you
what's up what
y'all wanna do
do you wanna [ __ ] go
wanna start something
don't make me
don't make me call the dogs on you
soldiers zip holy [ __ ] this is it
come on come on now let's go
come on
this
okay everybody hydrate
hey hey guys come on let's settle
down okay
we're not that different than each
other you know
we're all here to remember a fallen hero
it doesn't matter if your guy got hit by a tree
or if our guy got beat to death
by a couple of teens at walgreens
actually it was walmart walmart
we're all the same
as far as i'm concerned this is sacred
ground for all of us
and i'll be damned
yeah
yes
you guys all right that beer
was coming right for you
you guys good you okay
oh [ __ ] that is a dude
that is a [ __ ]
dude
oh [ __ ]