hi my name is holly
and i run happy hands daycare
the coronavirus shut down our daycare center
people just didn't feel safe
sending their kids
we were about to close our doors
but then we had an idea
we realized that there's probably so
many people stuck inside
with family members that they just can't stand
so we decided to reopen as a
daycare center
for uncles
hey uncle hank
good to have you today
i got a hemorrhoid like a monkey knuckle
all right
when most people have an uncle
they never think they'll spend all day with them
hey um
you guys think fire's beautiful right
morning miss holly my mom told me to say
thank you for all the prayers for our iguana
once covet hit
that nightmare became a reality
uncle
shane
hey good morning
wow wow nice shirt
what sound does a wolf make
wolves
so we offer a solution
we give uncles a place to go during the day
each day starts with a morning meeting
wait what
we give all the uncles a
scratch-off ticket
with their schedules on it
yoga
god damn it [ __ ]
then the uncles participate
in a variety of activities that suit
their skill set
okay uncle tommy yeah
how old are these girls
are any of them underage
well you can do this
i know okay go ahead
they're all beautiful angels
right but are any of them underage
i don't know
so i have to assume
they're all they're all underage
great jobs yes i'm so proud of you
yes
i'm proud of myself
remember guys as
developed as they may seem
it doesn't mean they're 18.
just my computer
did you guys get this laptop
this is conspiracy class
yeah so basically the hunter biden video
from his laptop is fake
but it's
actually him but they gave him a fake
giant boner
dude italian
he's saying italians
- oh it's valiant
i actually have evidence that jimmy hoffa
was one of the pilots on one of the
planes
my cousin told me
what yeah
we read the uncle some books to help debunk some of
their conspiracy theories
but i don't trust the vaccines cried the
rabbit
oh but you should rabbit they're safe
exclaimed farmer jim
if you don't take the vaccine you won't
be able to play with your rabbit friends
anymore
yeah all right but what happens when the
vaccine turns him gay
like what happened
with me
well remember uncle tim that's a conspiracy
yeah the vaccines don't make
the rabbits gay it makes them artistic
like painting and [ __ ]
- on an uncle
farmer's giving the rabbit the vaccine
so he can control his mind
here at our daycare we have lady uncles
too
with our lady uncles we give them a pack
of cigarettes a robe
and a window they can look at him
to keep an eye on things
see these kids out here look at these
kids
they're just riding their bikes
yeah from what country
at uncle daycare we provide snacks
hey hank feeling famished
the uncles get a beer at 8 a.m 9 a.m
11 a.m 1 p.m and 3 p.m
uncle tommy gets a beer every half hour
love your beers too
all right
we make sure the uncles get plenty of
exercise every day
gushers here yeah
kind of [ __ ] as
he gave me a
breathalyzer and now i can't ride my
harrow anymore so
uncle stem that's great
we do exercises
like taking out an air conditioner
moving it from the house to the car
put in that hatchback put in that
hatchback
you did that
we have other exercises
like bringing in the groceries
when
someone else buys
[ __ ] showers
Fuck
we try to return the uncles back to you
a little bit better than when you left
them
hey hey
sir
this [ __ ] just whistled at my daughter
she's 17.
sir sir listen
may seem
- i'm gonna kill this [ __ ]
-  they're uncles
yeah they're uncles
i'm sorry i didn't it's okay
you didn't
know
okay i didn't know buddy i didn't know
okay did you fall down the stairs i got
hit by an ice cream
hey uncle mike it's me again
MATTERS
uncle mike don't you think something
like this would hurt um
miss holly's feelings
a statement like this
might make her feel unseen and unloved
she knows i see her i stare at her all day she knows that
yeah she does know
that but that's not really what i'm
saying
um i think you can do better than this
come on
yeah
good
what do you have uncle tommy
it's a beer
oh your favorite that's awesome
yeah now go get me one
i fixed it oh
Even black
you know what to start
i'm gonna give it
to her i don't think
nice thanks
at the end of the day the
family's coming to pick them up
we walk the ankles out to the car and
call it a day
have a good one guys
you know people always ask me what's
harder uncles or kids
jane get out of there
it's uncles
come on tommy come on
come on all right come on tommy
kids
don't try to kiss you all day
no
they have better language dude
i'll suck your [ __ ] dick right now
no just
shut up
all people have feelings not italians
all feelings matter
nope
sometimes they make you feel a
little uncomfortable
i can't feel
pricks
kids don't do that [ __ ]
wait wait wait i gotta pee i gotta pick yeah
well just give me a second i'm gonna be
late
you were in the bathroom for a goddamn
hour
No
[ __ ] you
i gotta piss you
Tomorrow
uncle tommy