hello i'm bob isis of isis toyota
and we have a great collection of
pre-owned certified toyotas
but there's
one thing i want to make very clear
and it's that we have nothing to do with
the terrorists over there in the middle
east right now
and that's why we are the good isis
all right listen you got to lean into
the isis thing it's a good marketing
tool
the great marketing tool i agree with barbie
i think you should be like here
at isis toyota
we'll be head the competition
no
we're not doing this what are you guys
talking about
we're not wishing
death to any of our enemies
we are
wishing death to
low to high prices
me and barbie we can
hold ak-47s
yeah
no no that would be so cool
so i'm holding an ak-47 she's holding ak-47
you're like we're gonna do most toyotas
and i could be like i can be doing that
like terrorist turkey gobble thing
you know i mean we're like
at isis toyota we have nothing to do with abu
bakar al-baghdadi
and his vicious gang
of thugs
all we're trying to do is put you into
an affordable pre-owned certified toyota
people don't respect you
to the youngsters i
know you're having fun
i used to have fun myself
but there's something you need to know
stuff like that that's a load of crap
that's a load of crap
can i be in a commercial
no
come on why not
why
it's cause i'm black
no it's not because you're it's cause
your name is
oranthal james anderson
now isis we don't price gouge
but if we find a competitor with a lower
price
we'll kill them
ñut it cut that
we're not doing this
you don't love oj what are you saying he
did it
well
oh god damn it all i'm trying to do
is get you into a toyota
we made this jesus christ
that's great where is
the commercial
look at it
wear this in the comments i'm wearing
that why not i wore it on the bus here
dude you know how hard that was for me
you wore this on the bus yes i had to
bring it here
dedication
do you know how hard that is
to get off costs more than the damn car
like you're blowing it here like you're
really bored yes
would you quit it quit it
i'm losing money on half these things
because you and your punk-ass kids come
down and [Â __Â ] with our [Â __Â ]
you want an
ak-47
stop [Â __Â ] with our toyotas
come down and buy them like a man
i'm i'm under a lot of [Â __Â ] stress
i'll go [Â __Â ] nuts
we are closed on 9 11.
if your dad was real isis
you'd be up in heaven right now covered in virgins
but instead you're a fat
[Â __Â ] virgin covered in used toyotas
come down to isis toyota or i'll
[Â __Â ] kill myself and everybody here