dearly beloved we are gathered here
today
in presence of these witnesses to join
in matrimony
catherine and greg
which is not to be entered into
lightly or
unadvisedly
but solemnly discreetly
advisedly and seriously
if anyone present today can think of
just cause
for why these two should not be
joined
- let them speak now
- i do
i have something to say
catherine
catherine i love you
who is this
i've always loved you
it was just a welding accident you're all i
think about
it's the only face i see
i miss you i miss us
no i have never seen this man
sir please don't come up here
don't say that
catherine
the things we did sexually
wait what oh
let let him speak
push me the limit
and push you to your burden yourself
he doesn't know what he's talking about
if i don't say this now i'll regret it
the rest of my life
i don't know sure
please please
don't touch me please
[ __ ] what happened to your face
this is katherine johnson right
john's stun
[ __ ] [ __ ]
oh [ __ ]
i'm so sorry about
what i've done here
oh [ __ ] i'm so sorry
see
there's money in the basket
someone just please escort him out
this guy can see
oh maybe he's a good sense of smelly
dollars
out
fuck
maybe i did [ __ ]
oh [ __ ]
so where were we
love is patient
love is blind