Sir, sir, sir, sir, sir.
I'm going to need you to go ahead and
put that seat up for me.
- Why?
- Safety protocol. Sir, please seat in the
upright position.
- This is for safety?
- Absolutely. That's what I just said.
Dude, I'm
It's kind of embarrassing. I can't It's tough to fit.
I can't fit with it. If
with a back, it helps.
Yeah. You're having a tough time fitting
in that seat.
Maybe you should take
better care of your body.
Are you a psycho, dude?
Sir, I'm trying to keep safety protocols
in place. I'm doing this for your own
good.
Whoa. It does feel safer.
- Is there a problem here, sir?
- I'm fine.
Sensing a lot of attitude from you. I
just wonder if I've got to go get the
captain.
What are you going to tell the captain?
We got a guy reclining back there.
- What the [ __ ] he going to do? Turn it
around?
- He might.
- He might emergency land this thing
because I took a nap.
- He might.
Is that what did 911? 19 [ __ ] dudes
reclining.
- Did you just say 9/11?
- Oh boy, we got a guy reclining.
Sir, can I get you something to drink?
Maybe a diet coke.
Does your dad know you do this [ __ ]
How about some peanuts? You could scoop
them out of my hand, you big elephant.
You know, it used to be [ __ ] hot
ladies that had your job
- The [ __ ] wrong with you?
- A little of this. A lot less bad.
- What are you talking about?
- Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
Upright. Keep it upright. I'll see you
on landing.
Uh ladies and gentlemen from the flight
deck, this is your captain speaking.
It appears we've lost the left engine.
Not
to worry. Uh we have two engines.
This
plane is built to be flown with just one
engine and there is no way.
Uh [ __ ] There goes the second engine.
If you have someone you'd like to call,
I would advise that you do so now.
It's mom.
Listen,
I'm going to have to call dad. Okay. Is
dad Is dad there?
I'm not going to make
Just tell him I love him. Okay.
I'll tell Pup you love him, too.
This Rick's auto body.
Yeah. This is Shane with the [ __ ] red
Subaru.
Yeah. You guys [ __ ] suck at your job.
I'm going to come down there and beat
the [ __ ] out of you. You [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ]
All right, I'll be down in 10 minutes.
Get ready. You better start stretching.
I'm going to [ __ ] wear you out, dumbass.
10 minutes. Parking lot, [ __ ]
- Excuse me?
- What? Calling people I [ __ ] hate.
- Don't you have loved ones to call?
- Am I going to call my wife and kids?
Listen to her [ __ ] [ __ ] at me for
the last 5 minutes. [ __ ] that.
I'm about
to die, dude. She's going to [ __ ]
someone else like this year.
That
[ __ ] pisses me off a little bit.
Haley, just a minute.
What are you going to tell her? Fool. Fool.
Nobody wants to hear their [ __ ] mom die.
$100 she's putting on Netflix in one hour.
Actually, [ __ ] it. I'll bet you a billion dollars.
Call someone you hate
and really [ __ ] their [ __ ] up.
Give it a
shot, dude. God just gave us a gift. Try
it.
What are you doing with
Haley? Put your dad on the phone.
Hey, Mom. I'll talk to you later.
Okay, everybody
stay calm and we're going to brace.
How about I relax instead, [ __ ]
Do not put that back. Do not put that back.
Sir, get that seat up.
Hey, Dave.
[ __ ] you.
You know I love you. And I knew from the
moment I married you.
You'd ruin my life, you dumb [ __ ]
Remember 07 when I had to go see you in the hospital
and you thought I was
smiling because I was happy to see you?
I thought you was dead.
Yeah, I'm dying. The plane's crashing.
So, uh, [ __ ] you.
Oh, stop going out with your friends.
You're too late.
Yeah, learn how to [ __ ] end a story.
Jesus Christ.
I remember you. You're not a living
dummy. Goosebumps.
Of course you read Goosebumps, you
[ __ ] dumbass.
Ventriloquist looking ass [ __ ]
I do not look like a ventriloquist
dummy.
I know we're probably dying, but if you
Google that, that was a good reference.
Sir, do not fart in the internet.
I just put my nudes on Instagram.
- Yo, you're crazy.
- And tagged all my kids.
I'm going to die. You know I'm trying to
make someone come.
- I'll come.
- What?
Who said that? Marco.
We're going to make it.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- What the [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ]
You don't know what I do.
Are you [ __ ] joking me?
Crush this [ __ ] blade.
I was just kidding.
We're all going to die.
Yeah
You got me. You got me good there.