time i don't think ever
all right guys i gotta get out of here
uh no i gotta get to bed i gotta
i gotta patrol at 4am
oh my god patrol
yeah you know i cannot believe you're a
cop
yeah that makes two of us
just one more beer no no no
if i if i have one more beer i'll be pissing all night
no no no no
all right
i'm doing it go ahead
guys good night it was nice to see you
all right hey
make sure you lock the bedroom door
tonight okay
i know i know i will
yeah all right guys i'm out of here
you're welcome to stay thank you
one night
sleep
was a different time
don't startle him he's just gonna go to
the fridge
he's gonna get a snack
and he's gonna go back to bed
guys 10
seconds just please i'm begging you
please just be quiet
hey let me get a pickle
who's here
hey
this is a robbery
freeze
robe
all right everybody stop all right
officer everything is
oh my god
everybody get up it's time to
space change
you're going to block yourself and not me
all right everyone just turn around
is he just turning oh [ __ ] man
frank
guys
guy
eat
god
guys this is danny this is frank's partner
hey danny what up danny
he's done he's helped with this so many times
i've seen this
what are you doing
that's not normal he's not the safety's
on
nope safety's not on
frank be careful
frank be careful come on
his dick is out
oh my god
you
he's totally asleep you're better than
my [ __ ] wife
frank
it's a dream he's that's not he's a dream
he's definitely dreaming about you yeah all you
[ __ ] [ __ ] wife about this
[ __ ]
he's kidding with the whole thing
he's seeing you right back to the station
he's dreaming he's free i don't know
what he's doing
he's
joking around are you kidding
frank
no no no no me
oh he's going about he's gone
what
oh babe i gotta go
i'm gonna [ __ ] do it oh
fuck
don't take the shots
comings