Year
Next order of business, we must
determine the age of consent.
At what
age is it okay for a woman to have
relations?
Who would like to speak first?
Tail
the senator from Rhode Island
from Rhode Island.
12.
What do you mean? Ew. I talked to you earlier
and I said 15 and you went like
this. Go lower.
No. I said shh. Dude, people are going
to hear you being a [ __ ] sicko.
Why did I have to go through
Connecticut?
From Connecticut.
25.
What? Why?
25 sucks.
Yeah. I'm not having sex with a 25y old.
We're not [ __ ] old ladies again.
They've begun to decompose.
-  It's like sand down there.
I say
18.
I got an idea.
What about dibs?
- What?
- Dibs.
You see somebody that you'd like
to relate to carnally,
so you call dibs when she is younger
and then when she's
of age, she's yours.
That's a good rule. I think history is
going to look kindly on dibs.
At what age might we open the door for
dibs?
It's like 16.
16. You're no better than that pervert.
Look, me and that pervert have nothing
in common,
I'm not a pervert.
What I would like to
have a discussion with you gentlemen
about is minuation.
Oh, excuse me. Uh, don't write that
down. Don't write that down.
I will write this down, you pervert.
- You are sick.
- I am not sick. I am actually a doctor.
He's a good doctor. He's my doctor.
The other day, I fell on some rocks chasing a frog,
which I caught.
Anyways, cracked
my head open pretty bad
and he threw some leeches on it.
And guess what? Now
I'm gold is good.
Feeling great.
Nice going, dude. You [ __ ] killed
this guy. You turned them into donkey
brains.
I'm ready to go on it.
Look, I think it's fair and settled. You
can call dibs at 16.
- 16's a fair age.
- 16's too young.
You can't tell the difference between a
16-year-old and an 18-year-old.
Yes, I could. Bringing a 16-year-old and
an 18-year-old,
and I'll tell you the
difference right now.
All right, here they are. 16-year-old,
18-year-old. Which one's which?
- I know which one's 16. Come on.
- Point to it. Point to it.
It's rude to point. Jeffrey,
you said it. He was saying it. I could tell.
Now you're [ __ ] Which one?
That one.
It's me.
Shouldn't the woman maybe help decide
the appropriate age?
Ooh, dibs.