seats
now as most of you know
our conference has decided to integrate
this season
boo
settle down as long as i'm head coach at
chapel creek
i promise you this will be
a white football team
that's right
because football is a white male
paul is a white man sport
a lot of people think that oh
since we've been to the moon last year
that
we're you know should be more
enlightened
i don't know what's more
enlightening than just white people
having fun together
that's right when we
went to the moon guess what we found
what was what
and let me tell you
something you can print this in your
little papers
week one we're gonna rain hell down on
these black sun [ __ ]
loses
start
i think we might have taken it too easy on us
that's it we took it too easy on
that that's my fault that's my fault
week two i'm gonna switch up the offense
you thought that was a little run heavy
i agree we're gonna start airing it out on
that's right we're coming from the
sky this week boys death from above
loss
35-0
god damn it what the [ __ ] going on i
don't know what's going on out there
the
school board has informed me that we are
going to be forced to integrate
what
we're going to start the
integration process
with hiring our first black coach
coach johnson's going to be joining our staff
coach johnson's going to be taking over
running the defense for us
wait
a minute i run the defense now
this does mean we are going to have some
black players
i'm going to start the white
players in the first half
get out a big lead a commanding lead on
and we're going to let the black players
come in in the second half
and try to
you know try to play the game a little
bit
miracle
what a comeback down 48 in the first half
but god damn we came back and won
that thing huh
that's coaching
well the next one next week we do a
black players first half
white play the
second half
all right i just thought of something
disastrous
golly those white boys almost blew that
for us didn't they
hey i'm i'm sensing a pattern
pattern
i'm sensing the pattern myself
defense
i told you we'd start winning again
that's a winning streak
y'all gonna have to start making some
room in these chunky cases
these are an
old starting quarterback
i was starting a guy that had polio
i didn't know teenagers could look 45 years old
now we're playing teams
quarterbacks are running now
quarterback can run
uh the correct term is scrambling
scrambling isn't that fun scrambling
they all say cool [ __ ] like this
you guys i'm telling you gotta hang out with
them it's crazy
five
now golly that's good football
that's called
winning rebel faithful
i mean am i
[ __ ] crazy or is this
becoming something you and me
i mean bit of a friendship
i've been going to black
church
shit's fun man you can run around you
can dance
i can scramble
- you can't
scramble to save your life
like a
scramble right now scramble right now
scramble
please load no more whites on the
footballs
all right
now if i was warmed up i could do it better
all right take it easy kid you
got a whole life ahead of you now
life ahead of him he's got look at it
he's got the life expectancy of a pug
state
that's playoffs baby we just made the
playoffs
we went out and made the
there we go
oh [ __ ] you see that man i
can't believe how racist you guys were
earlier
wins
stay tuned state champions number one
some of you doubted some of you are
still racist
disgusting
no i did use slurs that is
true but that was
that was forever ago
it was like eight
weeks ago
i am now unity
coach at this time we'd
like to present you
with the martin
luther king
bravery award for champion diversity in
the community
thank you so much look at
this
you guys put this together
i was hoping
people were noticing how diverse i was
and how interesting i became
i'm number one i did it
i'm the most diverse guy ever
this whole
[ __ ] wouldn't have happened without me
thank you guys for watching
i'm the best and most diverse dude
ever ever
well we accept um growth coach
we do not accept
growth anymore
i was the last one to
grow now we're done
no more growth
you guys are all racist
forever
i'm changed