I'm-a order some
chili cheese fries.
-Oh, yeah? Get me some.
-Anybody else want an order?
A delivery
of chili cheese fries?
They'll be mush by the time
they get here. No way.
-Ah! Shit.
What are you doing, man?
You can't hit it that hard.
You got to use more finesse.
Well, finesse isn't
really my style, Charlie.
I like to dominate the table
into submission.
Dennis, I got to head out.
Tip me out.
- What?
-Give me my tips.
What tips, Dee?
What are you talking about?
Hey, any of you guys
tip Dee today?
-For what?
-Hell no.
- No.
- All right, whatever.
Just give me 40 bucks
from the register.
- What do you need money for?
- I'm going out.
I just need a little cash.
Where you going?
I'm going to a fancy place with
some fancy new friends of mine.
-What friends?
-What is happening?
Why is everyone
asking me questions?
Well, it's 'cause you're
sneaking around trying
to steal money
that you haven't earned
and looking like
Carmen Sandiego.
I mean, what-what
are we supposed to think?
-W-What are you hiding, Dee?
-What?
-Let me see
what's under that coat.
-No.
-I want to see what's under it.
-Show me.
-She's hiding something, Dennis.
You want me to hold her down
and rip it off her?
-Yeah.
-Stop it.
Stop. Stop it. Don't touch me.
Don't touch me. Okay?
I decided that I want
to take off the coat,
'cause it's hot in here.
Bowling? That's the fancy outing
you were, uh, hiding from us?
Dee, why were you hiding
that from us?
Because it's my thing, okay?
It's not your thing,
and I don't want
you guys getting involved.
-As if.
-As if, Dee.
-As if, Dee. As if.
Yeah, okay. All right.
Well, I'm gonna head out.
You guys enjoy sitting around
with your ding-dongs in your
hand doing nothing all night.
-Ding-dongs in our hand--
What is she talking--
What a bitch.
-Yeah.
My ding-dong wasn't even in
my hand. I mean, what do you...
-Mine was.
-Yeah, so was mine.
Yeah, I was scratching mine
when she said that.
I-I had my hands
fully down my pants,
if I'm being honest.
I had to push it to the left.
-They get itchy in there.
-That's a, such a coincidence.
-That is a lucky guess.
-That's a crazy-- yeah.
-It was a lucky guess.
But that's not the point.
Look-look, the point is...
...we have
a lot better things to do
than just go bowling.
BOWLING
Oh, hello, ladies.
You ready to roll?
Why is everybody
sitting on their butts?
We've been waiting here
for 20 minutes.
Okay, well, listen,
things are just gonna be
a little different
if you want me on your team.
I show up when I want.
Well, we don't want you
on our team.
It's just that our fourth
didn't show up
and literally no one else
was free on a Friday night.
-So you want me to be here.
-Not really.
Awesome. Good.
Do you have the $35 team fee?
-Ooh, I do not, but I have...
...something
much more valuable:
my expertise.
So listen to me
and you'll be in business.
Anyone want to snort
Jell-O shots?
-Oh...
- Snail?
You're on the team?
Yeah, I love bowling.
The whole scene is so hot.
I sucked off a rando
in the parking lot.
Ugh, my mouth hurts.
Gross. Waitress,
you're responsible for this?
I'm not responsible for this,
but this is my team, okay?
So you can't just come in here
and take over,
come in late,
not have your money, okay?
I signed us up, I booked
the lane, I made us shirts.
I even found us an appliance
company to sponsor us.
Frige-it.
-"Frige-it Bitches"?
- Yeah.
-God, you guys are stupid.
I'm not wearing this.
-No, it's so funny.
-It's not funny.
-We've been laughing all night.
-That doesn't surprise me.
Now listen up.
We're not here to laugh
or be funny.
-We're here to win.
Which you can do
if you listen to me.
Or perhaps I should let
my balls do the talking.
-Please do.
-Yeah.
-Hot shit, Dee.
-Do I have your attention?
- Well, well, well.
-Oh, God.
-What?
Pretty nice roll, Deandra.
Too bad it'll be your last.
- Can you please just leave and
let me have one thing to myself?
- Nah.
So these, uh, "frigid bitches,"
these are your new
"fancy friends"?
- What is this,
some kind of women's league?
- It's a coed tournament.
- So you'll be
competing against men?
- Vaginas and penises
together again.
I'll tell you what,
why don't we join this league
and have ourselves
a little competition?
Or are y
ou too scared
that you'll lose to us?
He did one, so I thought
we were doing... Okay.
Shit.
Anyone got a straw?
-I didn't know.
-Okay.
-It's fine. All right.
-Hey!
-Hey, guys?
-Let's have it.
Oh, for Christ's sakes.
- Shit.
-Are you kidding me?
-Please tell me
you guys don't own
this bowling alley.
We got out
of the video rental business
just after the bubble burst.
Bowling's always been
in our blood.
Ryan's got the forearms
of an elephant wrangler.
He could have been pro.
I could have been.
If not for my tragic accident.
The story is too horrible
for words, so don't ask me...
-We-we...
-We're not gonna ask.
We don't really care
-about that, yeah.
-You can keep that to yourself.
I'd tell you, but you wouldn't
be able to handle it.
-You clearly want to tell us,
but we're not here for it.
-We don't want to hear it.
Listen, I'm moving past this.
Can we sign up for the league?
-Impossible.
-Why, is it too late to sign up?
- No, you just couldn't afford it.
-How much is it?
-$35.
-We got that.
-Well, we got that, yeah.
That's fine.
Each.
-Uh, do you mind covering us?
-That's still...
W-We're good, we're good, yeah.
- Hey, listen, can we play
the Frigid Bitches first?
- Sure, whatever.
I don't give a shit.
You guys got
chili cheese fries here?
Franklin, we do have chili
and we do have cheese
and we do have fries,
but combining them
is strictly prohibited.
-Why?
-The story is too terrible
to tell.
-Oh, for Christ's sake.
Nobody cares.
-Oh, Christ's sake.
-Sign us up for the league.
-We won't combine the fries.
Make sure we're playing
the Frigid Bitches.
Yeah, give us some shoes.
W-What size shoe...
We'll get the shoes.
Three, two, one and smile.
-Great.
Let me check that picture.
-How's my ass look?
- That looks pretty good.
Oh, it looks huge. Sick.
Can we take another? I wasn't
sufficiently in character.
-In character?
-Yes, character.
I'm researching
a character I'm playing
named Donna Brunswick of
the Brunswick Bowling Dynasty.
Oh, goddamn. You guys are not
taking this seriously.
Okay? Let's cut the BS.
As your leader,
I demand we cut the BS.
Now let's talk order.
I'm thinking Snail, Artemis,
Waitress, best for last.
- Okay,
I'm just gonna remind you
that you're not the leader
and you can't be the leader
'cause you don't even know
everyone's names.
Mm, can you switch mine
to "Donna"?
-No.
- Well, well, well.
Looks like
the Frigid Bitches are going up
against
the Hanging Monster Dong
Lucky Strike
Chili Cheese Fryers.
Is that your name?
That's really stupid.
-It's too many ideas, man.
-I told you it was stupid.
I-I knew they were gonna
make fun of us
and they did make fun of us.
-Yeah, 'cause it's stupid.
You know what?
Uh, but it doesn't matter,
'cause you guys are dead meat.
Hey, did Dee happen
to tell you the history
of her experience with bowling?
-No.
-You should tell them,
you should tell them.
-You tell them, you tell them.
-Tell them, tell them.
-I-I was about to.
-Oh, you were?
-I was about to. Yes.
-He's gonna tell you.
-Are we doing laughs?
-Yeah, uh, no.
I'll just tell it.
-He's gonna tell you.
-Okay, well, when she was a kid,
she was, well,
she was pretty decent.
And I got to say, she worked
really, really hard at it.
So, she eventually became
the captain of the girls' team.
Can you believe that?
Now, I'm no fan
of women's sports.
-Yeah, they're not very popular.
Nobody watches--
Especially women.
Women don't even like
women's sports.
So I wouldn't have it.
And to prove that Dee's
female mind was mentally weak,
I started to go watch her,
and I would say, "gutter ball"
right before she rolled it,
and wouldn't you know it,
every time I said it,
she'd roll a gutter ball.
Since then, if I even so much
as look at Dee when she bowls,
she can't knock down
a single pin.
Not even one.
Well, that's
a bit of an exaggeration.
Anyway, good luck out there.
-Ladies.
-Gentlemen.
-That was so good. That was really good, Dennis.
-That was really good.
All right, I'm looking
at their lineup,
and I'm wondering who should
lead us off against Snail.
I'll start. It'll be good
to show our power and dominance,
you know, -for intimidation.
-Uh, Frank?
You should go against Artemis.
She's next.
Okay? And-and you should
go up after that,
'cause it's The Waitress,
and you're gonna irritate
the shit out of her and
that-that's a good thing, okay?
Oh, shit.
What?
Some kid's having, like,
a birthday party in the arcade
or something.
-Okay. So what?
-It looks fun.
-Charlie, do not be that guy
that everyone's looking for
when it's their turn.
That shit drives me crazy.
Please don't be that guy.
Okay, I'll go last against Dee
because it's gonna be
a lot of fun getting
in her head, so...
It's gonna really mess her up.
It's gonna be awesome.
All right. Hands in, boys.
Say it on three.
- Hanging Monster Ch...
Chili Cheese Fryers!
-Let's do it, bud.
Let's go, man.
Stride, stride, stride, execute.
-Okay, not bad, not bad, Mac.
-Not bad.
Not bad, dude.
Come on, Snail.
What the...
What? What?
Okay,
why are you so happy right now?
- Gail. What the hell was that?
-Ooh, my cooter's
on fire for Mac.
I want to have his baby.
Your cooter is most likely
on fire from a yeast infection.
Go in the bathroom, rinse it out
and be better next time.
Dennis, cover me. Cover me.
Ryan's eyeballing me
and I'm trying to mix these.
-I can't do that right now.
-Go stand over here.
I got Liam over here
eyeballing me.
I mean, I...
I think he is. Little hard
to tell with the eyepatch.
Ah. Anyway, it's your,
it's your roll, man.
Go, go, go. Go, yeah.
-Oh. I'm up?
-Yes, you're up.
-Up.
-Artemis.
-Frank.
How about we, uh,
test out the back seat
of my LeBaron after the roll?
Everybody stop trying
to have sex with each other.
Hey, you know,
another reason why
men and women
can't compete, Dee.
It's too sexually charged.
Donna Brunswick...
Strike.
Nice.
-Artemis, you can bowl?
-No.
My character can.
Me, I can't bowl for shit.
It's not gonna make it.
All right, Frank.
Good job, Frank.
-What? Oh, bullshit.
No, come on, that doesn't count.
Uh, no, the computer counted it,
so it counts.
-Hey, Artemis, let's mush.
What? No. No. You're not gonna
miss your turn, okay?
If you must mush, mush later.
- A quickie.
-Quickie it is.
-What?
- My character is also
a giant whore,
which is what
attracted me to the role
in the first place, so...
-No. No, no.
- Come on,
you can't go now.
Well, mush fast!
Hey, Tyrone,
do not take my spot!
Do not take my spot
at the air hockey table.
-Charlie, shut up.
-You should see the party
they got going there.
-It's great.
They got one of those...
...punching machines
that rates how, like,
how much power
you have in your punch.
-I don't care.
Shut up, I'm trying to focus.
-It's totally crazy.
By the way,
your hair looks great.
Charlie, shut up,
I'm trying to focus.
-Did you, like,
change your hair or something?
-Oh, my God.
Elbow in,
slight bend in the knee,
Come on.
All right. I'm coming!
-Charlie, Charlie,
where you going?
-Where you going?
-Put the cake down...
-I'll be back.
-Dee, you want to go first?
-Don't... Stop it. I know what you're doing.
-I'm not gonna say anything.
I swear to God.
Please, I insist.
I'm not.
-Fine.
-All right. Come on, Dee.
Gutter ball.
You-you dick.
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-That's not funny.
I couldn't resist.
It's... Sorry.
Don't say it again.
Okay? Just leave me alone.
-I'm not. I just... I'm not.
Gutter ball.
You goddamned son of a bitch!
How are you gonna talk to me
about form
after you bowl like that?
-Get off my back,
you frigid bitch.
- I knew inviting you
was a bad idea.
- Well, then, don't invite me.
Then don't invite me next time.
-I didn't invite...
Oh, isn't this fun?
Yeah. Yet another reason why
women can't compete with men.
Besides your
physical limitations,
if given the opportunity
to either work together
as a team
or tear each other apart,
you will always choose
the latter.
Because women are devious
a-and destructive
and will always default
to using their insidious venom
on the most sought-after
victim of all...
...each other.
Okay, Dennis is right.
Just hear me out.
If we want to win,
we can't compete like men,
but what we can do
is use those skills
of mental manipulation
against them.
Do you want to know why?
Why?
Because... they're stupid.
Hey,
Mac, how come
you throw the ball so straight?
I throw the ball straight
because, as a man,
dominance is my sporting style.
Uh, I heard it's 'cause
you have no finesse.
You don't know
how to spin the ball.
-What?
I have finesse.
I could spin the ball.
-You want to see me?
-Yeah.
-Hey, uh, Mac? Mac?
Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
Do not try and spin the ball.
She said that I can't spin,
and I can spin.
-You-- Do not try it.
-But Dennis, she said
I have no finesse,
and you know
that I have finesse.
-Don't do it.
Just play your game.
-Can I just spin one?
-I don't care...
-Let me spin one.
You don't need to spin it.
You just play your game
and we're gonna win.
Okay? Do not spin it.
Do not do it.
Okay, fine.
I won't, I won't spin it.
I won't.
Stride, stride, stride, spin!
Oh, goddamn it!
Gutter ball.
- I'm gonna try it again.
-I'm coming,
I'm coming.
Wait, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hey, Tyrone, double or nothing!
'Cause there's no way
you're beating me
two out of three, dude!
-Hey, Charlie? Excuse me.
Can I, can I ask your advice
on something?
-Yeah.
-Well, you're just such
a good natural bowler...
...and I'm having a hard time,
so I was wondering,
where are you putting your elbow
when you're rolling?
-My elbow?
- Yeah, before you throw the ball,
where is your elbow going?
You-you want me to show you
where my elbow goes?
-Yeah.
-My-my elbow's like...
-Uh-huh.
That looks good.
Gutter ball.
Holy shit. It's working.
-There we go.
-Okay.
Okay. It's okay.
Damn it!
-Just walk.
-What are you doing?
Stride, stride, stride, spin!
Come on!
-Gutter ball.
-S-Stop it.
Gutter ball.
You want one?
-What happened?
What the hell happened?
In the third act of my play,
Donna rolls a gutter ball
in the big match
against her rival high school.
-Are you serious?
-Oh, my God.
Can you knock it off
with the play, please?
Ah, well, well,
you done good, ladies.
Your little mind games,
they got you pretty far,
but unfortunately...
...still 11 points shy
in the final frame.
Now, technically,
I could pick up this spare
and push the lead
even further,
and I...
think we all know Dee's about
to roll two gutter balls.
So I'll tell you what.
Dee, if you would like,
uh, you could just quit now
and you could all admit
that you're inferior
in every single way,
and we could just call it
a night.
Okay, you know what, dick?
I don't like your sister.
She's a terrible person.
-She's a bitch and she's ugly
and I didn't want her
on the team.
- And she's gross.
- Sure, and she's gross.
But you know what?
You're even worse.
And I am not gonna sit here
and let you just shit on her
all night long.
You think
you're physically superior?
-Yeah.
-Then I challenge you
to a test of strength.
- This isn't fair.
- Oh. Is it not fair?
Okay, well, if you're scared,
we don't have to do it.
Okay, well, listen,
if you insist, that's fine.
-I do. Okay.
-Let's do it. Yeah.
Ladies first.
-All right, let's do it.
-Oh, thank you.
Go, Waitress, go.
Give it all you got.
- Shit. Didn't know you could kick it.
-Oh, yeah, you could kick it.
-And that's fine. Okay.
-Yeah, yeah, okay. Do it.
Show them what you got, Dennis.
Come on.
Let's go, buddy.
I summon the very fact
that I am a man!
I have defeated you.
And of course I have.
I've been blessed
with the genetic gifts to do so.
I've broken
every single bone in my hand.
I cannot bowl.
-What?
-Really?
-L-Listen to me.
There's nothing solid
left in there.
It's just bloody soup
and bone broth.
All right?
Now, I need to scream.
And I need you to find me
somewhere to scream
so I don't have to do it here.
No, wait a minute.
I'm going to scream here,
and now,
'cause I can't hold it in,
so here we go.
- Ryan, I need you to bowl for me.
- I'll never bowl again.
-Come on, man.
-Why not? What's the big deal?
The story's
too horrible to tell.
-For fuck's sake,
just spit it out.
- Yeah, you clearly want
to tell it, man.
Fine.
But brace yourself.
There I was,
practicing for
the state semifinals.
I was on my way
to a perfect game.
I was enjoying
some chili cheese fries.
They were delicious,
and I offered some to Ryan.
I accepted, but not realizing
my other hand was
in the ball return lane.
I never should have allowed
myself such indulgences,
because little did I know,
my ball was returning.
It pinched it really bad.
I had a nasty bruise for a week.
-That's it?
-That's why you won't bowl?
-You pinched your finger?
-You pinched your finger
-and you won't bowl?
-Big deal, man.
I'll bowl for you... Dennis.
-Okay, fine.
-Okay.
-Wait, what's happening?
What-what are you saying? What?
-Nothing.
-What?
-N-Nothing.
-What's going on?
Liam's gonna bowl for me
because I hurt my hand
a little bit.
Ow, I just,
I just twisted my ankle.
-No.
-Yeah, and I need Ryan,
I need Ryan to bowl for me.
-No way. No way.
-My ankle is hurt,
and I need Ryan to bowl for me.
-That...
-That is bullshit.
This is incredibly weird.
Ryan!
Brother!
Brother, what have I done?
Well, well, well, Dee,
it looks like
you're gonna have
to roll after all.
Fine. No problem.
Gonna make my team proud.
Oh, well, maybe you will.
Or maybe...
you'll roll a gutter ball.
One pin. That's all.
You can do this.
-Gutter ball.
-No. No.
Just don't think "gutter ball,"
that's all.
Oh, hi, Dee.
I'm in here, too.
Gutter ball.
-Gutter ball. Gutter ball.
You goddamned son of a--
bitch!
-No, no, no...
-No, no...
No, no, no, no...
I did it! In your faces.
Ha... Uh... What's going on?
Where'd everybody go?
-Frank's having a threesome
in the bathroom
with Gail and Artemis,
and, um, yeah, I think the guys
went to the Sixers game.
What?
Oh, goddamn it.
Well, why aren't you
celebrating?
yeah, honestly?
I don't give a shit
about women's sports.
translate