MAC:
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Guys, guys, guys,
guys, guys, guys.
"Congratulations,
Paddy's Pub.
"We are pleased to report that
we are interested
in featuring
"your bar on an upcoming
episode of our show.
"We will be sending a producer
to do a walk-through soon.
"Warmly, your friends at...
Bar Rescue!"
Yes!
This is like our dreams
come true, right?
What?
To be on a reality TV show?
Yeah. Wh--
How did this happen?
I've been writing them a letter
every week
since the show first started.
-Well, how long's it been?
-Too long.
DEE: I very much do
want to be famous,
but I don't know if I want to be
on a reality show
where they try and make us
look like jerks.
-CHARLIE: Right.
Oh, right, yeah.
'Cause, like, what
if they, like, edit it
to, like, make me
look stupid or something?
Yeah. This is a definite pass
for me. I'm out.
This could be huge for us.
What are you guys talking about?
I'm a little disappointed
that you didn't tell me earlier
because I would have been
working out
for weeks in preparation.
I mean, for God's sakes, man.
What if, what if
my shirt falls off?
Yeah, yeah. I'm a little off
my regimen, too.
Like, I haven't even been doing any of my... workouts.
-Ever. He never has.
You guys are missing
the bigger picture here.
I mean, wh-what are the odds
that they would pick our bar?
This is a million-to-one shot,
and I've got a really good
feeling about this, guys.
Things are about to change
here at Paddy's Pub
because our luck
just turned around.
CURSED
The second I clean it up,
you're making more crumbs.
-There should be more crumbs.
We should put crumbs
all over the goddamn bar.
Sorry, but, Charlie, why am I
seeing so many silverfish?
I-I don't know
where they're coming from, man.
I cannot get rid of them.
You should not get rid of them.
Don't you guys understand
what Bar Rescue is?
These are the exact
kind of things
that John Taffer's gonna come in
and hand our asses to us about.
-DENNIS: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I don't-- I don't want
to have my ass handed to me.
I mean,
how the bar comes across is
-a reflection of
how I come across. Okay?
And I, for one,
don't want to be known
as a silverfish man. Okay?
I want to look good
for the people watching
in their...
Uh... What's the-the thing?
The-the boxes
that-that people live in?
- You talking about their homes?
- Y-- uh, yes, yeah. Their homes.
-Jesus. I couldn't think of
that word. That's so weird.
Guys, we have a problem.
But whatever you do,
don't laugh.
-How are we not supposed
to laugh at that?
-I wouldn't laugh at that.
This is not funny, all right?
It's not a joke.
I don't know
what's going on with my face,
but it's broken or something.
-MAC: It's very funny.
-That's really funny.
-Ah!
-My egg's all bloody.
- Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
This is bad, dude.
This is the kind of stuff
that starts happening
when someone's
put a curse on you.
-Curse? What are you
talking about?
-What?
Let's just stop and think
for a second, okay?
Like, Dee,
did you have any run-ins
with anyone who might have
put a curse on you?
I mean, I had
a tiny little issue
with a neighbor last night.
-Yes!
-Spewing my hate
all over your teenage asses.
What?
Banging the goddamn door down.
Yeah.
What? Why are you trying
to break my door down
at 3:00 in the morning?
I baked you some brownies.
Why you baking me shit?
Trying to poison me?
No.
I just wanted to kindly ask if
you could keep the noise down.
Oh. Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize.
-That was really sweet of you...
-...to bake these for me.
Hey,
I have something for you also.
-Oh, it's so nice. What is it?
Well, it's a trophy. See?
It says "Cunt of the Year."
That's you.
You are a nasty woman,
and bad things are going
to happen to you one day.
I guarantee it.
Drop dead.
Well, there you go. It sounded
like that lady cursed you.
I don't know. I call old ladies
cunts all the time. We all do.
-Right.
-That's true.
-No, she brings up a good point.
-We do. We do.
-I called an old lady
a cunt this morning.
-See?
-Did you? Yeah.
-I sure did. I sure did.
-No, I might've done it,
too, actually.
-Honestly, for me this raises
an even bigger concern.
- Okay. What's that?
Dee had no right
to give that trophy away.
-I mean, we worked very,
very hard on that.
We did. It's not easy to make.
-Plus, she earned it, right?
-And you earned it.
And you're just gonna
give it away? I mean...
Either way,
this is all bullshit anyway,
because we're not having bad
luck, we're having good luck.
- What about my egg?
- You know what that
might've been?
Y-You might've gotten cursed
when you killed that seabird.
-What seabird?
-Oh, I didn't tell you guys
about this?
Okay. So, the other day, uh, Frank's
making a banana daiquiri.
Seagull flies
right into the bar.
-Cheers.
-Yeah. Here you go.
It's tasty.
-Oh, shit.
A seagull.
Oh, a little birdie.
Oh, what a sweet little birdie.
You want some food?
Want some?
-(seagull squawking)
-Whoa! Shit, Frank!
-Die!
-Ah, Frank. Jesus.
Come here, you rat, die!
And die, you fucking seagull.
Bitch. Fucking cunt.
Well, it's bad luck if a seabird
flies into a building.
No, dude. It's bad luck
to kill a seabird.
Every sailor knows that.
I don't sail.
Charlie,
will you stop trying to turn
our good fortune
into bad fortune?
All this doom and gloom.
Nobody is cursed.
Oh, really, Mac?
Because I straight-up heard
Cricket curse you yesterday.
All right.
It's time to make good
on your end of the bargain, Mac.
What are you talking about?
I still need proof.
Oh, come on, man.
Don't start with that.
-Cricket, what are you doing
in here, man?
That's what I was just saying.
Cricket, what are you doing
in here?
What? What-what-- No,
we're-we're talking business.
Business? I'm not doing
business with you, street trash.
What is your deal, man?
What-what...
One second you need me,
the next I'm a pile of garbage?
Is that what this is?
-Cricket, beat it, man...
- You better beat it, or I'm
gonna beat you with my shoe.
-Get out of the bar, dude.
- You know what? Screw you guys.
Oh. Hey, Mac.
A curse on you.
Vos omnes maledicti mille annis.
I mean, he-he literally
cursed you, man.
Now, guys, come on.
We got to take this seriously.
Like, let's look at this.
Like, uh, Frank.
Let-Let's do our homework
on sailors' curses.
Dee, Mac,
go make your apologies.
I will do nothing of the sort.
In fact, I am done
listening to this.
It's irritating, anti-God,
and most importantly
will not
make for good Bar Rescue banter.
I am leaving.
Come on, man!
Charlie, how do you know
all this curse...
-Stuff?
-Yeah.
That-- I mean, look,
maybe it's real, maybe it's not.
But, like, look at it this way.
Like, i-if a black cat
crosses your path,
do you spit
over your left shoulder?
-Uh-uh.
-Why would I do that?
-No.
-You guys don't do that one?
- I don't know what that is.
Well, I mean, like,
when you're hopeful
for something, though,
do you knock on wood?
-Oh, that one. No. No.
-I've heard of that one,
but I don't do it.
Well, do you make a wish
when you blow out
a damn candle? I mean...
-Of course we do.
-Yes.
-Ah, yes, that one I do.
-Candles, yeah, I like that.
Well, 'cause I want my wishes
to come true.
Okay. And why do you do it?
You do it just in case.
Just in case it's real, right?
And "just in case" is
as good a reason
to believe in anything as any.
I got to call a doctor
or something.
Oh, no, you definitely should.
I'm pretty sure you have
Bell's palsy.
I, uh, I looked it up.
But first you got to apologize
to your neighbor.
Yeah. Just in case? Hmm?
Just in ca-- No, no.
I don't believe in
that bullshit. No.
She's got the trophy.
I want to get the trophy back.
You had no right
to give that to her.
I swear to God,
if she doesn't have that thing,
I'm gonna paralyze
the other side of your face.
'Cause I want it.
Come on, that's-that's crazy.
You-you have to be nominated
for that.
Hello, um, you don't know me,
but I'm the brother
of this horrible woman,
and she just wanted to come by
and tell you
that she's very...
Uh, she-she feels--
She, uh...
Oh, what's the word?
To make better
the feelings?
-"Sorry"?
-Sorry. Yes. Goddamn.
Um... I don't know
what that--
Um, and also, she, um...
She gave you something,
uh, a trophy,
and-and it was not hers to give.
Do-do you perhaps
still have that?
-Yeah, I have it. I'll get it.
-Yeah? Okay, great.
You know what?
I got to look up some clinics,
'cause I really need a doctor
to fix my face
before we're on TV.
-Uh-oh.
Whoa. Did-did you see that?
-What?
See what?
Uh, a black cat just ran
out of her apartment.
-It just...
-I didn't see a cat.
You kidding me?
It ran right past us.
- Well, that's not good. A black cat?
-Yeah.
Well, shit. What'd Charlie say
we were supposed to do
if we saw it?
That's a bad omen.
Uh-oh. I got you, didn't I?
Sorry about that.
-Yes, you did.
Boy, that's a shame.
Thank you for this, though.
Um, listen, um...
Do you have a cat?
'Cause I think I just saw one
run out of your apartment.
-A cat?
-Yeah, yeah. A little black cat?
I had a little black cat.
Her name was Maureen.
But she's been dead for years.
Huh. That's crazy.
I was, I was murdered
to a woman named Maureen.
No, I meant married.
I'm sorry.
I was married
to a woman named Maureen.
I-I...
That's so weird.
I swear I saw a cat.
You know what?
This place is full of cats.
Can we get out of here,
please?
-Yeah, go. Go.
And please keep
the noise down at night.
Yeah. Okay, you got it, cunt.
- Are you sure about this,
Cricket?
- Yeah, I'm sure about it, man.
I've been greasing the doormen
of this building for years.
Chase Utley's back in town.
He's coming out of his apartment
any second now.
Is it good intel? 'Cause I only
got one good shot at this.
Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
What do I know?
I'm just a street rat, right?
I'm just trash.
That's what you said.
-Okay, Cricks, I'll tell you...
-You've got nothing for me.
- I knew you were gonna be
a little bit of
a bitch about this,
so I did something nice.
-I got
you a sixer.
-You got that for me?
- Yeah, I got a gift for you,
buddy.
- There's only four in here.
- I drank two of 'em, of course.
Okay. All right. Well,
thank you.
- Oh, I'm gonna buy a six-pack
and not drink two?
- Well, yeah. That's kind of
the kind thing to...
But I-- Look, um,
thank you for the four.
If I'm being honest,
I drank four.
Two of those are piss.
Because I was stuck in the van,
and you were out...
You know what,
I don't even care, frankly.
I'm just glad
to have a beverage.
-Dominus espritu sanctum, okay?
You're off.
-What was that?
- I was, uh, I was lifting
the curse that I put on you.
Oh. Yeah, no,
I don't believe in curses.
Yeah, that's anti-God,
and God is the reason
that all things happen.
And speaking of
things that happened,
I got to show you something,
Cricks,
but you got to keep it a secret.
Something wrong with your dick?
-What?
-Okay, I was waiting for this.
If it's your dick, though,
I-I got to charge you for it.
I'm gonna tell you right now.
No. It's not my dick, Cricket.
Well, if-if you're gonna
whip it out, uh,
we're on the clock.
All right?
-I'm not whipping anything out!
-There's a tiered system...
Look. This.
- What? What is that?
- It's a monkey paw,
and I think it's good luck,
like a rabbit's foot
or something like that,
'cause ever since I found it,
nothing but good things
have happened.
Uh, sorry, I thought
God was the reason
that anything good happens,
et cetera.
Well, no. God decides
who the good things happen to
and then who he smites.
You're not following.
I-I can't follow it.
It makes literally no sense.
I don't even know why I even...
-CRICKET: Let's get this open.
I'm feeling curious.
-Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, that's-- there he is,
there he is. Okay.
Let's go.
-Mr. Utley?
Mr. Utley?
Mr. Utley, a moment
of your time, sir.
Mr. Utley?
Mr. Utley, hello?
Hello. Oh, hi. Hi, Mr. Utley.
Hey, uh, would you
like an autograph?
Oh, no. That's a cl--
a classic, Mr. Utley.
-I-It's me, Mac.
-I don't know a Mac.
I wrote you a letter every week
for the last ten years.
Did you not receive my letters?
There was a video.
A video in response. Wait.
"Dear Mac, I feel like
I can call you Mac
"because you called me Chase.
"Thank you for the compliment
on my hair.
"It's my fourth favorite thing
after baseball,
"running fast and my dad.
"I'm sorry your dad
doesn't like you.
"Maybe you could
become a better son.
"Meeting you and having
a game of catch
sounds like a lot of fun,
but like I said,
"I'm really busy playing a lot
of baseball for the Phillies.
"I hope you have a good life.
"Fans like you make my life
a 'grand slam.'
Your good friend, Chase."
-Wait, you're that Mac?
-Yes.
I thought Mac was a little kid.
Yes, there's a child. A child...
A child born unto me.
Little Mac.
-What?
-He's Little Mac, I'm Big Mac,
and you shall have
a catch with him.
Your hair, it's throwing me.
It's making me very nervous.
On the Dodgers, yes,
you were the Silver Fox.
Philadelphia,
you were just the Fox.
- I don't know, man.
I'm pretty busy.
- Yes, we're all, we're all busy,
but the boy is sick.
He's very sick.
He's, he's dying.
He's got leukemia and you shall
have a catch with him.
-Where's my car?
-I'll tweet that you didn't.
I'm sorry. I threatened you.
Now I'm upset and so are you.
A catch, we shall have?
Later today.
Okay. Maybe, but for, like,
five minutes tops.
-Yes. Yes, yes.
-I'm really busy.
-CHARLIE: Mom?
Hey, can we pick your brain
about something?
Oh, Charlie, I didn't think
you could make it.
Come on in.
-Yeah, shit, I forgot
it's Uncle Jack's birthday.
Come on in, Charlie.
You can sit next to me.
Nah, I'm good. Uh, we'll
come back later or something.
No, no, no, no, Charlie.
I want a piece of cake.
-Come on.
-Oh, do you? Oh, shit.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Jack ♪
-♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
-Can we switch seats?
-Okay, make a wish.
Oh, right, right, right.
Okay, you and I hold hands.
-Nope.
-Okay, ready?
-Oh!
-Good. All right.
Very good, very good.
Hey, you want to know
my wish, Charlie?
-Sure don't, pal.
-Ooh, don't tell him your wish,
it won't come true.
-Yeah, there you go.
Exactly.
-I made a wish, too.
How about you and me go on
upstairs with some cake, Bon?
Hey, Frank, you don't
get a wish, okay?
That's not how
birthday candles work.
-Says who?
-Uh, look, that's not
why we're here!
Mom, Frank killed a seagull.
Hey, that's not good, Frank.
Yeah, we know it's not good,
Uncle Jack. Okay?
That's why-- that's why
we came here, all right?
Mom, now is that the kind
of thing that could put, like,
a curse on Frank?
-Yes.
They say that a sailor's spirit
lives on in the gulls,
and if you kill a gull,
the sailor
can haunt you
for the rest of its life.
-No shit?
-Yeah, well, is there
anything we can do,
-or, like...
-Well, you could slit
Frank's throat
with a horn of a goat
and drink a bowl of his blood.
What?
Well, uh, okay, yeah,
maybe not, maybe not that.
Is, like, there
anything else, or...
Ooh!
He could behead the gull
and wear its skull
around his neck
for the rest of his life.
Mom, that's not gonna work,
'cause we don't have
-the gull anymore.
-Yeah, we do.
It's at the bar.
-What? It is?
-Mm, yeah.
I kicked it under
one of the booths
so I didn't have to clean it up.
Okay, so you're telling me
that you want to wear
a seagull skull around your neck
for the rest of your life?
I don't know. Could be cool.
No, we're not doing that.
That's crazy.
Mom, anything else?
You could give the seagull
a proper burial.
What? Well, yeah,
that one, Mom. That one.
Why didn't you lead off with
that one in the first place?
Well, sometimes
you're at sea, Charlie,
and you wouldn't
have that option.
Do I look like I'm at sea, Mom?
-I don't know.
-You don't know if I'm at sea?
-You don't, uh--
Uncle Jack, stop.
Stop putting your hand on me.
Looking for this.
What is it?
Maureen Ponderosa.
-Well, why do you have that?
-Well, I wanted to keep it
as a-a-a...
Oh, a trophy? From the murder.
No, not a-- What?
No, not a trophy.
I-- As-- I wanted...
Like a souvenir,
f-from your victim.
Not a souvenir, no.
It's-it's, a...
It's a-- I wanted to keep it
as a w-way to spite her.
Which one? Which one's it under?
-Uh, by the jukebox. Over here.
-Oh-- ah!
-Over here.
-I see it, yeah.
Let me get a trash bag.
-What the hell is that?
-That's the gull Frank killed.
-All right.
-What's that?
Oh, that's his dead wife.
-Yeah.
-Looks like a trophy.
No, it's not a-a trophy, okay?
The crazy bitch had it
in her will that she wanted
to be buried in a pet cemetery,
and I refused.
Wait a second.
You refused your wife's
dying wishes
to be buried in a pet cemetery?
Why would you do that?
Because she's not a cat.
Yeah, but, dude, like,
that's-that's the exact
kind of thing that could
lead to a curse.
That... I know.
-I-- Yes. Okay, I get that now.
-This is bullshit, Cricket.
-I don't know what
you're so upset about.
Y-You said get a kid.
I mean, his name on the street
is literally "Kid."
-That's what he goes by.
-He is a grown man.
I can be whatever
you want me to be, champ.
-I'll make your dreams
come true.
-Oh, he can.
-Would you make it--
Do a, do a turn. Do a spin.
-Oh.
There you go. Make it sexy.
Let's go.
-Yeah.
Uh, move the bangs,
put the bangs.
Show them your face,
show them your face.
-Yeah. Huh?
-Hey.
-Get him out of here.
-All right, yeah. You're gone.
-Uh, here. Go.
-Oh, yeah...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Drugs? Mm.
-No eyes.
Okay.
It's all about respect.
Mac, what the hell is this?
Um, I believe that Cricket
is now a pimp,
and that was his boy slut.
Uh, t-that's oversimplifying it.
But, uh, that's-that's it
in a nutshell.
No, we got that.
He got, yeah, he means like...
Yes. I-I mean,
what are you doing with Cricket?
No, he's got a monkey paw.
Ugh, come on, Cricket.
That's a secret.
Oh, I can't keep secret--
Honestly, I'm so high,
I'm thinking about it,
and I'm gonna go
with him in the bathroom
and finish up the-- Yeah.
CHARLIE:
Mac, what's going on
with the monkey paw?
What is this?
You know how I've been
chasing Chase Utley
for years to have a catch?
Well, I finally got to him
and we were supposed
to have a catch tomorrow
with my "dying son."
Cricket was gonna
help me find one,
-but he brought back a junkie.
-Wait, wait, wait.
You actually met Chase Utley?
How'd you do that?
Well, ever since I found
this monkey's paw,
my luck has totally
turned around.
Well, actually,
it wasn't just a paw.
It was a whole monkey behind
the kegs, and he was dead.
He had this cash in his hand,
and when I went
to grab the cash, the whole hand
just, like, kind of popped out,
and I've been carrying it around
ever since.
Monkey in the bar,
right? Totally random.
Wha-- that-that's not
random at all.
That's probably the monkey
that worked here,
-robbed us and fucked our faces.
-FRANK: He got stuck
behind the keg.
-It's behind the kegs?
-MAC: Well, actually,
I found him by the office,
but I kicked him behind the kegs
because I didn't feel
like cleaning him up.
-Oh!
-Goddamn it!
-Well, he is decomposing
and there's also
a shit-ton of mold back there.
-Shit, now I smell it.
-I don't know
how I missed that.
CHARLIE:
Okay, okay.
I got a new fix, all right?
I got a new fix for everything.
We're gonna take, uh, your wife,
the gull
and what's left of the monkey,
and we're gonna bury them all
in a pet cemetery.
And Mac, you are gonna have
a catch with Chase Utley,
but not with your dying son.
-Why not?
-'Cause he's already dead.
CHASE:
I'm confused.
This is your son?
Oh, yes, Mr. Utley.
I didn't have the heart
to tell you earlier.
He was only ten years old
when he died. He's dead now.
Why is he buried
at a pet cemetery?
Dogs. He loved dogs.
Okay, man. What is this?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, I...
Look, I know you're
gonna think that this is crazy,
but I-I found this monkey paw,
and it's brought me
really good luck.
And I know that you don't think
superstitions are real,
and that this is all
ridiculous...
Not real?
Of course they're real.
-What, really?
-Yeah.
How do you think baseball
players get out of their slumps?
With superstitions.
'Cause what they believe
influences their actions.
But actions do have
consequences.
Like lying, Mac.
Why don't you hand over
that monkey paw?
You're right.
You're right, actions
do have consequences, and I...
I'm really sorry, man,
I think...
Hall of Fame, baby, here I come!
What the hell
was that all about?
I think Chase Utley
just stole my monkey paw.
Oh. Well, then, maybe
the curse has been lifted.
-Oh. Right, yeah.
-Uh, hey, guys? Um...
-Hmm?
-Check this out.
Okay, so, apparently, um...
temporary facial paralysis
and brain fog
are all symptoms of exposure
to high levels of mold.
-Huh?
-Oh...
You know what? That might
also explain the silverfish.
Yeah, no, it does.
Actually, it does.
They eat mold.
-Huh?
-And what about my egg?
Well, is it possible, Frank,
that that egg was a seagull egg?
-Oh...
-That might've been,
because, you know what,
-we found some eggs...
-And we...
-And you might've mixed them up.
-I might've swapped--
-mixed them up.
-Yeah, 'cause we had store eggs
-and we had found eggs.
-You did a flip-flop.
-Yeah, there you go.
So, the-- so, there's no curse.
Oh, no. Hold on a second.
"Dear Mr. McDonald,
we regret to inform you
that we came by your bar
and there was nobody there."
-Huh?
-"After several failed attempts
"to reach you, we have decided
to rescind our offer.
We wish you the best of luck.
Your friends at Bar Rescue."
Damn it.
If I had that monkey paw,
none of this would've happened.
Yeah, so that means
we are still cursed.
-Oh, no.
-Shit.
-It doesn't!
We're not-- There is no curse.
Okay? Mac, no,
you were never lucky.
Okay? You just bombarded them
both with mail.
And you stalked Chase Utley
for years.
We're not unlucky, okay?
We're just the type of...
We're just the type of people
to bury various animals
and-and wives in a pet cemetery
when we know
we should be at work.
-Oh, yeah.
-Let's go back to the bar.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, what about me?
What about my luck?
I don't know, Cricks, I guess...
there's no real explanation
as to why bad things
would happen to you.
-Yeah.
-Maybe it's just one
of those things, Cricket.
-That's life.
That's life, sometimes.
-Yeah, man.
-It is what it is.
-You got a dark cloud
-following you around.
-CHARLIE: It is what it is.
-FRANK: That's all
there is to it.
-MAC: It is what it is.
-CHARLIE: It is what it is.
-DENNIS: Nice day.