Everything looks good,
Mr. Reynolds.
Your blood work is all normal.
Excellent. As expected, right?
Does look like
your blood pressure's
a little high, however. Um--
-Wait.
I have high blood pressure?
-Well, yes, but
that's consistent
with your last visit.
We might want
to put you on a low dose
of blood pressure medication.
-Oh...
no.
Come on, Doc.
Pills are for old men.
Well, we all get
to a certain age where we need--
Do we? I don't.
So, no. I mean, you know,
let-let's not...
Listen, I-I can see
where you're headed with this.
Let's-let's not go there, okay?
If I wanted my blood pressure
to be low, I would simply
command my body to make it low.
That's really not how chronic
high blood pressure works.
Okay, well, it is how it works
with Dennis Reynolds, okay?
And if I'm chronically
having high blood pressure,
it's because
I'm chronically suffering fools
who won't listen to me
when I say that I can do things.
Uh, you know what, Doc?
It's fi...
I'm gonna take control
of this, okay?
Don't you worry about a thing
'cause Dennis Reynolds
is gonna
figure this all out on his own.
MENTAL
There we go.
Blood pressure.
Pulse. Resting heart rate,
syncs right to the phone.
And it records everything.
This is perfect.
Now I'll have proof I can smash
in that stupid doctor's face.
-Yeah.
- Oh, hey, Dennis.
- Uh, a-are we above
or below sea level?
-What?
- Tell him about
the family-style cooking.
Yeah, so we're doing
some family-style cooking now,
and we got this,
like, industrial-grade
pressure cooker.
Pretty badass, man,
but, you know,
we got to make sure
we're above sea level
just to be safe.
Well, we can't be
below sea level.
Otherwise, we'd be underwater.
But if it's under sea level,
it may explode.
-That's our big worry.
That this sucker's
gonna explode.
You can't take
a pressure cooker under the sea.
- It's not gonna explode.
- Yeah, that's not
how pressure cookers works.
You're telling me
that you can't bring
a pressure cooker
onto a submarine?
How do they feed
the entire U.S. Navy?
-They don't pressure-cook
the shit, Mac.
-Navy argument.
-Stop! Stop! All of you, okay?
I'm calling mental health day.
Mental health day?
What kind
of cuckoo shit is that?
It's a new thing.
It's like a sick day
but for your brain,
and if somebody calls it,
you have to give it to 'em,
you can't ask any questions.
Are you calling that?
Are you taking that for real?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm calling
mental health day, okay?
And I'm gonna drive out
to the beach...
...and spend the entire day
just staring at the ocean.
Isn't your car in the shop?
I'm sorry.
That's, uh, not a question
about mental health.
That's a question of logistics.
Ah, damn it. No, you're right.
Hey, Dennis,
I'll come drive you.
I could use a beach day.
Oh, shit. You know what?
This could be a good way
to find out whether or not
we're, uh, underwater.
We can take
the cooker there, yeah.
No. No.
Goddamn it!
Do you hear that beeping?
That means stop.
No!
This is my mental health day,
and none of you
are a part of it.
Goddamn it!
Hi.
Hi. How can I help you today?
Uh, yeah, I have a reservation
under the name Reynolds.
-Okay, let me check that out
for you.
-All right.
Wow. That's a lot of typing
you're having to do there.
You writing a novel?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
We have no more vehicles
available in that class.
No, no, no,
I made a reservation.
Sometimes
our system double-books,
so that's our mistake,
and we are happy
to offer you
a complimentary upgrade.
-Okay.
This is the Tsuma EVS,
a fully-electric car
with touch screen controls,
automated steering
made right here in America.
Oh, these are awesome.
I've seen these.
These are really cool.
Okay, yeah, no. I-I... I accept,
and I'll take those keys.
-There are no keys.
-Aha.
-There's an app.
-Oh, right.
-An app.
-Mm-hmm.
Boy, I got tell you, I...
I, uh, I don't love that.
I, uh, have a lot of apps
on my phone already,
and, uh,
keys are sort of a system
that have existed for millennia.
I don't know why we're trying
to fix that, but, uh,
yeah, no, now we got apps.
We got... we got apps
for everything, right?
Even for things
we already had things for.
I guess, uh, since
my blood pressure's going up,
really spiking here,
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna go with it.
We're gonna download the app.
Right? What's one more app?
The phone is the key now.
Simple.
This is nice.
Smooth ride, it's quiet.
Try this
automated steering thing.
Hey.
Hey!
That is awesome.
Time to kick
this mental health day off
with some feel-good plant tonic.
My good friend, Mr. Kratom.
Uh, this stuff's gnarly
as hell, though.
I need some...
some kind of a mixer.
Uh, Tsuma, direct me
to the nearest tea shop.
Rerouting to Teaspoon.
Holy shit.
Tsuma, play... Roxette.
-Now playing Roxette,
That is so cool.
I'll just sit here
and enjoy the ride, I guess.
This car's nailing it.
-Hi.
Uh, one herbal tea, please.
-Which flavor?
- Flavor.
Uh, I don't know. Jasmine?
- Uh, sorry, I meant for the boba.
- The little spheres
of, uh, tapioca and sugar?
The tea comes with boba.
Well, it doesn't
because I see the tea
right there,
and I see the boba over there,
so why don't we just
not combine 'em, yeah?
-You know, so, I'll take the tea
without the covert diabetes
delivery mechanism, please.
-The system won't
let me do that.
Okay. Yeah. No, fine.
One boba, please.
We'll call it
a mental health day treat.
Self-care, right?
Isn't that what people call it
whenever they need an excuse to
do whatever the fuck they want?
-I don't know.
-Yeah, I know.
Of course you don't.
One chewy sugar tea, please.
All right.
Uh, you can scan the code.
- Uh, why?
- Because the code takes you
to the app.
That's two apps today, yeah.
Got apps for everything,
you know?
Even though I'm already
talking to the person
that, uh, could just
take my order right here,
but I got to download an app,
right?
How about this?
I have cash, you have tea.
Why don't
we just streamline things?
We don't take cash, though.
Yeah. How about cards?
Take cards?
-Uh, yes.
-Oh, great.
But there is
a ten-dollar minimum.
There's no minimum
on the app, though.
Sorry. It's, uh...
It's not your fault.
You know, you didn't
create the system.
The system is just...
It is what it is,
and, yeah, we're
both victims here, so...
- What?
- Uh, nothing.
Two boba teas, please.
-Oh, shit.
That is rough.
It's so sweet.
Good, though. It's good.
-What do you mean,
"Key not found"?
Key not found?
Th-There is no key.
The key is my...
...phone.
Where's my phone?
Goddamn it, where's my phone?
Ah, shit. Ugh! Yes. What?
-Hey, Dennis. Hey, man.
Hey, uh, real quick.
You know that French dip
of yours in the fridge.
Can we eat that?
No, that French dip has been
in the fridge for a month, dude.
Do not eat it
and do not call me!
-We already ate it.
-Yeah, we ate it.
-It's been eaten.
-I told 'em not to eat it.
Dee tried to tell us
not to eat it, but look, anyway,
we're just calling now so
you don't get mad at us later.
-Yeah, we're hoping
that you get mad out there
and then you come back
and you're happy.
Do not expect that sandwich
when you get back,
'cause it's gone, okay?
But don't worry about it.
It has been pressure-cooked.
-Yeah, we pressure-
cooked the shit out of it.
-What do you mean?
No, you cannot pressure-cook
a French dip.
Oh, yeah, you can, and
I guarantee that the U.S. Navy
-is down on their submarine...
-Don't. Don't talk!
-Don't talk. Don't. Stop.
No more phone calls! No more!
Fantastic.
- Hello, Officer.
- License and registration.
-Uh, well, this is a rental,
actually.
-Hmm.
-Turn the car off.
Yeah.
I, uh... I can't
because I don't have a key.
Uh, well, technically
there is no key.
My phone is the key, and...
I don't have a phone.
Step out of the car, sir.
Uh, you know,
I'd really rather not
because I'm afraid if I get out,
then, um,
I'm not gonna be able
to start the car again.
Sir, out of the car, please.
Right. You don't care.
All right, stepping out.
Well,
who could've predicted that?
Hi. Good afternoon.
Fine,
and you? Thanks for asking.
Listen, my name is
Dennis Reynolds,
and I'm on a family plan
under the name Frank Reynolds,
and I need a new phone, please.
- Okay, I can help you
with that here.
- Great.
-Frank Reynolds, mm-hmm.
-My name's not that long.
-So, looks like I can get you
a replacement phone here.
Can have it to you
by end of day tomorrow.
Uh, no, that's-that's not
gonna work. I need it today.
Unfortunately, the phones are
at our warehouse, so...
Tell me about those,
'cause those look like phones.
Those aren't the phones.
-Those aren't the phones?
-No.
Hey, those aren't
the phones, guys, so,
you know, just so you know.
Those are just boxes
filled with phones
that aren't the phones.
-Phones for new customers.
-Oh, for new customer, right.
Not for old customers.
Not for the paying customers,
the people who have been paying
for months and months,
for years and years
and years and years.
Let's punish those people
and give the phones
that are right there
to the new customers.
It's just how the system works.
-Yeah, well, mm, that system.
I've been
running up against it all day.
Well, I'll tell you what, pal.
I am not mad at you, okay?
I am mad at the system.
Okay, but unfortunately
the system isn't here
for me to direct my frustrations
at it, s...
Good. Let's try something else.
Um, what if we add a new line
to the Frank Reynolds
family plan?
Would that make me
a new customer?
Yeah, I can do that.
I just need your PIN.
Right, 'cause the PIN's the key
to the phone,
and the phone's the key
to the car,
and everything's been
streamlined.
Excuse me, please. I need
to make a call on my watch.
-Are you sure
this is gonna work?
-Charlie,
diamonds are made
under pressure.
This is a pressure cooker.
We're going to cook diamonds.
It's very linear.
-So genius.
I just can't believe no one's
ever thought of this before.
We're gonna be rich, man.
- Oh, I know.
- It's Dennis.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh,
do not answer it.
-It's a mental health day test.
-A test. Mm.
-Test?
In my day, if you wanted
to get out of work,
you hit yourself with a hammer
or you got gnawed by a shark
or something simple.
-No, not gonna pick up now.
No, wh-wh-why would he?
Unreal.
Uh, let's try... 69-69.
Okay.
-Yeah, that's it.
-That worked?
You're all set.
-Seriously?
-That's it.
-This is the phone?
-That's the phone.
I'm gonna open the box,
I'm gonna turn it on,
the phone's going to work?
Yup.
It's gonna work.
It's your phone.
Why won't you talk
to each other?!
Talk! Talk! Talk! Talk!
Talk! Talk!
Dennis Reynolds.
D, E, "N" as in Nancy...
License plate-- "B" as in boy,
SX355.
I'm sorry. I didn't get that.
Yeah, no, I know you didn't
get it 'cause I didn't say it.
I didn't say what it was.
Did you say "January"?
No, I didn't say "January."
I didn't say anything.
I didn't give a month,
I didn't give a day.
Representative.
No, representative.
Human! Human!
D,
E, "N" as in "neighbor,"
I, S.
Dennis Reynolds.
"D" as in
"Deliver me from this!"
-"E" as in "Engage with human."
"N" as in "nightmare"!
"I" as in "Is this real?!"
"S" as in "Somebody help me!"
There has to be a way
to open this goddamn car!
How do I open the car?!
Dennis Reynolds.
D, E,
"N" as in "never-ending."
Thank you for calling
Tsuma Customer Care.
Your call is
very important to us.
Please enter your 17-digit VIN.
- Please say your name.
-Dennis Reynolds.
-Got it. Let me transfer you.
Thank you
for calling Tsuma Customer Care.
My name is Daisy.
May I please
have your name and 17-digit VIN?
No. No, no, no, no. No.
I just ent... I ju...
I just entered all that
information into the system.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I get it, but I do--
- That-That's okay. No, no.
That's okay. Daisy, was it?
Listen, don't be sorry, okay?
I'm not mad at you.
I'm a little upset, but I'm
upset at the situation, okay?
And-and the situation is this,
Daisy.
If you'll just give me a second
and indulge me, okay?
My new phone won't talk
to my car.
Okay, so I called
the car rental company,
and they put me on
with a supervisor
who told me
to call Tsuma Roadside,
so I called Tsuma Roadside.
Spoke to someone over there
who put me on
with another supervisor
who told me
to call the service center.
So I called the service center,
spoke to about--
I don't know--
two, three morons over there
who had no answers
for me whatsoever.
They put me on
with one of their supervisors,
and that person told me to call
the car rental company again.
So I called
the car rental company,
then roadside, service center,
rental company,
roadside, service center,
and around and around
and around like that
for hours and hours,
until finally someone had
the presence of mind
to let me know there's
a goddamn customer care line.
Okay, so I called
the customer care line
and now I find myself talking
to you, Daisy,
my little wildflower.
And you ask me
to enter in my VIN
and my date of birth again,
information which I already
entered into your system.
Okay, now, now, listen,
Daisy, Daisy,
bear with me here, okay?
I know you didn't create
the system, okay?
So you are not to blame.
But somebody did create
the system,
and I would very much like
to blame that person.
- So... who is that?
- Sir, I'm sorry. Who is...?
Who is the person who created
your customer service system
in such a way
that the information entered
into the computer
isn't passed on
to the human representative?!
Sir, I don't know. I can send
you to one of my supervisors.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, Dai... no.
No, don't send me
to a supervisor, Daisy.
Daisy, Daisy...
it's just you and me.
Just you and me, Daisy,
fighting the good fight
against a broken system
engineered
to drive us both so crazy
that we have to take days off
for our mental health!
- Daisy?
- Yes?
The Tsuma.
It's made in America, right?
Yes, it is.
Where?
Yup. Great, wonderful.
All right, yes, okay. Yup.
Oh, let me call you back.
Hello. How are you?
I've been better.
I've been worse.
Is the CEO in?
I'm sorry. Uh, who are you?
Dennis Reynolds.
D, E, "N" as in "Nancy,"
N, I, S.
Tsuma customer for, uh,
oh, six hours and 17 minutes.
I have some helpful feedback
that I would very much like
to pass on to your boss.
Can I get you a water
or something?
Listen, I have traveled
through blistering sun
and pouring rain to get here,
so, if you don't mind,
I'll just wait.
Uh, he is not in the office
this week,
but customer feedback
is very important to him,
so, if you'd like
to leave him a message,
I'll make sure he gets it.
If I leave you a message,
can you assure me
that you will get this to him?
Absolutely.
I'll make sure he gets it
when he gets back
from the beach house.
-The beach, huh?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
I was supposed
to go to the beach today.
-That's nice.
-Yeah.
-How about that, huh?
Which beach?
Brandon, dinner's ready!
Hi.
This is a medical marvel.
You lowered your blood pressure
by 20 points
in less than a minute, but how?
Well, just let off
a little steam, all naturally.
Told you, Dr. Tsuma.
Oh. Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh, hey, Dennis.
Uh, are-are we above
or below sea level?
I'll be right in.