Just have a seat right there.
Would you like a drink or?
- No.
- No?
How about a fresh glass of water?
I have to just go back
and gather myself with my buddies
- before we start this. Okay?
- Okay.
- Right. Good.
- But we are on the clock.
Oh, yeah. And for the record, you know,
you might want to jot down
how well you're being treated
at this professional establishment.
- Frank, get over here.
- Is she from the newspaper?
We are in big trouble.
We gotta come up with a statement
for this reporter.
- She's gonna butcher us.
- Yeah, this is bad.
Why don't we play dumb? Why do
we have to come up with a statement?
Because they found 500 gallons of
baby oil dumped in the Schuylkill River.
Wait. Dee might be right, 'cause they
can't actually prove that that was us.
Well, the 200 Paddy's pub T-shirts
floating around in it
- aren't exactly helping our case, pal.
- Yeah, not helping.
This is a good thing.
This could be our Paddy's-gate.
- Okay, there you go.
- No, but gates aren't a good thing.
I mean, Pizzagate, Watergate.
- Nipplegate. Nipplegate.
- Nipplegate.
Janet Jackson's career was never the same.
You're right, what happened--
- Some things you gotta keep covered up.
- Based off that. Yeah.
- We've gotta come up with a statement.
- Guys, guys, guys, guys!
We can handle this.
I mean this is why we went
to that corporate retreat in Idaho.
We didn't go to the retreat so much
as watched clips of it on YouTube,
but, you know, you're right, Mac.
Normally a situation like this
would have me clawing all your faces off,
but I'm not gonna do that.
I'm gonna utilize my words.
I do see your hand
is still in a bit of a claw.
Yeah, I was ready to pounce.
I had it hidden behind my head.
I was ready...
- Yeah, I hid it behind my leg.
- I had a feeling.
- Should we un...
- No, let's all unclaw our hands.
- Right? Because that was the old way.
- Yeah, yeah.
This is the new way, right?
We've got the tools
from the corporate retreat.
- We've got the vocabulary.
- Yeah.
We've got these awesome fleece vests
inspired by the retreat.
- Oh, my God, I love the fleece.
- God, I love these vests.
You can let it all go under here.
I appreciate you springing for that,
Frank. Thank you very much.
So, listen,
we can handle this unpleasantry
with the grace and elegance
of any major corporation
by utilizing a little thought leadership
and simply talking this thing out.
thought leadership
First and foremost, the business
must be protected at all times.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
The business is infinitely
more important than any individual.
Yes, we are of course a family,
but human emotion notwithstanding,
I would be remiss not to mention
that we are a business first,
and as a business, we must behave as such.
So I would like to posit, respectfully,
of course, that we put forth an offering.
Yes, a lamb if you will.
No, I would say, uh, that lamb right now
could be tender and delicious,
but we have kind of bigger issues
that we're dealing with
that we need to discuss
and maybe, you know,
eating lamb is not the best thing.
- Momentarily speaking.
- Thank you for that, Charlie,
but of course
I'm speaking of a sacrificial lamb.
- Ah!
- Maybe we need to
walk through the series of events
of the incident to figure out
who the fall guy should be,
and I would like to respectfully point out
that the phrase is fall "guy."
Thank you for pointing out
that gender inequity, Dee.
And, henceforth, let's refer
to that position
- as "fall person."
- Mmm.
Or we could circle back
to, uh, animal-related, uh, conversations.
We could consider "fall fish," uh,
or "scapefish" or even "fall bird,"
and then we're back to Dee.
Oh gosh, I'm so sorry guys,
but my hand
is so tightly clenched into a claw.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Same.
- I'm feeling the claw again.
All right, so why don't we do this?
Let's all take a deep breath
before we continue this conversation.
Unclaw our hands.
I think Dee is right.
I think we got to take this mess from
the beginning to find out how we got here.
- Uh-huh.
- Find out who's really to blame.
Now, as you recall,
it all started several weeks ago...
...when Frank
found that jug out back.
Yo, let me blow on that.
No, you make sounds when you bang on it,
not blow on it.
- No, you blow on it.
- No, no. Yeah, yeah.
It sounds different when you put water...
- But it's gonna be much deeper, like--
- No, no, no. He's right.
- You don't blow on it--
- If you blow on it like that it gets--
You turn it upside-down--
You don't bang on it--
That led to a vigorous debate
which in turn led to vigorous clawing
until we decided to stop fighting
and, you know, simply get our own jugs.
Annoyingly, however,
the jugs were filled with fluid.
What are we supposed to do
with all this fluid?
Uh... Yeah, can't really play them
as an instrument until we...
- Oh.
- Yeah, that's a problem.
We could... w-wash the bar with it.
Uh, you don't wanna wash the bar
with a... with a water-based liquid.
- Make a fire and...
- Plants love that.
- Make a fire and put water...
- Make a fire and put it out.
What are you talking about?
We're not gonna make a fire.
- Well, if we start a fire--
- Why would we start a fire?
So we... so we have a reason
to use all this liquid.
After an hour-long argument about
the best way to dispose of the fluid,
we caved and decided the best way
to make the jugs empty
was to simply drink the water.
Now if I'm braising something,
is that a way to cook something,
or is that shellacking it?
Like, am I putting sauce on it?
The inadvertent effect
of the water cooler
was not just hydration, but conversation.
Is it about the sauce
or the cooking technique, or both?
- It's about the crisping.
- About both.
The water tank became
a think tank for business scaffolding,
as well as recent health initiatives
and, you know, general interest.
Well, now I've taken
to using baby oil almost exclusively
when I get out of the shower, you know,
I-I don't know if you guys know this,
but you can actually put a tablespoon
of baby oil in your coffee in the morning
and it resets the pH balance
of your gut biome.
You drink it?
You know, if you're gonna dump stuff,
the best place is the ocean.
I mean, you know, you in a pinch,
you go to a lake or a river,
but you wanna get rid of something,
ocean is the only way to go.
Dennis, how do they get
the oil out of the baby?
Do they have to mash the babies up
or grind them?
Is it babies that are sick
and dying already, or what is the oil--
Don't be an idiot, Charlie.
The babies are alive.
They just wring them out like an old rag.
The Cybertruck
is by far the coolest piece of machinery
that the space nerd has ever made. Right?
- Absolutely.
- I love that truck.
I'm furious
that all cars don't look like that.
Dude, totally. You know what it is?
It delivers on the promise
of the future from our youth.
- Yes.
- Right?
We thought all cars were going to look
like that back in the day.
Hard lines, sharp corners,
DeLorean-like materials.
Yeah, you know, it's the
transportation fitting of a Terminator.
- Totally a Terminator.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, it's like a rhombus on wheels.
- Right, right. Absolutely.
- That's right.
We were firing on all cylinders,
but things took a most exciting turn
when one particular topic was raised.
Gentlemen,
what are your thoughts on slap fighting?
Slap fighting? I'm not aware of this.
Oh. Well, let me tell you.
Just like the Cybertruck
is the future of transportation,
slap fighting
is the future of dispute mitigation.
And, my God, was he right.
We had to try our hand at it.
- The Egyptians, they like the cats.
- Yeah. They like them.
I know, but it's a... it's a cat-based
society, you know what I mean?
Yeah, but I understand that. But--
- The cats are a huge part of their thing.
- They like the cats.
Everybody loved it.
We swapped out the clawing for slapping.
I mean, we were using it
to-to-to settle arguments.
We were using it to end the day,
to start the day,
to say goodbye, to say hello...
...to celebrate, to mourn,
everything, you know.
But then Mac had a business idea.
Gentlemen, let's discuss
professional slap fighting.
We were all slapped across
the proverbial cheeks with this venture.
Take your shirts off, though.
Dennis] It was this hand-face-based
business venture
that led to the off-lining
of certain corporate assets
into various aquatic bodies.
So, Mac is clearly the prime candidate to
fall on the metaphorical sword here. Yes?
- Yeah. Sounds good.
- Sure. Well, yeah. That adds up, right?
Mm-hmm. That does seem to be
the proper mathing. Yes.
Yeah, I do... I do hear you guys on this.
As long as we're outside
of the earshot of this reporter,
I'd like to add, you can stick this
line of logic up your various assholes.
- All right, that's harsher language...
- Interesting point.
...than I thought
we were allowed to use here, but...
Also Dennis
is leaving out a core friction point.
Things were going smoothly
until Dennis pointed out that
the whole thing sorely lacked eroticism.
Slaps and profits have gone up.
- That's great.
- Uh-huh.
But chick saturation has gone down.
- That's not good.
- Uh-uh.
The whole thing
is sorely lacking eroticism.
- The data is alarming.
- Yeah.
- Yeah! Yeah, yeah.
- Well, let's fix that.
- Go on.
- Yeah, yeah.
He pitched something
with the eroticism of mud wrestling
and the aggression of a Cybertruck.
The world just has not delivered
on the future that we were promised
when we were growing up.
We were promised mud wrestling.
We were promised wet T-shirt contests.
We were promised women going wild.
At a certain point,
we stopped women from going wild.
Why did we do that?
- They wanna go wild.
- They should go wild.
They want to go wild.
Let's let them go wild.
They're too dry,
and so they don't feel wild.
Yeah, exactly. Guys,
let's get back to our core values.
Th-There is an underserved market
for one-on-one erotic sport competition
between scantily-clad, oiled-up women.
He proposed pivoting away from dudes
and investing all of our resources
more heavily into women and baby oil.
This is why Dennis's head must roll.
I compliment him on the innovation,
but the idea was a little chunky,
if I'm being honest.
My personal distaste for women aside,
I think you crapped the bed
on the execution.
We were over-leveraged
in the baby oil department
and subsequential
environmental what-have-yous
from the off-lining have left us
in this particular situation.
Which is why I nominate Dennis.
Right time, right skull.
- I like it. I like it.
- I gotta say I'm impressed.
You know, you're coming at me
open-kimono here,
and I appreciate that, so kudos, you know.
But I do think we need to helicopter up,
stretch the vantage point a little bit.
I think we need
to chew on the key protein here,
- which I believe to be Dee.
- Mmm.
With the women slappers in the bar,
we were thriving,
but we weren't quite reaching the erotic
escape velocity that I was hoping for.
I mean... ...really, all it is
is there's one lingering problem
with the women.
- What? They're ugly.
- They're ugly.
- I didn't wanna say it, but they are ugly.
- Yeah.
They're a bit gruff, aren't they?
The big issue for me is you can't put
baby oil on any of these women, you know.
They'll bite you.
I had one almost
bend my arm completely in half.
- I tried to put baby oil on her and she--
- I got pinned by her too, man.
Yeah, yeah. So you know,
like, chick saturation is up. That's good.
- But the attractive/oil saturation...
- It's way down, yeah.
- It's way down.
- Way down. Why is that?
So, we need to find a way
to lure in hotter women.
Yeah, that's all it is.
You know what I mean?
Anybody got any ideas?
Back in the day when we were taking down
all the aluminum siding,
what are we gonna do
with all that asbestos that was left?
- We dumped it in the Schuylkill.
- Oh, you did?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
But, in order to get 'em to do it,
we lured 'em in with a Cadillac.
That's what you gotta do with the women.
- You think we get these gals a Cadillac...
- Yeah!
...and we say, you know, "You win
a slap fight, you get a Cadillac"?
- Everybody needs money.
- Wait.
I know exactly what we should do.
Oh! I was thinking the same thing.
I doubt it.
Look at this thing. Oh, man.
Frank, baby, this is quite the prize.
- Yeah.
- Nicely done, Frank.
- Look at the hard angles on this.
- Yeah.
It's beautiful, man.
The Cybertruck lured in
a much sexier talent pool.
We were really excited
about the quality of slapper,
but there was one
that stood out above all the others.
I mean, we couldn't take our eyes off her.
I can't wait to see the headlights on her.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
Yeah. Well,
and you never will see 'em, Frank.
Because there's only one single headlight.
- It's a single headlight, yeah.
- [Frank Oh.
We couldn't give her away.
We had to have her.
It wasn't long before we came up
with a plan to retain her for ourselves.
We would just have
to win the slap contest, you know.
We needed a ringer, someone
to tear through these waifish models
and ensure the truck
would remain in our portfolio.
What are you guys doing?
Dee was
tearing through girls
like a paper shredder
through company records.
And we knew she would,
as I had explained it with a graph.
The lower the self-esteem, the harder
the slap. And Dee could take a hit too.
Right? Years of getting
slapped around by Frank, right?
Yeah.
Those were the days.
- Oh, yeah. Better times.
- If say so, buddy. If you say so.
She had it all
and she delivered slap after slap.
Sexy women, aggressive violence,
futuristic trucks.
Everything was going according to plan.
Till Dee got knocked out.
Dee, I thank you for your service.
I love you like a sister.
Well, I am your sister.
Well, you know,
familial ties notwithstanding.
Uh, I think you kinda drained the kettle
on that one.
And hey, you know, no offense,
but I think you've proven yourself
to be pretty good at taking a fall.
Guys, I know things are getting hot, okay?
But I think we're styling
the wrong mannequin here.
I would have won that competition
if it wasn't for our associate deviating
from the business plan,
and that would be Charlie.
Oh. Uh... Wow.
He fell back on some old bad habits.
Fool.
What's up?
- What's going on? New car? I like it.
- Oh, God.
- Okay. What is this? Why are you here?
- Pretty sweet. Is that a Geo?
Well, I got
a business opportunity for you.
Oh, a business opportunity?
- Yeah. Check this out.
- Oh, good.
- Yeah, you're gonna like this.
- Great. I bet.
We're doing these oiled-up
slap fights in the bar.
Oiled-up slap fights?
Yeah, we're oiling girls
and they're slapping each other.
- You're oiling girls up?
- Yeah.
So I could oil you
or you could oil yourself, but...
Did you come here to ask me
if I want to get oiled by you?
- Are you stalking me again?
- Yeah.
Stalking? Whoa. Since when did I ever
stalk you? No, that's not my thing.
- Flirting, maybe. But...
- Okay.
Hey, look, you don't have to do it,
but I will say that the winner
of the thing is gonna get a free truck,
but I suppose you like this car better,
you know.
You're giving away a truck?
A Cybertruck.
Little did he know that
she wasn't just driving that crappy car,
she was living in it.
The allure of the Cybertruck
and a lifetime of petty misery
suffered by this woman
rendered her unstoppable.
Yeah. Okay. Who's next?
Uh... Hey. I got an idea, all right?
W-What if you and I get a little
side pot going, right?
You and me, we... we tone down
on the slaps, we call it a tie,
and that way we can share the Cyber--
Yeah!
I was sucker-punched.
- No.
- Mm-mmm.
- In your dreams.
No. You were looking right at her.
She slapped the shit out of me,
but I wasn't ready.
It was uncalled for
and it wasn't fair.
To make matters worse,
Frank reversed course
and refused to make her whole.
What do you mean I don't get the truck?
- It's all in the terms and conditions.
- What?
Look. "Cybertruck not included."
Can you read?
- Oh, my God!
- Can you read?
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- Screw you. Screw you guys so hard!
- In plain writing.
- Oh, I'm taking this public. For this.
- Don't you dare.
Needless to say, she was pissed,
and she promised to go public.
And let's face it,
we didn't have permits for any of this.
Which led to the panic
and dumping of assets
to erase the trail of corporate culture
and create plausible deniability.
I'm gonna call the newspaper.
As the crow flies here, I think
we could all see from a bird's-eye view
that had Charlie not invited the Waitress,
none of this would've happened.
So Charlie should take the fall.
And I would say all due respect,
but I don't respect you.
It's true, Charlie.
We may have reached our inflection point.
Okay, great. Yeah, that's all good. Yeah.
And I-I'm hearing you guys,
you know, ear-wise.
And, um, you know, mouth-wise, uh,
you're giving me various wordables,
uh, that are adding up to thoughts.
This is good. I see how you're trying
to clip my wings so that I can fly.
That's not how birds work.
That makes them "un-fly."
Okay. I did not know that
you were the bird expert.
But I would like to pivot here.
You know, before I fall on the sword
and say that I was also using my eyeballs
this entire time for various observables.
Because I realized...
...that Frank was, you know,
growing in hardness as the eroticism
in the bar was increasing.
And, uh, he was becoming
as hard as a Cybertruck himself,
you know, which you could see.
Cheese, of course, is also on this graph.
- Just keep going.
- Uh, moving past.
Well, the main thing here is that I think
we now have our open sliced lamb.
You know, open commando person.
- What?
- What are you saying?
I'm saying it should be Frank, man.
Because he was throwing an orgy
in the basement the entire time.
- What?
- Yes.
I realized Frank was trying
to capitalize on the erotic environment
and pivot into
a more orgasmic business model, right?
And I noticed various unsavory
investors were paying Frank
to try to get in on the ground floor.
Dear God. Damn, you are not good at this.
I'm tryna say dudes were paying Frank
to go into the basement.
- Mm-hmm.
- Right.
And he was failing in his efforts
to poach talent from the slapping pool.
Ooh. I like those straps and I can't wait
to see it off. Let's go downstairs.
And I knew this 'cause chicks
were slapping him constantly.
But then I saw him trying to headhunt
for new key players in this thing.
Yo, baby. I need a prostitute.
But he was running up
against some logistical hurdles.
Well, when's she coming back
from The Bahamas?
So, the slap fighting
and the basement full of men.
The whole thing was just a big red flag.
He had a target on his back and whatnot.
So, when The Waitress got all pissed off...
She wasn't gonna get a Cybertruck,
and the police were potentially
going to get involved, Frank panicked.
He was worried about the orgy,
which led to the dumping
into the Schuylkills and whatnot.
And so that is why he is the person
that... that should take this fall.
Um, also, there's still
a bunch of dudes in the basement.
- Uh... What? Right now?
- What?
Yeah, there's, like, guys down there now.
- Dude.
- Right? How many are down there?
- Eleven. Eleven. Eleven's the answer.
- Eleven dudes in the basement.
- The reporter could see all this.
- Yeah, one could come up.
- It could be an issue for us.
- Oh, shit.
We got to figure out what we're gonna do
and get her out of here.
I agree with Charlie. I think Frank
should take the fall for the whole thing.
- Well, that's insane.
- You drove a Cybertruck into the river.
I didn't know.
I thought it was an aquatic vehicle.
- It's an environmental nightmare.
- It should be, but it's not.
If anything,
it looks like it goes into space.
- Yeah, it should be but it's not.
- The liberal press is going to crucify us.
I gotta come clean.
I think the truck is ugly.
Damn it. I knew you were gonna say that.
I knew she was gonna say that.
Stupid. You're stupid.
I call bullshit on that.
All right. Enough, enough.
I've had enough with the charts
and the maps and the graphs.
It's clear you're all good foot soldiers,
loyal servants and whatnot.
But it's time we connect the Legos here
and boil down to our core values.
Yes, hammer down on our brand identity
and come out open commando.
- I said the commando thing.
- Didn't make sense the first time.
I thought it was... It sounded cool
and I want to circle back.
- Oh, if you're doing it 'cause it's cool...
- Okay. I got a plan, and this is it.
Okay. Here we go.
Um, ma'am, we are finally ready
to make our statement.
Yeah, yeah.
No comment.
That said, we are no longer gonna
drink, serve, or have anything to do
- that represents water.
- Yeah.
Water is not the cornerstone
of our company.
And we will hereby be getting rid
of the water cooler.
- Gone.
Excuse me, I-I'm not sure
what you're talking about.
Sorry. We got on talking like this
when we started over-hydrating.
Yeah, we watched a couple YouTube clips
about a corporate retreat.
Got some water, got hydrated.
So, we're not gonna talk
about that subject anymore.
- No more water.
- No comment is the main thing, right?
- Yeah. What I said in the beginning.
- Yeah. And no water.
I'm sorry, do you think I'm a reporter?
Yeah.
No. I'm here for the orgy.
Good. Great. Great.
Oh. Hey, guys, the whore is here.
- I was waiting for you.
- I told you guys, man.
- That's one woman.
- Yeah.
Yeah. T-That's not an orgy. That's a...
- That's a gangbang.
- That's a gangbang, yeah.
We really should find a way to exit Frank.