In other news, Tinseltown
is coming to Philadelphia.
Hollywood stars Bryan Cranston
and Aaron Paul are here
promoting their alcohol brand,
Dos Hombres.
Hey, Bryan, how does it feel
to be the kingpin of mezcal?
Oh, no, no. No, no.
Don't-don't put that on me.
No, I'm just a simple actor.
This, this is the man,
the brains behind
the whole operation.
-No. No, no, no.
It's a team effort.
Wow. Hollywood celebrities
right here in Philly, huh?
-I don't love it. I mean,
why can't
they stay in their lane?
Why do they have
into come into our lane?
The celebrity booze thing's
a little out of control.
It's a total sellout.
I mean, a complete cash grab.
Any idiot could take
a bottle of booze,
slap a celebrity's face on it
and-and make a fortune.
-I mean, we could do it
if we wanted.
-Oh, we know more about booze
than these two guys, probably.
-Are you kidding me?
Look, yeah,
is there an opportunity
for us to create a booze
of our own, right?
And go pitch those guys?
Yeah, of course there is.
-It would be so easy.
-Yeah.
-It would be so easy, you know?
And could we do
something like that?
-Also, yes.
Absolutely.
-Of course, we could, you know.
-But I mean,
are we gonna go do something
like that?
-Yes, we're gonna do that, yeah.
-Of course we are, yes.
-I think we should.
-It's already happening.
BOOZE
Okay, guys, I think
we can all agree we need to
come up with a brand
that is representative
of who we are as people
and as businessmen.
Now I ask you guys this:
what's the first word
that comes to your mind
when
you are trying to describe us?
-Premium.
-Mm, I was gonna say that, dude.
-You were gonna say that, too?
-And look, hey.
Listen, man, you're spot-on.
Premium.
Yes, our brand will, of course,
be a premium brand.
Now, what is the most premium
alcohol ever invented?
-Goldschläger.
-Goldschläger. Yeah.
Goldschläger. All right, hey!
We're all on the same page here.
This is good, I like this.
Okay, yeah.
Swiss cinnamon schnapps liqueur
with drinkable flakes of gold
floating in it.
My God, what's more premium
than that?
-Yeah, nothing.
-Nothing, right?
Here's a pitch. Okay,
I can get a bunch of nickels
and I could smash them up
and put them into a 'schläger.
Right? We call it
Nickelschläger,
and we pitch it as, like,
the working man's spirit.
And, you know, nickels are,
they're easy to find
and, uh, just as shiny.
Well, that sounds disgusting,
and, uh,
potentially dangerous as well.
-Yeah, I'm-a try it, though.
Listen, I think I've pinpointed
a small market trend
that we could corner
but that could
also totally represent us.
I'm talking about a blend.
A blend?
-Oh. Blends.
-Yes. Blends, blends.
-Blends!
-Yes.
Blends are very popular
these days.
Wine blends, whiskey blends,
you know?
So let me ask you this:
what is the second-classiest
drink in the world?
-Jägermeister. Yes.
-Jägermeister. Yeah, yeah.
-Jägermeister.
-Jägermeister, yeah.
Amazing, yes.
It's the 'meisters and the,
and the 'schlägers
and the schnapps.
I mean, those are the drinks
that make people feel high-end,
you know, like they're on
a European ski adventure, right?
-Yeah, it's true.
-Yeah.
Those drinks that make people
feel premium, you know?
So I say we do a blend
of all the most premium drinks.
We put them all together,
and we make one drink
called Paddy's
SchlägerSchnappsterMeister.
-That's brilliant.
-That's so smart.
-Well, because it-it blends them
-Dude, that is really smart.
It's fun.
-all together, like you said.
-Who's thought of that?
-It's a lot of fun, right?
- It definitely feels like you're
in Switzerland or something.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Great, so you guys get it,
okay. Great.
So I-I'm so glad we're on
the same page with this.
So, here's the thing.
All we got to do
is get those celebrity guys'
blessing and boom--
we are off to the races,
we're gonna be rich men,
but I don't think
we should approach them
without being
fully funded first.
So our first test
is gonna be landing a big fish
who can finance
this whole operation.
and I know just the guy.
-Yo.
-Yo, Frank,
I got you on speakerphone
with, uh, Mac and Charlie.
-Where are you right now?
-I'm in the sky.
-In the sky?
-What?
That's right, dicknips.
We're in the sky
on a private plane
on the way to Aruba.
- What the hell, Frank?
Why you taking Dee?
-Um, because
I'm more glamorous
than you guys.
Frank recognizes that
and so he invited me.
I was on my way to the jet,
she overheard me talking
about the flight
and she glommed on.
-Yeah, you know what?
We don't care.
Uh, Frank, we have a business
proposition for you, pal.
Frank, how would you like
to invest
in a celebrity alcohol brand?
No, I don't know about that.
I-I once had Greg Louganis
as the face of my apricot brand
in the '80s.
But when he cracked his noggin
at the Olympics,
the business took a nosedive
with him.
Okay, well, we're talking about
a much bigger celebrity
than that, okay?
We're talking about
a household name here.
Have you ever hear
of a little show called
Malcolm in the Middle?
Have I?
Changed the game.
-Changed the game, Frank.
-That it did. That it did.
- Yes. Yes.
-It did change the game.
-That it did.
One of
the greatest shows of all time.
Well, listen, the dad
from that show is in town
and we're gonna be
pitching him tonight.
And Malcolm. He's here, too,
although he's all grown up now,
-so you might not recognize him.
-Yeah.
Dang, that sounds
pretty glamorous.
I'd like to hang with celebs.
-Shut up, Dee.
- Shut up, Dee.
- Oh, God,
shut up, Dee.
Shut your mouth
or I will shut it for you!
When you get back,
Mac's gonna shut it for you!
We're gonna shut your mouth and
we're gonna sew your lips shut!
- Just shut up.
-Shut up!
-All right, well-well,
you know, if you can get,
uh, Malcolm and his dad
on the hook,
bring them to me at the jet.
When I land, we'll talk shop.
-Oh, good.
- Nice, dude.
-Big fish landed!
-All right!
How are they gonna
bring them to Aruba?
We were never going to Aruba.
We're circling Philly.
Oh, my God.
There's The Linc!
What the hell, Frank?
Why are we circling Philly?
I got to put enough miles
on the jet
to make it look like
I went to Aruba and back.
It's a tax thing.
Then why don't we just
go to Aruba and back?
Wouldn't that make more sense?
I have things to do in Philly.
But I don't want
to circle Philly for hours.
Hey, look, first you nag me
to get on the plane,
now you're nagging me
to get off.
Just-- No dice.
We're circling Philly.
-Oh, goddamn it.
It is popping off in there, man.
It is popping off.
Actually, Charlie,
I would also love for you
to pop off that hat.
-No, dude, you said dress nice.
I want to be able to tip
my cap to these guys
when I meet them.
-Yeah, but you look like
a limo driver.
-Whatever, dude.
I look good, man.
You guys want to hit
some of this, too, by the way?
-The hell is that?
-It's Nickelschläger, man.
It's delicious.
I've been drinking it all day.
- Throw that shit out. Do not
bring that up in the pitch.
-I'm gonna pitch it.
-Dude, do not-- Don't--
Oh, goddamn it.
-Over here, sir.
-Okay, you know what?
That might have been this.
Uh, here, I'll give it to you,
I guess. Uh, don't mind me.
-Anything in your pockets, sir?
-No, no, I'm good.
I'm good, I sh--
- Guys, why is it going off
on my stomach?
- Because you have
a belly full of nickels.
Oh, right. Shit.
Okay, you know what? Um...
I'll make myself throw up
and then I'll get--
Should I throw up here or, uh...
All right, I'm gonna go outside
and-and I'll meet you guys
back in.
-Great.
Good riddance.
He looks ridiculous anyway.
Yeah, well, you don't look
that much better, pal.
I mean, what-what,
what is going on with that suit?
Oh, I'm going for
a "Jordan in the '90s" look.
I mean, who's more premium
than MJ, right?
Now, I'm thinking
that I go pitch a fashion line
and sort of expand
into a lifestyle brand.
-No, don't do that.
Okay? Let's just-- Uh, can we
stick with the one thing?
Just stick with
the one thing, please.
-They're celebrities.
They're gonna get the look.
-I know they're celebrities.
I'm not saying they're not
celebrities. I'm saying--
- Do you know
who Michael Jordan is?
-Yes, I know who--
-Then why are you
-fighting me about this?
-Can we just go get in
the meet-and-greet line?
It's already getting
long as shit. Come on.
-Frank. Frank!
-What?
How much longer?
-Three hours.
-Oh, my God.
Can I watch
what you're watching?
'Cause the Wi-Fi
is not strong enough
for me to watch anything.
You should have
downloaded movies, then.
- I mean, I also have to go
to the bathroom.
- Well, that's not good.
Bathroom on the plane is busted.
-W-What?
-Yeah, but you can use
the emergency can.
- Where's the emergency can?
-You're sitting on it.
You just pull that cushion up
and, uh, get that
privacy screen over there.
- Is it a number one
or a number two?
- It's a number one.
Eh, let 'er rip.
It's still gonna go out
in the air anyway.
Are you sure you don't have
any food anywhere?
Why don't you sniff around
back there?
What's this?
There's a can of something.
Oh, that's an old can of oysters
from another flight.
-A can of oysters?
-Yeah, go ahead, have them.
Ugh, goddamn it.
All right, all right.
Getting pretty close here.
-Okay, now,
just go with me here, Dennis.
I want you to picture it,
all right?
It's a whole
lifestyle ecosystem.
-With booze and suits
and apps that link you
to personal trainers
who make you look good
in the suits.
Premium.
Dude, this is what I'm saying.
-No, listen, can we please,
please, please just
stick with the blend?
Stick with the blend.
-This is a blend of ideas.
- Yes, but it's a blend of
too many ideas.
I don't even
know what you're talking about
half the time.
-I'm talking about
branding, bro, it's branding.
-I know what you're--
You know what, actually,
you just keep
your mouth shut the whole time.
Just keep your
mouth shut, I'll do the talking.
We do the firm handshake, right?
'Cause that's essential
to setting tone
for a good pitch.
Got to have a firm handshake.
And then that's it.
I do the talking,
and don't say a goddamn thing
about booze and suits and apps.
-Here we go.
-Oh, okay.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, ladies.
-Thank you so much.
-Uh, all right. Come on, guys.
- All right.
-Okay, here we go.
-Hey, there, fellas.
-Hey.
Hi, uh, hello to you, kind sirs.
-Let's do a...
-Oh, uh...
-No.
No, I'm sorry,
we-we don't shake hands. So...
Uh, well, that kind of
throws off my whole thing.
I think-- We can't kick this off
without a firm handshake.
-Why don't you just--
-I really don't mind
shaking his hand.
How many times do we have
to go through this?
-We're not shaking hands.
-We don't know these people.
-Don't know you.
-Sorry.
-Oh.
Wow, look at that suit.
-Yeah. Look at that.
-I love that.
I'm not supposed to talk.
- I didn't say--
I didn't say--
-I'm not supposed to, either.
Oh-- Come on,
let's get this going.
-He's-he's kidding.
He's kidding.
-Uh, yeah, so-so...
-He's kidding.
-Oh, yes. He, uh, just...
-Yeah, but--
-Come on, everybody say,
"Dos Hombres."
-Oh, uh...
- Dos Hombres!
-All right, you can get
-Thanks so much.
-Yeah, so, we have a--
the photos with the QR code
that way.
-There you go.
-No, I don't need a photo.
Actually, I-I just
wanted to pitch you--
-I--
-All right, hey. All right.
What just happened?
You blew it, dude.
You choked.
I didn't choke, no.
It was... Malcolm.
He was throwing me a weird vibe.
-Yeah. He's very aggressive.
-He's super aggressive.
He's, like, he's, like
the alpha dog, dude.
-I didn't like that.
-Malcolm's not in the middle.
-He's on top.
-Shit.
-You know what, let's-let's
get back in the line.
Oh. Hey.
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, can I ask you something
really quick?
-Yeah, sure, man. What's up?
-Uh, hey, listen,
I've been throwing up
for a little bit.
Ugh, dude, sorry.
Yeah, I-I actually
kind of can't stop.
I think I'm having
a reaction to the metals.
But, uh, my real problem
is, like,
no matter how much I hurl,
like, the nickels
-keep coming out.
-Nickels?
Oh, yeah, it's a 'schläger play
I got going.
So, hey, look,
can you do me a favor?
On my next hurl,
you know, do you--
could you see if you see any
loose change in there, you know?
'Cause, like, I-I really got to
get a extra set of eyes on this.
-I can't help you. All right?
I-I'm waiting for somebody.
-Please, please.
-Sir, I'm begging you, please.
-It's not happening.
Listen, man,
I can't help, all right?
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry!
What the hell?!
-Damn it!
-Oh! Hey.
-Hey, man, hey, hey.
-Come here.
Come here. Look at this.
Look at this.
-Okay. Yes, sir.
-Look at this.
They're gonna ding me
for the cleaning fee.
-All right?
-Ah, yeah, look at that.
Peace and love, peace and love.
-Damn it!
-I'm sorry! Hey, hey.
-Just say by my car.
Stay by my car
-Hey, hey.
-Hey, hey!
-and watch this,
I got to figure this out.
-Get by the car.
-Okay, okay, okay.
I got your car.
I'll watch your car.
Yeah.
He was a big boy.
-Jesus.
-Damn it.
Hey, man, are you
the Dos Hombres driver?
Who?
You know,
the Malcolm in the Middle guys.
Yes, I am.
Come on, come on.
The dad did like my suit.
Would you shut up
about the dad and the suit?
-Thank you very much.
- What are they doing?
-Oh, great. Okay.
-Damn it.
They're wrapping things up.
That's great. We blew it.
We totally blew our one shot.
Goddamn it.
Hey, I think
I just saw Jalen Hurts.
-What? Seriously? Where?
-Yeah.
Dude, he just went
into the bathroom.
I'm sure that was him.
Okay, uh, listen.
We're gonna pivot, all right?
I mean, Jalen's a better fit for
our Philly-based brand anyway,
-don't you think?
-Yeah.
-Let's go talk to Jalen.
-Let's get Jalen.
Come on, let's go.
-Jalen.
-Yeah,
so, hey, listen, uh,
I know this is a little weird,
us bum-rushing you in the
bathroom like this, but, uh...
You always were good
against the rush.
Now, that is true.
You are good against the ru--
Now, you're not gonna get away
from us, though.
We gotcha.
That was a joke. Um...
Okay, uh, well, listen, uh,
we-we just, uh,
we wanted to pitch you
a-a really great
business opportunity.
Yes, now imagine this lifestyle:
you're on a Caribbean island
in an ill-fitting suit.
No, no, st-- no, uh, Jalen,
we're not-not here to...
-pitch you a lifestyle.
-Gritty?
-Wait...
-What the hell is this?
-Wh-- I...
I thought you said Jalen Hurts
came in here.
Is he in one
of the other stalls?
I don't know, I must have
gotten them confused.
How do you confuse
a young Black man
with a giant orange monster?
Okay, Gritty, picture yourself
on a Caribbean island.
-Don't pitch Gritty! We're here
to talk to a celebrity.
-[toilet flushes]
-Gritty's just Gritty.
What-- Oh, hey, Jalen! Jalen!
There he is. Jalen!
-Ah, we just missed him.
-What are you talking about?
-That was not Jalen Hurts.
-Yes, it was.
Oh, don't take his side, Gritty.
-Well, he's right.
-That was definitely
Jalen Hurts.
Uh, you know what, Gritty,
we don't need you anymore.
Why don't you take a hike, pal?
-Appreciate it.
-Goddamn it.
Hold on a second.
Oh, it's Charlie.
What-- Wait, wait, wait.
-What do you want, man?
-[Charlie] Hey, uh,
Dennis, uh, get to Frank
as fast as you can.
I have Malcolm and his dad.
-Are you serious?
-I'll explain later.
Just-- I'll delay them
as long as I can.
Hey, could you maybe just
not be on the-the phone?
-Yeah? Okay.
-Oh, yeah.
Of course, sir.
Yeah, I got to go.
-Please? Thank you.
-Uh, sorry about that.
-Very unprofessional.
-Thank you very much.
-Uh, apologies.
-Yeah, that's okay.
Does it smell funky in here?
Very funky.
-Oh, you guys
picking up an aroma?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, all right.
You-- There might be a funk
to it, Mr. Malcolm.
I did vomit in here earlier.
Oh, oh, great.
Thank you for that.
Wow. And my name is not
Mr. Malcolm, it's Aaron.
Okay, I got you. Yeah, yeah.
We can go by whatever code name
you feel most
comfortable with, sir.
You know, I can't imagine
the pressures of being
-a Hollywood celebrity.
-Oh, oh, please, please, please!
-Watch the road, watch the road.
-Oh, yeah! Shit!
-Jesus.
-Pardon my language.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Uh, pardon my driving.
I haven't driven a car
in a long, long time.
I-- We really got to start
vetting these drivers.
Okay? If we're driving around
in these crappy town cars
with lunatics
and now we're flying coach?
-Counterpoint.
-Coach?
I do like the grit.
-Oh, my God.
-Don't you?
I mean, it's associating
with the common man.
-Talking about me?
-Yes.
-Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-Absolutely.
-When I first stepped
onto the boards
in the Great White Way
of Broadway...
-Oh, and here we go again
about Broadway.
-Was I in the role
-of Richard III? No.
-Were you? No?
-Slipping it in, of course.
-No.
-I was his understudy.
-Okay.
-I never really got
to be on stage.
-Okay.
-But I was very close.
-You had to earn it, huh?
-You had to earn it.
-It's all about the work,
isn't it?
-See? He's working,
we're working.
-Yeah, right?
Yeah, we're-- We are working.
Now, you can never forget
where you came from.
-Remember how you got here?
Remember, huh?
-Yes.
This clown lost all of his money
playing slots
-at Pechanga. Yeah.
-It-- I-I--
No, you have a problem.
You know you have a problem.
The first step:
admitting you have a problem.
I admit I am a servant
to the gods of chance.
I pray at their altar.
-Yeah, way too much.
-Come on, baby.
-Way too much.
-Yeah, come on, baby!
Let 'er roll!
-Let 'er rip!
-No, this guy was a week away
from sucking off tourists, okay?
-Oh, my God.
-To pay his rent,
and you know that.
Fellas, you're not gonna
have to suck anyone off.
I'm taking you guys straight
to a private plane today.
-Hmm?
-Oh, great. Finally. See? See?
There you go. Aren't you happy?
-Doesn't that feel nice?
-I'm very happy. Yes.
Finally. Okay.
Sorry, I happen to be getting
another-another call here.
-I got to take it.
Hello, this is the driver.
-Oh, my...
Hey, Charlie!
You said to call when we landed.
What? We landed?
We landed 20 minutes ago.
I'm just gassing up.
Oh, goddamn it,
why didn't you tell me that?
I wouldn't have eaten
the disgusting oysters.
-Ugh.
-You ate those oysters?
What? You told me to.
That can is from
a shellfish company I started
with Tony Danza
back in the '80s.
Tony's Oysters in a Can-za?
-It was a catchy name.
Didn't go anywhere.
-Goddamn you.
Gross. I am out of here.
Frank?
-Charlie.
-Uh, this is Mr. Frank.
He's the owner of the plane.
-Oh, perfect.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, yes, Mr. Frank?
I have the father and son.
You got them, Charlie?
Bring them over right away.
All right. Ha, ha!
Charlie got Malcolm and his dad.
-Oh, shit. Are you serious?
-Oh, I'm staying.
-What are you talking about?
You've been complaining about
getting off the plane.
Now all of a sudden
you're staying?
-All right. Hey, guys. Come on.
Let's go. Out of the cabin.
What-what--
I'm not leaving my plane.
Oh, no, we've had
this whole situation
where Jalen Hurts felt trapped
and he just freaked out
-and ran away.
-It was not Jalen Hurts, okay?
-It was literally
just some Black guy.
-I-- It was definitely
-Jalen Hurts. Either way,
-It was not Jalen Hurts.
-let's just go. Let's go.
-Let's go. Come on.
-Up, up, up.
-Ugh, all right, all right.
-Yeah.
Yeah, but I always wonder
at whose expense.
You know,
when I was making my way
on the Great White Way
of Broadway...
-Oh, my God. Jesus-- Hey.
-It was hard.
You know, I-I have an idea.
Why don't you just shut
your eyes and go to sleep?
And then I will let you know
when you can wake up.
-Okay? Shh.
-Okay. Thank you.
Okay.
-Oh, but sleep's for pussies.
-Geez.
Let's party, am I right?
Hey, guys, I'm Dee.
Jesus, where'd you come from?
I didn't know we were
sharing the plane.
-Yeah, I-
Hi, I'm Frank, the owner.
And you don't
have to share the plane.
This plane, this
pretty little bird can be yours
for a mere price of $35 mil.
Sorry, actually, um...
-It's a beautiful bird.
-Hey, guys, don't worry.
We're not-not here to sell you
a plane. Frank, please, don't.
Yeah, we want to--
We-we'd sell the plane
-We would, but that's
not the point.
-if you would go for it,
-you'd buy it.
-Just-- We're not selling
the plane.
-Okay, we're here
to sell you, um--
-A lifestyle
-No, no.
-and ill-fitting suits.
-No, no, no, uh,
that-that's also wrong.
-We're not selling
any of that, okay?
-Okay.
-No, no, no. Let's-let's... No.
We're here to sell you a, uh--
Nickelschläger!
No, goddamn it! None of that.
None of that. Okay,
listen-listen to me. Listen.
-Look, we're just-- Listen.
-He's the driver.
Let's just start over, okay?
We're gonna start all over,
and we're gonna do it
with a firm handshake.
Oh. I'm not supposed to.
-Oh, come on, man.
- I think you're in
an abusive relationship.
Okay! This is absolutely insane.
Put your hand down, Bryan.
But I don't mind shaking
his hand, really, I don't--
No, put it down,
you silly little bitch.
Put it down.
-Put it down.
-No.
Don't you touch him.
I said no.
What? Oh, my God.
What is happening?
Sit down.
Please, just sit down.
-Y
ou want us to sit down?
-Sit down, please,
-all of you.
-We-we will sit down.
Yeah, why don't we all sit down?
I don't ask for a lot.
An Emmy here, a Tony there.
Little pocket change for
the one-armed succubus in Reno.
But you.
You, you're--
It's never enough for you.
You want it all.
And you deceived me
into thinking
that-that I wanted it all, too,
and I don't.
And you took charge
of our little operation,
and ever since then,
you've been... you've been
controlling my life.
You control everything.
Or do you?
Maybe...
you are the one being deceived.
Maybe being the front man
of an alcohol business
places your head
so far out in front of you
that you don't even realize
that your neck is exposed.
Enough to be lopped off
by a public
so thirsty to taste the blood
of greedy celebrities.
So, when they come--
and they will--
who are they gonna
come after, huh?
The sweet, hapless boob...
...or the slick-talking,
scheming millennial?
So, I ask you...
...bitch...
...who is really in charge here?
Boom.
And that, my friends,
is acting.
-What? Wow!
-What?!
-Wait, wait.
-That was--
-That-that was all fake?
Made it all up.
Fake, fake, fake, fake.
No offense, anything I said.
-Oh, no, you're welcome...
-I was just joking.
But I do love to perform.
-I do, it's in my blood.
-You got the stuff.
Uh, you should consider
doing a drama, Mr. Middle.
-You really should
consider doing drama.
-Yeah.
-That's a good idea.
-I think you got the goods, man.
Hey, so listen,
do you guys want to invest?
-Boss?
-Fuck no.
-Fuck no! No.
-Fuck no!
Of course not.
I don't want to spend
another moment with you crazies.
-Not another minute.
-You people are insane.
Get me off this plane.