-Things were starting
to look up.
-Very proud of you, Steven.
Remember,
we're gonna just try to...
-Avoid triggers.
-There it is. Yeah.
-I'm sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Little setbacks
would happen every now and then,
but I felt in control.
I can't help. I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
I felt like it was all
in the past.
It was just a bad dream.
Your job is really cool.
Who are you?
I don't know
the first thing about you.
-I'm...in between things
right now.
Yeah, I had
a rough couple of years.
Had to go away
for a little while.
This is not
first-date material.
Sorry.
-It's okay.
We all have...something.
-My something
was hard to explain.
My something was that "Avatar,"
one of the most expensive movies
in history,
used Papyrus as its logo.
I wasn't going back to that.
I found my peace.
And then it happened.
I came face-to-face
with my demons.
There I was -- trapped.
Can we turn this off?
Just turn it off, please.
All my progress, all my work
about to be undone
when I see that title.
Can you please turn this off?
They changed it?
-Oh, yeah.
They swim now, yeah?
-The logo is different.
Okay, it's not
a huge improvement,
but it's -- it's not Papyrus.
Somebody must have
said something.
So, yeah, again,
just to be clear,
not a huge improvement,
but it made me feel like
there was hope in the world,
like maybe,
if we raise our voice,
change can happen.
He just put it in bold.
All the money in the world,
and he just put it in bold.
It's him.
It's the same designer.
He just put it in bold.
[ Keyboard thumps ]
God damn it!
It took him seconds...
[ Whirring ]
...a minute, tops.
-And if you see the logo...
-I have a plan.
-It's so boring.
I mean, wants to hear about
someone who works in IT?
-IT for Disney.
-I didn't tell you
I worked for Disney.
-Years to right the wrong
of the first logo.
And what does he do?
He just highlights
the first one...
and puts it in bold.
Where do you go?
Mind if I sit?
-Uh, sure.
I'm coming to your work event.
-What? To the Disney...
-Disney Graphics
Awards Ball.
-Ow! My hand!
-This is really cool.
I just --
I want to thank you all
for, uh,
recognizing my latest creation,
the brand-new "Avatar" logo.
Uh, we really had so much fun
working on this thing,
and, um...
-Tell them what you did.
Tell them what you did!
♪ The "Avatar" logo's
Papyrus and bold ♪
Papyrus and bold! ♪
It's an afterthought!
-"Avatar" spawned worlds, right?
Every little leaf
of every little flower,
every little eyelash
of every little creature
thoroughly thought out.
But the logo --
it's Papyrus in bold.
Nobody cares.
Does James Cameron care?
I don't think so.
He's probably at the bottom
of the [bleep] ocean!
-Who the hell are you?
-Just Steven Wingdings.
[ Chuckles ]
Is your father
Jonathan Wingdings?
-Yeah.
-I can't imagine
what that would be like --
to be raised by such
a deliberately obtuse man...
someone who created
something so...
complicated.
-This is not about me.
This is about you --
-No, I think this is about you.
Do you know why I like Papyrus?
Because Papyrus was there
from the very start,
ushering in enlightenment
after enlightenment.
Papyrus was the first drop
in the great well
that is the human brain.
From the conception of Reiki...
to the first Western publishing
of the Kama Sutra...
to the pioneer middle-schoolers
who burn the edges
of their book reports
to give it
that old-timey feel...
to, yes, "Avatar."
And here Papyrus compelled me
to make it bold...
to bring you to me...
to teach you to let go.
Yeah.
[ Crying ]
My dad was so hard to read.
And "Avatar" wasn't too big
of a movie to use Papyrus.
It's humble enough...
...to say thank you.