Hosted
Really
Safer
Press
[ Cheers and applause ]
Yes, hello. Hello, everyone.
It is I, President and CEO
of Gaza Hotel and Casino,
Donald Trump.
And I'd like to welcome
President Zelensky here
to this incredible trap.
It's going to be a big,
beautiful trap.
And we're going to attack
him very soon for no reason.
Right, JD?
Watch out.
'Cause this kitty's got claws.
Rawr!
Very butch.
And Marco Rubio is here, too.
Little Marco.
Little Marco, are you excited
to attack our European ally?
Um, no English.
De nada.
Before we get started,
I'd like to thank
President Zelensky
for dressing
like casual "Star Trek."
We love "Star Trek"
because there's no DEI.
The White guy was the leader
and he bossed around Spock,
who I believe was Guatemalan.
We love that.
President Zelensky,
you want to say a few words,
maybe tell Mr. Putin
how much you love him
and that you're sorry
you invaded Russia?
Maybe you offer him
one night with your wife.
Mr. President,
with all due respect--
Excuse me. I'm sorry. What?
I'm sorry.
I have to jump in here because
that's how we planned this.
What happened to "thank you"?
Okay.
Remember "thank you"?
You haven't said thank you to us
once in the past 15 seconds
I've been yelling at you.
I've said thank you.
You didn't say it now,
but you didn't say it now
when you walked in here,
you didn't say thank you.
You didn't say anything about
us being handsome.
Who are my handsome little boys?
You didn't ask us that once.
Look, he's right,
and we're very handsome, okay?
Our ties are matching,
and they're growing,
frankly, by the minute.
We don't even
have to dust in here anymore.
The ties sweep away the dust.
And yet,
you don't compliment the ties.
You don't say thank you.
You don't tell
us how hot we look. Okay?
You don't say,
"If I was gay,
I'd be all over you two." Okay?
And we're supposed to help you?
But if I could just say--
You have been talking
this entire time.
I'm sorry. Does the sign outside
say "Ukraine House"?
No, it says "America House."
Oh. Oh, man.
Look at Rubio over there,
fully dissociating.
He looks like Homer Simpson
disappearing into that hedge.
To quote
the late good Tom Petty.
He's free fallin'.
I'm sorry if I--
You know, you say you want to
end this war,
but frankly,
you don't have the cards.
Okay,
I have the cards.
All right?
I have Skip.
I have Draw Four.
I have Reverse.
I have Get Out of Jail Free.
The Supreme Court
gave me that one.
I have Pikachu and
Charmander and Charizard.
All I'm missing is a Charmeleon.
But without us,
you don't have any of the cards.
Okay, you got no cards.
You're playing poker,
and Putin's playing
Magic the Gathering.
And the Russians
have been treated very badly
with respect to the war.
And also, frankly, "Anora."
Right?
Anora was misled,
and she fell in love.
And now she might
even lose to "Brutalist."
It's disgusting.
You know, maybe
you should come visit Ukraine.
Hey, don't you even dare.
I have been
to Ukraine on Google Maps.
It's a mess.
You think you're getting
any money from us after your
little outburst today?
To quote my personal hero,
Willy Wonka,
"You broke the rules.
You get nothing, you lose.
Good day, sir."
And you know what?
You're also--
You're not even wearing a suit.
It's disrespectful.
Who shows up to the White House
in a T-shirt and jeans
like a garbage person?
Elon. Elon.
H-Hi, guys. Hi, guys.
Elon, we love your outfit.
Very official and respectful.
And I love
when he gets that chainsaw
right next to my head.
Oh, thanks.
Uh, Donald,
what are you doing in my office?
Y-You know I'm the President now, right?
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Okay.
Maybe not. Maybe not.
Awesome, awesome, awesome.
You got to make a joke,
you know, you got to
legalize comedy!
Legalize comedy!
Come on. Legalize it.
I'm so comfortable
with all of that.
I really enjoy everything
you're doing with DOGE, Elon.
Well, they're saying I'm
firing people with no cause.
But I do have cause.
It's 'cause I feel like it.
[ Laughs ] Come on!
Glitch.
Better. B-Better.
They're doing mass firings
in the government.
We love mass firings
because you don't have to know
what any of their names are
or what exactly they do.
I mean, w-w-we're not going to get
it perfect, you know?
But we are firing the nonessential employees,
like air traffic controllers.
Yes, yes.
And sure, some of the planes
are going to land upside down,
but then the luggage falls right into your lap
and you're ready to go.
It's official.
And Elon's got this incredible
team of professionals,
like a 19-year-old
who's known as "Big Balls."
Yo! Reporting for duty, sir.
And, uh, Big Balls, you've
been doing some awesome
DOGE stuff, right, Big Balls?
Oh, for sure.
This week I fired
a Black general
and a woman admiral.
It was awesome!
So awesome, yeah.
It's awesome. It's awesome.
And in addition to DOGE,
we've started another initiative
called the Department of Undoing
Child Healthcare and Education.
Or DOUCHE.
Yeah.
DOUCHE is-- is gonna be epic.
DOUCHE is going to really clean everything out.
Comedy's back, comedy's back!
Come on, come on.
Well, uh, I think that
concludes a pretty much perfect
press conference.
We humiliated this guy,
and JD finally got to audition for
"Real Housewives of Potomac."
I'm willing to throw
a wine glass at anyone.
And to cap off an amazing
week, we're gonna finally
release the Epstein files.
Yes.
America is going to see
all the names from A to S.
No T.
So, Zelensky,
you want to say it with me?
I guess I have to.
Live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
Shane Gillis!
Thank you. Thank you.
So, it's wonderful to be here.
Thank you, guys.
Yeah. How are you?
Uh, I'll tell you this.
This was bumming me
out a little.
I don't know. I just realized
we'll never get to see
Donald Trump debate ever again.
That kind of a bummer?
Even if you don't like him,
that was fun. We had fun, right?
That was fun.
Now he's in office.
That's still funny.
Uh-huh? Yeah.
You guys are having fun.
He's already hitting us with,
like, fifth-grade level ideas,
which is fun.
Gulf of America.
Do you ever think about that?
I like it.
Greenland.
Ooh, now I want Greenland.
I never even
thought about Greenland.
Now it's all I think about.
My favorite thing
with Trump wanting Greenland is,
you know, it's--
you know how they call Greenland--
The Vikings used to call
Greenland, Greenland and
Iceland, Iceland to, like,
keep people away.
When in fact,
Greenland is ice and
Iceland is green.
And I wonder if that trick,
Leif Erikson's trick
from a thousand years ago
made it all the way to 2025,
where Donald Trump was staring
at a map going,
"Green.
And we love green."
I don't know. I'll miss Biden.
Biden was fun. Also hilarious.
My favorite thing about Biden
was anytime he was giving
a speech,
in between teleprompters,
his face would go
back to being dead.
Do you remember that?
He'd be out there like,
"Ah, ah."
"I'm serious."
Look, I get it. You guys are
pretty liberal here.
Look, I understand being
liberal, dude, it feels good.
It's powerful.
It's too powerful, dude.
It's like the Sith.
You can, like,
lose yourself, dude.
Somebody says something you
don't like at work.
You're like, "Ah, eh!"
[ Chuckles ]
"Do it."
All right, now I'm
going to lose you even more.
Uh, for my next trick...
There's a-- There's a thing
I've noticed that White guys do,
and, uh, most White guys I know do it,
and nobody seems to be talking about it,
all right?
And it is racist.
All right? There's a thing
White guys do that,
whenever they're dating a woman
for the first time,
they always ask 'em eventually,
"Have you ever, uh"...
See, I didn't even finish.
Every one of you.
It's a weird thing to ask.
You shouldn't do it.
All right?
You got to find the right time
to ask, though.
You don't want to go
too early with that.
You'll look like a psycho.
You don't want to be, like,
on Tinder like,
"Have you ever had sex
with a Black guy bef--"
It's a shameful thing to ask.
All right? It's weird.
I've done it.
I'm not proud.
One time,
I was in the car with the girl
I was dating at the time.
We were driving home from
my friend Jamal's house.
All right?
And out of nowhere,
the girl I was dating
at the time, she just goes,
"Mm. Jamal's handsome."
I was like,
all right, that's fine with me.
I'm not insecure or racist
or whatever would make
me care about that.
But she brought it up,
so now I can ask
without looking like a psycho.
So I was like, "Have you ever,
uh... would you ever... ever...
Have you ever had sex
with a Black guy?"
And she goes, "Ew, no."
I was like, "Jesus Christ,
what are you, racist?"
Hey.
All right. I'll tell you this.
Now that I've got your
attention, I, uh...
I'm getting older.
I can tell I'm getting older
because the only thing I watch
is historical documentaries.
Every night I put on
historical documentaries.
I also drink a lot,
so I don't--
I haven't retained
one piece of information.
I turn it on and I'm asleep.
I've watched the same episode
of "World War II in HD."
I'm on episode one.
I've been on episode
one for four years.
I wake up at 4:00 AM.
It's still on,
volume at 50.
Episode eight, "Stalingrad."
Just wake up
to artillery every night.
Just, "Ah!"
But my favorite
historical documentary is--
it's called
"Ken Burns' Civil War."
All right?
"Ken Burns' Civil War,"
if you haven't seen it,
it's 900 hours long.
No one on Earth
has ever finished it.
It's also-- It's
Kryptonite to women.
If you put that on,
they will fall
asleep immediately.
You know, that's a little--
You know, they're yapping
a little, you go,
"How about some Ken Burns?"
That's a little Cosby tip
for you, actually.
Who needs roofies when we have
"Ken Burns Presents
the History
of the Buffalo" on PBS.
But "Ken Burns' Civil War"
is my favorite one.
It's the most boring thing
you've ever seen.
Obviously, there's no footage.
It's the Civil War,
so all they do
is just slowly zoom in on
black-and-white photos
while historians talk,
and they give you
facts and information.
But there's one historian,
if you've ever seen it,
he's the funniest guy
in the whole thing.
His name is Shelby Foote.
All right?
Shelby is this old Southern guy
who's clearly
cheering for the South.
The entire documentary.
Anytime he's talking, he's like,
"Oh, the South had
some fine gentlemen."
You're like, "All right,
Shelby, take it easy."
But all the other
historians are at, like,
library desks or in an office.
Shelby is in his living room,
and he's clearly freestyling.
Everyone else is giving
you facts and dates.
Shelby's clearly just
making up stories.
Every time the camera cuts
to him, he's like, "Well, now,
after the Battle of Fredericksburg,
a couple of the Rebel soldiers,
they got up on the ramparts
and they started yelling down
to the defeated Federal Army.
They yelled out.
They said, 'Hey, Johnny Yank,
we whipped you today.'
Now, the Yanks,
they didn't like that much.
So they yelled back.
They said, 'Hey, Billy Reb,
we're gonna lick ya tomorrow.'"
You go, what? Why'd you
just make up that story
in the middle of the show?
I'm not a historian,
but I know that didn't happen.
The guys without teeth or shoes.
Do you think that's
how they talk to each other
after they shot him?
"Oh, you pulled a fast one
on us the other day."
No, that real conversation was
like, "Argh!"
[ Laughter ]
All right. I don't know
how to get out of this joke,
but I really wanted to talk
Ken Burns with you folks.
The only way I can think
to get out of it is Shelby--
Shelby is the funniest guy
in the whole thing
because he loves--
He's almost, like, sexual
how much he loves the South.
Anytime he talks about 'em,
he's like,
"Oh, the women gathered in town
when the Southern
soldiers marched through.
They loved the pageantry.
I have here a love letter
written from a private
from Tennessee back
to his sweetheart.
It reads, 'Dearest Clara,
tomorrow I go into battle.
I may never see you again.
Oh, how I wish I could kiss
your sweet, supple lips
but one more time.
Clara, before I go into battle,
I do have
but one question for you.
You ever, uh...
You ever'"--
All right, all right.
That was fun.
You guys are great.
We got a great show tonight.
Tate McRae is here.
Stick around.
We'll be right back.
Oh, honey, look at this view.
Not too shabby, eh, son?
And I was talking
about the winery,
not the new girlfriend.
All right, all right, Dad,
take it easy.
Stop. It's cute.
And I just want to say thank
you guys for this trip
and being so lovely and
for making James.
Aww.
Well, uh-oh, son. Red flag.
She's too good for you.
Oh.
Don't I know it.
Okay. And plus, your mom and
I already have something in
common-- Merlot.
Ain't that right, sister?
Oh, Tessa, you are a doll.
Oh.
Oh, my God,
is that an orange tree?
Oh, my God, I love those.
Wait, baby,
baby, take a picture.
All right.
Take a picture of me.
Okay. Sorry, Mom and Dad.
Time for my full-time job.
Okay. Wait. Let me get--
Okay. Hold on. Wait. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Take it.
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
Okay. Uh, just one sec.
And there. It's great.
Okay. Can I see?
Um, actually,
can you take another one?
Uh, for real?
Yeah. Yeah, baby.
This is what happens
when you have a hot girlfriend.
Maybe, like, um, do a series.
Yeah. What's a series?
Where you just keep pressing
the button, okay?
Okay. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Closed mouth.
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
Open mouth.
Laughing. [ Laughs ]
Laughing again. [ Laughs ]
Oh.
And then one for the veterans.
Did you get it?
Yeah, I think I got it, babe.
Okay. Awesome. Can I see?
Yeah.
Okay. Um, no. No.
What are you doing?
These are bad.
What's wrong with these?
You look hot.
You think I look hot?
I look like Michael Cera.
Okay, tour's moving on,
y'all, we should--
Just take it. Hold it.
Well, you just said hold it.
Hold it, just hold it.
You're not giving me
any directions.
Okay, so the direction is...
be a man.
You're not a baby boy anymore.
You're a big man.
Babe.
Just say it.
Say, "I'm a big man who knows
how to take pictures."
I'm a big man who knows
how to take pictures.
Okay, now take it.
Yeah.
Hold it.
Get the top of my head,
not my shoulders,
but then my legs.
How is that possible?
Okay.
And then, baby, do a boomerang.
[ Laughing ]
Babe, that's scary.
It looks like you're
puking into your hands.
You know, why don't we just
take a group picture and get
back on that tour, huh?
Yeah, I think that's a great
idea.
[ Baby talk ] Babe...
your parents are kind of ugly.
I'm sorry.
They are
kind of ugly in the pictures.
I know they're kind of ugly,
but they're my family.
Oh, oh.
Everything
going okay over there?
[ Mocking ] Everything
[ Normal voice ] Yes.
I'm trying to take a picture
so we can go drink, girl.
Well, gang, I think we got
what we need here.
[ Stammering ] ...here
That's how you sound.
Babe, your parents are rough.
Can we please go?
I'm sweating.
No, not until I get a picture
of my hot boyfriend. Go.
All right. Just be nice.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Smile, babe.
Ew, ew, unh-unh, unh-unh, no.
Baby, baby. Hide your hands.
What's wrong--
Baby, hide your hands now.
'Cause you look like a cartoon
bear.
All right.
Okay. Act like--
Baby, act like you have
an egg in your mouth.
Egg in your mouth.
What?
Egg in your mouth. Okay.
Egg in your mouth
and smile with your nose.
Smile with your nose.
Okay. Now hands out
like you're catching a baby.
You-- Yeah, cute!
Okay. And then, can
you take one more of us?
Okay, but this is the last
one.
Okay. Okay.
Look hot. Look hot.
Laugh at me.
Now kiss-- kiss me.
[ Laughs ] And then dip me
while I'm laughing.
[ Laughing ]
Have a great day, gang.
You too, hon.
You wouldn't know it,
but a few months ago,
anxiety and depression
were ruining my life.
I was struggling at work.
Hey, you need something, bud?
I was struggling as a father.
Gah! Come on, Andrew.
You can't be bad at school
and sports.
And struggling as a husband.
I'm upset because my mom's
doctor thinks
that we should move her
into an assisted living place.
Oh, that's awesome.
I was at a real low point.
That's when I talked to my
doctor about
a CouplaBeers.
A CouplaBeers
is a revolutionary medicine
that treats anxiety and
depression fast,
and within minutes of taking it,
I'm back to my old self.
Andrew,
I love you, buddy.
You're the best in the whole world.
And my confidence is
through the roof.
What are you guys laughing at,
how stupid you are?
Jane, you look freaking hot.
You been doing, like, Pilates?
Excuse me?
Oh, sorry.
I'm just having a tough time
adjusting to my new medication, so...
The way it works is simple.
CouplaBeers quickly
turns a cloudy, rainy day
into a sunny one.
It's that easy.
Now I'm the me I want to be.
And I'm not the only one
who's noticed the change.
Cheryl's making me feel so
bad for skipping her birthday
trip, but it's like--
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
She's just jealous 'cause
you're so beautiful.
CouplaBeers
is a clinically proven treatment
for conditions like...
Boredom
Depression
Winter
Museum
Hangovers
Affair
Italian wife
And if you miss a dose of
CouplaBeers, don't worry.
You won't.
Brother, you will never miss
a dose.
It's the kind of thing
the only thing
you really remember after a while
is to take it.
The most common side effect of
a CouplaBeers is drowsiness.
So you may want to ask
your doctor about aLilBump.
The way aLilBump works
is simple.
Once the drowsiness of a
CouplaBeers sets in,
you simply take aLilBump
and let
the medication do its thing.
♪
Come on.
Back behind the fence.
Trying to teach my kid how to
swing, [bleep] face.
So if you're ready
to get your life back,
talk to your doctor
about a CouplaBeers.
Maybe even aLilBump.
Honey, can you come sit down?
We need to talk.
No.
CouplaBeers.
What's the big deal? Calm down.
God.
Mom and Dad...
what are you guys doing here?
And welcome back.
You're watching
WANU Mid-day News.
In just a bit,
we'll have more on
that incoming winter snowstorm.
Get ready to bundle up,
folks, but first,
the latest on what's happening
over in Westlake.
So sad.
Community members remain rattled
after yet another
gang related drive-by shooting
that took place in
the 4000 block
of Reisterstown Road
late last night.
The shooting is believed
to be in connection
to last week's string
of violence in the same area.
After questioning witnesses
and reviewing nearby
surveillance footage,
police have identified
the suspects
and located the 2018
Dodge Charger used
in last night's crime.
The suspects are believed
to be four White--
Whoo! I know that's right.
I'm sorry. What's going on?
Oh, nothing.
Yeah. Just relieved
that the police have
White-dentified the suspects.
Mm-hmm. Exactly. Very White.
Um, okay.
Crime is crime,
and we are all relieved.
Oh, sure. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, it's shaping up
to be quite a busy week
for local law enforcement,
as police deliver
on their promise to crack down
on the increasing drug traffic.
Uh-oh.
Not drugs.
A raid earlier this morning
uncovered a major meth ring.
Okay. We're good.
That's y'all for sure.
In a quiet
suburban neighborhood.
Now, you know. [ Laughs ]
Know what?
That they ain't one of us.
Okay?
Well, how do you know that?
Uh, meth, quiet. Come on now.
All right,
let's see the picture.
Why are you entertaining
this stupid game?
Because we're down 2-0,
Suzanne. You want to lose?
Show the picture.
Lose what?
Police say they are still
on the lookout for this man.
Oh!
"Breaking Bad"-looking ass.
That's 2-0.
All right,
all right, let me do one.
Police are looking for looters.
Huh?
You hear that?
These looters were spotted
after wildfires devastated homes
in Hunt Valley Township.
Looters.
Okay. Just read the story.
That's enough.
Looks like they
stole televisions, bikes.
Who do you think that was?
What-- What color do
you think that was?
Do your job, Dale.
All right.
Police are on the lookout
for the alleged ringleader,
a local man named
Ethan Kapowski-- damn it.
Ka-pow! Ka-pow!
That's 3-0. We in yo ass.
All right. This is childish.
It's time to take a moment
to hear from our eye in the sky,
Sheldon Holmes,
with the latest on traffic.
Thanks, Suzanne.
As usual,
we've got a bit of a lunch hour
bottleneck situation heading
east on Route 30.
And speaking of 3-0,
get your brooms ready,
'cause it's looking like a
sweep, y'all!
You heard? You heard!
Fine.
Let's see about this one.
Mayhem at the barber shop.
Aw, damn.
No, no.
After a customer was shot...
Oh, Lord.
...during an argument
over Drake and Kendrick.
Yeah. Yeah. That's us.
Yeah. That's us. Okay. 3-1.
3-1.
Yeah. You guys sure you don't
want to see a picture?
Okay. Shut up, shut up.
We're still in the lead.
How about this?
Violence erupted in
the parking lot of a concert...
I like where this is going.
...where Shaboozey was
performing.
Who the heck is Shaboozey?
He's a genius,
but this sounds like us.
When a man selling
bootleg T-shirts opened fire.
Oh, look at that!
Buzzer beater!
That's you guys all day. 3-2.
This is kind of fun now.
Let's keep it rolling.
A Florida middle school teacher
has resigned after falling
in love with an eighth grade
student--
4-2.
Suzanne.
Suzanne, whose team are you on?
Okay, wait.
Pick a different one.
Wait. I haven't finished
reading yet.
Authorities have charged
38-year-old Lakisha Williams.
3-3.
Oh, what?
3-3. Thank you, sweet baby
Lakisha.
Lakisha, girl,
what is you doing?
All right, all right.
3-3. Next one takes it.
All right, I got it.
A Harford County man
has been hospitalized after
taking on a bizarre challenge
of eating raw chicken every day.
That's y'all.
That's you guys.
What are you talking about?
Raw food. That's y'all all day.
Yeah, but it's chicken.
So?
So come on.
You guys are the chicken people.
What?!
Who's the chicken people?
I mean, yes, but no.
Okay, okay.
This is getting a little heated.
Okay, why don't we move on
to a feel-good story?
A 90-year-- 91-year-old
woman won a dance contest--
Girl, who cares?
She don't got long left anyway.
Come on, keep it going.
All right,
let's get back to the game.
All right.
For all the marbles,
a woman is suing the state
after her adopted
pet monkey-- damn it.
Yes. All right. Good game.
Okay. All right.
Good game, good game.
And that's all the time
we have today at
WANU Mid-day News. Tune in--
No, no, we've still got
a few more seconds.
Real quick, do another one.
Okay, okay.
Guys!
A TSA agent-- Aw, damn it.
That's us.
Yes. We're tied again.
We're tied again.
One more, one more, one more.
We got time for one more.
[ Cheers and applause ]
**
You're watching PBS kids.
Later, it's an all-new episode
of "Caillou: The College Years."
But now it's
time for "Dad's House."
Hey, kids, are you ready
for your weekend at Dad's House?
No.
Well, that's the arrangement.
Now, here he is-- Dad.
Hey, friend.
Welcome to Dad's House.
It's my weekend with the kids,
and I couldn't be
more excited and sober.
There they are,
right over there.
That's my baby girl, Crystal,
and, uh...
Matthew.
Matthew. Yeah, I know, bud.
[ Doorbell rings ]
Oh, that must be the mail.
Which means it's time
to sing the mail song.
♪ Oh, no,
it's the worst time of the day ♪
♪ Nothing ever good
comes in the mail ♪
Hey, looks like we got a letter
from Mommy's attorney.
That brings us
to the word of the day,
"alimony."
Alimony is a form
of legal stealing.
If you took a gun into a bank
and made them give you $2,000
every month, you'd go to jail.
But if you do the same thing
to me while living in a house
I bought, apparently,
that's fine. Isn't that cool?
Alimony was the word
of the day last time.
Well, it's
a big part of my life.
Dad, can we eat?
We're hungry.
Of course. I don't want mommy
thinking I don't feed you,
like you told her last time.
Yeah. You didn't think that
that would get back to me, Mike?
Matthew.
Whatever.
All right, so come on, friends,
let's whip
up a healthy breakfast
for my little guys.
All right.
First you get a plate,
then you get some
of these little Vienna sausages.
You just kind of go ahead
and get them out there.
Just kind of fan them out
to make them look like that.
That looks nice.
And then, because it's
breakfast, get a little splash
of syrup in there-- huh?--
for dipping.
And now, here you go, guys.
Eat up.
What is that?
It's sausages. It's good.
I eat them all the time.
Can I have something else?
Come on. I'll even let
you shoot the juice.
Oh, that's disgusting, Dad.
All right, your loss.
Ohh!
So gross.
Yeah, Dad. Come on.
We want a real breakfast.
I can make you breakfast.
So nice
to finally meet you kids.
Dad? Who's that?
Oh, looks like dad's
friend, Bridget, is still here.
What's, uh...
The hell are you doing here?
I'm waiting for my Uber.
Did you not want me
to meet your kids?
Of course not. No, not after
what you did last night.
You liked what I did last
night.
Yeah, I liked it, but I don't
want someone who does that
around my kids.
What? Excuse me?!
Sorry. Look, just call me on
Monday.
Kids, say good-bye to Bridget.
Bye.
Jesus.
Uh, anyway,
so now that you've eaten, what
do you guys want to do today?
Can we go to the aquarium?
Yeah.
Sean took us to the aquarium.
It rocked.
Who the hell is Sean?
He's mom's friend.
And mommy lets him take you
places?
Sometimes.
Okay. All right.
You know what? I'll just call
mommy and get directions
to the-- to the aquarium.
[ Cell phone rings ]
Oh, my God, what happened?!
Are the kids okay?!
The kids are fine-- don't
answer the phone like that.
Oh, my God.
Okay. What is it then?
Nothing. Just the kids were
talking about the aquarium,
and I guess I'm just wondering
if you think it's a good idea
to keep traipsing dudes in and
out of the house like a hooker.
Oh, okay. There it is.
Good-bye, Christopher.
Everything okay, Trish?
Is that Sean? Put him on.
Sean Hedges.
Who've I got here?
Hey, Sean.
I got two questions.
What's your favorite fish,
and how long have
you been donging my wife?
Uh, well,
technically it's not a fish,
but I'm kind of a dolphin nut.
Oh, oh, Sean. Come on.
Chris, go to hell.
Wait, I-I love you.
♪
Well, that's all the time
we have today on "Dad's House."
Come on, kids, let's go to the
mall and get something to eat.
Come on.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Welcome to
blind auditions for "The Sound."
After four weeks,
our coaches are on their way
to assembling their dream teams
of America's next star singers.
During the blind auditions,
all that matters is your voice.
One stage,
one song, one opportunity.
Anybody from anywhere
can blow us away
and be on our team.
So get ready, America, let's
see if you have the voice--
the sound. Sorry.
The judges are ready,
and so is our first contestant,
Reggie T.
Let's get it.
That's very nice.
Dang, that's hot.
Let the bidding war begin.
Who wants me?
It seems, for the first time
in "The Sound" history,
the judges
have revoked their selection.
Hey, you can't do that.
You already turned.
[ Clearing throat ]
What are you all doing for
lunch later?
Turn around.
You can't bail on me
because of my looks or my vibe.
The judges knew
Reggie was right.
You know, you're right.
We were just caught off guard.
Let's start fresh, yeah?
Why don't you tell
us about yourself?
I'm Reggie. I'm from Kansas.
I'm what the Japanese would
affectionately refer to as
an otaku.
I didn't want him anyway.
Let's see.
My greatest influence is
Chris Brown,
but my greatest
musical influence...
Come on, just give me a shot.
I really need this.
♪ Can we just start over? ♪
He needs it. He needs it.
I really appreciate that.
I'd like to shake your hand.
You can walk.
Why do you have a Jazzy then?
I don't know,
maybe because it's cool.
It helps me get laid.
Unh-unh. Don't look at her.
Why? She liked it.
She does not like it.
She loves it. You hate it.
Ugh, I can't believe this is
happening to me on my birthday.
Oh, it's his birthday?
Let's give him a shot. Come on.
- How old are you turning?
- 14.
There is no goddamn way
you're 14, man.
Leap year birthday, brother.
- So you're actually...
- 56.
Yeah, but don't tell
the girls I Snapchat with.
Whoa!
What is wrong with him?
I want to be on the lady's
team, she's sexy.
Mnh-mnh. I'm out. Peace.
Talkin' 'bout he 14 years old.
Meanwhile, he look like
Mr. Filch.
You know what? You guys don't believe in me.
But one day, you'll see.
One day you'll all see.
Dude, there is no way in hell
you will ever make it as a mus--
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ Sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch ♪
♪ Like me ♪
Our chemistry is amazing,
Reg.
Maybe now you'd want to...
No, thanks.
I'm a 14-year-old boy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tate McRae.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Whispering ] * I think you
know what this is ♪
♪ I think you wanna uh ♪
♪ No, you ain't got no missus ♪
♪ Oh, but you got a sports car ♪
♪ We can uh-uh in it ♪
♪ While you drive it real far ♪
♪ Yeah, you know what this is ♪
♪
[ Singing ] * Hey, cute jeans ♪
♪ Take mine off me ♪
♪ Oh, golly gee ♪
♪ I can't take no more ♪
♪ I'm goin' weak in my knees ♪
♪ Where'd you put those keys? ♪
♪ We can share one seat ♪
♪ In the alley, in the back ♪
♪ In the center of this room ♪
♪ With the windows rolled down ♪
♪ Boy, don't make me choose ♪
♪ In the alley, in the back ♪
♪ In the center of this room ♪
♪ With the windows rolled down ♪
♪ Boy, don't make me choose ♪
♪ I think you know
what this is ♪
♪ I think you wanna uh ♪
♪ No, you ain't got no missus ♪
♪ Oh, but you got a sports car ♪
♪ We can uh-uh in it ♪
♪ While you drive it real far ♪
♪ Yeah, you know what this is ♪
[ Reporters clamoring ]
♪ Pretty blue streetlights ♪
♪ And my hazel eyes ♪
♪ And if it feels right ♪
♪ We could go again like three,
four times ♪
♪ So my type ♪
♪ Got butterflies ♪
♪ So good it hurts ♪
♪ Thinkin' 'bout what we did
before this verse ♪
♪ On the corner of my bed ♪
♪ Oh, and maybe on the beach ♪
♪ You could do it on your own ♪
♪ While you're lookin' at me ♪
♪ I think you know
what this is ♪
♪ I think you wanna uh ♪
♪ No, you ain't got no missus ♪
♪ Oh, but you got a sports car ♪
♪ We can uh-uh in it ♪
♪ While you drive it real far ♪
♪ Yeah, you know what this is ♪
♪ I think you know
what this is ♪
♪ I think you wanna uh ♪
♪ No, you ain't got no missus ♪
♪ Oh, but you got a sports car ♪
♪ We can uh-uh in it ♪
♪ While you drive it real far ♪
♪ Yeah, you know what this is ♪
♪ Oh, my guy ♪
♪ You don't wanna waste my
time ♪
♪ Let's go ride ♪
♪ Oh, my guy ♪
♪ You don't wanna waste my
time ♪
♪ Let's go ride ♪
♪
♪ I think you wanna, wanna ♪
♪ But you got a sports car ♪
♪
♪ While you drive it real far ♪
♪ Yeah, you know what this is ♪
It's "Weekend Update"
with Colin Jost and Michael Che.
Good evening, everyone.
Welcome to "Weekend Update." I'm Michael Che.
I'm Colin Jost.
I was worried I
was being set up again.
Okay.
President Trump met
with Ukrainian president
Volodymyr Zelensky yesterday.
Let's see how it went.
You're gambling
with the lives of millions
of people.
You're gambling
with World War III.
You're gambling with World War III.
Pretty good.
And now, thanks to that meeting,
now you actually can gamble
on World War III on FanDuel.
Trump repeatedly scolded
Zelensky,
telling him,
"You have real problems."
Yeah, man, he's in a war.
No one's asking to borrow
missiles so they can take
the party to the next level.
Zelensky was asked
to leave the White House.
Then he appeared on Fox News
and said he thinks he
can still salvage
his relationship with
President Trump,
which is like
Justin Baldoni saying,
"I'd love to work
with Blake again."
President Trump posted
an AI-generated video featuring
a transformed Gaza
with a Trump Hotel,
bearded belly dancers,
and
Benjamin Netanyahu
lounging on a beach.
The video was titled
"ISIS Recruitment Ad."
Attorney General Pam Bondi
sent a letter to FBI
Director Kash Patel,
saying that she learned
from a source
that the New York FBI office
has
thousands of Epstein files
that it still hasn't released.
Kash Patel is currently
looking for those files
in two different directions.
Elon Musk, seen here letting
ketamine take the wheel...
...sent an e-mail
to federal employees
telling them to list five things
they did last week
or they would be fired...
which was easier for Elon to do
because all five of his
were "got a lady pregnant."
It was reported
that internal television
monitors at the offices
of Housing and Urban Development
showed an AI-generated video
of President Trump
kissing the toes of Elon Musk.
You can tell the video is AI
because in it,
Trump is able to bend.
Ron DeSantis is pushing
for his wife, Casey,
to succeed him
as governor of Florida.
But I don't know.
Those are some pretty
gay boots to fill.
Dozens of dead birds
believed to have died
from avian flu
have washed up
on a Long Island beach.
But don't worry--
RFK is almost done eating them.
Former New York governor
Andrew Cuomo
has decided to run for mayor
of New York City.
Cuomo plans
to use his old campaign slogan
of "honk-a, honk-a."
The Oscar campaign
for Best Picture nominee
"Emilia Pérez"
was badly damaged
after problematic old tweets
about George Floyd
surfaced from transgender star
Karla Sofía Gascón.
And I think we
can all agree--
What?
Last week, a U.S.
appeals court blocked
a Biden-era student debt
relief plan,
which means the only way
for young people to pay off
their student loans
is by dating Bill Belichick.
This week,
MSNBC fired its only non-white
prime-time host,
and Lester Holt announced
he is stepping down
as the anchor of
"NBC Nightly News."
Well, NBC...
only one more to go, baby.
Wait a minute. Are you guys
rooting for me to leave?
Yeah, sure. "Whoo!"
Well, guys,
the Oscars are tomorrow night.
Here with his prediction
for Best Picture
is The Movie Guy.
Hey!
How's everybody doing tonight?
I'm The Movie Guy, and I'm here
to talk about which movie
is going to win Best Picture.
'Cause right now, it's
a very tight race.
That's right.
I've heard that.
So who are your top contenders?
Well, let's start
with "Anora."
The only problem with "Anora"
is, I wish she had a "more-a"
the boobies
and a less of the talking.
[ Laughter ]
Okay. All right, Movie Guy.
Sure.
No, no, I'm just kidding.
With full disclosure,
I didn't see that one.
But I would like to talk about
"A Complete Unknown."
This movie is a complete unknown
to me because I didn't see
this one, as well.
[ Laughter ]
Right. Okay.
I guess I'm starting
to wonder why you're here.
Because I'm The Movie Guy.
[ Laughter ]
Okay.
Listen, listen, man,
I know that Timothée Chalamet do
a perfect "imperfatation"
of Bob Dylan.
But you know who my favorite
Bob?
"PlumbBob."
I'm sorry. Who?
"PlumbBob"!
[ Laughter ]
"PlumbBob" SquarePants.
What?
You know him.
His best friend is a "tar."
He's in love with a "quirrel."
One episode,
he learning to drive a car,
and then the next episode
he delivering pizza,
and then the next episode,
he ripping his pants.
The only way
to describe the plot
of "PlumbBob" is unlimited.
[ Laughter ]
You know [Laughs]
You know, you...
You call yourself The Movie Guy,
but it seems
like you're more interested
in talking about SpongeBob.
You're right. [ Laughs ]
You're right, man.
Let's talk about movies, okay?
Let's talk about "Conclave."
Yeah.
Yeah, this movie has to be
about the Pope, right?
[ Laughter ]
Yes, yes,
it's about the Pope.
Yes, it's about the Pope.
That's what I said.
[ Laughter ]
The [Laughs]
The only thing that's weird
is that I didn't see that one.
[ Laughter ]
But the Pope made
me think of Popeyeh.
Who?
Popeyeh! You know him.
He the little bald guy
that loves 'pinach.
Am I right, guys?
[ Laughter ]
You are talking
about Popeye?
Why are you saying it like that?
You better be very careful
in the way that you're
talking to me right now.
[ Laughter ]
Anyways, we got to talk about
"I'm Still Here."
Yeah.
This movie is about a guy
and everybody is saying,
"Did he leave?"
[ Laughter ]
No. He had not left quite yet.
[ Laughing ] He's still here.
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughs ] Sorry.
I guess I'm just confused as to
how you became The Movie Guy.
And you know what?
There's a lot of people
that are very confused
about a lot of that stuff that's
happened in your life, as well.
[ Laughing ] Okay.
[ Laughter ]
However, my ultimate pick
for Best Picture
is "The Brutalist."
"The Brutalist." Right.
Please tell me
that you've watched this.
Of course I watched
this movie, man.
I'm The Movie Guy.
[ Laughter ]
This movie is
about an architect.
That's actually right, yes.
Yeah.
And he escape
a concentration camp.
And then
he want to build something.
And you know what
he build?
A pineapple
under the sea for "PlumbBob."
Am I right, guys?
The Movie Guy, everyone.
It could be "Wicked."
I don't know.
I'm The Movie Guy.
A couple on a Qatar Airlines
flight was forced to sit next
to a dead body
after the woman next to them
passed away mid-flight.
But on the bright side,
at least she finally
stopped coughing.
Well, someone
up there really liked it.
Two people at a movie theater
in Washington State
watching
"Captain America:
Brave New World,"
were surprised
when the theater ceiling
collapsed on them.
Surprised, but grateful.
[ Laughter ]
CBS this week premiered
the first daytime
black soap opera called
"Beyond the Gates,"
and also a crossover
white soap opera called
"How'd Those People Get
Beyond the Gates?"
[ Laughter ]
[ Chuckles ]
That was pretty good.
A woman at Lesley University
set a record
when she became the first
Division III women's
basketball player
with only one arm
to score in a game,
but she
was playing against girls,
so...
[ Laughter ]
It's the '90s.
Would you relax?
[ Laughter ]
Dunkin'--
Speaking of '90s...
Dunkin'-- Dunkin' announced
that it will stop charging
you more money
if you ask for plant-based milk
in your coffee,
but they will keep
calling you a pussy.
[ Laughter ]
Colombian authorities
arrested a man who was trying
to smuggle $10,000 worth
of cocaine
by hiding it in his wig.
$10,000 of cocaine in a wig
is more commonly
known as Silk Sonic.
[ Laughter ]
A recent study found that
nearly 50% of Gen Z is single.
Here, with some tips
on wooing potential love
interests is dating expert
Jane Wickline.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Hi. Hi, Colin.
Hi, Jane.
Thanks for being here.
So you have some
dating advice for us?
I do, yeah.
So if you want someone
to fall for you,
I've found the best thing
to do is sing them
a very romantic song.
That sounds great.
So if anyone here
is trying to romance
a beautiful woman,
feel free to use this.
This is called "I Choose You."
♪ Girl, I would lay
my life down for you ♪
♪ I would lay down
on the train tracks for you ♪
♪ I would let a train remain
on a collision course
with five people ♪
♪ I'd do nothing ♪
♪ I'd let them all
get squished rather than divert
the train to a track
with just you ♪
♪ Girl ♪
♪ And if you were already
in a train's path
and I had to pull a lever
to send the train towards
five people actively ♪
Um...
I have no idea.
That's an impossible question, girl.
But I can promise you this.
♪ Either way,
I'd be so wracked with guilt
I would kill myself
within a year ♪
♪ Which is kind of
like dying for you ♪
Thank you.
Okay.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Uh... okay. Yes.
That kind of just sounds
like the trolley's problem.
It's pretty romantic, right?
No, it's actually more of,
like, a disturbing
moral dilemma.
I feel like the song
shouldn't be about trains.
Right.
♪ Maybe I could pull the lever
halfway
so the wheels would get jammed,
and it would slow
the train down
and giving me a window
to lie down next to you, girl ♪
Is that...
Lie down next to her?
Why wouldn't you just untie her?
Well, there wouldn't be time.
The trolley's coming.
What trolley?
This is an imaginary scenario.
This is never going
to happen to you.
But what if she lives
in San Francisco?
It's riddled with trolleys.
[ Laughter ]
Jane, this song
isn't just romantic.
I mean,
don't you think you should sing
something nice about her?
Okay.
♪ Girl, you're my true love
and my best friend ♪
♪ I will keep you safe ♪
♪ There are no exceptions ♪
This is great.
♪ I'll keep you alive
by barring you from transit ♪
♪ I will make you stay
home with the baby ♪
♪ Feed you safe foods
like carrots and lettuce ♪
♪ Girl ♪
What?
To shield her from harm.
But here's the thing
about control--
It's impossible.
♪ One day, you sneak out
for a walk by the tracks,
girl ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no ♪
♪ My precautions created
the very curiosity that led you
to getting your foot stuck ♪
♪ You try to yank it free
from the tracks,
but the train is coming fast ♪
♪ I look down
and I see a lever ♪
Umm...
Oh, my God,
how is this happening again?
And who are the five people
on the other track, Colin?
Tell me, are they good?
I have no idea.
No one is asking you
to solve the trolley problem.
♪ Do I save the five? ♪
♪ I take too long to decide
and the train flattens you
like a pancake, girl ♪
♪ Squish, squish ♪
Or you could just,
like, get her a bracelet.
Dating expert Jane Wickline, everyone.
Thanks.
For "Weekend Update,"
I'm Colin Jost.
I'm Michael Che.
Good night.
♪
And do you, Angela,
take this man
to be your husband?
I do.
All right. Now, if there's
anyone who doesn't believe
that these two should be wed...
Wait.
Angela, I have something to say.
Oh, my-- Oh, my God.
Brad, what are you doing here?
What, are you, nuts, man?
This is our wedding day.
Yeah. Who is this?
It's my stupid
ex-boyfriend, Brad.
I told you,
it's over between us.
I know.
I'm marrying Greg.
No, I'm not trying
to ruin anything.
I just-- I need to say this.
I always knew you'd find
someone else,
and that he'd make you happier
than I ever could.
Brad!
It's okay.
I'm really happy for you.
And, Greg, you're a lucky man.
You got a good girl.
Congratulations, man.
Respect, man, but do you mind
if we get married now?
Of course.
I'm just here to redeem this one
thing, and then I'm out
of your life forever.
Brad--
Brad, seriously?
Wait. What is it?
It's a coupon from Angela.
It's good for one hand job,
and it expires never.
Wait, what?
Brad, I will literally
kill you.
You gave this to me,
Angela, remember?
What's he talking-- What?
Valentine's Day 2020.
I got you those Usher tickets
and a gold necklace
with matching bracelet.
And in return,
you gave me this coupon
good for one open eyes hand job
to completion.
Remember that?
I-I'm sorry.
Did you say "open eyes"?
Yeah, it's--
it's more intimate that way,
Your Honor.
I ain't no judge.
I cannot believe
you are doing this right now.
I never thought I would have
to, baby.
I thought being with you meant
handies would never go away.
But now that you're really gone,
I'd like it.
You'd like what?!
The tug job.
I'd-- I'd like it right now,
actually.
Oh, oh! No, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
young man, this is a church.
Uh, actually, it says right
here, "Good anytime, anywhere,"
Your Honor.
Dad? Say something.
Yeah. Hey, Brad, get the heck
out of here before I kick
your butt to space.
Your daughter made a vow,
sir.
Look, this is a promissory note.
No different than a US dollar.
If we can't honor that,
what do we have?
Nothing.
He's absolutely right.
It was a stupid joke gift.
It doesn't mean anything.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Okay, so what does this one
mean?
Babe, babe...
Christmas 2024.
Good for one "butt stuff."
Both eyes open, before
or after dinner.
Expires never.
Why do you have that
in your tuxedo pocket?
That's not the point.
Okay, you gave this to me.
So is this a "joke gift," too?
No, that one's real.
Well, then, so is this one.
Let the record show this is the
exact same paper, Your Honor.
Again, I am not a judge.
Can't be no judge
with the record that I have.
All right, fine. I'm sorry.
The coupons aren't real.
Now, can
we please continue the wedding?
Well, unfortunately, no.
Uh...
What?
Angela, you gave this to me
in lieu of payment for today.
It's for a nonsexual,
open eyes, foot rub.
See, I got really bad feet.
Oh, my God. Fine!
I'll just write you a check.
Oh, sure.
Like I can trust that.
Dad, he's ruining my wedding.
Father's day 2004.
Coupon for a zillion hugs
and infinity kisses.
So I guess that was a bunch
of horse crap, sweetheart?
Do you think it's
okay to just give guys coupons
and not honor them?
It's not a big deal. Okay?
Hey, Gail. Gail, back me up.
College graduation 2016,
coupon for one open eyes
"lesbian sesh"
to see if I might be a lesbian.
What's up?
Guess I'll never know.
Look, I'm sorry I'm cheap.
Okay? Now, can we please,
please just finish the wedding?
Fine.
By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you, Angela,
guilty on all charges.
Yes. Thank you, Your Honor.
Let's all boo her.
[ All booing ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
Once again, Tate McRae.
♪
♪ Lay there,
back of my mind ♪
♪ He stay there,
pops up time to time ♪
♪ Like, "Hey there," haven't
seen you in two years ♪
♪ But baby, we still breathe
the same air ♪
♪ New love and it's almost
working ♪
♪ And I never used to be this
person ♪
♪ But here I am ♪
♪ Hands on my chest and my knees
on the carpet ♪
♪ Hoping you'll stop it ♪
♪ Dear God ♪
♪ Take his kiss right out
of my brain ♪
♪ Take the pleasure
out of my pain ♪
♪ Take the way he used to say,
"I love you" ♪
♪ Dear God ♪
♪ Get his imprint out of
my bed ♪
♪ Take amazing out of our sex ♪
♪ Take away the way I still
might want to ♪
♪ Facts ♪
♪ All the memories, babe ♪
♪ I play 'em all, play 'em
all, play 'em all, play 'em all
back ♪
♪ To erase his name ♪
♪ Yeah, I'd give it all, give
it all ♪
♪ Give everything that I have ♪
♪ I pray about, pray about, pray
about, pray about that ♪
♪ Take away the way ♪
♪ I still might want to ♪
♪ Hottest ♪
♪ Thing I've ever touched,
just being honest ♪
♪ Really tryna be good,
I promise ♪
♪ That's why I'm here with my
hands on my chest ♪
♪ And my knees on the carpet ♪
♪ Hoping you'll stop it ♪
♪ Dear God ♪
♪ Take his kiss right out of
my brain ♪
♪ Take the pleasure out
of my pain ♪
♪ Take the way he used to say,
"I love you" ♪
♪ Dear God ♪
♪ Get his imprint out of
my bed ♪
♪ Take amazing out of our sex ♪
♪ Take away the way I still
might want to ♪
♪ Facts ♪
♪ All the memories, babe ♪
♪ I play 'em all, play 'em
all, play 'em all, play 'em all
back ♪
♪ To erase his name ♪
♪ I'd give it all, give it
all ♪
♪ Give everything that I have ♪
♪ All my no good thoughts ♪
♪ I pray about, pray about,
pray about, pray about that ♪
♪ Take away the way I still
might want to ♪
♪ Dear God ♪
♪ Dear God, I hope you're
listening ♪
♪ I play 'em all, play 'em
all, play 'em all, play 'em all
back ♪
♪ I pray it ain't him I'm
missing ♪
♪ Dear God, I hope you're
listening ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd give it all,
I'd give it all ♪
♪ Give it all back ♪
♪ Dear God, I hope you're
listening ♪
♪ Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God ♪
♪ I play 'em all,
I play 'em all ♪
♪ I play 'em all ♪
♪ Oh, God, oh, God ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪
Yeah, we just got into
soaking.
No, it's-- it's usually
for Mormons,
but any religion can do it.
[ Knock on door ]
Oh, I got to go.
Come in.
Hi, I'm Dr. Bashar.
Sorry about the wait out there.
It's a zoo.
No problem.
Great.
All right, let's just start
with a quick physical.
Wait.
Is your first name Zach.
Are you Zach Bashar?
Uh, Dr. Zachary Bashar, yeah.
Did you happen to go to
Emerson Middle School?
Uh, I did, yeah.
I'm sorry. Do we, uh--
Do we know each other?
Dude, it's Mikey.
Mikey Peters, we were in
eighth grade homeroom together.
Oh, wow.
Michael Peters, right.
Yeah. I do think I remember you.
Yeah. You were-- You were
very good at handball, I think.
Yeah, I was.
Hey, didn't
you go down on yourself?
Didn't you--
You went down on yourself.
Yeah. No, I heard you.
I just, uh...
It's not ringing any bells.
That's crazy,
because I remember it perfectly.
It was our first big
eighth grade graduation party.
Robbie Barton did a backflip
into the pool, and everyone
clapped, and then you stood up
on a table and said,
"You guys think that's cool?
I can go to third base
on myself.
I'm talking beef to teeth."
And I remember
that because you used
those exact words.
I've never heard that before.
"Beef to teeth."
And then you went into
the pool house and did it.
You know,
or at least you said you did.
I mean, you were in the pool
house for a while, and you were
making those crazy noises.
It was like...
[ Making guttural noises ]
Okay. Yeah, yeah,
I'm remembering now, yeah.
Robbie Barton did
a backflip and then...
That's right.
I did that thing you mentioned.
Yeah. You gave yourself
mouth.
We even had a term for it.
We called it a "me-jay."
Right. Um, all right,
why don't we just get into
this examination? Okay.
All right, you're gonna have to
open your mouth and say, "Ah."
Hey, that's what you did
in the pool house.
All right. Sure. Okay.
Um, let's just, uh, go back
to the medical history.
Do you drink alcohol?
Let's just put it this way.
Yes.
So, can you still do it?
You know,
use your slinky as a binky?
No, I can't still do it.
I was in middle school.
I was 3'9".
Could have sucked
anything on my own body.
I mean, you're not, like,
the tallest guy now.
What do you want me to say,
Michael?
You want me to say I miss it?
Of course I do.
You want me to say I'm sad
because no one will ever be
able to please me the way
I'm able to please myself?
I am. Do you think I like that
I have to take someone to dinner
25 times to get a worse version
of what I could do on my own.
It shatters me every single day.
I'm sorry, Dr. Bashar.
I wasn't trying
to antagonize you.
You were a legend, man.
We called you Mr. DIY--
Dong In Yourself.
No, no, it's-- It's okay.
I lost myself
there for a moment.
That was-- That was no way
for a doctor to behave.
All right. Sorry.
Let's see what
you're here for today.
You'd like to remove
your top two ribs?
Yes, please, sir.
Nice.
Nice, nice.
My thanks to Tate McRae,
Mike Myers...
[ Cheers and applause ]
...Lorne Michaels, the cast,
the crew.
You guys have been so nice
to me.
I appreciate it so much.
Thank you, guys.
[ Cheers and applause ]
**
♪