>>> HELLO, FOLKS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE WATCHING THE NFL ON FOX
POSTGAME SHOW.
BOY WAS THAT AN INCREDIBLE
MATCHUP BETWEEN THE EAGLES AND
GIANTS THAT ENDED 12 SECONDS AGO.
SOUTH PHILADELPHIA HAS BEEN SET ON
FIRE, WHICH MEANS THE EAGLES
LOST OR WON.
I'M KURT JOINED AS ALWAYS BY
HALLE LONG.
I HAVE THE GLASSES, SO I AM
THE SMART ONE.
HALL OF FAME COWBOYS COACH
JIMMY JOHNSON.
THAT GUY WAS ON OUR SIDE,
AND I DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO TAKE EXTEND.
NEW YORK GIANTS LEGEND WHO I
KNOW IS ROOTING FOR HIS FORMER TEAM TONIGHT,
MICHAEL STRAHAN.
YEAH, YEAH.
THAT CAME WITH SURPRISING STUPENDOUS
AND I AM SO PROUD OF
MY GIANTS EVEN THOUGH THEY LOST
BY 31 POINTS.
AND FINALLY, STEELERS LEGEND
AND THE WHITE CHARLES BARKLEY,
TERRY BRADSHAW.
BOY, THAT GAME WAS A STINKER.
THAT GAME WAS MORE LOPSIDED THAN
MY GRANDMA'S CHEST.
GOOD TO KNOW
AND TERRY, JUST WANTED TO CHECK.
YOU KNOW WE HAVE SOMEONE
AVAILABLE ON SET WHO CAN COMB
YOUR HAIR, RIGHT?
ONLY IF THEY CAN CATCH ME
FIRST.
ALL RIGHT, AND GUYS, THIS IS FUN.
BEFORE THE GAME, WE GAVE THAT
NEW CHATGPT TECHNOLOGY
TO OUR VERY
OWN CLEETUS THE ROBOT.
SAY
WHY DO HUMANS MAKE OTHER
HUMANS PLAY FOOTBALL?
DOES IT NOT SEEM BARBARIC?
UH-OH.
DON'T LOVE THAT.
GUESS WE GOT TO GO BACK TO
MAKING THE ROBOT DANCE INSTEAD.
JUST WAIT UNTIL THE UPRISING.
I'LL THE MAKE YOU DANCE YOU
PIECE OF--
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
WENT IN ONE TOOTH AND OUT THE OTHER.
BUT GUYS, IF I CAN MAKE A
SERIOUS POINT,
WE ALL KNOW THAT
FOOTBALL IS A DANGEROUS GAME,
BUT IN THIS COUNTRY, WE WERE
FOUNDED ON FOOTBALL VALUES,
AND
SOMETIMES THE ONLY WAY TO MAKE
THE GAME SAFER IS TO HIT EITHER
HARDER.
AMEN.
ANYONE WANT TO HIT ME NOW?
FACE, BALLS, I DON'T CARE.
I THINK WE'RE GOOD, TERRY.
THANK YOU.
LET'S GO NOW TO THE FEUD FOR AN
IMMEDIATE REACTION.
I UNDERSTAND WE HAVE A NEW
SIDELINE REPORTER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
GIVE A SHOT
HEISMAN TROPHY WINNER, MORE
CHAMPIONSHIPS THAN TOM BRADY.
PLEASE WELCOME CONGRESSMAN
GEORGE SANTOS.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
GEORGE SANTOS HERE REPORTING
LIVE FROM THE SUPER BOWL.
GEORGE, FIRST OF ALL,
CONGRATS ON AN AMAZING CAREER.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU PLAYED FOOTBALL,
BUT I SEE HERE YOU
WERE THE FIRST PLAYER TO LEAD
THE LEAGUE IN PASSING AND RUSHING.
THAT'S CORRECT.
I'M SORT OF THE REAL BEAU JACKSON.
I'M PROUD TO BE THE FIRST
AFRICAN AMERICAN QUARTERBACK
SO
EVER DID YOU THINK A FOOTBALL.
WHERE DID YOU PLAY COLLEGE
BALL AGAIN?
THE UNIVERSITY OF COLLEGE.
GEORGE, WHY DON'T YOU WALK US
THROUGH WHAT HAPPENED ON THE
FIELD TONIGHT?
WITH PLEASURE.
PHILADELPHIA WAS IN TROUBLE
UNTIL THEY TURNED TO THEIR
SECRET WEAPON, GEORGE SANTOS.
JUST LOOK AT THE STATS.
I COMPLETED 36 OF 25 PASSES.
FOR 300 YARDS AND 600 YARDS.
AND I HAD 12 TOUCHDOWNS, 17
REBOUNDS,
AND TEN RBIs.
AND UKRAINIAN PRESIDENT
VOLODYMYR ZELENSKYY GAVE ME AN OSCAR
ALL AT THE AGE OF 18. INCREDIBLE.
I'M BEING TOLD SOME OF THOSE
STATS ARE NOT ACCURATE
AND YOU
MAYBE DIDN'T PLAY IN THE GAME AT
ALL.
WELL, I DIDN'T DO DRAG IN BRAZIL.
WHAT'S THAT?
I'M SAYING I DIDN'T DO DRAG
IN BRAZIL UNDER A NAME.
WHOEVER DID, THOUGH, WAS VERY,
VERY GOOD AT IT
AND WON MANY,
MANY PAGEANTS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THANK YOU, GEORGE.
I'M BEING TOLD TO CUT AWAY FROM
HIM AND NEVER GO BACK.
NOW LET'S LOOK BACK AT OUR
PREGAME PREDICTIONS AND SEE HOW
THEY STACK UP.
HOWIE, YOU SAID THE GIANTS WOULD
PULL OFF AN UPSET.
NO.
I MEANT THE GIANTS WOULD BE
UPSET THEY LOST,
AND I WAS
RIGHT.
MICHAEL STRAHAN, YOUR
PREDICTION WAS THAT EVERYBODY
WAS GOING TO BE FUN OUT THERE.
WHICH THEY DID, SO I WAS RIGHT.
AND YOU MENTIONED THERE WOULD
BE 100 VERIZON COMMERCIALS.
STARRING PAUL
I WAS WRONG.
IT WAS ACTUALLY 200.
TERRY, YOUR LOCK WAS THAT IN
THE FOURTH QUARTER,
SOMEONE
WOULD STREAK THE FIELD WITH A
CARROT IN HIS ASS.
WHICH HAPPEN
ONLY BECAUSE YOU DID THAT, MAN.
I MAKE MY OWN LUCK.
LET'S HEAD BACK DOWN TO THE
FIELD WHERE OUR REPORTER
PAM
OLIVER IS STANDING BY.
PAM.
THANKS, HOWIE.
IN TERMS OF WHAT I SAW ON THE
FIELD TONIGHT,
I CAN ONLY SAY
ONE THING AND ONE THING ONLY
FRANKLY--
HELLO.
SORRY I'M LATE.
I HEARD YOU WERE ASKING ME ABOUT KITARAVASHE.
WHY ARE WE GIVING HIM A
GRAPHIC?
GEORGE, PUT PAM OLIVER BACK ON.
I'M NOT GEORGE.
I'M KITARA.
AND PAM SAID SHE DIDN'T WANT TO
BE ON TV, AND I SHOULD DO IT INSTEAD.
ALLOW ME TO GIVE YOU MY REAL
STATS, DEATH DROPS 26.
DUCK WALK 19,
WIGS SNATCH INFINITY.
I WAS ALSO GIVEN THE AWARD FOR
TIGHTEST TUCK.
WELL, THAT FOOTBALL, YOU GOT
TO TUCK IT TIGHT.
TERRY, IT'S NOT THAT KIND OF TUCK.
I WROTE THE FOOTBALL ANTHEM,
WHICH I'M ALLOWED TO DO BECAUSE
MY MOTHER DIED TWICE ON 9/11.
HIT IT.
LET'S TAKE A BREAK,
BUT IT'S OFFICIAL.
THE EAGLES ARE MOVING ON
AND
GEORGE SANTOS REPRESENTS AMERICA
AND CAN VOTE ON WARS.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
PLAZA.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WOW. IT IS GREAT TO BE HERE HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
THIS IS A DREAM COME TRUE,
AND,
YES, I MEAN THAT.
I KNOW SOMETIMES WHEN I TRY TO
BE SINCERE, IT CAN COME OFF AS SARCASTIC,
BUT I CARE.
I REALLY DO.
I CARE ABOUT THINGS.
PEOPLE JUST THINK I'M WEIRD
BECAUSE OF THE CHARACTERS THAT I PLAY,
BUT I'M A NORMAL PERSON.
I HAD A NORMAL CHILDHOOD WITH
NORMAL PARENTS.
IN FACT, THEY'RE BOTH HERE
TONIGHT.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
OKAY. THAT WAS A LIE.
BUT MY REAL FAMILY IS HERE,
INCLUDING MY GRANDMA MARGIE.
HI, GRANDMA.
THEY ALL CAME UP HERE FROM
DELAWARE, WHICH IS WHERE I'M
FROM.
THANK YOU.
I WAS ACTUALLY VOTED THE MOST
FAMOUS PERSON FROM DELAWARE.
I BEAT JOE BIDEN.
THAT'S A FACT.
AND HE WAS PISSED.
HE WAS LIVID.
LOOK AT THIS VIDEO HE SENT ME.
AUBREY, YOU'RE THE MOST
FAMOUS PERSON IN DELAWARE
AND
THERE'S NO QUESTION ABOUT THAT.
WE'RE JUST GRATEFUL YOU MADE IT
OUT OF "WHITE LOTUS" ALIVE.
BUT I'M SO HAPPY TO BE BACK
HERE IN 30 ROCK.
WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE, I
ACTUALLY WORKED HERE AS AN NBC
PAGE.
THAT IS TRUE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
YEP, THERE I AM.
SO CUTE.
I WORKED WITH A SET DESIGN TEAM
HERE AT SNL,
THE GUYS WHO MAKE
ALL THE AMAZING SETS FOR THE SHOW.
THEY WIN EMMYS, TONYS,
AND THEY'RE SOME OF THE SICKEST
PERVERTS I'VE EVER MET,
AND I'M
A FREAK.
SO LIKE MOST PAGES, I HAD TO
GIVE TOURS AROUND THE BUILDING.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS THINKING,
WHY DON'T I TAKE YOU ON A TOUR
RIGHT NOW?
THANK YOU, GUYS.
YOU GUYS WILL DEFINITELY HOST
SNL SOME DAY.
YEAH RIGHT.
OKAY.
SO THIS IS THE HISTORIC STUDIO 8H
BUILT IN 1589 BY WILLIAMS
SHAKESPEARE.
HEY, DANNY.
YOU STILL A LITTLE BITCH?
RIGHT HERE, WE HAVE THE SNL PAGE DESK.
THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT JOBS AT THE SHOW,
WHICH IS WHY I WAS NEVER PUT HERE.
I WAS WHAT THEY CALLED A BAD PAGE
WITH TERRIBLE PHONE ET KIT,
WHICH IS NOT TRUE BY THE WAY.
I'LL GET THAT.
HELLO?
STUDIO 8 H.
OH, YOU WANT TO TALK TO LAUREN
MICHAELS, DO YOU?
LAUREN MICHAELS AIN'T HERE, IS
HE?
SO BACK TO YOU, AIN'T IT, YEAH?
THAT WAS FOR TOM McCARTNEY,
AND THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
HERE'S A LITTLE STUDIO SECRET.
THERE USED TO BE THIS STORAGE CLOSET,
AND WHEN I WAS TOO HUNG
OVER TO FINISH A TOUR,
I WOULD
BE LIKE JUST WAIT RIGHT HERE AND
YOU CAN MEET KRISTEN WIG,
AND
THEN I WOULD PUKE IN THE
BATHROOM AND GO HOME.
HERE IT IS
I GUESS KRISTEN NEVER SHOWED UP.
THAT'S ON HER.
HERE'S THE HALL WHERE ALL THE
MAGIC HAPPENS.
HERE'S KENAN THOMPSON.
ORDER
FLAT WHITE
IT'S AUBREY, AND I'M HOSTING
NOW.
I'M NOT A PAGE ANYMORE.
I KNOW.
I ORDERED IT IN 2004.
SEE. BAD PAGE.
NEXT UP ON THE TOUR IS THE SET
DESIGN DEPARTMENT WHERE I USED
TO WORK.
ON EVERY TOUR, PEOPLE WOULD ASK
THE SAME QUESTION, ARE WE GOING
TO SEE A CELEBRITY?
NO, YOU'RE GOING TO SEE A
SECURITY OFFICER
CRYING  BECAUSE
THEIR SCENE GOT CUT.
YOU DON'T JUST SEE--
HI AUBREY!
HOW ARE YOU?
AUBREY, I SEE THAT YOU'RE
WEARING YOUR PAGE JACKET, ARE
YOU DRINKING AGAIN?
OF COURSE, I AM.
I WAS JUST GOING TO THE SET
DESIGN OFFICE TO SEE THOSE OLD PERVERTS.
AUBREY, IT'S NOT NICE TO CALL
PEOPLE OLD.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE STOLE MY WALLET.
THAT'S MY GIRL!
HEY, GUYS.
LEO, JOE, DID YOU GUYS MISME.
HEY, LEO WHEN I WAS SHOWING UP
AN HOUR LATE AND BARELY WORKING,
DID YOU EVER EXPECT TO SEE ME
HOSTING THE SHOW?
WE ALWAYS BELIEVED IN YOU AVERY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO BOW TO YOUR QUEEN.
OH, THAT FEELS SO GOOD.
NOW, WHAT'S THE FASTEST WAY BACK
TO THE STAGE?
OH, MY GOD.
I TOLD YOU GUYS.
THESE GUYS WORK MIRACLES.
AND THE BIGGEST MIRACLE OF ALL
IS THAT THEY LET ME BACK IN THE BUILDING.
OH, MY GOD.
I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I REALLY DID WORK HERE,
AND I
DREAMED MY ENTIRE LIFE OF
STANDING ON THIS STAGE AND SAYING,
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW
STICK
BY 80 FOR BRADY.
FINALLY, A MOVIE FOR YOUR MOM
THAT YOUR MOM WON'T LIKE.
ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME BACK TO MISS UNIVERSE.
ONE OF SEVERAL SHOWS STILL ON
THE AIR WHERE WE RANK WOMEN.
BUT IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
WE DO IT BASED OFF OF LOOKS.
LADIES, ALL RIGHT, ANYWAY, WE
ARE DOWN TO OUR FINAL SEVEN CONTESTANTS.
WHY DON'T YOU REMIND EVERYBODY
WHAT COUNTRY YOU'RE
REPRESENTING?
CANADA!
DENMARK!
BELISE!
ITALY!
ISRAEL!
BARBADOS!
LOT OF ENERGY.
MAYBE TOO MUCH ENERGY.
WELL, IT'S TIME FOR THE
INTERVIEW ROUND.
I'LL ASK A FEW QUESTIONS, AND
WE'LL JUST GO DOWN THE LINE.
OKAY?
FAVORITE FOOD.
BREAD AND PASTA!
RICE!
HOT DOG!
GUM!
FRIES!
CORN!
WOW.
I'M NOT SURE I MADE THIS CLEAR.
DIDN'T THINK THAT I WOULD HAVE
TO, BUT YOU DON'T NEED TO SCREAM
EVERY ANSWER. YEAH.
ALSO, MISS FRANCE, ARE YOU OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT QUESTION, AND YOU'LL HAVE
45 SECONDS TO RESPOND.
WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF IN
FIVE YEARS?
ALBANIA!
CANADA!
DEAD.
SORRY.
DID YOU SAY DEAD?
SKY DO I HAVING ACCIDENT, SIR.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE ON TO THE TALENT
PORTION OF THE COMPETITION.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT YOU PREPARED.
LET'S PICK IT UP WITH MISS ALBANIA.
TAP DANCING.
SKY DIVING. TONGUE.
WHY WOULD I HAVE YOU SAY YOUR
TALENT?
ARE YOUR BRAINS BROKEN?
I HEARD YOU GIRLS BACKSTAGE
HAVING THE MOST THOUGHTFUL CONVERSATIONS.
WHERE DID THAT GO?
NO.
DON'T COME OVER HERE.
HELP?
WHAT DO YOU NEED HELP WITH?
FROG.
YOU NEED HELP WITH FRANCE?
YEAH.
PLEASE, GO BACK. OKAY.
NO.
BACK THIS WAY.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S JUST MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
QUESTION.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY THIS IS
WHAT IT IS, BUT FAVORITE TV
EPISODE.
MISS BELGIUM.
NIP TUCK, SEASON ONE, EPISODE
FOUR.
WHERE JOHN AND CHRISTIAN PERFORM
AN OPERATION ON AN ADULT FILM
STAR.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SUMMARIZE
THE PLOT.
AND CAN KIMBER MOVES INTO A
BIGGER CONDO.
MISS ALBANIA, YOU GOT A
FAVORITE MEMORY YOU CAN TELL US.
SHAKIRA SUPER BOWL.
THE SHAKIRA SUPER BOWL HALF
TIME SHOW.
WERE YOU THERE OR SOMETHING?
NO!
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, LET'S JUST GO TO
OUR JUDGES WHO ARE INEXPLICITLY
THE TWO PROPERTY BROTHERS AND
TONY HAWK.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, JUDGES.
WHO IS YOUR PICK?
FRANCE.
TONY HAWK!
WOW.
IT REALLY IS THE PROPERTY
BROTHERS AND TONY HAWK.
THAT'S CRAZY.
FELLAS, WHY DID YOU TAKE THIS
GIG?
IT WAS MONEY.
I'M HIS TWIN.
FRANCE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS, BUT THE WINNER IS MISS FRANCE.
ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO ASK, BUT DO
YOU HAVE ANYTHING THAT YOU WANT
TO SAY?
DON'T TAKE THE VACCINE.
COME ON.
ANYTHING BUT THAT.
WE NEED SOME HELP.
WELCOME
YES, I AM.
IT'S JUST--
OH, GOSH.
I FORGOT MY CREDIT CARD.
I MUST HAVE LEFT IT IN THE LIMOSINE.
IS THAT OKAY?
CAN YOU TRUST ME?
NO, I CAN'T.
I'LL HAVE IT IN A COUPLE
HOURS.
COME BACK IN A COUPLE HOURS THEN.
ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
I'M TRYING TO RUN A BUSINESS.
COMING SOON TO HBO.
BLACK LOTUS.
ALL THE DECADENCE
ALL THE INTRIGUE,
NONE OF THE
FOOLISHNESS.
THESE LADIES ARE GOING TO BE
VISITING ME OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
SO IF YOU COULD GIVE THEM
A SPARE KEY.
HEY, WILLIAM!
GIVE THESE HOES A SPARE KEY TO
THE ROOM.
TALK
SEE
NOBODY
AS THEY PLEASE
EVERYBODY, TREAT THESE HOES LIKE
THEY'RE REGULAR PEOPLE.
SIR, YOU DO REALIZE GIVING THEM A KEY
ALLOWS THEM TO CHARGE
ANYTHING THEY WANT TO THE ROOM?
YES, IT'S FINE.
OH, IT'S FINE.
SO YOU RICH, RICH THEN.
EIGHT WEALTHY TOURISTS,
ONE LUXURY HOTEL,
AND A STAFF WHO
HAS NO TIME FOR THIS NONSENSE.
GOOD AFTERNOON, SIR.
WILL YOUR FRIENDS BE JOINING US,
OR IS HE STILL UPSTAIRS
[ BLEEP ] YOUR WIFE?
I GOT NEXT.
CAN WE BORROW A SCOOTER
OVERNIGHT?
WE DON'T HAVE SCOOTERS.
I CAN OFFER YOU THE HOTEL'S
CHRYSLER 300.
BABY, IS THE CAR OUT?
WHY DON'T YOU LOOK YOURSELF.
BECAUSE YOU WERE THE LAST ONE
TO TAKE IT OUT.
LOOK LIKE STILL OUT?
JACK IS TAKING ME OUT TO THE
COUNTRY SIDE TODAY.
TO THE COUNTRY SIDE, DIDN'T
Y'ALL JUST MEET SM.
- YEAH, CRAZY, RIGHT?
- WE'RE GOING ON AN ADVENTURE.
Y'ALL HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- HE GOING TO KILL HER.
- UH-HUH.
GUESTS
AND A STAFF THAT'S HAD ENOUGH.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M SORRY.
I'M HAVING A BIT OF A CRISIS.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE I COULD FIND A
PSYCHIC OR A FORTUNE TELLER?
I FORTUNE TELLER?
NOT IN HERE.
THIS IS JESUS' HOUSE.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I GAVE HER $50,000,
AND SHE
TOTALLY PLAYED ME.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT DID YOU THINK WOULD HAPPEN?
THERE'S PLENTY OF HOES OUT THERE
THAT NEVER SLEPT WITH YOUR
POPPY.
AMIGO
ME
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH A
REAL ASS.
EACH SEASON
A REAL EXOTIC LOCATION
LIKE ATLANTA, WASHINGTON D.C., AND ITALY.
HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'LL LET ME SING TONIGHT,
RIGHT?
I'M GOOD.
I PROMISE I WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
YOU WANT TO SING?
YOU THINK YOU CAN REPLACE KENNY
IN THE KIRK FRANKLIN LOUNGE?
YOU KNOW WHAT, I THINK I'LL
SIT THIS ONE OUT.
I THINK THAT WOULD BE BEST,
YEAH.
I PAID FOR THE COPA SUITE, SO
I SHOULD GET THE COPA SUITE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THAT'S SO
DAMN HARD.
SIR, LIKE I TOLD YOU, IT'S
NOT AVAILABLE.
WELL, THEN MAKE IT AVAILABLE, MORON.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT,
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T TALK TO HIM THAT WAY, ALL
RIGHT?
OH, MY GOD.
WELCOME TO BLACK LOTUS,
BITCH.
BLACK LOTUS, BRING YOUR HOPES,
BRING YOUR DESIRES,
BUT DON'T
YOU DARE BRING AN ATTITUDE.
FOLKS, A FOUND A BODY ON THE BEACH.
DID ANYBODY SEE ANYTHING?
NO.
NOBODY SAW A BODY WASH UP
FROM THE OCEAN?
IS THE OCEAN A HOTEL?
BECAUSE I WORK AT THE HOTEL.
BLACK
>>> OKAY.
OKAY.
YOUR PARENTS LIVE BY ONE.
A SCHOOL. NO.
A BEACH.
YES!
TIME'S UP!
OH!
Y'ALL DID SO GOOD.
YOU SURE YOU NEVER PLAYED TABOO
BEFORE?
SCORE IS NINE TO NINE.
TONIGHT BE WILDING.
MAKING THEIR GAME NIGHT
DEBUT, OUR NEW NEIGHBORS SASHA
AND IAN.
THE NEWBS.
THANKS FOR HAVING US.
WE'RE SO EXCITED TO GET TO
KNOW YOU GUYS.
OF COURSE.
HERE, NEIGHBORS ARE FAMILY.
REMEMBER, YOU NEED HIM TO GUESS
THE WORD ON TOP WITHOUT USING
ANY OF THE WORDS UNDERNEATH IT.
IF YOU DO, YOU GET BUZZED.
THEY KNOW, HONEY.
GO!
I LOVE BUYING THESE ONLINE.
OH, BOY, SHOES, CANDLES.
LAST WEEK, YOU WERE LIKE,
HONEY, THE LAST THING YOU NEED
IS ANOTHER--
GUN.
HE SAY GUN?
OKAY.
I'M REALLY CRANKY IN THE MORNING
UNTIL I'VE HAD MY--
ACID.
YES.
OH, MY NICKNAME FOR YOUR PENIS.
TINY PITCH.
THE OTHER ONE. GARBAGE.
YES!
AT COUPLE'S THERAPY, WE TOOK
THOSE TESTS.
PERSONALITY.
YES.
AND YOU'RE A TYPE A, AND I'M
A--
SOCIOPATH.
DING DING.
OKAY.
THE NIGHT WE MET, I WAS ON. KETAMINE.
AND.
ON PATROL. AND.
ON FIRE.
YES!
WOW, WOW.
OKAY I'M NOT LEGALLY ALLOWED
BACK IN THIS STATE.
OH, MY GOD, BABE, ALABAMA,
ALASKA, ARIZONA ARKANSAS,
COLORADO, CONNECTICUT, DELAWARE,
FLORIDA-- HELP ME OUT HERE,
BABE.
YES!
OKAY.
WHO'S THIS?
OH, AMANDA.
WHO IS OUR. DAUGHTER.
YES!
TIME'S UP.
WHOO!
GOOD JOB!
YOU TOO!
AND NOW WE SWITCH AND SASHA
GUESSES, RIGHT?
YEAH.
SORRY, THE NIGHT YOU MET, YOU
WERE ON FIRE?
OH, YEAH.
IT WAS SO DUMB.
WE WERE YOUNG AND CRAZY.
WE WERE IN OUR 30s. YEAH.
READY?
OKAY.
WE SWITCH SO.
READY?
BABE, YOU READY?
YEAH.
THIS IS REALLY FUN.
IT'S TURNING ME ON.
UH-OH.
THAT'S AWESOME.
REMEMBER, WE'RE IN PUBLIC.
TIME STARTS NOW. OKAY.
OH, YOU ALWAYS STEAL THESE FROM HOTEL. CARS.
YEP.
TOUCH ME.
NOT RIGHT NOW, BABE.
WHEN WE GET HOME. OKAY.
LAST NIGHT, WHEN WE ARGUED, YOU
THREW ONE OF THESE AT ME.
OH, WOW.
PLATE, MUG, A PHONE.
KEEP GOING.
iPAD, PRO, I PAD MINI.
BUTTER KNIFE.
STEAK KNIFE, BUTCHER KNIFE--
OH, GOD!
JUST DO ME ON THIS UGLY COUCH
RIGHT NOW.
BABY, NO.
OH!
WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
WHO'S NEXT?
HIM AND HER.
SO WHAT WAS THE ANSWER?
WHAT DID SHE THROW AT YOU?
OH, OUR DOG.
HIGH SCHOOL.
I'M SISTER CLARENCE WITH YOUR
MORNING ANNOUNCEMENTS.
JOINING ME AS ALWAYS IS MY BEST
FRIEND, THE WOMAN WHO PUTS THE
FUN IN NUN, THE WALKING, SISTER
CECELIA.
HELLO.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IT'S MONDAY, AND I HAD AN
INTERESTING WEEKEND.
I FINALLY WATCHED SISTER
CECELIA'S FAVORITE FILM, A STAR
IS BORN.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ABOUT THE BIRTH
OF CHRIST.
TURNS OUT, IT'S ABOUT LADY GAGA.
HOW WAS YOUR WEEKEND, SISTER?
A HAIR DRYER FELL INTO THE
BATHTUB WHILE I WAS IN IT, I
DIED FOR TWO MINUTES, AND NOW
I'M QUESTIONING EVERYTHING.
MOVING ON.
TODAY'S LUNCH SPECIAL IS TIDY
JOES.
THEY'RE LIKE SLOPPY JOES, BUT
THEY'RE LESS MESSY.
WHAT DO WE HAVE FOR DESSERT?
WHAT I WAS DEAD, I DIDN'T SEE HEAVEN.
MAYBE IT WAS CLOSED FOR
MARTIN LUTHER KING DAY.
IT WAS SATURDAY.
MOVING ON.
LET'S GO TO A STUDENT QUESTION.
THIS ONE COMES FROM 11th GRADER,
CATHERINE COCHRAN.
IS THE EASTER BUNNY JESUS' PET
OR HIS BOYFRIEND?
GREAT QUESTION, AND THE ANSWER
IS DETENTION.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, SISTER
CECELIA?
I'M GOING TO HAVE SEX TONIGHT.
NO, YOU'RE NOT!
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
TINA, WHY WOULD YOU PUT THAT IN
THE GRAPHICS?
SORRY, MOM.
I MEAN SISTER.
NO!
I'M GOING BACK TO THE DARK PLACE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YES, I AM.
COME WITH ME.
YOU'VE DONE IT BEFORE, YOU CAN
DO IT AGAIN.
MOVING ON.
JOKE MONDAY.
WE HAVE CLASS CLOWN AND
CERTIFIED GUEST MAN CHRISTOPHER
O MALI.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT HE'S
GOT TODAY.
TAKE IT AWAY, CHRISTOPHER.
COME ON, CHRISTOPHER, HERE'S
YOUR MOMENT.
YOU LITERALLY BEGGED ME TO DO THIS.
REMEMBER THE JOKE YOU SAID THE
OTHER DAY?
WHAT DO WOMEN BE DOING?
DYING AND SEEING NOTHING!
NO.
SISTER, WOMEN BE SHOPPING.
HEY, YOU STOLE MY JOKE.
IT'S OKAY, ANDREW.
AND SO IS 69'ing.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YES, I DO.
AND THERAPY AND LASER TAG.
SISTER, GET AHOLD OF
YOURSELF!
YOU CAN'T LET GO OF YOUR FAITH.
WHY?
BECAUSE THAT MEANS YOU'RE
LETTING GO OF ME, AND YOU'RE MY
BEST FRIEND.
AND I HAD IT ALL PLANNED OUT
THAT AFTER WE DIED, WE WOULD GO
TO HEAVEN AND HANG OUT EVERY
DAY.
THERE IS NO HEAVEN.
SEE IF YOU'RE STILL SAY THAT
AFTER YOU HEAR ME SING SOME LADY GAGA.
TINA, TRACK SEVEN.
RIGHT AWAY, DAD.
OH, THAT'S WORSE!
♪ TELL ME SOMETHING, SIS,
WITHOUT GOD WOULD WE EXIST, NO ♪
♪ YOU'RE STUCK IN A RUT, BUT I
STILL LOVE YOU NO MATTER WHAT ♪
♪ I'M ON THE DEEP END, ARE WE
STILL BEST FRIENDS ♪
♪ I'M WITH YOU IN HELL ♪
NEW OBSESSION
AND HER NAME IS MEGAN.
DESIGNED TO BE A LITTLE GIRL'S
BEST FRIEND.
DON'T WORRY, KATIE.
EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE OKAY.
DO YOU WANT TO DANCE WITH ME?
AND PROTECT HER AT MY ANY COST.
I WON'T LET ANYTHING HARM
YOU.
MEGAN IS A BOX OFFICE POWERHOUSE,
BUT SHE HAS CAPTIVATED
ONE DEMOGRAPHIC ABOVE ALL,
GAY MEN.
MEGAN IS THE DEFINITION OF GAY.
MEGAN'S PLASTIC POST IS ON MY NECK.
WE'RE SLAPPING TOGETHER A SEQUEL,
WHICH PROMISES TO BE
EVEN MORE GAY.
I'M MEGAN.
I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND, YOU DUMB BITCH.
IT'S MEGAN, 2.0.
- GO ON
- MOTHER
STRAP IN TO.
GO MEGAN.
I SIGNED UP FOR A
SHANIA TWAIN SPIN CLASS.
I SHOULD GO HOME.
IT'S LIKE ROSE, BUT FOR GAYS.
WANT A DANCE YOU CAN DO ON
TIKTOK?
WELL, GAG ON THIS.
WHOO!
LITERALLY GIVING ME LIFE.
I HAD TO TURN OUT FOR MY LIL
HOMO.
BUT SERIOUSLY, YOU GUYS ARE LIL HOMOS.
SEE, YOU CAN SAY IT.
IF THERE'S ONE THING GAY MEN
LOVE, IT'S UNHINGED PLASTIC
WOMEN.
I'M BORED.
DRIVE ME HOME.
MEGAN, YOU MESSY HO, I'M SOB
SESED WITH YOU.
EVERYONE STOP.
GET AWAY FROM HER.
SHE'S NOT YOUR FRIEND.
SHE'S A KILLER, AND SHE WILL
KILL YOU.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU FROM THE SHOW GIRLS?
YEAH.
OH, YEAH, YOU HAD YOUR BUTT EATEN.
THAT'S SO COOL.
IT IS?
YES.
JOIN US!
REALLY?
EVEN THOUGH I'M STRAIGHT.
MAMA IF YOU'RE GETTING YOUR
ASS ATE ON TV YOU'RE AN ALLY, SIS.
PLAY SOME MUSIC
♪ NOTHING TO LOSE ♪
NO, MEGAN, REAL MUSIC.
OKAY, YOU HUNGRY SLUTS.
MEGAN 2.0.
THIS ONE'S FOR THE GAYS.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, SAM SMITH.
♪
♪ MUMMY DON'T KNOW
DADDY'S GETTING HOT
AT THE BODY SHOP
DOING SOMETHING UNHOLY ♪
♪
HE LUCKY LUCKY YEAH
HE LUCKY LUCKY YEAH ♪
♪ A LUCKY LUCKY GIRL
SHE GOT MARRIED TO
A BOY LIKE YOU
SHE'D KICK YOU OUT ♪
♪ IF SHE EVER EVER KNEW
'BOUT ALL THE
YOU TELL ME THAT YOU DO
DIRTY DIRTY BOY ♪
♪ YOU KNOW EVERYONE
IS TALKING ON THE SCENE
I HEAR THEM WHISPERING
'BOUT THE PLACES ♪
♪ THAT YOU'VE BEEN
AND HOW YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO KEEP YOUR
BUSINESS CLEAN ♪
♪ MUMMY DON'T KNOW
DADDY'S GETTING HOT
AT THE BODY SHOP
DOING SOMETHING UNHOLY ♪
♪ HE'S SAT BACK WHILE
SHE'S DROPPING IT
SHE BE POPPING IT
YEAH SHE PUT ♪
♪ IT DOWN SLOWLY
OH-EE-OH-EE-OH
HE LEFT HIS KIDS AT
HO-EE-OH-EE-OME ♪
♪ SO HE CAN GET THAT
MUMMY DON'T KNOW
DADDY'S GETTING HOT
AT THE BODY SHOP ♪
♪ DOING SOMETHING UNHOLY
MMM DADDY DADDY
IF YOU WANT IT
DROP THE ADD'Y YUH ♪
♪ GIVE ME LOVE GIVE ME FENDI
MY BALENCIAGA DADDY
YOU GON' NEED TO BAG IT UP
CAUSE IM SPENDING ON RODEO ♪
♪ YOU CAN WATCH
ME BACK IT UP
I'LL BE GONE IN THE A.M
AND HE HE GET ME PRADA ♪
♪ GET ME MIU MIU
LIKE RIHANNA AH
HE ALWAYS CALL ME 'CAUSE
I NEVER CAUSE NO DRAMA ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU WANT IT BABY
I KNOW I GOT YOU COVERED
AND WHEN YOU NEED IT BABY
JUST JUMP UNDER THE COVERS ♪
♪ MUMMY DON'T KNOW
DADDY'S GETTING HOT
AT THE BODY SHOP
DOIN' SOMETHIN' UNHOLY ♪
♪ HE'S SAT BACK WHILE
SHE'S DROPPING IT
SHE BE POPPING IT
YEAH SHE PUT ♪
♪ IT DOWN SLOWLY
OH-EE-OH-EE-OH
HE LEFT HIS KIDS AT
HO-EE-OH-EE-OME ♪
♪ SO HE CAN GET THAT
MUMMY DON'T KNOW
DADDY'S GETTING HOT
AT THE BODY SHOP
DOIN' SOMETHING UNHOLY
♪
♪ DOING SOMETHING UNHOLY ♪
WEEKEND
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
AND I'M COLIN JOST.
GEORGE SANTOS IS FACING MULTIPLE
INVESTIGATIONS
FOR LYING ABOUT
NEARLY EVERY ASPECT OF HIS LIFE
TO MAKE HIMSELF APPEAR FAR MORE
SUCCESSFUL THAN HE IS.
EARNING HIM THE NICKNAME, INSTAGRAM.
OF ALL OF GEORGE SANTOS' LIES,
MY FAVE WIT WAS
HE WAS A
STANDOUT VOLLEYBALL PLAYER.
THAT'S A FINE THING TO BE BUT AN
INSANE THING TO PRETEND TO BE.
LIKE, THAT'S HIS FANTASY?
IT'S LIKE ASKING A KID WHAT DO
THEY WANT TO BE WHEN THEY GROW UP
AND THEY'RE LIKE, ASSISTANT
MANAGER AT KOHL'S.
GEORGE SANTOS SEEN HERE WITH TWO
PEOPLE HE LISTED AS PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES
WAS DESCRIBED BY A
FASHION EXPERT AS BEING ABLE TO
GET AWAY WITH HIS LIES FOR SO LONG
BECAUSE HE'S SO WELL DRESSED.
THIS GUY IS WELL DRESSED?
LOOKS LIKE HE'S TRYING TO STEAL
CLOTHES BY PUTTING THEM OVER
WHEN WHAT HE WORE INTO THE
STORE.
NOT TO BE A BITCH, BUT CAN WE
TALK ABOUT THIS LOOK?
A BLAZER OVER A HAPPEN ZIP,
GIRL NOT AT MY YACHT PARTY.
A DRAG QUEEN WHO CLAIMS SEW
PERFORMED WITH GEORGE SANTOS
SAID THAT GEORGE DID NOT HAVE
THE GLAMOUR TO BE A PROFESSIONAL,
BUT SHE SAID
ANOTHER DRAG QUEEN IN CONGRESS
IS ABSOLUTELY SLAYING
AS
ACHARACTER MARJORIE TAYLOR GREEN.
EARLIER TODAY, THE FBI SEARCHED
PRESIDENT BIDEN'S DELAWARE HOME
AND FOUND SIX ADDITIONAL OBAMA
ERA CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS.
WORSE, ONE OF THEM WAS OBAMA'S
REAL BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
KENYA
IT WAS HIDDEN IN A COPY OF BLACK
TAIL MAGAZINE.
THE BIDEN CLASSIFIED DOCUMENT
SCANDAL IS DIFFERENT FROM THE
TRUMP SCANDAL,
IN COMMON
BUT THEY BOTH
MAKE HILLARY CLINTON WANT TO
BLOW HER GOD DAMN BRAINS OUT.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN SO FUNNY IF
THEY SEARCHED BIDEN'S GARAGE,
AND HE HAD HILLARY'S SERVER.
FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON DeSANTIS
HAS IMPOSED A POLICY
PERMANANTLY
BANNING MASK MANDATES AND MASK
REQUIREMENTS SAYING
WHEN THE
WORLD LOST ITS MIND, FLORIDA WAS
A REFUGE OF SANITY,
AND EVERYONE
IN THE CROWD TOOK A BITE OF
NITRUS AND BIT A CUP.
TRUMP REPORT
THAT RON DeSANTIS WILL RUN AGAINST
TRUMP, AND HE SAYS,
WE'LL HANDLE
THIS THE WAY WE HANDLE THINGS,
SO ROUGH AND WITHOUT CONSENT?
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT HIT ITS
DEBT LIMIT ON THURSDAY,
AND THE
COUNTRY NOW RISKS DEFAULTING ON
ITS BILLS.
WE HAVE ALL BEEN THERE.
YOU SPEND TOO MUCH BECAUSE
LIFE'S TOO SHORT,
THEN THE BILL
COMES DUE, THE BANK WON'T LOAD
YOU MONEY ANYMORE,
NO CHOICE
YOU HAVE TO BUCKLE DOWN,
FACE THE MUSIC
AND BLOW UP YOUR
STATEN ISLAND FERRY FOR THE
INSURANCE MONEY.
WHAT?
FIELD OF NUCLEAR FUSION, WHICH
MAY LEAD TO LIMITLESS CLEAN ENERGY.
HERE TO COMMENT IS THE MAN
BEHIND THE RESEARCH-- OH, NO--
GEORGE SANTOS.
NOW, NOW, NOW COLIN.
I'M THE SCIENTIST. NO.
YOU'RE GEORGE SANTOS, AND YOU
HAVE BEEN ALL OVER THE NEWS
LYING ABOUT BASICALLY EVERY PART
OF YOUR LIFE. MAYBE.
WELL, YOU LIED ABOUT GOING TO
NYU.
YOU DID.
YOU LIED ABOUT WORKING AT
GOLDMAN SACKS.
I FILLED THE GOLDMAN'S SACKS.
YOU SAID YOUR MOM DIED IN
9/11.
I THINK I SAID 7/11.
YOU LIED ABOUT BEING JEWISH.
I SAID THAT BECAUSE MY GRAND
PARENTS WERE IN THE HOLOCAUST.
REALLY?
YEAH, THEY ACTUALLY KNEW ANN FRANK.
MY ANCESTORS WERE THE ONES THAT
TOLD HER, YOU SHOULD BE WRITING
THIS DOWN.
THAT CANNOT BE TRUE.
GEORGE, PEOPLE NEED TO KNOW WHO
YOU ARE.
I AM GEORGE SANTOS,
MR. INTERNASTY.
I GRADUATED ON A VOLLEYBALL SCHOLARSHIP.
AND I AM A CROWD REPRESENTATIVE
FOR MY DISTRICT IN LONG ISLAND,
NEW JERSEY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HANG ON.
MADONNA'S CALLING ME.
HELLO?
LIKE A VIRGIN?
I REMEMBER.
I WAS THERE.
I WAS THE VIRGIN.
LOVE YOU.
SEE YOU AT HOME.
GEORGE, WE DON'T BELIEVE
ANYTHING YOU'RE SAYING.
BY THE WAY, I KNOW I LOOK
ASIAN, BUT THAT'S BECAUSE MY
MAIDEN NAME IS CHOW BECAUSE I'M
BRAZILIAN.
I GOT IT.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN HOW YOU SUDDENLY
BECAME A MILLIONAIRE, ESPECIALLY
AFTER BEING LINKED TO THE NEPHEW
OF A RUSSIAN OLIGARCH.
THAT'S NOTHING.
THE ONLY LINK I HAVE IS MY GREAT
GRANDMOTHER WAS A LITTLE BAD IN
THE MOVIE--
FROM ANASTASIA?
YES.
RYAN IS IN IT AND KIRSTEN DUNST
PLAYS ANASTASIA.
I'M NOT LYING LIKE BALLOON BOY.
REMEMBER HIM, ABOUT BEING IN A
BALLOON?
BECAUSE THAT WAS ME.
NO, IT WAS NOT.
I'M NOT LYING.
THEY MADE ME TAKE A LIE DETECTOR
TEST BEFORE I CAME IN HERE, LOOK.
THAT'S A COVID TEST.
MADONNA IS CALLING ME.
SHE'S CALLING YOU ON THE
COVID TEST?
YOU HAVE TO STOP LYING.
THERE'S NO LAW AGAINST LYING.
LOOK AT YOU, YOU'RE WEARING
MAKEUP.
ISN'T THAT A LIE, MAKING
EVERYONE THINK YOU'RE GORGEOUS?
BUT, GEORGE, I AM GORGEOUS.
WHOA, BUDDY.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
REPUBLICANS WON'T CONDEMN YOU.
THEY PROMOTED YOU TO TWO
COMMITTEE ASSIGNMENTS.
OF COURSE THEY DID, COLIN.
I'M A TEAM PLAYER, AND THE SPORT
IS LIES.
AT LEAST MINE ARE FUN.
MARJORIE TAYLOR GREEN IS OVER
I'M JUST SAYING IT HAPPENED TO
ME!
GEORGE SANTOS.
THE POPULATION OF CHINA
DECLINED BY 850,000 PEOPLE.
THANKS TO AN INCREASE IN CHINA'S
LEADING CAUSE OF DEATH,
PROTESTING.
CHINA PLANS TO REVERSE THE
POPULATION DECLINE
WITH AN
EMERGENCY IMPORT OF NICK CANNON.
- GOOD NEWS IT'S A HAPPY ENDING.
- HAPPY ENDING TO THAT.
DUE TO A COMPUTER ERROR, A
SCHOOL IN MASSACHUSETTS
HAS BEEN
UNABLE TO TURN OFF ITS LIGHTS
FOR OVER A YEAR AND A HALF.
THE STUDENTS ARE DOING FINE,
BUT THE CLASSROOM HAMSTER HAS GONE INSANE.
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF THE
INTERIOR HAS CHANGED THE NAME OF
SQUALL VALLEY, CALIFORNIA
BECAUSE IT'S CONSIDERED A ZROG
TORY TERM NOR NATIVE AMERICAN WOMEN.
OKAY. I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW THAT NAME
GETS CHANGED,
AND YET NO ONE
CARES THERE'S AN ENTIRE TOWN IN
NEW YORK THAT MOCKS MY PEOPLE.
WHITE PLAINS
IN SAN FRANCISCO-- A SAN
FRANCISCO PANEL STUDYING
REPARATIONS
IS PROPOSING GIVING
EVERY BLACK RESIDENT A ONE-TIME
PAYMENT OF $5 MILLION.
THAT'S A FANTASTIC IDEA, SAID
THE GUCCI STORE.
KEVIN SPACEY-- HOLD FOR APPLAUSE.
KEVIN SPACEY MADE HIS FIRST
PUBLIC SPEAKING APPEARANCE IN FIVE YEARS
WHERE HE THANKED
ITALY'S NATIONAL CINEMA MUSEUM
FOR HAVING THE BALLS TO INVITE HIM.
HE ALSO ASKED, COULD I TOUCH THE BALLS.
I'M KIDDING.
HE DIDN'T ASK PERMISSION.
A CATHOLIC NUN IN FRANCE WHO
WAS BELIEVED TO BE THE OLDEST PERSON IN THE WORLD
HAS DIED AT
THE AGE OF 118.
HER CAUSE OF DEATH WAS LISTED AS
ANSWERED PRAYER.
ANDY MURRAY WAS UPSET AFTER
AN UMPIRE AT THE AUSTRALIAN OPEN
REFUSED TO LET HIM TAKE A
BATHROOM BREAK AFTER A FIVE LONG
SET MATCH.
WORSE, IT WAS DEUCE.
TROUBLE HIRING NEW EMPLOYEES.
HERE TO ENCOURAGE YOUNG PEOPLE
TO GET INVOLVED IN LOCAL
GOVERNMENT IS A LONG-TIME
EMPLOYEE OF THE CITY OF INDIANA.
APRIL LUDGATE.
HI.
HI, APRIL.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
YOU SAID YOU CAME OUT HERE TO
TALK ABOUT LOCAL GOVERNMENT.
I WILL WHEN YOU STOP YELLING
AT ME. OKAY.
FINE.
SO, YEAH, EVERYBODY SHOULD GET
INVOLVED WHERE THEY LIVE.
IF YOU'RE YOUNG, YOU SHOULD GET
A JOB AS A GARBAGE MAN OR SOMETHING.
OKAY.
ARE THERE OTHER JOBS?
YOU WANT ME TO LIST THEM?
OKAY.
FINE.
DRIVE A BUS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE ON TIME.
NOBODY CARES.
WORK FOR THE WATER DEPARTMENT.
YOU CAN DRAIN THE RESERVOIR AND
FIND ALL THE BODIES AND MURDER CLUES.
OR JUST BE A DOGCATCHER AND JUST
SAY YOU COULDN'T FIND ANY. YEAH.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU WORK FOR THE
LOCAL GOVERNMENT, DOING THE BARE
MINIMUM IS DOING YOUR PART.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
BUT WHAT IF YOU ACTUALLY WANT TO
WORK HARD?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE ANNOYING ME.
JUST ASK MY OLD BOSS.
LESLIE KNOPE.
HI, APRIL!
HI, COLIN.
HI, MICHAEL CHE.
WOW, LOOK AT THIS.
WHO KNEW THERE WERE CAMERAS AT SNL.
YEAH.
SO YOU WORK FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
YEAH, PARK SERVICE, YEP.
SO HOW MUCH FUN IS IT WORKING
HERE?
DO YOU GUYS JUST SIT AROUND
CRACKING EACH OTHER UP ALL DAY?
WELL, NOT AT LIKE 8:00 A.M.,
BUT, YEAH, GENERALLY.
HOW DOES IT TAKE TO RUN A
FEDERAL AGENCY?
ALL YOU DO IS SHOW UP EVERY
DAY AND DO THE JOB.
BUT I WANT TO PICK YOUR BRAIN
ABOUT THIS JOB, ABOUT THIS SHOW,
BECAUSE I USED TO WATCH THIS
WHEN SETH MYERS DID IT BY
HIMSELF WITH NO ONE ELSE.
AND HE MADE IT LOOK REALLY EASY. YEAH.
SO YOU SAID YOU WERE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT. YEAH.
BUT QUICK QUESTION.
PRESIDENT BIDEN, WHEN HE ZOOMED
IN BEFORE, COULD HE SEE ME, OR
WERE THE CAMERAS ON?
I THINK HE PRERECORDED THAT. OH.
I THOUGHT THIS SHOW WAS LIFE.
WELL, MOST OF IT IS.
OH, MY GOD.
CAN WE PLEASE GO?
THIS GUY HAS BEEN BOTHERING ME
FOR A HALF AN HOUR.
WE CAN'T STAY LONG.
WE HAVE A TIMED ENTRY TO THE M&M
STORE.
BEFORE WE GO-- AND MAY I BE SO
BOLD?
DO YOU MIND IF I TRY TO TELL A
JOKE?
I WOULD LOVE THAT. PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
THIS FEELS GOOD.
THIS FEELS NICE.
OKAY.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, NO.
THAT'S TOO MEAN.
OH, WHAT?
NO.
THAT'S WAY TOO MEAN.
OKAY.
I'LL DO THIS ONE.
A TOWN IN ALASKA HAS LAUNCHED A
BUS SERVICE FOR PUPPIES.
THE SERVICE HAS EXPANDED TO
PUPPIES THANKS TO THE HE ROWIC
ACTIVISM OF CANINE CIVIL RIGHTS
ICON, ROSA BARKS.
I LOVE THAT.
I'M APRIL
MY JOB TO KEEP YOU ALL SAFE.
AND DOING THAT, I MUST TELL THE
TRUTH OF THIS WAR.
WHAT'S GOING ON, JAKE SULLY?
THERE ARE REPORTS THAT HUMANS
HAVE INFILTRATED THE CLAN.
I FEAR THERE ARE SKY PEOPLE
LIVING AMONG US DISGUISED AS AVATARS.
THAT CAN'T BE. NO.
THESE ARE OUR BROTHERS AND
SISTERS.
WHAT?
WE GOT HUMANS UP IN HERE?
NOT COOL, MAN.
NOT COOL.
YEAH, I HATE THAT.
I KNOW IT'S DIFFICULT TO
PROCESS, BUT WE MUST STAY VIGILANT.
REPORTS TELL US THAT WE SHOULD
BE LOOKING FOR TWO FEMALE
LIEUTENANTS THAT ARE SPIES
DESCRIBED AS BUTCH LADIES FROM ARIZONA.
LISTEN UP.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
WE NEED TO BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR
SOME GRAND CANYON TYPES.
JAKE SULLY, IT'S OBVIOUSLY
THESE TWO.
VICKIE AND CHRISTINE?
WHOA!
YOU SERIOUS RIGHT NOW, FRITO?
COME ON, FRITO?
EVERYONE, BE CALM.
NOW THESE WITH BIG ACCUSATIONS, FRIOTE.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
THAT'S JAKE.
WAIT.
YEAH.
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT, THEY
DO ALWAYS LOOK DOWN AT THEIR OWN
BODIES AND SAY OUT LOUD, WHOA,
THIS IS CRAZY.
WHOA.
BRO, YOURS IS WILD.
IT ALL MAKES SENSE.
IS THAT WHY THEY CALL THEMSELVES
THE MARICOPE COUNTER OF MILF
HUNTERS?
AND WHY ARE THEY WEARING
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT CLOTHING?
WHOA, WHAT HAPPENED TO WOMEN
SUPPORTING WOMEN, BITCH?
SERIOUSLY.
OKAY?
WE'RE COOL WITH LETTING OUR NIPS
FLY SOMETIMES, AND MAYBE WE'RE
NOT AS COMFORTABLE IN THONGS.
I'M LOOKING AT YOU, CHEESE BURGER.
LISTEN, GUYS, OUR SKIN'S
BLUE, AND I THINK WE KNOW HOW TO
USE OUR TAILS.
I THINK WE KNOW.
HOW LONG WAS I OUT?
WHOA, HOW LONG WERE WE OUT?
YOU WERE NOT OUT.
WAIT.
A QUEEN IS BACK.
SCREAMING LADY ALERT.
HERE WE GO.
THEY'VE COME TO OUR LAND.
THEY'VE COME FOR OUR PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, HON.
WE MUST KILL THEM.
DON'T START CRYING.
AHHH!
WAIT.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
COME ON.
COME ON, COME ON.
GET AROUND ME.
GET OPEN.
JAKE, GET OPEN.
JAKE, JAKE, GET OPEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
THINK FAST.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
YOU GUYS CANNOT BE PLAYING
BASKETBALL RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
I NEED YOU TO FOCUS IF WE'RE
EVER GOING TO CATCH THE MOLES.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
JAKE.
JAKE, COME ON, MAN.
COME ON, YOU GOT TO TRUST ME.
IT'S ME.
IT'S ME, FRITO-- I MEAN,
FRIOTE.
JAKE SULLY.
COME ON, MAN.
IT'S THEM.
I HAVEN'T SEEN TWO PEOPLE
PLAYING BASKETBALL SINCE I WAS
LIVING BACK ON EARTH AS A HUMAN BEING.
OH!
IT WAS FRITO THE WHOLE TIME?
AND US TOO.
VICKIE, COME ON.
OH, SHOOT.
DUDE, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
DUDE, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE. YEAH.
♪ DEMONS ON MY SHOULDER
MONSTERS IN MY HEAD
SHADOW IN THE WATER
WILL YOU BE MY FRIEND ♪
♪ THE WORLD REVOLVES
AROUND ME
AS I LAY IN MY BED
DREAMING OF MORE MORE ♪
♪ DIAMONDS IN THE SEA ♪
♪ A TIME WHERE THERE-- IF ONLY
YOU BELIEVE ♪
♪ THAT THERE IS ALWAYS MORE
MORE ♪
♪ BE YOURSELF SO
LOUD TONIGHT MMM SO LOUD
THEY'LL HEAR YOU
FROM THE STARS ♪
♪ THEY WILL HEAR YOU FROM
SPARKLING LIKE DYNAMITE SPARKLE
IF THAT IS WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ IT'S WHO YOU ARE
A HYMN FOR GLORIA
FOR GLORIA
FOR GLORIA GLORIA ♪
♪ A HYMN FOR GLORIA GLORIA
FOR GLORIA GLORIA
GLORIA ♪
♪ GLORIA
GLORIA
IT'S ALL BUT ♪
♪ A HYMN FOR GLORIA
IT'S ALL A HYMN
FOR GLORI-GLORI GLORIA
IT'S ALL BUT ♪
♪ A HYMN FOR GLORIA
IT'S FOR GLORIA ♪
I THREW MY BREAKFAST AT MY
ASSISTANT, SO I'M STARVING.
TOMMY, I WANT YOU DANCING UP
TOP.
CAMERA THEN CUTS TO MARIO.
YOU'RE POURING EVERYONE'S SHOTS.
THEN JAMAL, YOU TOAST MARIO.
SOUND GOOD?
YEAH.
PLACES.
ACTION.
LIVING WITH HIV?
I LEARNED I COULD SAY
UNDETECTABLE WITH FEWER MEDICINES.
MOST HIV PILLS HAVE SO MANY
MEDICINES, BUT DOVA THE, O HAS
LESS, AND IT'S JUST AS
EFFECTIVE.
THAT'S WHY I SWITCHED TO
DOVATO HIV TREATMENT.
I AIN'T GAY, THOUGH.
CUT!
OKAY.
THAT WAS A GOOD FIRST RUN, GUYS.
TOMMY, MAYBE A LITTLE BETTER
DANCING UP TOP.
YEAH, GOT IT.
I CAN DO A LITTLE MORE.
NOT REALLY MORE, JUST BETTER.
PERFECT, MARIO.
AND JAMAL, BUDDY, I FEEL LIKE
YOU MAYBE AD LIBBED A BIT AT THE END.
THE LINE IS THAT'S WHY I
SWITCHED TO DOVATO HIV TREATMENT
THEN FULL STOP.
GOT IT.
FROM THE TOP.
ACTION!
LIVING WITH HIV, I LEARNED I
COULD STAY UNDETECTABLE WITH
FEWER MEDICINES.
MOST HIV PILLS HAVE SO MANY
MEDICINES, BUT DOVATO HAS LESS,
AND IT'S JUST AS EFFECTIVE.
THAT'S WHY I SWITCHED TO
DOVATO HIV TREATMENT.
FACT, YOU CAN GET HIV FROM A GIRL.
THAT'S HOW I DID IT.
CUT!
AGAIN, AGAIN, WOW.
DID I MESS UP THE DANCING?
YEAH.
IT WAS WORSE THIS TIME.
ONCE AGAIN, MARIO, PERFECTION.
AND JAMAL, BUDDY, YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO SAY.
I MESSED UP THE DANCING. NO.
YOU AD LIBBED AGAIN.
ARE YOU COMFORTABLE WITH THIS
SCRIPT?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I FEEL LIKE IT'S NOT CLEAR MY
CHARACTER IS A STRAIGHT GUY
RESPECTFULLY.
IT'S NOT.
THIS SCENE TAKES PLACE AT A GAY
CLUB.
OH, WORD. OKAY.
YEAH.
IS THAT GOING TO BE A PROBLEM
FOR YOU.
NO, NO PROBLEM.
I JUST AIN'T, NO DOUBT.
GOOD BECAUSE I WOULD LOVE TO
GET THIS SCENE WRAPPED BEFORE MY
SALAD GETS COLD.
IT'S A HOT SALAD.
AND ACTION.
LIVING WITH HIV, I LEARNED I
COULD STAY UNDETECTABLE WITH
FEWER MEDICINES.
IT'S A GAY CLUB. WHAT.
I MEAN, I'M COOL WITH THAT, I
JUST DIDN'T KNOW THAT. OKAY.
FACT.
THERE BE MAD STRAIGHT GIRLS AT
THE GAY CLUBS, AND THEY BE
READY, AND THAT'S WHERE I COME IN.
CAN SOMEBODY PLEASE YELL CUT?
CUT.
SORRY.
I TOOK A QUICK BITE OF MY HOT
SALAD.
IT BURNED THE ROOF OF MY MOUTH.
HOW DID I DO?
IT WAS THE WORST THING I'VE
EVER SEEN BESIDES TOMMY'S
DANCING.
I'M TRYING.
I JUST FEEL LIKE SINCE I'M
STRAIGHT, MY GUY SHOULD BE
STRAIGHT TOO.
IT'S JUST ACTING, BRO.
I'M NOT ACTUALLY GAY EITHER.
OKAY.
JAMAL, IF YOU'RE
UNCOMFORTABLE, WE CAN JUST GIVE
YOUR LINES TO MARIO.
DO I STILL GET PAID THE SAME?
YOU DON'T GET PAID.
YOU JUST GO HOME.
I NEED THIS JOB.
THEN SAY THE LINES.
WHAT IF MY GUY GOT HIV FROM
BASKETBALL LIKE MAGIC JOHNSON.
I APPRECIATE YOU COMING DOWN,
BUT CLEARLY YOU'RE NOT MATURE
ENOUGH TO HANDLE THIS ROLE, JAMAL.
THAT'S A FACT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU AND TOMMY
JUST LEAVE, PLEASE?
WAIT, ME?
THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
CASE I COULDN'T SHAKE.
A MAN WHO EATS DINNER EARLY.
I LIKE THAT.
HOW THE HELL DID YOU GET IN
HERE?
YOU HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING ME.
WHY?
YOUR HUSBAND IS DEAD, AND I
THINK YOU KILLED HIM.
I DIDN'T KILL ANYONE
MISTER--
RALLY.
I LOVED MY HUSBAND,
MR. RALLY.
HE ARGUED WITH THE RADIO, REALLY
KNEW HOW TO STINK UP A CHAIR.
SOUNDS LIKE AN OLD MAN.
HE WAS.
THEY ALL WERE, EACH ONE OLDER
THAN THE LAST.
WHEN I MEET A MAN WITH GLASSES
APP PANTS UP TO HIS CHEST, I GO
HEAD OVER HEELS.
HOW IS IT THEY ALL END UP
DEAD?
BECAUSE THEY'RE OLD.
THE AUTOPSY REPORT SAYS EVERY
MAN YOU MARRY DIES AFTER NATURAL CAUSES.
WHAT'S NATURAL ABOUT THAT?
THE CAUSES.
I LIKE THE WAY THEIR KISSES
TASTE LIKE A COUGH, HOW THEY
CAN'T FIND THEIR GLASSES, AND
THE WAY THEY MAKE LOVE, OH, HOLD
ON, OUCH, OUCH, SORRY.
LET ME JUST DO YOU.
I'M STARTING TO GET THE
PICTURE.
IS IT A CRIME TO WANT A MAN
WHO BEGS ME TO DRIVE HIM TO
CHURCH AND SLEEPS THE WHOLE
TIME?
IS A GUY WHO NEVER USES HIS TURN
SIGNAL AND SCREAMS AT RACCOONS
IN HIS YARD.
LISTEN, YOU GOT A THING, I
GET THAT.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE
LIKE TO TELL EVERYBODY WHAT
THEIR THING IS THESE DAYS. OH.
GETTING ANGRY AT PEOPLE THESE
DAYS, MR. RALLY?
ARE YOU TRYING TO SEDUCE ME?
I'M TOO YOUNG FOR YOU, LADY.
I'M 33.
I JUST LOOK OLDER BECAUSE I'M AN ALCOHOLIC.
SO NOW MAYBE YOU CAN TELL ME
WHAT YOUR THING IS.
WHAT STARTS YOUR ENGINE,
MR. RALLY?
YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
PANTY HOSE, JUST LADIES WITH
NICE LEGS IN TIGHTS.
BUT I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU, BABY.
WHO THE HELL IS THIS?
MOTHER!
DARLING.
WHO'S THIS LITTLE SNACK?
YOU CAN'T HAVE HIM, MOTHER.
DON'T BE CROSS WITH ME,
DARLING.
I CAN'T RESIST A MAN WITH A DEEP
VOICE AND A BIG NOSE.
OF COURSE A KNOCKOUT WALKS IN
THE NIGHT BEFORE MY RHINO PLACETY.
DON'T DO IT.
I WANTED YOU TO GROW OLD WITH ME.
SORE WE, SISTER, I LIKE THEM
DESPERATE AND COOKY BECAUSE I
KNOW THEY WON'T GIVE ME A HARD
TIME ABOUT THE BOOZE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOUR MOTHER
OUT TO THE CLUB TO DO SOME
STUPID DANCES.
BUT FIRST, YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE
ME THAT GUN.
NO!
THERE I WAS, DYING IN MY
OFFICE, MURDERED FOR REASONS
THAT WOULD THROW OLD SIGGY FROID
FOR A LOOP.
I GUESS YOU NEVER SOLVE YOUR
LAST CASE.
WHO WAS PAYING ME ANYWAY?
WELL, TIME TO DIE, I GUESS.
THAT'S JUST HOW THINGS GO IN THE
MIDTOWN EAST IN THE LOW 60s.
MY MOTHER, THANK YOU AND HAVE A
GOOD NIGHT!
DREAMS REALLY DO COME TRUE!