>>> YOU'RE WATCHING "FOX &
FRIENDS."
>> GOOD MORNING VIETNAM!
WELCOME TO "FOX & FRIENDS."
THAT'S BRIAN KILMEADE.
>> HELLO!
>> AND THE AINSLEY EARNHARDT.
>> OKAY.
Y'ALL ARE GOING TO KILL ME WITH
THESE JOKES.
>> AND I'M STEVE DOOCY HERE ON
THIS GORGEOUS 30 DEGREE SPRING
NEW YORK MORNING.
WHAT A HELLHOLE OF A CITY.
BRIAN, HOW WAS THE WEEKEND?
>> OH, VERY EXCITING, STEVE.
I GOT ON TRUTH SOCIAL.
>> OOH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S EXCLUSIVE NEW
SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORM?
>> FANCY.
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
I DOWNLOADED THE APP, OPENED IT,
AND MY PHONE IMMEDIATELY GOT
VERY, VERY HOT.
LIKE OVER 140 DEGREES.
>> WOW.
JUST FROM THE APP?
>> YEAH.
IT BURNED MY SON, ACTUALLY.
ANYWAY, TRUTH SOCIAL, FIVE
STARS.
>> OKAY.
GUYS, SPEAKING OF TRUTHS
CRUSH
OF THE WEEK, TED CRUZ.
ABSOLUTELY WIPED THE FLOOR WITH
KETANJI BROWN JACKSON LAST WEEK
BY WAVING A CHILDREN'S BOOK AT
HER.
>> SO POWERFUL.
>> FATALITY.
>> I'M SORRY, MS. JACKSON, BUT I
AM FO THE FIRST AMENDMENT.
- YES.
>> WELL, HERE TO TALK ABOUT THAT
AND THE SUPREME COURT
ARE TWO FRIENDS OF OURS.
HANDLING THEIR OWN LITTLE
CONTROVERSY THIS WEEK,
JUSTICE
CLARENCE AND GINNI THOMAS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HI, FRIENDS.
>> WELL, FIRST OFF, HONORABLE
JUSTICE THOMAS, YOU WERE JUST IN
THE HOSPITAL.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY.
>> YEAH.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU FEELING OKAY?
>> I GUESS WE'LL SEE.
>> YEAH.
FOLKS WERE SAYING YOU HAD COVID.
BUT NOT TRUE, THOUGH, RIGHT,
JUSTICE T?
EVERYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
>> JUSTICE THOMAS, ALWAYS
PLAYING IT CLOSE TO THE VEST.
I RESPECT THAT.
NOW, GINNI, THE LEFT IS CURRENTLY
LOSING THEIR MINDS
OVER A
COUPLE OF COMPLETELY NORMAL TEXTS
YOU SENT TO YOUR PAL MARK
MEADOWS ON JANUARY 6th.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> IT SURE IS.
>> AND NOW THEY WANT THE
HONORABLE JUSTICE TO RECUSE
HIMSELF.
I MEAN, YOU'RE ALLOWED TO SPEAK
YOUR MIND.
>> YES.
AND I DON'T WANT ANY TROUBLE.
I TAKE MY DUTY AS THE YOKO ONO
OF THE SUPREME COURT VERY
SERIOUSLY.
ALL I WANT IS A TIDAL WAVE OF
BIBLICAL VENGEANCE
TO WASH AWAY
THE BIDEN CRIME FAMILY ALL THE
WAY TO GITMO
AND THEN WE RELEASE
THE KRAKEN.
>> OKAY.
WELL, THAT IS TERRIFIC.
>> JUSTICE THOMAS, SHE DOESN'T
TALK TO YOU ABOUT THIS STUFF,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
SOME SAY YES, SOME SAY NO.
>> WELL, JUSTICE T, IT'S SO
GREAT TO HAVE SOMEONE HERE
WHO
ISN'T AFRAID TO TELL US WHAT HE
REALLY THINKS.
>> WHO?
>> WELL, YOU OF COURSE, SIR.
YOU CRAZY, MAN.
>> WELL, GREAT.
THANK YOU BOTH SO MUCH.
NOW, LATER THIS AFTERNOON ON
FOX, IT'S "THE FIVE."
LET'S CHECK IN WITH CO-HOST
JUDGE JEANINE PIRRO TO SEE
WHAT'S IN STORE.
>> HELLO, MY ONLY FRIENDS.
LATER ON "THE FIVE," DISNEY HAS
AN EXCITING NEW PROJECT.
TURNING YOUR KINDERGARTNER GAY.
LAST WEEK GOVERNOR DeSANTIS
SIGNED A BILL PROTECTING OUR
PRECIOUS FLORIDA SCHOOLS
FROM
AMERICA'S DANGEROUS ELLENS AND
CAITLYNS.
BY THE WAY, CAITLYN JENNER,
WELCOME TO THE FOX NEWS FAMILY.
NOW, WOKE DISNEY WON'T STOP
UNTIL ALL OF DISNEY WORLD
IS PACKED WITH TWINKERBELLS,
CINDERFELLAS
AND THAT GAY MR.
TOAD.
THEN REPRESENTATIVE MADISON
CAWTHORN.
OH, MADISON.
YOU HAD ME AT WHITE SUPREMACY.
YOU LOST ME AT ORGY.
ALL THAT AND KYLE RITTENHOUSE
DEBUTS HIS NEW COOKBOOK,
COMING
UP ON "THE FIVE."
>> WELL, THANK YOU SO MUCH,
JUDGE.
THAT SOUNDS TERRIFIC AS ALWAYS.
>> YOU BET.
SALUD.
>> LOVE THAT.
NOW, THIS IS EXCITING.
I'M HEARING WE ACTUALLY HAVE A
SURPRISE ON THE LINE.
AM I CORRECT?
>> UH-OH.
IS HE HERE?
HELLO?
MR. PRESIDENT, ARE YOU ON THE
FACE-TIME?
>> IF YOU BUILD IT, I WILL COME.
HELLO, FRIENDS.
CAN YOU SEE ME?
>> MR. PRESIDENT.
WOW.
WHAT A TREAT.
THANKS FOR FITTING US INTO YOUR
BUSY SCHEDULE.
>> VERY BUSY, STEVE.
HERE AT MAR-A-LAGO WITH THE GOLF
AND THE WEDDING RECEPTIONS AND
GETTING CLUMPS OF BACON WITH
TONGS AT BREAKFAST BAR.
>> WELL, SO MUCH TO DISCUSS,
BUT I'VE GOT TO ASK, SIR, DID YOU
SEE THE FAMOUS SLAP?
>> YOU KNOW, I DID SEE SLAP.
I ENJOYED SLAP.
I WAS VERY IMPRESSED BY HITCH.
QUITE AN ARM ON HITCH.
I ALWAYS KNEW HITCH HAD AN ARM.
BACK IN "PURSUIT OF HAPPYNESS,"
HE'S LUGGING THE MACHINE ON AND
OFF THE SUBWAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GREAT.
THEY SLEPT IN THE BATHROOM IN
THAT MOVIE.
IT'S SO SAD.
BUT IT'S A SAD NIGHT FOR HITCH
TOO.
VERY SAD.
THAT KIND OF BEHAVIOR IS NOT
GOING TO HELP KEVIN JAMES GET A
DATE WITH ALLEGRA COLE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AMEN TO THAT, SIR.
>> NOW, SIR, THE JANUARY 6th
COMMITTEE IS GEARING UP TO MAKE
ALL SORTS OF CLAIMS.
SO LET'S JUST PUT THIS TO REST.
DID YOU COMMIT A COUP, SIR?
>> NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE WAS NO COUP.
IT WAS AN EVENT.
PERHAPS A TAKEBACK EVENT.
A COUP PERHAPS.
BUT I DON'T LIKE COUP.
I JUST DON'T LIKE COUP.
I DON'T LIKE THE P AT THE END OF
COUP.
YOU SHOULD TAKE THE P AND PUSH
IT.
IF YOU TAKE OFF P YOU HAVE COW
WHICH GOES MOO,
WHICH IS
PERHAPS WHERE THEY GET COUP.
BUT COULD COUP.
WHO DO?
YOU DO.
DO WHAT?
REMIND ME OF THE BABE.
BUT IT WAS AN INTENTIONAL
PLANNED COUP, YES.
>> RIGHT.
OKAY.
>> BUT THEY'RE SAYING THERE IS
THIS SEVEN-HOUR GAP IN WHITE
HOUSE CALL LOGS THAT DAY.
YOU DIDN'T USE A BURNER PHONE,
DID YOU, SIR?
>> NO.
NOT TRUE.
NEVER USED BURNER PHONE
EXCEPT
PERHAPS ON JANUARY 6th DURING
THAT SEVEN-HOUR PERIOD.
I COULDN'T EVEN TELL YOU WHAT A
BURNER PHONE LOOKS LIKE,
HONESTLY.
I WAS TOO BUSY WITH PHONE CALL
AND BURNER PHONE AND COUP.
>> OKAY.
GOT YOU.
BUT LET'S BE REAL, SIR.
THE LEFT WANTS TO PAINT JANUARY 6th
AS SOME VIOLENT REVOLUTION.
IT WASN'T.
>> COULD HAVE BEEN.
SHOULD HAVE BEEN MAYBE.
VIOLENT IS -- VIOLENT IS PERHAPS
GOOD.
YOU KNOW, THEY USED TO DO
VIOLENT ALL THE TIME.
YOU'D LINE UP THE OPPONENTS,
YOU'D GO BING, BING, BING,
SHOOT THEM DEAD.
SO EASY.
SOLVE SO MANY PROBLEMS.
YOU SHOOT THEM DEAD.
WITH A BIG FAT BEAUTIFUL
UNCIRCUMCISED GUN.
NOW, THAT'S WHAT I CALL A COUP.
HEY, BY THE WAY, DID YOU HEAR
THIS?
I GOT A HOLE IN ONE.
DID ANYBODY HEAR THAT?
>> YES, YES.
CONGRATS, SIR.
PLEASE TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> YOU KNOW, I'D LOVE TO.
BUT MY PHONE IS GETTING VERY,
VERY HOT TO THE TOUCH.
>> YOU'VE GOT TRUTH SOCIAL, SIR.
>> YES INDEED.
TRUTH SOCIAL.
THE ONLY APP WITH A SMELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, SIR.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK AND --
>> And live from New York, it's
Saturday Night!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN --
JERROD CARMICHAEL!
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
I'M NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I WANT TO BE CLEAR UP TOP.
I TALKED ABOUT IT ENOUGH.
KEPT TALKING ABOUT IT.
KEPT THINKING ABOUT IT.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
AND YOU CAN'T MAKE ME TALK ABOUT
IT.
BUT -- I'VE GOT A QUESTION.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
LIKE AREN'T YOU SICK OF TALKING
ABOUT IT?
ISN'T IT KIND OF CRAZY -- IT
FEELS LIKE WE'VE BEEN TALKING
ABOUT IT FOR SO LONG. I HAVE --
THIS IS GOING TO
REALLY BLOW YOUR MINDS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE --
IT'S BEEN SIX DAYS.
SIX DAYS.
THIS HAPPENED A WEEK AGO.
DOESN'T IT FEEL LIKE IT HAPPENED
YEARS AGO?
LIKE DOESN'T IT FEEL LIKE IT
HAPPENED WHEN WE WERE ALL IN
HIGH SCHOOL?
LIKE IT FEELS LIKE IT HAPPENED
BETWEEN JAMIROQUAI AND 9/11.
A LONG, LONG TIME AGO.
ENTIRE LIVES
IT HAPPENED ON SUNDAY.
SUNDAY.
IT'S SATURDAY, BRO.
ON MONDAY IT WAS EXCITING.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE.
MONDAY -- IF THIS WERE MONDAY,
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO GET ME
TO SHUT UP ABOUT IT.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT IT ALL
MONDAY.
TUESDAY, STILL TALKING ABOUT IT.
A LITTLE LESS EXCITING BECAUSE
IT STOPPED BEING ABOUT IT ON
TUESDAY.
IT STARTED BEING ABOUT A LOT OF
PROXY ARGUMENTS.
HAIR AND BLACK MEN AND WHITE
PEOPLE ON TWITTER.
IT WAS JUST -- IT WAS TOO MUCH
BY TUESDAY.
BY WEDNESDAY I WANTED TO KILL
MYSELF.
I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER
THURSDAY.
BUT BY FRIDAY, BY FRIDAY I MADE
A VOW TO MYSELF.
I PROMISED MYSELF I WOULD NEVER,
EVER TALK ABOUT IT AGAIN.
THEN LORNE CAME INTO MY DRESSING
ROOM.
HE WAS LIKE, "I THINK YOU NEED
TO TALK ABOUT IT."
HE SAID THE NATION NEEDS TO
HEAL.
DON'T TURN YOUR BACK ON ME,
LORNE.
THE NATION NEEDS TO HEAL.
I SAID THE NATION NEEDS TO WHAT?
YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT?
THE NATION DON'T EVEN KNOW ME.
THE NATION HAS NO CLUE WHO I AM.
I HAVE TO BE
THE LEAST FAMOUS
HOST
IN "SNL" -- LIKE THE LEAST.
I WAS SO EXCITED TO COME HERE.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
JUST KNOW THOSE CLAPS DID
NOTHING FOR MY SELF-ESTEEM.
ALL YOU WERE DOING WAS -- WERE
YOU MAKING IT BETTER?
I WAS HAPPY.
I WAS ACTUALLY REALLY HAPPY TO
COME HERE
AND TALK TO YOU GUYS
AND INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M JERROD CARMICHAEL, BY THE
WAY.
HI, EVERYONE.
HELLO.
I HAVE A NEW SPECIAL OUT ON HBO.
I REALLY HOPE THAT YOU WATCH.
IN THE SPECIAL I COME OUT AS
GAY.
WHICH IS NICE.
BUT AN EXPECTED RESPONSE IN NEW
YORK.
IT'S ACTUALLY WHY I LIVE HERE.
IF YOU SAY YOU'RE GAY IN NEW YORK,
YOU CAN RIDE THE BUS FOR
FREE AND PEOPLE JUST GIVE YOU
PIZZA.
HONESTLY, IF YOU'RE GAY AND YOU -- IN NEW YORK,
YOU GET TO
HOST "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
NO, NO.
THIS IS THE GAYEST THING YOU
COULD POSSIBLY DO.
LIKE I CAME OUT RIGHT ONTO THE
STAGE.
I BASICALLY --
WE'RE BASICALLY
LIKE IN OUR ANDY WARHOL FEVER
DREAM RIGHT NOW.
HEAL THE NATION?
I'VE BEEN GAY FOR LIKE 48 HOURS,
BRO.
LIKE THERE'S SO MUCH GAY STUFF
I'VE GOT TO DO BEFORE I CAN HEAL
THE NATION.
I'VE GOT SO MANY HOMOPHOBIC
COUSINS I CAN'T EVEN HEAL MY
FAMILY.
YOU WANT ME TO HEAL THE NATION?
I WAS EXCITED.
I WAS EXCITED TO BE HERE.
LIKE I HAD A LOT OF THINGS
PLANNED.
STUFF I WANTED TO TALK ABOUT.
ACTUALLY REALLY --
WE'VE GOT TIME.
REALLY QUICK.
I DON'T KNOW HOW OFTEN I'M EVER
GOING TO BE ON LIVE TV,
AND I
KNOW I'LL NEVER GET TO TALK TO
HIM.
SO I HAVE TO DO THIS.
BARACK OBAMA, YOU WANT TO MEET
ME AT CAMERA 2 REALLY FAST?
HEY, B.
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
I'M JERROD.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO REAL QUICK, YOU JUST CHILLING
RIGHT NOW?
LIKE YOU'RE JUST NOT -- YOU JUST
WRITING BOOKS?
WHICH IS NICE.
I BOUGHT THE LAST ONE, BUT IT'S
LIKE 900 PAGES AND --
ANYWAY.
YOU GOT US ALL HOPPED UP ON HOPE
AND CHANGE.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, I HAVE SOME
NEWS FOR YOU, BARACK.
AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LIKE
THIS.
WE NEED YOU BACK BECAUSE I -- I
THINK YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
THE NATION NEEDS TO HEAL.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW TONIGHT.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
GUNNA
So stick around, and we'll be
right back.
>> HELLO.
HELLO, HELLO.
WELCOME TO THE GAME ALL OF US
PLAY EVERY DAY.
IS MY BRAIN OKAY?
WHETHER IT WAS THE YEAR IN
ISOLATION, THE TWO YEARS WITHOUT
ANY SEMBLANCE OF SOCIETY, OR THE
VIRUS ITSELF PHYSICALLY
SHRINKING OUR BRAINS, ONE
THING'S FOR SURE, WE GOT STUPID.
BEFORE WE GET STARTED, LET'S
MEET OUR CONTESTANTS.
DEREK FROM QUEENS.
WHAT DID YOU DO BEFORE COVID?
>> I WAS A MARKETING DIRECTOR
FOR IBM.
>> AND WHAT DO YOU DO NOW?
>> MUSHROOMS.
>> I GET IT.
I TOOK A BUNCH BEFORE THE SHOW.
JENNIFER FROM INDIANAPOLIS.
TELL US A FUN FACT ABOUT
YOURSELF.
>> GOOD, THANK YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> UH-OH.
AND VICTOR FROM NEW MEXICO.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY?
>> TIRED FOR NO REASON.
>> TERRIFIC.
NOW, YOU ALL KNOW HOW THE GAME
WORKS.
EVERY ANSWER IS SOMETHING YOU
DEFINITELY KNEW BEFORE COVID.
BUT DOES YOUR BRAIN STILL
REMEMBER IT?
LET'S FIND OUT.
FIRST QUESTION, WHAT IS THIS
CALLED?
REMEMBER?
SOMETHING YOU USE TO CARRY
THINGS.
>> BICYCLE?
>> NO.
NO.
MIGHT SEE IT IN THE BACKYARD.
>> FARM BICYCLE.
>> NO.
IT'S GOT A WHEEL IN THE FRONT.
>> WHEEL MONKEY.
>> OOH.
SORRY.
WE WERE LOOKING FOR WHEELBARROW.
>> I KNEW THAT.
>> YOU DID.
YOU DID KNOW THAT.
IN 2019.
NOW IT'S JUST A FARM BICYCLE.
OKAY, NEXT QUESTION, WHAT DAY OF
THE WEEK IS IT?
>> THAT'S EASY.
TUESDAY?
>> NOPE.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> WHAT IS THURSDAY?
>> NO.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO PHRASE IT
AS A QUESTION.
>> NO, I WAS GENUINELY ASKING.
WHAT IS THURSDAY?
>> DEREK, WHAT DAY OF THE WEEK
IS IT?
>> OKAY.
I REMEMBER YESTERDAY WAS MY
BIRTHDAY.
AND MY BEST FRIEND TEXTED,
"BIRTHDAY ON A FRIDAY NIGHT,
DOG, WHAT ARE WE DOING TO
CELEBRATE?"
AND I GOT SO ANXIOUS, I DIDN'T
RESPOND AND WENT TO SLEEP BEFORE
5:00 P.M.
SO TODAY MUST BE SATURDAY?
>> CORRECT!
YES.
AND BONUS FOLLOW-UP, DEREK.
WHAT MONTH IS IT?
>> JUNE.
>> OOH.
SORRY.
WE WOULD HAVE ACCEPTED FEBRUARY,
MARCH, APRIL, OR MAY.
BUT LET'S PUT 100 POINTS ON THE
BOARD FOR DEREK.
WHOEVER HAS THE MOST POINTS AT
THE END WILL HAVE THAT NUMBER OF
STEM CELLS INJECTED INTO THEIR
BRAIN IN THE HOPES OF -- WHAT'S
THE WORD?
THE THING YOU DO WITH CARS.
>> TIRES.
>> NO.
WHEN THE BATTERY'S DEAD YOU'VE
GOT TO LIKE --
>> SELL THE CAR.
>> NO.
IT -- WHAT YOU DO WITH THE
CABLE.
>> WHEELBARROW?
>> NO.
JUMPSTART.
YEAH.
THE STEM CELLS WILL JUMPSTART
YOUR BRAIN AGAIN.
DAMMIT, WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
>> YOU'RE DEPRESSED.
>> NO, NO.
I WASN'T REALLY ASKING.
>> YOU NEVER FELT MORE ALONE?
>> STOP GUESSING.
>> YOU WANT TO CALL YOUR
THERAPIST BUT SHE BLOCKED YOUR
NUMBER.
>> HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
>> YOU JUST GIVE OFF THAT EXACT
AURA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE DEREK 100 MORE
POINTS.
GREAT.
WHICH MEANS HE'S UNLOCKED A
BONUS QUESTION THAT INVOLVES A
MYSTERY GUEST.
DEREK, WHO IS THIS?
>> OH, THAT'S EASY.
THAT'S ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS
FROM COLLEGE.
>> UH-HUH.
AND WHAT'S HIS NAME?
>> HE WAS ONE OF MY BEST
FRIENDS.
>> YOU SAID THAT.
BUT WHAT'S HIS NAME?
>> I KNOW IT'S SOMETHING REGULAR
LIKE GREG OR -- STEVE, RIGHT?
>> WE LIVED TOGETHER FOR THREE
YEARS, MAN.
>> OOH.
SORRY, DEREK.
THE CORRECT ANSWER WAS DEREK.
>> WE'VE GOT THE SAME NAME?
>> THAT WAS OUR WHOLE THING,
MAN.
D-1, D-2.
>> DAMN, THAT'S REALLY BAD, MAN.
I'M SORRY.
WE SHOULD GRAB A DRINK OR
SOMETHING SOMETIME AND CATCH UP.
>> UH-OH.
THE SOUND OF SOMEONE INVITING A
FRIEND TO DRINKS WHEN THEY HAVE
NO INTENTION OF EVER GETTING
DRINKS MEANS WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
SO LET'S GO TO THE FINAL
QUESTION TO DETERMINE IF YOUR
BRAIN IS OKAY.
CONTESTANTS, WRITE DOWN YOUR
ANSWERS, PLEASE.
IF YOU HAD TO TALK TO A PERSON,
WHAT'S A GOOD WAY TO START?
AND GO.
**
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE YOUR IDEA OF HOW TO
START A CONVERSATION.
JENNIFER, I NOTICED YOU WROTE
WITH YOUR TONGUE.
>> WELL, THERE'S STILL ONE
VARIANT I HAVEN'T GOTTEN.
>> OKAY.
JENNIFER SAID, "LET ME BE INSIDE
YOU, NOW."
AND JENNIFER, WHO DO YOU IMAGINE
SAYING THAT TO?
>> ANYONE FROM STRANGERS TO
PARENTS.
>> OKAY.
SORRY.
THAT'S INCORRECT.
YOUR BRAIN IS NOT OKAY.
VICTOR, HOW WOULD YOU START A
CONVERSATION?
LET'S SEE.
"HEAVEN MUST BE MISSING AN ANGEL
BECAUSE WHEN I WOKE UP THERE WAS
A GLOWING FIGURE HOVERING OVER
MY BED.
I GUESS IT COULD HAVE BEEN A
GHOST.
I'M WORRIED I'M LOSING MY GRIP
ON REALITY.
HA-HA-HA."
>> YES, I'VE GIVEN THE GHOST A
NAME.
BLUEBAR.
>> OKAY, WELL THAT'S VERY
INCORRECT.
YOUR BRAIN IS ALSO BAD.
>> WHEN YOU TALK, ALL I PICTURE
IS THE SKELETON INSIDE YOUR
HEAD.
>> WELL, MAMA.
OKAY.
DEREK, IT'S DOWN TO YOU.
AND YOU WROTE, "IF YOU SET THE
CLOCK AHEAD YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
ALIVE AS LONG."
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD, I WON?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAME UP WITH A GREAT WAY TO
MINIMIZE THE TIME WE'RE AWAKE
AND ALIVE.
AND YOU CAN CHOOSE YOUR PRIZE.
A TWO-WEEK ALL-INCLUSIVE TRIP TO
HAWAII OR YOU CAN GO BACK TO
YOUR APARTMENT AND STAY THERE.
>> APARTMENT.
>> THEY ALWAYS SAY APARTMENT.
THANKS FOR WATCHING "IS MY BRAIN
OKAY?"
IF YOU'VE GOT TO ASK, IT'S
PROBABLY NOT.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> THESE DAYS WHEN I SIT DOWN
TO WATCH A MOVIE,
I CAN FIND
JUST ABOUT ANYTHING IN THE
WORLD.
BUT NIGHT AFTER NIGHT, THERE'S
ONLY ONE KIND OF MOVIE I'M
ALWAYS LOOKING FOR.
* AND THAT'S A *
* SHORT-ASS MOVIE
A REALLY SHORT MOVIE
LIKE AT MOST AN HOUR 40 *
* GIVE ME THAT
SHORT ASS MOVIE
A SHORT-ASS MOVIE *
* A REALLY SHORT MOVIE
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
I AIN'T GONNA SIT HERE *
* AND WATCH NO LONG-ASS MOVIE
FOUND A FLICK
ABOUT TO PICK IT *
* BUT RIGHT BEFORE
I CLICK IT
I LOOK DOWN *
* RIGHT BELOW THE LINE
AND THAT'S WHEN I SEE
THE RUN TIME *
* 3 HOURS 47 MINUTES
BRO YOU MUST BE CRAZY
NO THANKS *
* I'M GONNA WATCH
A SHORT-ASS MOVIE
LIKE DRIVING MISS DAISY *
* I'M NOT PUSHIN' P
UNLESS IT'S
UNDER TWO HOURS *
* LIKE LION KING
OR BAD MOMS
OR ALL THREE AUSTIN POWERS *
* I HEARD THE BATMAN
WAS GREAT
SO I WENT TO A THEATER *
* AND SAW IT
I PISSED MY PANTS TWICE
THAT [ BLEEP ] WAS LONGER *
* THAN THE HOBBIT
GIVE ME THAT
SHORT-ASS MOVIE *
* A 90-MINUTE MOVIE
LIKE LIAR LIAR
EVIL DEAD *
* ERASERHEAD
A SHORT-ASS MOVIE
A REALLY SHORT MOVIE *
* 'CAUSE I'M A SIMPLE MAN
WITH NO ATTENTION SPAN
GIVE ME THAT *
* SHORT-ASS MOVIE
LIKE BAMBI
GOT TO BE TINY BUT GOOD *
* LIKE SHRIMP SCAMPI
AND WHEN IT'S MOVIE NIGHT
YOU WON'T BE GETTING
ANY YESES *
* IF YOU ROLL UP
TO THE CRIB
WITH ONE OF THEM *
* DOUBLE VHSs *
>> WHY DOES THIS MOVIE LOOK LIKE
A BOOK?
>> BYE-BYE.
* I ALWAYS KEEP IT A HUNNID *
* KEEP THAT RUNNING TIME
UNDER 100
IF MY ASS STUCK ON *
* THE COUCH FOR MORE
THAN TWO HOURS
IT CAUSES ME DISCOMFORT *
* WE TRIED TO WATCH
THE MOVIE HEAT
WHEN WE WAS HANGING *
* AT MY HOUSE
BUT BARELY 20 MINUTES IN
MY BOYS WERE DROOLING *
* ON THE COUCH *
>> THE ONLY ONE NOT SLEEPING IS
THE WEIRD GUY WHO PICKED THE
MOVIE.
>> I STAND BY MY CHOICE.
* GIVE ME THAT *
* SHORT-ASS MOVIE
A REALLY SHORT MOVIE
LIKE ENCINO MAN *
* YES PLEASE
OR GOOD TIME
BY THE SAFDIES *
* A SHORT-ASS MOVIE
A REALLY SHORT MOVIE
IF IT'S LONG *
* MY EYES GET GLASSY
NOW TELL THEM HOW IT IS
DIRT NASTY *
* YO IT'S YOUR BOY DIRT
IF YOU LIKE SHORT MOVIES
I'VE GOT NINE GREAT ONES *
* JUST WAITING
FOR YOU
THERE'S *
* ERNEST GOES TO CAMP
AND ERNEST SAVES CHRISTMAS
AND ERNEST GOES TO JAIL *
* AND ERNEST SCARED STUPID
THERE'S
ERNEST GOES TO SCHOOL *
* THAT'S ONLY 89 MINUTES
AND SLAM DUNK ERNEST
THAT ONE'S *
* GOT KAREEM IN IT
THERE'S ERNEST IN THE ARMY
MADE ME WANT TO *
* JOIN THE SERVICE
- AND ERNEST GOES TO AFRICA
- THAT POSTER *
MAKES ME NERVOUS
BUT THE GREATEST
THING OF ALL *
* A TRUE THING OF BEAUTY
IS THE THREE-MINUTE SHORT
BEFORE EVERY PIXAR MOVIE *
>> IT'S SO SAD.
>> SO THINK ABOUT THIS.
SEX AND THE CITY 2 WAS 2 HOURS
AND 26 MINUTES LONG.
TO PUT THAT IN PERSPECTIVE, THE
MOVIE "JURASSIC PARK"
WAS TWO
HOURS AND SEVEN MINUTES LONG.
THAT WAS A MOVIE THAT TOLD THE
HISTORY OF DINOSAURS,
HOW DNA WORKS
AND EXPLAINED THE SCIENCE
OF BRINGING DINOSAURS BACK TO
LIFE.
AND "SEX AND THE CITY 2," YOU
KNOW, WHICH WAS A MOVIE ABOUT
FOUR WOMEN WE ALREADY KNEW, WAS
20 MINUTES LONGER.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT'S BAD OR
ANYTHING.
I'M JUST SAYING, THAT'S SOME
CRAZY [ BLEEP ] RIGHT?
>> HOW LONG WAS "THE KING OF
STATEN ISLAND?"
>> IT WAS LIKE 2 HOURS AND
17 MINUTES.
BUT WE NEEDED -- WE NEEDED ALL
THOSE MINUTES.
* GIVE ME A SHORT-ASS MOVIE *
* A REALLY SHORT MOVIE
GIVE ME A SHORT-ASS MOVIE
A REALLY SHORT MOVIE *
* EVERY NIGHT *
SHOP TV HOME SHOPPERS.
DOT AND RHETT BACK LIVE WITH
Y'ALL.
>> DOT AND RHETT.
I THINK RHETT AND DOT SOUNDS
BETTER.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO BE A PILL
ALL HOUR?
>> MAYBE.
>> AYE, AYE, AYE.
OKAY, WELL, IT'S 5:00 P.M.,
WHICH MEANS IT'S TIME FOR SQUEAL
DEALS.
WE ASKED Y'ALL TO FIND A NEW
SQUEAL SOUND EFFECT WEEKS AGO.
>> SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE'S GETTING
KILLED, ODELL.
IT'S CHILLING, ODELL.
>> NEED SOMETHING LIGHT.
OKAY.
LATER IN THE HOUR WE LOVE HIM
HERE.
THOMAS PARKER NUBS WILL UNVEIL
HIS NEW LINE OF CHRISTIAN
LUNCHBOXES.
>> THE ARTWORK FEATURES JESUS
DOING MODERN YOUNG PERSON
THINGS.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
IS THAT JESUS?
GOT ON ONE OF THOSE OCULUS VR
DOODADS?
>> OH, KIDS ARE GONNA FLIP.
>> WELL, SPEAKING OF KIDS, OUR
FIRST SQUEAL DEAL TODAY IS AN
ADORABLE DOLL.
>> OH, IS SHE GORGEOUS?
>> YEAH, AND WE HAVE THE
DESIGNER HERE, MR. KEVIN -- NOW,
IS IT LICKETT?
>> YES, SIR.
MY MAMA ALWAYS SAID WE WAS NAMED
LICKETT BECAUSE WE'RE SO SWEET.
>> AW.
THAT'S ADORABLE.
KIND OF MADE ME SAD FOR SOME
REASON.
BUT OKAY.
TELL US ABOUT THIS PRETTY LADY
HERE.
>> THIS IS RILEY RAINBOW LOCKS.
>> GET OUT.
WHAT A CLEVER NAME.
>> STUDENT BY DAY AND MAGICAL
POP STAR BY NIGHT.
>> OOH.
I LOVE THAT.
>> PERFECT ROLE MODEL FOR LITTLE
GIRLS.
>> OR LITTLE BOYS.
WE GET IN TROUBLE IF WE DON'T
SAY THAT.
>> AND HERE'S THE BEST PART,
YOUR CHILD CAN CUT AND STYLE
RILEY'S RAINBOW LOCKS HOWEVER
THEY WISH.
AND WHEN THEY WANT TO GIVE HER A
NEW DO, YOU JUST TURN THIS HERE,
AND HER HAIR GROWS.
>> OH, WOW.
>> GET OUT OF TOWN.
WELL, THAT'S AMAZING.
>> AND YOU CAN GET THIS PRETTY
LADY FOR JUST $34.99.
>> ORDER WITHIN THE HOUR AND YOU
GET AN ADDITIONAL OUTFIT AND TWO
EXTRA HAIR SPOOLS FOR FREE.
>> NOW LOOKS LIKE SHOPPERS ARE
ALREADY SCOOPING HER UP.
LET'S GO TO THE SHOP TV PHONE
LINES.
HI, CALLER.
>> OH, MY NIECE IS GOING TO LOVE
THIS DOLL.
YOU KNOW, WHAT EXTRA OUTFIT DOES
SHE COME WITH?
>> I'LL SHOW YOU.
BY THE WAY, RILEY'S VERY EASY TO
CHANGE.
IT'S ALL VELCRO.
JUST WATCH THIS.
>> OKAY.
A LITTLE CHANGE.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NOW, WHAT THE HELL?
WHY DOES THAT DOLL HAVE A
RAINBOW BUSH?
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT A BUSH.
>> SURE LOOKS LIKE ONE TO ME.
THAT'S A 1970s RAINBOW BUSH.
>> IT'S NOT.
THAT'S THE END OF THE HEAD SPOOL
INSIDE SO YOU CAN SEE THE SPIN.
IT'S AN ANCHOR POINT.
ANY DOLL MAKER WOULD KNOW THAT.
>> WELL, I'M NOT A DOLL MAKER.
SO WHAT I SEE IS A THICK-ASS
RAINBOW VAJAFRO.
I WILL BE CANCELING MY ORDER.
GOODBYE.
>> OKAY.
>> I DIDN'T MAKE A VAJAFRO.
>> Y'ALL DON'T NEED TO KEEP
SAYING VAJAFRO.
>> YOU NEED IT SO THE SPOOL
SPINS AND THE HAIR ON THE HEAD
WILL GROW BACK.
IT'S DOLL MAKING 101.
>> OKAY, IF YOU'RE JUST JOINING
US, THIS IS NOT PRIVATE HAIR.
>> IT ANCHORS THE SPOOL INSIDE.
>> ODELL, CAN WE MAYBE GET A
PRODUCT IMAGE?
MAYBE THROW THAT UP WHILE WE PUT
RILEY'S OUTFIT ON.
>> YOU GET RILEY RAINBOW LOCKS
FOR THE SHOP TV EXCLUSIVE PRICE
OF JUST $34.99.
>> AND LOOK WHO'S ALL DRESSED
AND READY TO HIT THE BEACH.
RILEY IS READY FOR SUMMER WITH
THIS RETRO ONE-PIECE SWIMSUIT.
>> CUTE, CUTE, CUTE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I MIGHT TRY AND
STICK IN SOME OF THIS BUSINESS.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
>> IT'S STICKING OUT.
>> I KNOW.
BUT A GROWN MAN POKING HIS
FINGERS AROUND THAT AREA.
>> HE SAID THE DOLL'S IN
COLLEGE.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER IF SHE'S IN
YOU KNOW WHAT, CAN WE JUST CUT
AWAY FROM THIS CLOSE-UP?
OKAY.
LET'S TALK TO SOME PEOPLE WHO
ORDERED A RILEY RAINBOWLOCKS.
>> YEAH, CALLER, YOU'RE ON WITH
SHOP TV.
>> THIS IS A COLLECT CALL FROM A
FEDERAL CORRECTIONS FACILITY.
PRESS 1 TO ACCEPT THIS CALL
FROM --
>> THE PALMDALE PERVERT.
>> HANG UP, ODELL.
>> NO THANK YOU, WE DO NOT
ACCEPT THAT CALL.
>> ICKY, ICKY CALL.
YOU KNOW WHAT, IN FACT, I THINK
I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND PUT
THE OTHER RILEY WE'VE GOT HERE,
THE ONE WITH CLOTHES ON -- NOW,
KEVIN.
TELL US WHAT HAPPENS IF RHYLEE
RUNS OUT OF HAIR FROM THE SPOOL
INSIDE.
CAN IT BE REPLACED?
>> IT SURE CAN.
IT'S VERY EASY.
SOMETIMES PART PLACEMENT CAN BE
A LITTLE HAIRY.
>> LOOK AT YOU MAKING A LITTLE
JOKE.
>> SO YOU JUST PUSH THE QUICK
RELEASE BUTTON HERE ON THE BACK.
>> OKAY.
THAT IS -- THAT'S KIND OF A
YUCKY PLACE TO PUT A BUTTON.
>> WELL, IT HAD TO GO THERE
BECAUSE IT HAS TO CONNECT TO THE
PANEL LATCH.
ANY DOLL MAKER WOULD KNOW THAT.
>> YOU KEEP SAYING THAT AS IF
WE'RE ALL DOLL MAKERS, BUT WE'RE
NOT, SWEETIE.
YOU ALMOST FINISHED IN THERE?
>> YEAH.
SORRY.
BUTTON'S STUCK.
SOMETIMES YOU'VE GOT TO WIGGLE
IT.
>> OH, HER PRETTY FACE IS FACING
THE CAMERA.
LET'S CHECK THOSE SALE NUMBERS.
ITEMS SOLD.
OH, MY GOD.
THESE ARE SELLING LIKE HOTCAKES,
RIGHT NOW.
>> SOMETIMES IT HELPS IF YOU
RELEASE THE LATCH AND PULL THE
HEAD HAIR AT THE SAME TIME.
>> WHY WOULD YOU GO -- WE CAN'T
SHOW THAT!
>> WE'RE MOVING ON.
AFTER THE BREAK OUR NEXT SHOP TV
SQUEAL DEAL.
>> THAT'S A WORSE SOUND EFFECT,
ODELL!
>>> OH, NO WAY.
WILL SMITH?
EXCUSE ME, MR. SMITH?
I KNOW I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO TALK
TO YOU.
I'M JUST A SEAT FILLER.
BUT I WANTED TO SAY I AM A HUGE
FAN, MAN.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
THAT MEANS A LOT.
>> I LOVE ALL OF YOUR MOVIES.
PURSUIT OF HAPPYNESS IS SO
INSPIRING.
I JUST SHOWED IT TO MY SON.
>> I LOVE THAT, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
>> AND NO JOKE, "GETTING JIGGY
WITH IT" IS MY RING TONE TO THIS
DAY.
>> THAT'S HILARIOUS.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SOUND CORNY
BUT YOU'RE MY HERO, MAN.
THIS IS THE COOLEST NIGHT OF MY
LIFE.
WILL SMITH.
CHRIS ROCK JUST GOT UP ON STAGE.
CAN I GET A SELFIE REAL QUICK?
>> OF COURSE.
>> JADA.
I LOVE YOU.
G.I. JANE 2.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT.
>> BE RIGHT BACK, MAN.
SO WHERE ARE YOU FROM, MAN?
NOWHERE, MAN.
>> I LIKE YOUR TUX.
BY THE WAY, LOOK GOOD, FEEL
GOOD.
AM I RIGHT?
KEEP MY WIFE'S NAME OUT YOUR
[ BLEEP ] MOUTH!
MAN, I LOVE THE OSCARS, MAN.
I LOVE MOVIES, MAN.
I JUST SAW "PADDINGTON 2."
BEST MOVIE I'VE EVER SEEN.
I LOVE THAT LITTLE BEAR.
ONE SECOND.
KEEP MY WIFE'S NAME OUT YOUR
[ BLEEP ] MOUTH!
WHAT ABOUT A SELFIE, MAN.
WHAT'S UP?
>> NO, MAN.
THAT'S OKAY.
>> COME ON, MAN, LET'S DO IT.
>> NO, I DELETED MY PHONE.
>> ENJOY THE SHOW, MAN.
>> BATHROOM LINE IS CRAZY.
WHAT'D I MISS?
OH, MY GOD.
WE'RE RIGHT NEXT TO WILL SMITH?
I'VE GOT TO TWEET THIS.
WOAH, AND HE'S TRENDING.
OH, MY GOD.
>> HEY.
NICE TO MEET YOU, MAN.
I'M WILL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> I DON'T -- THEY DIDN'T GIVE
ME ONE.
>> THAT'S WEIRD.
AMY SCHUMER'S BEING HILARIOUS,
RIGHT?
HEY, WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE
COMEDIAN?
>> CHRI- -- NOBODY.
I DON'T THINK ANYTHING IS FUNNY.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE COMEDIAN,
MAN?
>> DORY.
>> WHO?
>> "FINDING DORY."
>> YOUR FAVORITE COMEDIAN IS
FINDING DORY?
WELL, SHE IS A FUNNY FISH.
RICHARD WILLIAMS WAS A FIERCE
PROTECTOR OF HIS FAMILY.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M GOING TO SAY THAT IN MY
SPEECH, MAN.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, WHAT ELSE SHOULD I SAY?
WHAT ELSE COULD I POSSIBLY SAY?
>> LOVE MAKES YOU DO CRAZY
THINGS?
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> LOVE MAKES YOU DO CRAZY
THINGS.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I'M GOING TO USE THAT.
I'M GOING TO CREDIT YOU.
>> PLEASE DON'T.
>> THE LAST COUPLE YEARS HAVE
BEEN CRAZY.
WITH COVID.
THE ZOOM MEETINGS.
THE RED TABLE TOP.
Y'ALL EVER SEEN RED TABLE TOP?
>> NAH, I'VE NEVER --
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING,
ACTUALLY.
>> HEY, DON'T ANSWER THAT MAN!
LET IT RING.
EVERYTHING IS NORMAL, Y'ALL!
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, GUNNA.
**
I'M THE BANK
I SMACK HER *
* SHE LOVE TO GET SPANKED
I TACKLE HER
LOVE TO WRESTLE *
* YOUNG BACHELOR
WE LOVE TO PLAY
SUN COME OUT WHEN *
* I MOVE THE DRAPES
KNOW MY MOVE WHEN
I GRAB YOUR WAIST *KNN YOU CAME*
* I LOVE YOU IN SO MANY WAYS
DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU NEVER COMPLAIN *
* AND WITH YOU
I CAN NEVER BE SHAMED
AND I USUALLY *
* NEVER SAY NEVER
AH LOOK AT ME TODAY
LOVE YOUR VIBE *
* I DON'T NEED NO SAGE
CLIP COLD AND YOUR
CAR LOOK GLAZED *
* GOOD SEX
AIN'T ALL WE MADE
I DON'T WANNA *
* GET TIRED OF YOU
I'M IN THE -- AND
WE WAY AT THE TOP *
* AND WE GOT US A OCEAN VIEW
I KNOW I GOT IT
I'M ALL IN HER BODY *
* AND NOBODY GOT A CLUE
WE IN A COUPE PULLIN' UP
BOARD A PRIVATE *
* A G5 FOR ONLY TWO
I REALLY LIKE IT
I WAN' STAY EXCITED *
* DON'T WANNA GET
TIRED OF YOU *
* OOH, DON'T WANNA GET
* YOU WAKE UP AND YOU
WANNA GO SHOPPIN' *
* PICK OUT A CAR
YOU GOT TOO MANY OPTIONS *
* BUBBLEGUM BABY, YEAH
YOU GOT IT POPPIN'
LOVE WHAT YOU DO *
* I DON'T WANT HER
TO STOP ITANOT US A OCEAN VIEW
I KNOW I GOT IT *
AND NOBODY GOT A CLUE
WE IN A COUPE PULLIN' UP *
* BOARD A PRIVATE
A G5 FOR ONLY TWO
I REALLY LIKE IT *
* I WAN' STAY EXCITED
DON'T WANNA GET
TIRED OF YOU *
* OOH, DON'T WANNA GET
* DON'T WANNA GET
TIRED OF YOU *
**
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS ARE
SAYING THAT VLADIMIR PUTIN IS
BEING MISINFORMED BY HIS
ADVISERS ABOUT HOW BADLY THE
RUSSIAN MILITARY IS PERFORMING
IN UKRAINE.
WHICH IS KIND OF LIKE WILL
SMITH'S AGENT TELLING HIM, "YOU
CRUSHED IT AT THE OSCARS."
WILL SMITH, FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DON'T KNOW, WALKED ON STAGE
DURING THE ACADEMY AWARDS AND
SLAPPED CHRIS ROCK AFTER HE MADE
A JOKE ABOUT JADA PINKETT-SMITH,
WHICH I THINK WAS A DISGRACEFUL
ACT THAT SETS A TERRIBLE
PRECEDENT FOR HAVING TO DEFEND
YOUR WIFE AT AWARDS SHOWS.
>>> DURING HIS ACCEPTANCE SPEECH
WILL SMITH SAID, "LOVE WILL MAKE
YOU DO CRAZY THINGS."
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE MAKES YOU DO
CRAZY THINGS?
CRAZY.
BUT I UNDERSTAND WHERE WILL'S
COMING FROM.
I MEAN YOU CAN'T EXPECT HIM TO
SIT THERE AND WATCH ANOTHER MAN
JUMP ALL OVER HIS WIFE.
WITHOUT SIGNING AN NDA.
>>> YESTERDAY WILL SMITH
RESIGNED FROM THE ACADEMY OF
MOTION PICTURES ARTS AND
SCIENCES.
HE WASN'T GOING TO.
BUT THEN JADA GAVE HIM THAT
LOOK.
IF WILL SMITH HAD BEEN EXPELLED,
HE WOULD HAVE JOINED A SMALL
GROUP OF PEOPLE KICKED OUT OF
THE ACADEMY INCLUDING BILL
COSBY, ROMAN POLANSKI, AND
HARVEY WEINSTEIN.
OR AS THEY'RE ALSO KNOWN, "BAD
BOYS FOR LIFE."
>>> CAN WE STOP PRETENDING
EVERYBODY KNEW JADA HAD
ALOPECIA?
AS MUCH AS WE HEARD ABOUT JADA
AND WILL'S PERSONAL LIVES, YOU
CAN'T EXPECT US TO RETAIN
EVERYTHING.
IT'S LIKE KANYE SAYING "DON'T
ACT LIKE Y'ALL DIDN'T KNOW I HAD
PSORIASIS."
JUST SELFISHLY AS A COMEDIAN I'M
TIRED OF PEOPLE PUTTING THEIR
INSECURITIES ON MY JOKE
INTENTIONS.
I CAN'T MAKE A JOKE ABOUT IT
BEING COLD OUTSIDE WITHOUT
SOMEBODY YELLING BACK, "STOP
MAKING FUN OF MY SMALL PENIS!"
KEEP MY SMALL PENIS --
GO AHEAD.
I'M SORRY.
>>> I ALSO REALLY LOVE THAT THE
REASON THEY LET WILL SMITH STAY
IN THE AUDIENCE WAS THAT THEY
ASKED CHRIS ROCK AND HE SAID IT
WAS OKAY.
SO NOW WE JUST ASK THE VICTIM
RIGHT AFTER THEY GET HIT IN THE
HEAD?
"HEY, ARE YOU COOL IF THE GUY
WHO JUST ATTACKED YOU HANGS
AROUND FOR A WHILE?
YOU DON'T WANT TO MAKE HIM MAD
AGAIN."
I CAN'T BELIEVE THE ACADEMY HAS
A WORSE CONCUSSION PROTOCOL THAN
THE NFL.
AND HONESTLY, I CAN'T EVEN BLAME
THE ACADEMY FOR NOT KNOWING WHAT
TO DO.
NOBODY KNEW WHAT TO DO.
EVEN PEOPLE AT THE OSCARS WERE
GOOGLING, "DID WILL SMITH JUST
SLAP CHRIS ROCK?"
I THINK WE SHOULD JUST
ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THAT WAS ONE OF
THE CRAZIEST THINGS WE WILL EVER
SEE IN OUR LIVES.
IT'S TRULY LIKE THE SUPER BOWL
WARDROBE MALFUNCTION BUT IF
JANET'S NIPPLE SLAPPED
TIMBERLAKE.
>>> NOT TO MENTION, CHRIS ROCK
HAS BEEN VERY PUBLIC ABOUT HIS
NON-VERBAL LEARNING DISORDER.
WHICH MEANS IT'S HARD FOR HIM TO
UNDERSTAND NON-VERBAL SIGNALS.
SORT OF LIKE HOW WHEN HE SAW AN
ANGRY WILL SMITH CHARGING TOWARD
HIM INSTEAD OF MOVING OUT OF THE
WAY HE PUT BOTH HIS HANDS BEHIND
HIS BACK, SMILED AND SAID,
UH-OH.
>>> AND IN NON-OSCARS NEWS,
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN MADISON
CAWTHORN, WHO'S THE ONE ON THE
RIGHT --
#?
THAT 70-YEAR-OLD REPUBLICANS
INVITED HIM TO AN ORGY AND DID
COCAINE IN FRONT OF HIM.
WAIT, SO YOU WENT TO THE OLD MAN
ORGY?
AND YOU THOUGHT THE WEIRD PART
WAS DRUGS?
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM, SEEN
HERE PICTURING THE ORGY MADISON
CAWTHORN --
#?
BROWN JACKSON IS A PERSON OF
EXCEPTIONALLY GOOD CHARACTER BUT
HE WOULD NOT SUPPORT HER FOR THE
SUPREME COURT.
SO LIKE MANY SOUTHERN GENTLEMEN,
HE'S COMFORTABLE WITH BLACK
FOLKS UNTIL THEY WANT TO MOVE IN
NEXT DOOR.
>>> U.S. OFFICIALS ARE CONCERNED
THAT VLADIMIR PUTIN IS KEEPING
MILITARY UNITS POSITIONED NEAR
KYIV DESPITE EARLIER PROMISES TO
WITHDRAW.
PUTIN'S FAILURE TO PULL OUT HAS
EARNED HIM THE NICKNAME NICK
CANNON.
WERE CRITICIZED FOR ASKING
IRRELEVANT, SENSATIONAL
QUESTIONS DURING THE SUPREME
COURT CONFIRMATION HEARING OF
JUDGE KETANJI BROWN JACKSON.
HERE TO COMMENT IS ONE OF THOSE
SENATORS, MARSHA BLACKBURN.
>> HELLO, COLIN.
OH, WOW.
WHAT A WEEK.
ALL ANYONE IS TALKING ABOUT ARE
THESE CONFIRMATION HEARINGS.
OH, WE CRUSHED IT.
SO MANY GREAT, SMART QUESTIONS.
ARE BABIES RACIST?
IS MURDER BAD?
AND THOSE ARE REAL QUESTIONS
THAT MY FELLOW REPUBLICANS ASKED
AN ADULT JUDGE.
>> RIGHT, YEAH.
AND WHAT DID YOU ASK HER?
>> OH, I HIT HER WITH THE COUP
DE GRACE.
YOU READY FOR THIS?
DEFINE WOMAN.
>> DEFINE WOMAN?
>> DEFINE WOMAN.
AND SHE COULDN'T DO IT.
I MEAN, HUH?
>> WELL, IT'S KIND OF A NUANCED,
COMPLICATED QUESTION.
>> COMPLICATED HOW?
>> WELL, OKAY.
HOW DO YOU DEFINE WOMAN?
>> ARE YOU JERKING MY PERM?
YOU HONESTLY DON'T KNOW?
COLIN, IT'S BIOLOGY, COLIN.
OKAY?
IT'S YOUR PRIVATE PARTS.
THE ONES YOU HAVE WHEN YOU'RE
BORN.
BUT JUST THE BOTTOM PRIVATE
PARTS BECAUSE THE ONES LATER --
OKAY, I'M GOING TO -- IT'S YOUR
PERIOD.
UNLESS YOU'RE OLD OR YOUNG.
OR PREGNANT.
OR STRESSED OUT.
OR DOING GYMNASTICS.
NO, SCRATCH THAT.
I'M GOING BACK TO BABY PRIVATES.
FINAL ANSWER.
>> BABY PRIVATES?
>> IT'S NOT JUST BIOLOGY.
OKAY?
WOMAN IS CHEERLEADER,
NURSE, TEACHER, PROSTITUTE.
COME ON.
YOU'VE SEEN THEM.
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT BE
SHOPPING.
>> I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> YES, YOU DO.
WOMAN IS LIKE --
UH, UH, UH.
AND MAN IS LIKE UH! UH!
>> YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE.
>> YOU ARE JUST NOT GETTING IT.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
OOH, YES.
DON'T WE LOVE THESE BIG STUPID
DUMB-ASS BOARDS WITH THESE BIG
STUPID DUMB-ASS PICTURES?
COME ON, LOOK HOW SIMPLE IT IS.
THE COLOR PINK.
THE ONES WITH BEEHIVE HAIRDOS
AND A PART SIDE.
IT'S LONGER THINNER CIGARETTES.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE HAVING FUN
DANCING AROUND IN A COMMERCIAL
FOR UNDERWEAR YOU CAN PEE IN.
DO YOU GET IT YET?
>> I THINK I GET IT LESS.
>> OKAY.
WELL --
>> WHY IS DEFINING WOMAN EVEN
RELEVANT TO A CONFIRMATION
HEARING?
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
IT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
FOR A SUPREME COURT JUSTICE.
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT A
WOMAN IS, HOW THE HELL ARE YOU
GOING TO TAKE HER RIGHTS AWAY?
CAN I GET AN AMEN?
>> NO.
MARSHA BLACKBURN.
>> SOMEONE SAID THEY WANT TO SET
ME ON FIRE.
HOUSE TO JOIN MSNBC.
DAMN.
SHE'S STILL AT WORK AND HAS HER
NEXT JOB LINED UP.
THAT'S AS CRAZY AS SOME OF THE
SKETCHES ON "THAT MICHAEL CHE"
THIS SUMMER ON HBO MAX.
>>> WORKERS AT THE ADAMSON
WAREHOUSE IN STATEN ISLAND VOTED
TO BECOME THE FIRST AMAZON
WORKERS IN THE COUNTRY TO FORM A
UNION.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE NEW UNION EXPLAINS AMAZON'S
NEW SLOGAN.
"IT WOULD BE A REAL SHAME IF
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOUR
PACKAGE."
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW STUDY,
MEN WHO EAT TOO MUCH MEAT ARE
RAISING THE RISK OF BECOMING
INFERTILE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, THIS DUDE HAS
FIVE KIDS THAT WE KNOW OF.
>>> THE CONSERVATIVE MEDIA
THEY WILL SPEND $100 MILLION TO
CREATE CHILDREN'S PROGRAMMING TO
COUNTER WOKE MEDIA COMPANIES.
PROGRAMS WILL INCLUDE "CLIFFORD
THE BIG STRAIGHT DOG."
ENCANTO, BUT IN ENGLISH.
AND "ONE FISH, TWO FISH, THAT'S
HOW MANY FISH GENDERS THERE
ARE."
>>> WILDLIFE OFFICIALS SAY THAT
A FLAMINGO THAT ESCAPED FROM A
KANSAS ZOO 17 YEARS AGO HAS BEEN
SPOTTED IN TEXAS.
OR, AND HEAR ME OUT.
FLAMINGOS LOOK LIKE OTHER
FLAMINGOS.
>>> WILDLIFE OFFICIALS IN
TENNESSEE HAVE CAPTURED A
500-POUND BLACK BEAR LIVING ON A
COLLEGE CAMPUS.
A BLACK BEAR THAT, LET'S FACE
IT, TOOK THE SPOT OF MORE
DESERVING WHITE AND ASIAN BEARS.
>>> IN A RECENT INTERVIEW TYLER
PERRY REVEALED THAT HE HAS USED
HIS MADEA VOICE WHILE HAVING
SEX.
DAMN.
DUDE MUST LIKE SEX DRY AS HELL.
>>> A NEW STUDY SHOWS THAT IN
THE PAST 20 YEARS PREDIABETES IN
CHILDREN HAS MORE THAN DOUBLED.
THANKS LARGELY TO THE POPULARITY
OF MOUNTAIN DEW BREAST MILK
BLAST.
ROCK AT THE OSCARS SEEMS TO HAVE
DIVIDED HOLLYWOOD, WITH MANY
CELEBRITIES PUBLICLY TAKING
SIDES.
HERE TO COMMENT IS -- AND HE
WROTE HIS OWN INTRO.
HEISMAN TROPHY WINNER AND STAR
OF "NAKED GUN," O.J. SIMPSON.
>> HEY.
SNL.
WELL, IT'S ALWAYS GOOD TO HEAR
APPLAUSE FOR O.J.
>> HI, O.J.
SO WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON, CHRIS
ROCK OR WILL SMITH?
>> OH, NOW MICHAEL, YOU KNOW ME.
I HATE CONFLICT.
THEY BOTH SEEM LIKE GOOD GUYS.
BUT HONESTLY-I DIDN'T EVEN
UNDERSTAND CHRIS ROCK'S JOKE.
WHAT THE HELL IS G.I. JANE?
>> OH, THAT'S JUST A MOVIE FROM
THE '90s.
>> THE '90s?
OH, I DON'T REMEMBER NOTHING
FROM THE '90s.
THAT WHOLE DECADE IS MY N WORD.
ANYHOO.
IN MY HUMBLE OPINION, WILL SMITH
MIGHT HAVE OVERREACTED BY
SLAPPING CHRIS ROCK.
I MEAN, WILL, I DON'T WANT TO
SAY THAT YOU GOT RAGE ISSUES.
BUT HEY, IF THE GLOVE FITS.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU'RE ON CHRIS ROCK'S SIDE?
>> WELL, I DIDN'T SAY ALL THAT,
MICHAEL.
I MEAN, CHRIS AIN'T EXACTLY
INNOCENT EITHER.
NOBODY LIKES TO BE MADE FUN OF.
I MEAN-U MIGHT BE TOO YOUNG TO
REMEMBER BUT PEOPLE USED TO MAKE
A LOT OF MEAN JOKES ABOUT ME.
>> REALLY?
ABOUT WHAT?
>> ALL KIND OF STUFF.
SOMETIMES JOKES CAN GO TOO FAR.
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT'S ABOUT A
MAN'S FAMILY.
BECAUSE LIKE WILL SMITH SAID IN
HIS SPEECH, LOVE WILL MAKE YOU
DO CRAZY THINGS.
ALLEGEDLY.
>> SO YOU'RE ON WILL SMITH'S
SIDE.
>> I ALREADY SAID I'M NOT
ANYBODY'S SIDE, MICHAEL.
DON'T YOU BE ACCUSING ME OF --
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I AIN'T ACCUSING YOU, MAN.
>> SORRY.
MIGHT HAVE LOST IT I LITTLE BIT
THERE.
WHENEVER PEOPLE ACCUSE ME OF
STUFF IT MAKES ME JUST WANT
TOO --
ANYHOO.
I JUST WANT TO GIVE THEM
BROTHERS SOME ADVICE.
YOU KNOW?
WHENEVER YOU FEEL ANGER BUBBLING
UP INSIDE, INSTEAD OF REACTING
JUST DO WHAT I DO, TAKE A NICE
LONG DRIVE.
OR MAYBE LET A FRIEND DRIVE YOU
AROUND SO YOU CAN LAY DOWN IN
THE BACK AND CALL THE NEWS
STATIONS.
>> YOU KNOW, O.J., SOME PEOPLE
ARE SAYING THE ACADEMY SHOULD
TAKE AWAY WILL SMITH'S TROPHY.
>> YOU AIN'T TAKING MY TROPHIES!
ALL RIGHT?
>> RELAX, MAN.
CALM DOWN.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT, MICHAEL.
HEY.
CAN I MAKE A BIG CONFESSION
THAT'S BEEN A LONG TIME COMING?
>> YES.
PLEASE.
>> I DIDN'T WATCH THEM OSCARS.
>> O.J. SIMPSON, EVERYBODY.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, MAN.
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE" I'M
MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> HE ISN'T GONE, SON.
POP-POP WILL ALWAYS LIVE ON
INSIDE OF ALL OF US.
>> THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> WELL SAID, SIR.
>> WELL, SWEETIE, ARE YOU READY
TO SAY GOOD-BYE?
>> YEAH.
BUT FIRST I WANT TO SHARE
SOMETHING WITH YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW, THIS SPOT WAS WHERE
POP-POP WOULD TAKE ME AFTER MY
BALL GAMES.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, I WASN'T MUCH
OF AN ATHLETE.
OKAY, OKAY.
HA HA.
BUT POP-POP, HE'D TAKE ME HERE,
HE'D POINT OUT TO THE SEA AND
SAY, "SON, LIFE IS LIKE THE
TIDE.
THERE'S HIGHS AND LOWS BUT
EVENTUALLY IT ALL WASHES AWAY."
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU, DAD.
>> WOW.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL STORY,
MR. KLEIN.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING.
>> THANK ALL OF YOU FOR ALLOWING
US AT BOUDREAU'S MORTUARY FOR
ALLOWING US TO BE PART OF THIS
MOMENT WITH YOU.
>> NOW IF YOU'RE READY, PLEASE
BOW YOUR HEADS AS WE SCATTER THE
REMAINS.
READY?
>> OH GOD, NO!
>> THESE MOMENTS ARE ALWAYS SO
HARD.
WE'LL GIVE YOU FOLKS SOME SPACE.
>> WHAT THE HELL DID YOU JUST
DO?
>> WE SAID GOOD-BYE TO POP-POP.
>> HE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
CREMATED!
>> WHO WAS?
>> MY FATHER.
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE CREMATED,
NOT CHUCKED OFF A CLIFF.
>> MM.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY.
>> SO THAT WAS NOT RELAYED TO
US.
>> YEAH.
BUT IN A WAY WASN'T THIS KIND OF
BETTER?
>> I'LL SPEAK ON THAT.
>> WELL, YOU GOT THE BODY ASPECT
OF A BURIAL BUT WE STILL GOT TO
THROW HIM.
>> YEAH.
I LIKE THAT.
WELL --
**
>> TIME FOR THE DREADED CHECK.
DAMN YOU, SIR!
WHO'S THE BOSS AROUND HERE?
YOU, I ASSUME?
JUST KIDDING, SPORT.
MAYBE --
>> DO NOT TOUCH ME, MAN!
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SIR, WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO PAY FOR
THIS.
>> MM.
MAY I ASK WHY?
>> YOU THREW MY FATHER-IN-LAW
OFF A CLIFF!
>> OKAY.
SEE, I THOUGHT WE RESOLVED THAT.
>> NO, WE DID NOT!
>> HONEY, CALM DOWN.
YOUR CONDITION.
>> OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS ARE MAD.
HOW ABOUT I JUST GO GET HIM?
AH!
>> SO WHAT YOU GUYS GOT COOKING
UP THIS WEEKEND?
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT THAT.
>> WHY DID YOU BRING AN URN?
>> OH, THIS?
THIS ISN'T AN URN.
IT'S SOUP.
>> YOU KEEP SOUP IN AN URN?
>> NO, IT'S A THERMOS.
IT LOOKS LIKE AB URN.
I GOT IT AT THE MORTICIAN'S
CONFERENCE.
>> I GOT HIM.
>> GOOD JOB, MAN.
>> WHAT WERE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT?
>> THEY WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
THE URN.
>> OH, THE THERMOS?
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
>> NO, IT ISN'T.
IT'S NOT COOL!
JESUS, JUST GET THE BODY BACK!
>> DON'T WORRY, SIR.
I GOT POP-POP RIGHT HERE.
>> THAT ISN'T POP-POP.
>> THAT'S CLEARLY A YOUNG
CYCLIST.
HE'S WEARING THOSE LITTLE SHOES.
>> MM.
MM-HMM.
OKAY.
AND THAT'S A DEALBREAKER FOR YOU
GUYS?
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST PUT HIM BACK.
SO HEY.
YOU THINK I CAN GET SOME OF THAT
SOUP?
>> OH, HELL, YEAH.
HEADS UP.
IT'S SHRIMP BISQUE.
LIKE WHETHER HE DID IT OR NOT.
>> WOW.
THAT IS INSANELY COOL.
AND BRADFORD, KATIE WAS SAYING
THIS IS YOUR FIRST TIME IN NEW
YORK?
>> YEAH.
IT'S BEEN REALLY AWESOME.
THE CITY'S LIKE REALLY
INTERESTING.
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO SHOW MY
FAVORITE COUSIN WHAT THE BIG
APPLE'S ALL ABOUT.
>> HEY, GUYS.
SORRY I'M LATE.
>> OH, BRIAN!
BRIAN, THIS IS MY COUSIN
BRADFORD.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
GUYS, I HAD THE CRAZIEST
MORNING.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
>> TELL US.
>> BRIAN'S OUR COLLEGE FRIEND.
HE HAS LIKE THE BEST STORIES.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S AMAZING.
BEAR WITH ME.
SO I'M HAVING COFFEE WITH MY
BOSS ANTHONY.
>> OH, WOW.
OKAY.
>> RIGHT.
I MEAN, WE DO THAT A LOT.
BUT WE'RE AT THIS FRENCH SPOT BY
THE OFFICE.
>> OH.
HERE WE GO.
FRENCH.
GREAT.
>> YEAH, IT'S JUST A COOL LITTLE
CAFE WE GO TO EVERY COUPLE
WEEKS.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> ANYWAY.
THE WAITER COMES UP TO US AND
HE'S LIKE HEY, WE MADE THIS
EXTRA CHEESE CREPE.
DO YOU GUYS WANT IT?
>> OH, NO.
I THINK I SEE WHERE THIS IS
GOING.
THIS IS -- PLEASE, PLEASE.
>> SORRY.
JUST LET ME -- I'M JUST GOING TO
FINISH THE STORY REAL QUICK.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OF COURSE.
YEAH.
>> SO WE ACCEPT THE CREPE.
WHY NOT?
I PUT MY FORK IN.
>> I'VE GOT LIKE A MENTAL
PICTURE RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS AMAZING.
>> BRADFORD.
COME ON.
>> TURNS OUT IT'S TRIPLE
CHOCOLATE.
KEEP IN MIND IT'S 11:00 A.M.
>> OH, MY GOD!
BECAUSE I THOUGHT IT WAS LATER.
NO!
>> YEAH.
I'M LIKE DUDE SAID IT WAS
CHEESE.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> IT'S THE FRENCH WAITER.
WAS HE LIKE HIGH ON DOPE OR
SOMETHING?
>> WHAT?
NO.
I'M GETTING TO IT.
>> BY THE WAY, SO NEW YORK.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
ANYWAY, I LOOKED OVER.
WHO'S SITTING AT THE BAR WITH A
SLY GRIN ON HIS FACE?
>> THE FRENCH WAITER.
>> NO.
>> OBAMA?
>> WHAT?
NO.
>> OKAY, WAIT, WAIT.
DON'T TELL ME IT WAS FRANK.
>> IT WAS FRANK.
>> OH, MY GOD, FRANK.
>> THAT IS HILARIOUS.
>> FRANK?
WAIT.
WHO'S FRANK?
>> HE'S JUST OUR FRIEND.
HE'S A BIT OF A PRANKSTER.
>> WOW.
THAT IS -- I'VE NEVER HEARD
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH.
KIND OF FUNNY.
RIGHT?
ANYWAY, HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
HOW WAS MEXICO?
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT WAS SO FUN --
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
SO THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> DID YOUR BOSS JUST WIG OUT?
HE'S LIKE KNOCKING OVER THE
TABLE LIKE AH, EVERYONE'S FIRED!
>> NOPE.
IT'S PRETTY MUCH THE END OF THE
STORY, MAN.
>> OH.
BUT THE FRENCH WAITER WAS HIGH
ON DOPE, RIGHT?
>> WHAT?
HIGH ON DOPE?
>> NO.
EVERYTHING WAS NORMAL.
IT WAS JUST A DUMB STORY.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ELSE?
>> OH.
SORRY.
I THOUGHT THE FRENCH WAITER WAS
HIGH ON DOPE THE WHOLE TIME.
STILL AMAZING.
>> THE PLACE WAS FRENCH.
NOT THE WAITER.
I NEVER SAID THE WAITER WAS
FRENCH.
>> OH.
SORRY.
>> IT'S FINE.
ANYWAY, YOU SAID MEXICO WAS
GOOD?
>> SO GOOD.
YEAH.
TURNS OUT YOGA RETREATS ARE
RELAXING.
WHO KNEW?
>> DIDN'T MEAN TO CALL THE
WAITER FRENCH.
MY BAD.
SORRY AGAIN.
>> ALL GOOD, DUDE.
LET'S JUST DROP IT.
WE'RE MOVING ON.
>> WELL, BRADFORD HAD A GREAT
TIME AT THE MET.
IT WAS SO COOL, RIGHT?
>> I REALLY DID LOVE THE STORY,
MAN.
>> THANKS.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE
CRAZY BOSS AGAIN?
WAS IT ANDERSON?
>> IT WAS ANTHONY.
WE DON'T NEED TO TALK ABOUT IT
ANYMORE REALLY.
>> ANTHONY.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE PERFECT NAME
FOR IT.
REALLY SORRY IF I SCREWED UP THE
STORY.
>> BRADFORD.
IT'S FINE.
>> NO.
IT'S ACTUALLY NOT.
BRIAN, YOUR STORY WAS AMAZING.
IT HAD GREAT CHARACTERS.
AND THE PART WHERE THE CREPE
ISN'T CHEESE WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
AND THEN I MESSED THE WHOLE
THING UP.
I DON'T DESERVE TO BE YOUR
FRIEND.
>> DUDE, WE JUST MET.
HONESTLY, IT'S FINE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
LUNCH IS ON ME.
AND I WANT TO PAY YOUR RENT FOR
THE REST OF THE YEAR, TOO.
>> WHAT?
THAT'S SUPER GENEROUS, MAN.
>> HERE'S A CHECK FOR $1,000.
THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.
>> THAT'S NOT EVEN ENOUGH FOR
ONE MONTH'S RENT.
>> OH, OKAY.
DIDN'T KNOW.
WELL, SEE YOU.
HEY.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, GUNNA.
YEAH PUSHIN' P, TURN ME UP
TURN ME UP, P, UH-AH *
* POINTERS IN THE PATEK AND
MY PIECE, I'M PUSHIN' P
COPPED NEW HAMMERS *
* FOR MY P
WE DON'T WANT NO PEACE
GOT A SPOT ACROSS THE SPOT *
* EXOTIC PS
SHE NOT A LESBIAN, FOR P
SHE TURN PESBIAN *
* PUSH P, PUSH P *
* OFF CAPITAL P
I ROCK THESE PRESIDENTS
COUNT PRESIDENTS *
* PORTUGUESE ON HER
MOPPIN' DOWN A P
SHE LET ME SQUEEZE *
* THEN SHE LEAVE 'CAUSE
SHE KEEP IT P
* I'M PUSHIN' P, YEAH
PUSHIN' P *
* I'M PUSHIN' P
* I'M PUSHIN' P, YEAH
POP A P, I'M PARANOID
I CAN'T JUST SLEEP *SHIN', UH, H
WATCH IS PINK *
* PUSHING P, PUSHING P *
* YEAH *
THE KIDS.
>> YOU KNOW HE'S GOING TO BE A
HEARTBREAKER JUST LIKE HIS DAD.
>> OH, LOOK.
THEY'RE LIKE A TINY LITTLE BABY
COUPLE.
>> NOT TO ASSUME.
MAYBE THAT'S WEIRD FOR YOU GUYS.
I'M SORRY.
>> NO, WE THINK IT'S CUTE.
>> YOU LOVE SEEING YOUR LITTLE
ONE AS A FUTURE HEARTBREAKER.
BUT WHAT IF YOU DON'T WANT TO
ASSUME YOUR BABY'S GOING TO BE
STRAIGHT?
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
WITH THE NEW FORMED THIS WAY
LINE FROM OSHKOSH B'GOSH.
YOUR LITTLE TYKE WILL LOOK
ADORABLE WITHOUT BEING SO
EXCLUSIVE.
WITH SAYINGS LIKE "FUTURE
TWINK."
LIL' LES.
MESSY DJ.
AND "IN THE CLOSET" BECAUSE I
CAN'T WALK.
>> I PRAY TO GOD MY SON IS GAY.
>> I WOULD LOVE THAT.
>> BORN THIS WAY HAS DESIGNS
YOUR BABY WILL LOVE.
LIKE WORDPLAY.
>> ROCK-A-BI BABY.
>> MY MOMMY HAD A DADDY.
>> POLITICAL STATEMENTS.
>> I LOVE MILK.
HARVEY MILK.
R.I.P.
>> SILENCE EQUALS VIOLENCE.
BUT CRYING EQUALS HUNGRY.
>> ALEXANDER HAMILTON WAS A
TURF.
>> AND BUTCH.
>> OH, WHAT IS THIS?
A TINY BELT LOOP FOR A RING OF
KEYS?
THIS SLAYS.
>> SOME PARENTS FORCE THEIR KIDS
TO WEAR LITTLE SPORTS JERSEYS.
MY SON CAN BE WHOEVER HE WANTS.
>> IMAGINE BOXING A CHILD INTO
SOMETHING THAT DOESN'T FEEL
RIGHT.
>> I WOULD HATE THAT.
>> IT'S SO ARCHAIC TO PIERCE
YOUR BABY'S EARS FOR THEIR
BAPTISM.
OUR KIDS WILL NEVER HAVE TO
CONFORM TO SOMETHING THEY DON'T
WANT.
THANKS, BORN THIS WAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE DATING.
>> OH, PLEASE.
THEY'RE NOT EXCLUSIVE.
YOU KNOW HOW GAY GUYS ARE.
>> BORN THIS WAY.
FROM OSHKOSH B' GOSH.
OH, RELAX.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY CAN READ.
**
>>> I'VE GOT TO SAY THIS HAS
BEEN ONE OF THE BEST WEEKS OF MY
LIFE.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
THE CREW, THE AMAZING CAST.
LORNE AND THE CAST OF WRITERS.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
FUTURE, GUNNA.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU GUYS.
HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.