>>> YOU'RE WATCHING C-SPAN.
UP NEXT, FORMER PRESIDENT TRUMP
ADDRESSES RESIDENTS OF EAST PALESTINE, OHIO
FOLLOWING THIS
MONTH'S TRAIN DERAILMENT.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
HELLO. IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE HERE IN THE
TOWN OF EAST PALESTINE,
NOT A
GREAT NAME.
BUT I HAD TO COME HERE AND SEE
THESE WONDERFUL PEOPLE
WHO HAVE
BEEN ABANDONED BY BIDEN.
HE'S ON SPRING BREAK IN UKRAINE
WITH HIS FRIEND ZELENSKYY IN THE
T-SHIRT, VERY DISRESPECTFUL.
ZELENSKYY THINKS HE'S ROCKING
THAT RINGADEE LIKE SCOTT PILGRIM.
BUT I'M HERE, AND I BROUGHT HATS.
CAMERAS AND HATS BECAUSE IT'S
TERRIBLE WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
EARLIER TODAY, A FARMER CAME UP
TO ME, BIG FELLA,
AND HE SAID,
SIR, WE HAVE NOTHING TO EAT
BECAUSE OUR DIRT IS POISON,
AND
I SAID, WELL, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
EATING THE DIRT?
DON'T EAT THE DIRT, FOLKS.
DON'T EAT THE DIRT.
YOU SHOULD BE EATING THE COLD
McDONALD'S I BROUGHT YOU,
AND
TRUMP ICE.
I'LL BE HONEST, I JUST PUT MY
STICKER ON SOME DASANI.
WE LIKE TO SAY DASANI.
I'VE HEARD ALL ABOUT YOUR
SITUATION WITH THE WATER,
BUT I
WAS LOOKING AT YOUR RIVER, AND
IT'S SO SHINY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN WATER SO BEAUTIFUL.
BEAUTIFUL RAINBOWS AND
DISCOLORATION.
IT'S GREAT.
IT'S WEARING MAKEUP.
FENTY BEAUTY WATER.
FENTY BY RIHANNA.
BY THE WAY, SHE WAS PREGNANT
DOING SUPER BOWL.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I SAID, OF COURSE SHE IS.
SHE'S NOT MOVING AT ALL.
SHE WAS JUST DOING ARMS THE
WHOLE TIME.
BUT YOUR TRAIN EXPLODED.
AND WHO DO WE BLAME?
WHO DO WE BLAME?
WE BLAME BUTTIGIEG.
PETE BUTTIGIEG.
THIS WAS HIS RESPONSIBILITY.
UNFORTUNATELY, HE WAS TOO BUSY
BEING A NERD AND BEING GAY
TO
HAVE DEALT WITH THE VERY MUCH
MORE IMPORTANT ISSUE
OF SHOULD
DRAINS HAVE BIG POISON.
AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I CALL
HIM PETE BUTT.
I CALL HIM PETE BUTT.
THERE'S NO WAY AROUND IT.
THAT'S JUST THE BEST ONE.
BELIEVE ME, I'VE TRIED IT EVERY
WHICH WAY,
AND IT REALLY DOESN'T
GET BETTER THAN PETE BUTT.
BUT THIS WOULD HAVE NEVER
HAPPENED UNDER MY
ADMINISTRATION.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING I MADE THE
TRAINS LESS SAFE.
NOT TRUE.
OKAY?
I DID A LOT FOR TRAINS.
I MADE THEM BIGGER, FASTER,
LESS SAFE PERHAPS, BUT
I'M PAYING MY
RESPECTS BECAUSE YOUR TRAIN
EXPLODED
AND NOW YOUR BIRDS AND
FISH ARE ALL DEAD.
WAKE UP IN THE MORNING AND NOT
HEAR THE BEAUTIFUL CHIRPING OF BIRDS
AND INSTEAD HEAR TRAINS
EXPLODING AND DERAILING ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
YOUR TOWN IS HURTING.
THAT'S WHY YOU NEED ME.
I FEEL LIKE I COULD "SCHITT'S
CREEK" THIS PLACE, RIGHT?
BUT I NEED BIG EYEBROWS.
YOU WATCH "SCHITT'S CREEK"?
NO, YOU GUYS WATCH YELLOW STONE.
THE DUTTONS.
ANYWAY, I HAVE A SURPRISE GUEST
THIS WEEK.
TV THIS WEEK
IT'S THE FOREMAN OF THE GEORGIA
GRAND JURY INVESTIGATING ME.
IT'S EMILY KOHRS.
THIS IS SO COOL.
FIRST GIULIANI AND NOW YOU.
SIR
SHE'S AN ODD DUCK, BUT WE
LIKE HER.
SHE'S EITHER 70 OR 40, BUT WE
CAN'T TELL.
SHE'S GOT A BIG SECRET FOR SUCH
A LITTLE LADY.
POTENTIALLY.
I MIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T LIKE THAT.
WE DON'T LIKE THAT SOUND.
BECAUSE SHE KNOWS IF I'M GETTING
INDICTED.
SHE'S HEAD JUROR, CAN YOU
BELIEVE THAT?
THEY ELECTED HER.
THEY'LL ELECT ANYONE.
I STARTED THAT.
SO COME ON, SPILL THE TEA.
COME ON.
NOPE.
YOU JUST WANT ME TO RUIN THE CASE.
BUT I GUESS I CAN SAY WE HAVE
BEEN SAYING YOUR NAME A LOT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
THEY ALMOST HAD ME,
AND THEN
THIS LITTLE HORSE GIRL COMES IN
AND SAVES THE DAY.
THANK YOU, EMILY.
FAIR THEE WELL.
DO WE LIKE HER?
SHE LOOKS LIKE HALEY JOEL OSMENT,
AND SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
WELL, I'M GOING TO GET OUT OF
HERE SOON BECAUSE THE AIR IS
FULL OF POISON.
BUT EVERYBODY IN OHIO ALWAYS ASKS ME,
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
THERE'S POISON GAS IN THE AIR.
COULD BE A GOOD THING.
I KNOW SOME OF THE HUSBANDS ARE HAPPY TO HAVE
THE STINKY GAS AS
AN EXCUSE.
- HONEY, DID YOU PASS GAS?
- NO, IT WAS THE TRAIN.
BLAME THE TRAIN, RIGHT?
YOU WOULD NORMALLY BLAME THE
DOG, BUT THEY'RE ALL DEAD NOW,
AREN'T THEY?
SO IN CONCLUSION, "SCHITT'S CREEK,"
RIHANNA, PETE BUTT,
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WOODY
HARRELSON!
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
HELLO, YOU BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE.
AND YOU UGLY PEOPLE TOO.
NO. I JEST.
THIS COUNTRY SEEMS SO DIVIDED,
BEAUTIFUL, UGLY, BLACK, WHITE, BLUE, RED,
I LOVE EVERYBODY.
MAYBE BECAUSE I'M A RED NECK HIPPY.
YOU KNOW, THE RED IN ME THINKS
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED TO OWN GUNS.
THE BLUE IN ME THINKS, SQUIRT
GUNS.
SO I'M RED AND BLUE, WHICH MAKES PURPLE.
I'M PURPLE.
SO THIS IS MY FIFTH TIME DOING SNL.
WELL, AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
NO JACKET. OKAY.
THE LAST TIME I DID SNL WAS
AROUND THANKSGIVING 2019,
THREE
YEARS AGO.
AND YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE WHAT
HAPPENED AFTER THE SHOW.
THE NEXT DAY-- IT WAS A SUNDAY,
AS IT ALWAYS IS THE DAY AFTER I
DO "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
IT'S LIKE A PATTERN I NOTICED.
ANYWAY, I WENT WALKING IN THE
GREATEST PART OF THIS CITY,
CENTRAL PARK,
LEANED AGAINST A
TREE, AND STARTED TO READ THE
CRAZIEST SCRIPT.
OKAY.
FULL DISCLOSURE, I SMOKED A
JOINT FIRST.
THE REASON I LIKE HERB MORE THAN ALCOHOL
IS BECAUSE IT MAKES ME
FEEL GOOD, NO HANGOVER,
AND I
NEVER WAKE UP COVERED IN BLOOD.
BUT REGARDLESS, I HAVE DECIDED
TO QUIT SMOKING POT ALTOGETHER,
AND I'M STICKING WITH IT--
UNTIL AFTER THE SHOW.
YEAH.
LAST WEEK IN AUSTIN, I WAS
TALKING WITH MY FRIEND NICK.
WE HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
HE WROTE "TRUE DETECTIVE" AND I
WAS IN "TRUE DETECTIVE."
I'M VEGAN, AND ALL THE ANIMALS
HE EATS ARE VEGAN.
ANYWAY, I WAS COMPLAINING ABOUT
HOW I START SMOKING AROUND NOON
AND GET PROGRESSIVELY DUMBER AS
THE DAY UNFOLDS.
FORGET BASIC WORDS, SIMPLE
OBJECTS E-T-CETERA.
I WAS HOPING THE WIFE MIGHT SAY,
OH, NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
INSTEAD SHE SAYS, AT LEAST
YOU'RE AWARE OF IT.
AND I SAY, WELL THAT DOESN'T
FEEL LIKE MUCH CONSOLATION.
AND SHE SAYS, THINK OF ALL THE
DUMB PEOPLE WHO DON'T KNOW
THEY'RE DUMB.
YOU'RE AHEAD OF THEM.
THANKS, HON.
BUT ON TOP OF THE HERB, I'M A
WEE BIT OF A DRINKER.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I WENT IRISH THERE.
ANYWAY,
BUT IN A PERSONAL
TRIUMPH, LAST YEAR,
I HAD SEVEN
MONTHS WITH NO ALCOHOL,
AND FIVE
GLORIOUS MONTHS.
ANYWAY, WHAT WERE WE TALKING
ABOUT?
OH, YEAH.
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT THAT SCRIPT.
SO I BLAZE A FATTY, WHICH, YOU
KNOW, I GOT IN LA
AT MY
DISPENSARY, THE WOODS.
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY, I DIDN'T
TRANSPORT THE HERB FROM
CALIFORNIA TO NEW YORK
BECAUSE
THAT'S HIGHLY ILLEGAL.
MY MANAGER, JEREMY, DID. YEAH.
HE MULED IT FROM LA.
YEAH. SPEAKING OF JEREMY, HE'S HERE
TONIGHT.
BROUGHT
NEWLY SINGLE, LADIES.
VERY HANDSOME.
I KNOW HE WOULD PREFER I TALK
ABOUT OUR MOVIE "CHAMPIONS"
THAT'S COMING OUT IN TWO WEEKS.
COMEDIC MASTERPIECE, BUT I'M NOT
HERE TO SELL "CHAMPIONS."
IT SELLS ITSELF.
PROJECTIONS HAVE IT MAKING MORE
THAN "AVATAR",
BUT WHATEVER, I'M
NO SALESMAN.
WHERE WAS I?
OKAY.
SO THREE YEARS AGO, CENTRAL PARK,
SUNDAY MORNING, THE LORD'S DAY,
TRYING TO RESIST THE
TEMPTATION TO PUFF TOO EARLY IN
THE DAY.
OF COURSE, I SUCCUMB.
LIKE A LOT OF PEOPLE, I HAVE A
DEVIL ON ONE SHOULDER,
AND ON
THE OTHER SHOULDER, I HAVE A
LARGER, MORE FRIGHTENING DEVIL.
AND THERE'S A BATTLE GOING ON IN
HERE.
I'M JUST SAYING I AM MANY
DIFFERENT THINGS,
ANARCHIST, MARKIST,
ETHICAL HEDONIST,
NONDISCRIMINATORY EMPATH,
EPISTEMOLOGY DECONSTRUCTIONIST,
A TEXAN.
BUT BACK TO THE TREE IN CENTRAL
PARK AND THAT SCRIPT.
PUT YOURSELF IN MY PLACE,
LAY THE CURVE OF YOUR NECK AGAINST
THE ROOTS OF THE TREE.
WHAT KIND OF TREE WAS IT?
WHAT KIND DO THEY HAVE IN
CENTRAL PARK?
OH, YEAH, IT WAS A PALM TREE.
LAY YOUR HEAD AGAINST THE PALM,
FIRE UP THE HOOTER FROM JEREMY,
AND START READING.
SO THE MOVIE GOES LIKE THIS,
THE BIGGEST DRUG CARTELS IN THE
WORLD GET TOGETHER
AND BUY UP
ALL THE MEDIA AND ALL THE POLITICIANS
AND FORCE ALL THE
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD TO STAY
LOCKED IN THEIR HOMES,
AND
PEOPLE CAN ONLY COME OUT IF THEY
TAKE THE CARTEL'S DRUGS
AND KEEP
TAKING THEM OVER AND OVER.
I THREW THE SCRIPT AWAY.
I MEAN, WHO WAS GOING TO BELIEVE
THAT CRAZY IDEA?
BEING FORCED TO DO DRUGS?
I DO THAT VOLUNTARILY ALL DAY
LONG.
ANYWAY, IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME.
STILL NO JACKET.
OKAY.
WELL, WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR
YOU TONIGHT.
HERE, WE|LL BE BACK
>>> ALL RIGHT, 6117, YOU GOT
FIVE MINUTES.
CARLA JEAN, GOD, IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOUR FACE.
I MISS YOU TOO, WILLY.
LOOK, I KNOW I MADE A DAMN
MESS OF THING ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT I SWEAR I'VE CHANGED.
I HOPE SO.
I'M TIRED OF COMING HERE, WILLY,
I REALLY AM.
I KNOW, HONEY.
LISTEN, WHEN I GET OUT OF HERE,
I'M GOING TO DO YOU RIGHT.
YOU HEAR ME?
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THE LIFE
YOU'VE ALWAYS DESERVED.
MARK MY WORDS, I'M GOING TO BE
OUT OF HERE SOON.
NO HE NOT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THAT'S YOUR CONVERSATION.
LISTEN HERE, CARLA JEAN.
YOU REMEMBER THAT HOUSE ON
CHERRY LANE, THE ONE WITH THE
WHITE PICKET FENCE?
WHEN I GET OUT OF HERE, I'M
GOING TO BUY US THAT HOUSE.
WHEW, IN TODAY'S MARKET?
THAT IS FUNNY.
I'M SORRY.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
SEEM TO ME LIKE YOU WANT ONE.
LEAVE ME OUT OF THIS.
ALL Y'ALL GET ON MY DAMN NERVES.
THIS MAN SAY HE'S GOING TO BUY
HER A HOUSE.
BUY A HOUSE.
YOU KNOW, CARLA JEAN,
PRISON'S BEEN GOOD FOR ME.
HE LYING.
I'M READING A LOT.
SAY HE WANT TO BUY A HOUSE.
I'M EVEN GOING TO GET MY GED.
I CAN'T BUY A HOUSE, AND I'M
NOT IN JAIL.
I RENT A ONE-BEDROOM APARTMENT
WITH A ROOMMATE.
ALWAYS SEEING HAIR ON MY BAR OF
SOAP, AND NOT FROM HER HEAD
EITHER.
WANT TO BUY A HOUSE.
I HAD A HOUSE.
EX-BOYFRIEND CAUGHT IT ON FIRE.
WOULD YOU PLEASE?
I'M TRYING TO TALK TO MY WIFE.
THAT'S YOUR WIFE?
Y'ALL STILL MARRIED?
LISTEN, BABY.
YOU'RE THE ONLY MAN FOR ME, AND
NO MATTER HOW LONG YOU'RE IN
HERE, WHETHER IT'S A DAY OR A
THOUSAND YEARS, I WILL ALWAYS
WAIT FOR YOU.
NO, SHE NOT.
I'M SORRY.
CAN YOU NOT?
HEY, I'M NOT HERE.
I'M JUST WALLPAPER, OKAY?
BUT SHE SURE HAD SOME TALL
BROTHER DROP HER OFF.
HE OUT THERE WAITING IN THE CAR,
AC CRANKED ALL THE WAY UP,
PROBABLY WASTING ALL THE DAMN
GAS, LISTENING TO CLUB RANDOM,
BILL MAHER'S PODCAST.
LITTLE WILLY JR. GROWING UP
SO FAST.
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
NO HE DON'T.
COME ON. WALLPAPER.
LITTLE BOY GOT RED HAIR, THOUGH.
YOU AIN'T GOT RED HAIR, HE AIN'T
GOT RED HAIR.
TALL BROTHER IN THE CAR GOT SOME
RED HAIR, THOUGH.
SOMEBODY'S MATH AIN'T MATHING.
THAT BOY LOOK LIKE CHUCKY.
YOU KNOW CHUCKY FROM THE RUG RATS.
NOT KNIFE CHUCKY.
COME TO THINK ABOUT IT, KNIFE
CHUCKY GOT RED HAIR TOO.
EVERY DAMN CHUCKY GOT RED HAIR.
NAME ME ONE THAT DON'T GOT RED HAIR.
PROBABLY CHUCK E. CHEESE.
WHAT'S HE?
A RAT WITH A HAT?
UNDERNEATH THERE PROBABLY SOME
RED HAIR.
I'M TIRED OF HEARING YOU.
I'M NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
WHAT I AM IS WALLPAPER.
EL PAPEL OF THE WATER.
HOLD UP.
CARLA JEAN, LET ME SEE THE PHONE.
YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME?
WHAT'S UP?
THIS FOOL OVER HERE TALKING
ABOUT HE GOING TO BUY HER A
HOUSE.
IT'S CALLED MANIFESTING.
WHY YOU EVES DROPPING?
THIS LADY OVER HERE TALKING
ABOUT SHE GOING TO WAIT FOR HIM
BECAUSE SHE THINK SHE GETTING
THAT HOUSE.
HOUSE?
HOW HE GOING TO BUY A HOUSE.
OUT THERE WITH THE DAMN
CHUCKY, GOT THE AC ALL JACKED
UP, LISTENING TO CLUB RAP, YOU
KNOW THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT CARS.
THEY GOT ME AS SOON AS I PAY
OFF SOME OF THAT--
YOU KNOW WHAT I SHOULD DO, GO
IN ON A TIMESHARE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING. OKAY.
I GUESS I'M JUST GOING TO GO.
YEAH, I'LL JUST HEAD BACK TO
THE JAIL.
GO ON AHEAD, MAN.
TALKING ABOUT ANOTHER CHUCKY
WITH RED HAIR.
>>> FELLAS, WHAT ARE WE UP TO
TONIGHT?
YOU GUYS COMING OVER, PLAYING
TONY HAWK?
- I'M BUSY TONIGHT.
- I'M TIRED TONIGHT.
YOU'RE BUSY AND YOU'RE TIRED?
- MAYBE TOMORROW.
- OH, YEAH.
COOL.
NO SWEAT.
NEXT TIME.
HEY, MAN.
EVERYBODY OKAY WITH YOU AND YOUR
LITTLE FRIENDS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M KIND OF WORRIED THEY'RE
HANGING OUT WITHOUT ME.
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD MAYBE
FOLLOW THEM, FIND OUT?
FOLLOW THEM?
YOU DON'T MEAN A--
YEAH.
A STAKEOUT.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING OUT HERE
IN THE SUBURBS?
WHO'S HOUSE IS THIS?
WOW, DUDE.
I'M GOING TO TEXT THEM.
- WHO'S THAT?
- BEN.
DID HE JUST THROW HIS PHONE
AWAY?
THAT'S A LOW BLOW, MAN.
WELL, TIME TO GO IN THERE AND
KILL THEM?
NO, MAN.
WHAT?
WE'LL MAKE IT LOOK LIKE A
ROBBERY.
JESUS, DUDE.
THAT'S NOT WHY WE'RE HERE.
I'M JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHY THEY BAILED ON ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THEM?
THEY LOOK REALLY COZY.
THIS IS REALLY NICE.
ARE THEY TOGETHER?
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
SHOULD WE HEAD OUT?
WE'RE NOT DONE, MAN.
OH, MY GOD.
THEY'VE GOT A BABY TOO.
KNOWN
- KIDS, DINO NUGGETS ARE READY.
- FAVORITE.
THEY HAVE A FAMILY?
UH-OH, AND ONE MOODY TEEN.
DINO NUGGETS AGAIN?
OKAY, MISTER, I WORKED VERY
HARD.
HONEY, RADICAL ACCEPTANCE.
THIS IS INSANE.
IT'S 2015.
IT'S NOT INSANE TO BE GAY.
IT'S NOT 2015, MAN.
AND I'M NOT MAD THEY'RE GAY.
I'M MAD ABOUT THIS SECRET
BEAUTIFUL LIFE THEY NEVER TOLD
ME ABOUT.
MAYBE THEY'RE SCARED TO TELL ANYONE.
KISS
KIDS, UNCLE KENAN IS HERE.
UNCLE
I'M GOING TO TEXT HIM BECAUSE
KENAN WOULDN'T LIE TO ME.
THEY CAN'T JUST KEEP THROWING
THEIR PHONES AWAY.
YOU NEVER SAW ANY SIGNS OF
THIS IN THE PAST?
NOT THAT I REMEMBER.
WE WOULD ALWAYS JUST HANG OUT
AND LAUGH TOGETHER.
MAYBE THEY WERE JUST AFRAID TO
TELL ME BECAUSE THEY'RE AFRAID
TO HURT ME.
THEY CAN'T RISK LOSING ME
BECAUSE THEY LOVE ME TOO MUCH.
ARE YOU SURE?
WHERE DID THEY EVEN GET THAT?
COME ON, KIDS.
TIME FOR BED.
WE GOT WORK TO DO.
WHAT WORK?
NEXT
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE DOING
AUDITIONS TO REPLACE YOU.
HAIRCUT
WAIT
I'M GOING IN THERE.
AND SATURDAYS, YOU'RE
AVAILABLE BECAUSE--
BEN--
IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
THEN TELL ME WHAT IT IS.
JOHN AND I HAVE A SECRET
FAMILY, AND WE'RE HOLDING
AUDITIONS TO REPLACE YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT IT WAS.
THIS IS INSANE, MAN.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
YOU'RE RIGHT, MAN.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WE SHOULDN'T BE HOLDING
AUDITIONS TO REPLACE HIM
BECAUSE
THERE'S ONLY ONE YOU.
WHAT
DO
ONLY
AND YOU ARE IRREPLACEABLE.
RIGHT, BEN?
THANKS, GUYS.
BAD BOYS FOR LIFE.
MAN, I FEEL LIKE WE'RE BACK AT NYU.
OH, MY GOD, DUDE.
SO MUCH BETTER THAN BEN.
HE'S THE PERFECT REPLACEMENT.
>>> OH, MAN, HERE WE ARE, Y'ALL.
COME ON.
Y'ALL WANT TO DO THE SLINGSHOT?
LOOK AT THIS THING, IT'S SO HIGH.
MAN, THAT'S WAY UP THERE.
COME ON.
IT'S NOT THAT HIGH.
LET DO IT.
WHO'S COMING?
YOU KNOW I CAN'T GET ON THAT THING.
I GET TOO SCARED.
COME ON.
PLEASE?
SAM WILL GO WITH YOU.
COME ON, SAMMY.
YOU CAN'T PUNK OUT IN FRONT OF
YOUR GIRL.
YEAH, SAM.
HE NEEDS A PARTNER.
YOU'RE BRAVE, RIGHT?
I GUESS.
GENTLEMEN, READY TO FLY?
WE'RE CLEAR FOR TAKEOFF.
YOU THINK THIS THING'S SAFE,
RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
JUST SHOOTS YOU UP 400 FEET IN
THREE SECONDS.
NO PROBLEM, RIGHT?
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME. YEAH.
JUST TEN Gs RIGHT IN YOUR FACE.
HOPE YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME AT ALL.
I'M A VETERAN.
I WAS IN THE AIR FORCE.
LOVE THAT.
I WANT TO GET OFF.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT, SAMMY.
I REALLY, REALLY WANT TO GET OFF.
HE CAN'T HEAR YOU, MAN.
JUST GET READY FOR THE COUNTDOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S HAPPENING IN THREE, TWO--
AHH!
OH, MY GOD, JESUS!
THIS IS SO HIGH!
WHOO!
IT'S LIKE WE'RE BIRDS.
HEY, KEVIN, I THINK I CAN SEE MY
HOUSE!
KEVIN, YOU SEE IT?
I GOT IT-- HEY, HEY!
HEY, MAN, YOU PASS OUT?
KEVIN?
?
OH, MY GOD, DID YOU SEE HOW FAST
THEY WEREN'T.
IT WAS SO INSANE.
HERE THEY COME.
HEY, YOU'RE ALIVE.
HOW WAS IT?
CRAZY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID THAT.
THEY SHOOT YOU UP SO HIGH.
THAT WAS PRETTY WILD.
SO WAS IT FUN?
OH, ACTUALLY, IT WAS.
I MEAN, THAT WAS A
ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE.
IT SURE WAS.
LET GO ON AND GET IN THE CAR
NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT, KEVIN, I'LL DO IT.
OH, YOU WANT TO DO IT?
YOU'LL DO IT WITH ME, RIGHT,
BABY?
OF COURSE.
GO, GIRL.
I LOVE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE DOING THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT NEITHER.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT A RETURN CUSTOMER.
VERY BRAVE.
YEAH, YEAH.
HEY, MAN, CAN WE GO UP REAL SOFT
AND COME DOWN REAL GENTLE LIKE.
NO CAN DO.
THIS THING HAS ONLY ONE SPEED.
BABY, WE'RE GOING TO BE OKAY,
RIGHT?
I WANT TO SAY YES.
I GUESS WE JUST GOT TO WAIT FOR
THE COUNTDOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
IN THREE, TWO-- AHH!
AHH!
OH, KEVIN!
KEVIN, YOU OKAY, BABY?
OH, MY GOD, TALK TO ME!
I'M PASSING OUT-- I'M
PASSING OUT!
YOU WERE IN THE AIR FORCE.
OH, YES, YES.
I WAS ONLY PAINTING THE PLANES, THOUGH.
KEVIN, JUST CALM DOWN.
BABY, I LOST MY JOB THREE
WEEKS AGO.
YOU LOST YOUR JOB?
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I'M 17 YEARS OLDER TOO BY THE
WAY.
I THOUGHT YOUR DADDY WAS GOING
TO TELL YOU.
WHAT?
KEVIN!
I'M PEEING.
I'M PEEING ON EVERYTHING, ALL
OVER THE PLACE, HONEY.
OH, GET ME OUT OF HERE!
YOU KNOW WHAT, I WANT TO DO IT.
OH, GOOD.
KEVIN WILL GO WITH YOU.
NO, I'M DONE.
OH, THIS IS FUN.
WHY IS NOBODY LISTENING TO
ME?
OH, I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
I'M NOT READY!
AHH!
CREW, PRESENT AND ACCOUNTED FOR, SIR.
THANK YOU, MR. DOBBS, AT
EASE.
LITTLE FISH, THERE'S TROUBLE OUT
THERE IN THE WATERS, SO THEY
TURNED TO US.
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING OUT THERE
WITH OUR PANTS DOWN, NO, SIR.
UNCLE SAM GAVE US FIRST CLASS
TICKETS ON A $5 BILLION NUCLEAR
SUBMARINE, AND THIS HIGH-CLASS
KILLING MACHINE HAS BEEN
ENTRUSTED TO US FOR ONE PURPOSE.
TO DEFEND OUR COUNTRY, GOD'S
COUNTRY.
NOW THE PRESIDENT MAY CALL THE
SHOTS, BUT THIS HERE IS MY
SUBMARINE.
AND IT'S A PROUD BOAT, ISN'T IT,
MR. DOBBS?
VERY PROUD, SIR.
IT REPRESENTS THE BEST OF US.
THE ABSOLUTE BEST, SIR.
AND THIS SHIP BEARS A NOBLE
NAME, DOESN'T IT, MR. DOBBS?
VERY NOBLE, SIR.
AND WHAT IS THAT NAME,
MR. DOBBS?
MR. DINGLEBERRY'S
GOOCHBALLOON ASDFJKL SEMICOLON
6969, SIR.
SAY IT AGAIN.
MR. DINGLEBERRY'S
GOOCHBALLOON ASDFJKL SEMICOLON
6969, SIR.
AND WHY DOES IT HAVE THAT
NAME?
BECAUSE IT WAS DECIDED BY AN
ONLINE POLL, SIR.
AND WHY DID WE LET THAT BE
THE NAME?
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T TAKE THE
POLL SERIOUSLY UNTIL IT WAS TOO
LATE, SIR.
AND WHAT PERCENTAGE OF PEOPLE
VOTED FOR THIS TO BE THE NAME?
AN OVERWHELMING MAJORITY,
SIR.
AND WHY DID WE HAVE A POLL IN
THE FIRST PLACE?
TO GET MORE FOLLOWERS ON
INSTAGRAM, SIR.
AND DID THIS MISSION SUCCEED?
WE GOT MORE VIEWS ON OUR
STORIES, BUT OUR FOLLOWERS GREW
AT PRETTY MUCH THE NORMAL RATE,
SIR.
AND WHO IS MR. DINGLEBERRY?
EVERYONE ASSUMES IT WAS YOU,
SIR.
AND WHAT WAS THE RUNNER UP IN
THE POLL?
DOOKY CRUISER, SIR.
AND WAS THAT ANY BETTER?
IT WAS SHORTER BUT EQUALLY
BAD, SIR.
AND WHAT DOES MR.
DINGLEBERRY'S GOOCHBALLOON
ASDFJKL SEMICOLON 6969 MEAN?
IT'S JUST WHAT YOU GET IF YOU
ROLL YOUR FINGERS ACROSS THE
FINGER BOARD, SIR.
AND HOW DID WE ASK TO
PRONOUNCE IT?
BY SAYING AS-DA-FA-JACKAL.
AND WE DECIDED WHAT?
THAT IT WAS TOO COMPLICATED
AND WE SHOULD JUST SAY THE NAME, SIR.
AND DID WE KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH THE SEMICOLON?
WE DID NOT, SIR.
SO WHAT DID WE DECIDE TO DO?
TO JUST SAY SEMICOLON, SIR.
AND WHO WAS BEHIND THIS?
>>@GAY KEVIN FROM THE OFFICE.
AND WHO WAS@GAY KEVIN FROM
THE OFFICE?
JUST A RANDOM GUY FROM THE
OFFICE, SIR.
HELLO, MY DARLING, IS IT
URGENT?
IS AND WHY IS IT URGENT?
AND WHY ARE YOU LEAVING ME?
AND ON WHICH DAYS WILL I SEE THE
KIDS?
OKAY, THEN.
NOW YOU KNOW WHO THINKS THEY
KNOW WHY MY WIFE IS LEAVING ME?
WE ALL DO, SIR.
AND WHY IS THAT?
BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T WANT TO BE
MRS. DINGLEBERRY, SIR.
AND WHO BLEW UP THE SUBMARINE
JUST NOW?
WE ALL DID, SIR.
AND WHY DID WE DO IT?
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT TO DIE
ON SOMETHING CALLED THE GOOCH
BALLOON, SIR.
DAMN RIGHT.
CHIEF OF THE BOAT, DISMISS THE CREW.
CREW.
AYAY.
MR. DINGLEBERRY CREW, FALL OUT
MEANS IT'S TIME TO START
SCREENING FOR CLONE CANCER, AND
THERE'S NO EASIER WAY TO DO IT
THAN WITH COLOGUARD, THE SIMPLE
BOX DELIVERED TO YOUR DOORSTEP.
HI.
I'M COLOGUARD.
OH, YEAH, MY DOCTOR ORDERED
YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE I'M SAFE, EASY TO USE.
HOW'S IT WORK?
I JUST NEED TO COLLECT A
SAMPLE, SO OPEN ME UP AND GO
INSIDE ME.
INSIDE YOU?
YEAH, JUST GO INSIDE ME.
IT'S OKAY.
I LIKE IT.
ARE YOU GOING TO LOOK AT ME
LIKE THAT WHILE I DO IT?
SURE.
I'M JUST SMILING BECAUSE I LOVE
MY JOB, AND I LOVE WHAT YOU'RE
ABOUT TO DO TO ME.
WELL, I DON'T LOVE THAT YOU
HAVE A FACE AND A LITTLE MOUTH.
AND A NAME.
I'M THOMAS.
WHY DO I HATE KNOWING THAT?
COME ON, IT'S FUN FOR BOTH OF US.
YOU GET THE SATISFACTION OF
KNOWING YOU'RE DOING EVERYTHING
YOU CAN TO PROTECT YOUR COLON,
AND I GET ANOTHER KIND OF SATISFACTION.
SO GO AHEAD, UNLOAD IN ME.
WHY IS THE U.P.S. GUY
WATCHING?
HE'S WAITING TO COLLECT THE
SAMPLE AFTER YOU'RE DONE.
GO AHEAD, UNLEASH.
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
DOING THIS IN FRONT OF YOU GUYS.
WOULD YOU FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE UNLOADING ON A
LITTLE WOMAN LIKE ME?
WOULD THAT MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE A
REAL MAN?
GOD, NO.
I JUST WANT TO BE SCREENED FOR
COLON CANCER.
THEN GO AHEAD, DESTROY ME,
DADDY, BLOW MY BOX OPEN.
YEAH, I WANT TO SEE YOU BLOW
THAT BOX WIDE OPEN.
THIS IS SICK.
BUT NOT SICK FROM COLON
CANCER.
SO JUST GO INSIDE HER, THEN PASS
THE SUPER WARM BOX TO THE U.P.S.
GUY.
GET IT NICE AND WARM BEFORE
YOU HAND IT BACK TO ME.
I'LL EVEN CLOSE MY EYES WHILE
YOU DO IT.
I SEE YOU PEEKING.
HOW MANY OF YOU ARE THERE?
IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE JUST HERE TO WATCH.
WE'RE FRIENDLY LIKE MINIONS,
SO GO AHEAD AND UNLEASH.
STOP SAYING UNLEASH.
WOULD IT HELP IF YOU KNEW
THEIR NAMES?
THAT'S KYLIE, VICTOR, NEIL, AND
SHEVAT.
WE CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU UNLEASH.
I'M ACTUALLY GOOD.
I JUST REMEMBERED THAT I
SCREENED FOR COLON CANCER LAST
YEAR, SO.
AND YOU WOULDN'T BE LYING TO
US, RIGHT?
OF COURSE NOT.
BECAUSE WE CAN ALSO DETECT LIARS.
NOW DROP YOUR PANTS, BLOW OUT
HIS BOX, AND THIS WILL ALL BE OVER.
JUST DO WHAT THE LITTLE BOXES
SAY TO DO.
I'LL GIVE YOU WHAT YOU WANT,
JUST PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
MAN, IS WOODY OKAY?
I KNOW HE SMOKES A TON OF
WEED, BUT I'M REALLY STARTING TO
WORRY ABOUT HIM. OH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S HEAD INSIDE AND GIVE HIM
SOME PRIVACY.
ACTUALLY, I'M GOING TO STAY.
I'M GOING TO WATCH HIM UNLEASH.
COLOGUARD, GO AHEAD, WE LIKE
COLOGUARD, GO AHEAD, WE LIKE IT.
HE'S BEEN HERE FIVE TIMES TOO.
DOES HE GET A JACKET?
ANYWAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
JACK WHITE.
I'LL BET YOU DO
WHEN YOU
TAKE OUT THE FIGURES
PULL ALL THE TRIGGERS
WELL YOU'RE
TAKING ME BACK
WHEN YOU LISTEN TO MYSTICS
LAY AT YOUR PICNICS
YOU'RE TAKING ME BACK
TAKING ME BACK
I'LL BET YOU DO
NOT FOR LONG
I'M ALONE
WHEN YOU
DROP THE MAIL OFF TO ME
MAKE US BOTH COFFEE
ARE YOU TAKING IT BLACK
BREAKING MY BACK
WHEN YOU
DROP THE MAIL OFF TO ME
MAKE US BOTH COFFEE
ARE YOU TAKING IT BLACK
ARE YOU TAKING ME BACK
I'LL BET YOU DO
BUT NOT FOR LONG
WHEN YOU TALK
ABOUT FRICTION
TALK ABOUT CHRISTMAS
ARE YOU TAKING ME BACK
TAKING ME BACK
WHEN I RECALL THE HISTORY
THESE KIDS ARE A MYSTERY
THEY'RE TAKING ME BACK
THEY ARE TAKING ME BACK
I'LL BET YOU DO
WHEN THE MOON IS ABOVE YOU
DOES IT TELL YOU I LOVE YOU
BY SCREAMING
WHEN THE SUN
STARTS TO FALL
IT'S CRUSHING THE WALLS
AND THE CEILING
I CAN'T CONTROL
WHEN THE DARK
COVERS THE LIGHT FROM
THE SPARKS IN THE CITY
TO KEEP US ALIVE GONNA HIDE
ELECTRICITY
WEEKEND
EVENING
WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE?
I'M COLIN JOST.
THIS WEEK, PRESIDENT BIDEN MADE
A HISTORIC VISIT TO UKRAINE AND
MED WITH UKRAINIAN PRESIDENT VLADIMIR ZELENSKYY
WHERE THEY
GREETED EACH OTHER LIKE TWO
ACTION FIGURES HAVING SEX.
ANN
BOTH
BARRIER
BIDEN
REPUBLICANS CRITICIZED
BIDEN UKRAINE
INSTEAD TO THE OHIO TOXIC
TRAIN DERAILMENT,
BUT BIDEN SAID
HE WAS WAITING TO SHOOT THE
TRAIN DOWN UNTIL IT WAS OVER THE
OCEAN.
>>> PRESIDENT BIDEN IS BEING
PRAISED FOR HIS SURPRISE VISIT
TO UKRAINE
BY TAKING A TEN-HOUR
TRAIN RIDE FROM POLAND.
YOU KNOW WHO ELSE
TAKES A TRAIN RIDE THROUGH AN
ACTIVE WAR ZONE?
EVERY NEW YORKER.
CHINA
IMPOSED A 12-PART PLAN FOR
PEACE.
THE PLAN IS THE 12 PARTS HAVE TO
BE ASSEMBLED BY CHILDREN.
DONALD TRUMP VISITED EAST
PALESTINE, THE SITE OF THE RECENT TRAIN DERAILMENT
BECAUSE
TRUMP YOU USUALLY TRIES TO MAKE
HIMSELF LOOK BETTER BY STANDING
NEXT TO A TRAIN WRECK.
THE TRAIN THAT DERAILED WAS
CARRYING HIGHLY TOXIC VINYL CHLORIDE
WHICH I THINK IS
SOMETHING TRUMP RECOMMENDED AS A
CURE FOR COVID.
WHILE VISITING THE DISASTER
SITE, TRUMP ALSO GAVE OUT
BOTTLES OF TRUMP BRAND WATER.
SAID RESIDENTS, THANKS, BUT WE
WOULD RATHER DRINK THE TOXIC
TRAIN WATER.
PETE BUD JEENL VISITED THE SITE,
AND WAS CRITICIZED FOR
WEARING LEATHER BOOTS.
GIVE HIM A BREAK.
THAT'S ALL THEY HAD AT BABY GAP.
TUCKER CARLSON SEEN HERE AT A
WHITES ONLY RAVE
HAS BEEN
GRANTED ACCESS TO OVER 40,000 HOURS
OF SECURITY FOOTAGE FROM
THE JANUARY 6th RIOTS.
WATCHING ALL THAT WOULD MAKE YOU GO INSANE,
SAID DOCTORS ABOUT
TUCKER CARLSON'S SHOW.
GEORGIA REPRESENTATIVE AND
COCAINE BEAR MARJORIE TAYLOR GREEN
TWEETED THE COUNTRY NEEDS
A DIVORCE.
WHICH MAKES SENSE.
FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON DeSANTIS IS
RELEASED A NEW MEMOIR
CALLED THE COURAGE TO BE FREE,
EVEN THOUGH
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A BLACK HISTORY
BOOK HE'S BANNED.
IT WAS ANNOUNCED THE
PRODUCERS OF THIS YEAR'S ACADEMY
AWARDS HAVE PUT UP A CRISIS TEAM
TO DEAL WITH INCIDENTS SIMILAR
TO LAST YEAR'S WILL SMITH SLAP.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
IF ANYTHING, IT HELPS RATINGS.
THE PROMO SHOULD BE, WHO'S GOING
TO GET SLAPPED THIS YEAR?
ARMAS TAR
WHICH BANSHEE WILL KNOCK THE
SHOES OFF?
AND WHO HAS WHAT IT TAKES TO
WHALE ON BRENDAN FRASER.
JAMES ARE STRUGGLING.
HERE IS NBA ANALYST AND HALL OF
FAMER BILL WALTON.
AMAZING TO BE HERE, SATURDAY
NIGHT LIFE, THE PREMIER COMEDY
SHOW IN THE HISTORY OF
CIVILIZATION.
MICHAEL CHE, LORD OF THE LOWER
EAST SIDE, THROW IT DOWN, BIG
FELLA.
SURE, MAN.
SO YOU'RE AN NBA ANALYST.
YOU ALSO HAVE YOUR OWN SHOW ON
NBA TV.
AND YOU'RE ALSO A LITTLE WEIRD.
MICHAEL, I'M AN ATHLETE, I'M
AN ANALYST.
I AM A SPIRITUAL NOMAD.
I AM A CURIOUS NYMPH IN GOD'S
ASTONISHING GARDEN, AND I WAS
JUST BACKSTAGE IN WOODY
HARRELSON'S DRESSING ROOM.
THE SECOND HALF OF THE SHOW IS
GOING TO BE BANANAS.
SO TODAY THE LAKERS ARE 13th
IN THE WESTERN CONFERENCE.
DO YOU THINK THEY'LL MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS?
THE LAKERS HAVE A HISTORY
THAT WOULD MAKE AVADAGO'S
BEAKERS BOIL WITH CHEMISTRY.
LeBRON, ANTHONY DAVIS, AND THE
NEWBY DEANGLO RUSSELL, THEIR ON
THE COURT ARTISTRY MOVES ME TO TEARS.
ANTHONY DAVIS FOR THREE, GREAT
SHOT.
ARE YOU CALLING A GAME RIGHT
NOW?
MY SPIRIT GUIDE SENDS ME
FLASHES OF WHAT IS, WHAT WAS,
AND WHAT SHALL BE.
SO I'M CALLING A GAME THAT TAKES
PLACE NEXT WEDNESDAY.
OH, D.LO WITH THE LAYUP, AND THE
LEAD IS CUT TO SIX.
SO YOU MUST KNOW THE FUTURE.
I'LL ASK AGAIN.
ARE THE LAKERS GOING TO MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS?
A LONG TIME AGO IN A GALAXY
FAR, FAR AWAY, GOD HERSELF
BIRTHED THE TECH TONIC MARVEL WE
CALL LOS ANGELES, CHE.
OUT OF BOUNDS.
LAKERS BALL, THE REFS ARE GOING
TO TAKE A LOOK AT THIS ONE.
YES!
WHAT WE NOW CALL PARADISE
STARTED AS A MEGABONE YARD, BUT
ITS SPIRIT HAS CARRIED ON JUST
LIKE THE GRATEFUL DEAD CARRIED
ON WHEN THEY BROUGHT IN THE
NOODLER OF NATIONS, JOHN MAYIER,
A POET WHOSE ONLY COLLEAGUES ARE
THE PLANETS THEMSELVES.
BIG DUNK FROM LeBRON, THROW IT
DOWN!
GOD, I WISH YOU COULD SEE THIS,
MICHAEL.
WELL, I CAN'T.
SO TELL ME ARE THE LAKERS GOING
TO MAKE THE PLAYOFFS?
YES OR NO?
YES THE LAKERS CAN MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS IF THEY CAN ANSWER ONE
SIMPLE QUESTION.
IS THERE AN AFTERLIFE, AND WHAT
SCIENTIFIC BASIS IS THERE FOR
THE PERSISTENCE OF THE SOUL
AFTER DEATH?
OH, FOUL ON DAVIS.
OH, FOR UNITY WITH THE STARS ARE
PLACED IN THE MASSIVE-- TO BE
CRADLED IN OUR CREATOR'S
MAGNIFICENT BOSSOM AND HAVE HER
WHISPER THE MAGICAL WORDS OF
JABA THE HUT.
BILL WALTON, EVERYBODY.
THE LAKERS ARE FOULED.
THANK YOU.
SOME OF HIS INSENSITIVE LANGUAGE
LIKE THE WORDS FAT AND UGLY AS
WELL AS MODERNIZING HIS
PORTRAYAL OF WOMAN.
WHICH WILL MOST LIKELY AFFECT
THE BOOK, THE FAT UGLY WIFE WHO
KNEW HER PLACE.
IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT
BRITTNEY GRINER HAS SIGNED WITH
THE PHOENIX MERCURY FOR ONE YEAR.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE WNBA PAYSLESS
THAN A RUSSIAN PRISON.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LIKE THIS
NEXT ONE.
A FOUR-FOOT LONG ALLIGATOR WAS
DISCOVERED IN BROOKLYN'S
PROSPECT PARK.
SO YOU CAN PROBABLY TAKE DOWN
ALL THOSE MISSING DOG POSTERS.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
YEAH.
THIS WEEK, BOTH HARVEY WEINSTEIN
AND R. KELLY WERE GIVEN
ADDITIONAL PRISON SENTENCES ON
TOP OF THE ONES THEY ARE ALREADY
SERVING, WHICH BRINGS US TO
MICHAEL CHE'S NEW SEGMENT.
WHAT DO THEY EVEN DO WRONG?
I MEAN, MAINLY THEY'RE GUILTY
OF LOVING TOO MUCH, RIGHT?
A PLAYER'S GOT TO PLAY.
AM I RIGHT, LADIES?
NO.
THIS HAS BEEN, WHAT DID THEY
EVEN DO WRONG.
YOU MAKE SOME GOOD POINTS, MICHAEL.
A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT NEW
JERSEY HAS THE SECOND WORST
ROADS IN THE COUNTRY.
WHILE THE WORST ROADS ARE THE
ONES THAT GO INTO NEW JERSEY.
EXPERTS HAVE DEBUNKED CLAIMS
THAT AN UNWANTED PREGNANCY CAN
BE TERMINATED WITH HIGH DOSES OF
VITAMIN C.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME I ASK A
WOMAN TO STAY OVER FOR
BREAKFAST, COLIN.
THE NBA'S SLAM DUNK CONTEST WAS
WON BY MAC McCLUNG, A 6'2" WHITE
MAN WHO HAS ONLY APPEARED IN TWO
NBA GAMES, WHICH IS JUST A
TERRIBLE WAY TO END BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
THE NATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF
SKIERS IS PUSHING FOR GREATER
REPRESENTATION OF BLACK PEOPLE
IN WINTER SPORTS, WHICH ARE
PREDOMINANTLY WHITE.
HUH, SO IT SEEMS LIKE SOMEONE'S
A LITTLE JEALOUS WE TOOK THEIR
PRECIOUS DUNK CONTEST.
MONDAY IS NATIONAL POLAR BEAR DAY.
PREVIOUSLY KNOWN AS NATIONAL
POLAR BEARS DAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVE THIS AUDIENCE.
THIS IS GOING GREAT FOR ME.
A WOMAN-- A WOMAN AT AN ART
FAIR IN MIAMI ACCIDENTALLY
SHATTERED A JEFF CON SCULPTURE
WORTH MORE THAN $40,000.
I GUESS IT'S LIKE YOU ALWAYS
SAY, COLIN, COONS AIN'T SAFE IN FLORIDA.
FLORIDA.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET ME KILLED.
A NEW STUDY SHOWS THE COVID BABY
BUMP IS OVER AS FEWER AMERICANS
ARE CHOOSING TO HAVE KIDS.
HERE TO COMMENT ON JOYS OF
MOTHER HOOD IS GINA BIANCHI, A
WOMAN WITH FOUR DAUGHTERS AND
ONE SON.
HEY, SWEETHEART.
YOU BOYS LOOK SO NICE.
THANK YOU.
SO YOU'RE A MOM OF FIVE.
TELL US ABOUT MOTHERHOOD.
I LOVE IT.
SO I'VE GOT MY FOUR DAUGHTERS,
AND MY DAUGHTERS ARE FINE.
BUT MY SON, OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE MY SON.
SO HE CAME OVER LAST SUNDAY, HE
WAS HUNGOVER.
HE'S ALWAYS HUNGOVER.
HE'S IN MY FRIDGE, HE'S PULLING
OUT HAM, TURKEY, THE MAYONNAISE.
HE'S FILLING UP A COOLER, HE
LEAVES, DOESN'T SAY BYE.
I'M CRACKING UP.
MY DAUGHTERS SAY, THAT'S MA'S
FOOD.
YOU CAN'T TAKE MA'S FOOD.
I SAY, WHO CARES?
GIRLS, SHUT UP.
ANTHONY'S 38 YEARS OLD.
HE'S A GROWING BOY.
MY DAUGHTERS, SO ANNOYING.
BUT MY SON, OH, I LOVE MY SON.
GOT IT.
SO WHAT WOULD YOU TELL SOMEONE
THAT'S ON THE FENCE ABOUT HAVING
KIDS?
THEY SURPRISE YOU EVERY DAY.
LIKE YESTERDAY, MY SON, HE CAME
OVER, WHAT WAS HE DOING?
OH, HE WAS GOING THROUGH MY
WALLET.
THE KID IS PULLING OUT 20, 40,
$60 BILLS.
HE WRITES HIMSELF A CHECK FOR 14
GRAND FROM MY CHECKBOOK.
WHAT'S HE WRITE IN THE MEMO?
PUTTING UP WITH MA.
I'M DYING OVER HERE.
MY DAUGHTERS SAY, THAT'S MA'S
MONEY.
YOU CAN'T TAKE MA'S MONEY.
I'M LIKE, GIRLS, PLEASE, YOU'RE
NOT PRETTY ENOUGH TO BE THIS IRRITATING.
BUT MY SON, OH, MY GOD, I LOVE
MY SON. YEAH. NO.
WE'VE HEARD A LOT ABOUT YOUR SON.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME ABOUT YOUR
DAUGHTER.
THEY'RE DOCTORS.
BUT MY SON DID THIS HILARIOUS
PRANK LAST NIGHT WHERE HE
PRETENDED TO ROB ME AT GUN POINT.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
MY DAUGHTERS SAY, YOU CAN'T
DO THAT.
MY DAUGHTERS, THEY BOUGHT ME A HOUSE.
BUT MY SON, I MEAN, I WOULD IF I
COULD.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL--
I WOULD.
I--
GETTING BACK TO THE TOPIC OF PARENTHOOD.
DO YOU THINK YOUR KIDS ARE GOING
TO HAVE KIDS SOME DAY.
OH, PLEASE.
THERE'S NOT A WOMAN OUT THERE
GOOD ENOUGH FOR MY SON.
SO ANTHONY'S SINGLE?
NO.
HE'S BEEN MARRIED FOR TWO YEARS.
AND I JUST HAVE THIS FEELING,
OKAY, THAT SHE IS GIVING HIM
NOTHING IN BED.
LIKE SHE COMPLETELY IGNORES HIS BALLS.
OKAY.
WHAT?
WHY ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT
THAT?
OKAY.
AND I BET SHE'S OBSESSED WITH
HAVING AN ORGASM.
LIKE, NO, HONEY.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
WHEN HE'S DONE, YOU'RE DONE.
GINA BIANCHI, EVERYONE.
I LOVE ALL MY KIDS EQUALLY.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M
COLIN JOST.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
GOOD NIGHT.
THE STUDIO.
OH, NO.
GOD, WAS IT ABOUT THAT POTENTIAL
WRITER'S STRIKE. NO. WORSE.
THE GENIUSES AT THE STUDIO ARE
NO LONGER INTERESTED IN A
GUT-WRENCHING DRAMA ABOUT
OBESITY, SO THEY'RE SHUTTING THE
FILM DOWN.
THAT'S A WRAP ON THE HIPPO.
I KNOW HOW MUCH WORK YOU ALL DID
TO WORK ON YOUR ROLES.
I SHADOWED A THERAPIST FOR
TWO WEEKS TO GET INTO CHARACTER, BLAKE.
AND JONAS GREW A BEARD, WHICH
I KNEW HE HATES.
I DO HATE IT.
AND FOR HIS ROLE, KEITH
GAINED 450 POUNDS IN SIX MONTHS.
TO BE CLEAR, THE MOVIE IS
OFFICIALLY DEAD AS IN WE'RE NOT
MAKING IT?
NO.
THE HIPPO WILL NEVER SEE THE
LIGHT OF DAY.
HUH, THAT IS-- THAT'S ROUGH
TO HEAR.
WAIT.
SO IF WE'RE NOT MAKING THE
MOVIE, THAT MEANS I DYED MY HAIR
BROWN FOR NOTHING?
HEY, HEY, IT'S FINE.
WE'RE ALL UPSET.
KEITH, YOU LOOK LIKE THIS IS
HITTING YOU PRETTY HOARD TOO, BUDDY.
YEAH.
I GOT TO SAY, THIS IS REALLY
UNFORTUNATE FOR ME PERSONALLY.
YEAH, FOR ALL OF US.
WE ALL SACRIFICED FOR THIS FILM.
I SHADOWED THAT THERAPIST ON MY
OWN TIME.
I CAN'T GET THOSE TWO WEEKS BACK.
AND I GAINED 450 POUNDS IN
SIX MONTHS.
THAT'S A LIFESTYLE CHANGE.
I HAVE SOMETHING CALLED
TRIABETES NOW.
IT'S THE ONE AFTER DIABETES.
AND I HAVE THIS GOD DAMN BEARD. SORRY.
IT'S ITCHY, AND GROWING IT WAS A
HORRIBLE EXPERIENCE.
I CAN RELATE BECAUSE GAINING
450 POUNDS IN SIX MONTHS ALSO
WAS NOT FUN.
I HAD TO EAT SOMETHING CALLED
GRISTLE LOAF.
DOES ANYONE KNOW ABOUT THIS?
IT'S A COMPRESSED BEEF FAT AND
CORN SIR UP.
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW YOU FEEL, KEITH.
MY HAIR IS SO BRITTLE FROM THE
BROWN DYE.
WELL, THIS IS GRISTLE LOAF BY
THE WAY.
IT'S WHAT THEY FEED SICK
ELEPHANTS AT THE ZOO TO GET THEM
BACK TO THEIR NORMAL WEIGHT.
ATE NINE OF THESE A DAY BECAUSE
I THOUGHT I WOULD WIN THE OSCAR.
AND YOU WOULD HAVE.
DAMN IT.
I SHOULD HAVE SEEN THIS COMING.
THE STUDIO WAS FIGHTING ME FROM
DAY ONE.
SHAINA, DID YOU KNOW THEY WANTED
YOUR PART TO BE PLAYED BY A
WHITE WOMAN?
THE SAD THING IS I'M NOT
SURPRISED.
AND JONAS, THEY WANTED TO CUT
YOU OUT OF ACT THREE.
AND THEN THERE WOULD BE NO
RESOLUTION TO THE CUSTODY STORY
LINE?
THEY ARE SO AFRAID OF ORIGINAL IDEAS.
AND GET THIS, INSTEAD OF
GAINING 450 POUNDS IN SIX
MONTHS, THEY WANTED KEITH TO
WEAR A FAT SUIT.
IS THAT-- WAS THAT AN
OPTION?
YEAH.
BUT I TOLD THEM, I SAID, KEITH
IS A METHOD ACTOR.
HE'S NOT GOING TO WEAR A FAT
SUIT.
I REALLY KIND OF WISH YOU HAD
BROUGHT ME INTO THAT
CONVERSATION.
OH, REALLY?
THAT'S MY BAD, MAN.
I'M SORRY.
GUYS, THIS WHOLE THING IS MY BAD.
BUT LOOK, AT LEAST YOU GUYS ARE FREE.
YOU OKAY?
AT LEAST YOU GUYS ARE FREE TO DO
OTHER PROJECTS, RIGHT?
LIKE KEITH, YOU HAD AN OFFER FOR
A MARVEL MOVIE, RIGHT?
I THINK THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
I'M NOT EXACTLY IN X-MEN SHAPE
RIGHT NOW.
WELL, SOMETHING ELSE WILL
COME ALONG.
WELL, I DO THIS ON ALL MY FILMS, GUYS.
ON OUR LAST DAY OF SET, WE ALL
SAY ONE THING THIS EXPERIENCE
GAVE US.
SO I'LL GO FIRST.
I HAVE 28 NEW FRIENDS.
I HAVE ONE HELL OF A STORY.
I HAVE A DEEPER RESPECT FOR
OUR CRAFT. SAME.
ALL RIGHT.
YOUR TURN, KEITH.
I HAVE--
NOT SEEN MY PENIS IN FOUR
MONTHS.
KEITH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAKE THAT 29 NEW FRIENDS FOR ME.
I WASN'T INCLUDED IN YOUR
ORIGINAL FRIEND COUNT?
HEY, DID THE STUDIO SAY WHY
THEY SHUT THE MOVIE DOWN?
OH, YOU'LL LOVE THIS.
THEY SAID THE SCRIPT IS ALMOST
WORD FOR WORD THE SAME AS THAT
BRENDAN FRASER MOVIE, THE WHALE.
I SAW IT.
BRENDAN FRASER IS GOING TO WIN
AN OSCAR.
OH, GOOD FOR HIM.
JACK WHITE!
ASK YOURSELF IF YOU ARE HAPPY,
AND THEN YOU CEASE TO BE
THAT'S A TIP FROM YOU AND ME
I DON'T ASK MYSELF FOR NOTHING
ANYMORE
MY PEACE IS FREEDOM FROM THE
MASSES
THE MASSES CANNOT SING
THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE IN ME
AND I KNOW FOR SURE I DON'T
NEED NOBODY'S HELP NOW ANYMORE
WILL I BE ALONE TONIGHT, OH, I
DON'T KNOW
OH, LEAVE ME ALONE TONIGHT,
OH, I DON'T KNOW
EVERYWHERE HE GOES, SOMEONE
SEEMS TO KNOW THE TRUTH ABOUT
THE THINGS HE USED TO DO
AND THAT'S HARD FOR YOU, IT'S
SO HARD TO BE THE ONE WHO KNOWS
IT'S TRUE
I'M WALKING THROUGH THE
PARKING LOT, FINGERS ARE
CLENCHING TIGHT, AND THEN I
NOTICE THAT I'M ALL ALONE
TONIGHT
BUT IT'S HARD TO TELL FOR SURE
IF I EVEN NEED TO THINK NOW
ANYMORE
OH, WILL I BE ALONE TONIGHT,
OH, I DON'T KNOW
OH, WILL LOVE LEAVE ME ALONE
TONIGHT, OH, I DON'T KNOW
>>> AND NOW, TWO MEN SPEAK IN HELLO.
MIND IF I USE MY KENNEL BELLS
NEXT TO YOU?
ONLY IF YOU'LL SPOT ME.
I ALREADY DID FROM ACROSS THE ROOM.
I LIKE YOUR SUIT.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY
ONE HERE WHO WORE ONE.
WELL, I'M COMING FROM A
WEDDING.
WHOSE?
MY OWN.
HER NAME IS ASHLEY OR SOMETHING.
SHE SOUNDS BEAUTIFUL.
WELL, SHE LOOKS UGLY.
SHE HAS A FACE FOR A KN-95.
THAT'S WHY I COME HERE, TO ESCAPE.
ME TOO.
AND THE MUSIC EXHILARATES ME SO.
CAN WE TURN IT UP, MORRIS?
OF COURSE, SIR.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT IS THAT YOU'RE PLAYING?
A BIG PIANO, SIR.
AH, I THOUGHT SO.
SO IS IT LEG DAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T CELEBRATE THAT IN MY CULTURE.
OF COURSE.
WELL, IT'S CHEAT DAY FOR ME.
DOES THAT MEAN--
I'M ALLOWED TO COMMIT
ADULTERY, YES.
I SHOULD TELL YOU I'M ALSO
MARRIED.
YES, I THINK OUR WIVES KNOW
EACH OTHER FROM THAT LESBIAN
RELATIONSHIP THEY'RE IN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
I THINK IT'S DISGUSTING.
ONE PAIR OF BOOBIES IS BAD ENOUGH.
SAY, DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE
MACHINE?
I LIKE THE ONE THAT MAKES THE
TOAST.
I MEANT ONE AT THE GYM. OH.
I GUESS IT'S A TIE BETWEEN THE
COBBLESTONE TREADMILL AND THE
STATIONARY VESPA.
HMM.
THIS GYM IS SO CLASSY IT SHOULD
BE CALLED JAMES.
NOW, EXCUSE ME.
I'M GOING TO USE THE ROWING MACHINE.
BOAT RIMES WITH FLOAT,
COINCIDENCE?
I THINK NOTE.
WOW.
LOOK AT YOU GO, GIRL.
THANKS FOR NOTICING.
I'VE REALLY BEEN GOING BEAST
MODE LATELY IN THAT I KEEP A
BEAUTIFUL ROSE UNDER A BELL JAR.
OF COURSE.
OH, SHOOT.
I FORGOT MY PROTEIN POWDER.
I BROUGHT SOME. AH.
MAY I BORROW?
OF COURSE.
HOW DO YOU TAKE IT?
HERE AND HERE.
GOOD.
THANK YOU.
ARE YOU GOING TO WIPE THE
MACHINE?
WIPE?
WHY?
DID IT DOO DOO?
DID IT DOO DOO, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
MORSE CODE.
WELL, I WAS IN THE ARMY. BTS.
AND I WAS IN THE NAVY.
RIHANNA.
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY USED THAT
MACHINE BEFORE, BUT I LIKE HOW
THERE'S A POSTER THAT SHOWS YOU
HOW TO DO THE EXERCISE.
AH, IT LOOKS LIKE TWO FELLOWS
EXPLORING EACH OTHER'S BODIES.
IT'S HELPFUL EITHER WAY.
YOU KNOW, THIS PLACE CAN BE SO
SENSUAL.
LOOK, MY GYM CRUSH IS OVER THERE.
I SEE YOU.
WHAT A HUNK.
THIS GYM REALLY IS A PLACE FOR
EVERYONE.
ROID BOYS, YOGA GIRLS, GYM RATS. LOOK.
THERE'S A GYM RAT OVER THERE. WOW.
WHAT A GREAT DAY AT THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL GYM IN THE WORLD.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK I'VE MADE
A NEW BEST FRIEND.
AS HAVE I, FRIEND.
NOW SHALL WE GET BACK TO OUR
WORKOUT?
GREAT IDEA.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE A GOOD
OLD-- OH, NO!
I TORE MY ACL.
WHAT DOES THAT STAND FOR?
MY ASS CRACK AND LEGS.
OH, NO.
I THINK WE'VE DONE ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
WE'VE ALREADY WORKED THE MOST
IMPORTANT MUSCLE.
THE PECTORALS?
CLOSE.
THE HEART.
JACK
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ON
BEHALF OF EVERYBODY HERE AT SNL,
I WOULD LIKE TO PRESENT THIS
FIVE-TIMERS JACKET
TO JACK WHITE.
I GOT YOU, BABY.
THERE IT IS.
VERY NICE, VERY NICE.