EARLIER
>>> HELLO.
I'D LIKE TO THANK PRESIDENT
TRUMP FOR HAVING US.
THOSE OF US FROM THE
PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRY
ARE
HONORED TO BE HERE TODAY
ALONGSIDE RFK JR. AND DR. OZ.
WE'RE GOING TO DISCUSS LOWERING
THE PRICE OF WEIGHT LOSS DRUGS.
FOR YEARS, MY COMPANY, ELI LILLY,
HAS BEEN AT THE FOREFRONT
OF PROVIDING AMERICANS WITH --
>> OH, NO!
>> OH, HI.
DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
SOMEONE WAS DYING IN MY OFFICE.
I THINK I'M PLAYING THIS VERY
NORMAL.
JUST STAND THERE AND STARE LIKE
A SOCIOPATH.
PRETEND LIKE I WAS GOING TO HELP,
SOMEONE DROPS SOMETHING
AND YOU DO THE FAKE BEND, OH,
LET ME HELP YOU PICK THAT UP,
YOU GOT IT
RFK OUT OF HERE LIKE
SOMEONE WAS TRYING TO GIVE HIM A
VACCINE.
BRAINWORM, TAKE THE WHEEL!
THAT THING RATATOUILLE'D HIM OUT
OF THE ROOM.
EACH WEEK, I LIKE TO CREATE A
BIG VISUAL
THAT SUMS UP HOW
THINGS ARE GOING.
LAST WEEK IT WAS THE DEMOLISHING
OF THE EAST WING.
THIS WEEK IT'S A MEDICAL
PROFESSIONAL ALMOST DYING IN MY OVAL OFFICE
AT THE MERE THOUGHT
OF CHARGING LESS FOR DRUGS.
MAYBE NEXT WEEK A BALD EAGLE
WILL FALL DEAD OUT OF THE SKY
AND SPLAT RIGHT ON THE WHITE
HOUSE LAWN.
BY LAWN I MEAN BIG OUTDOOR
CONCRETE FLOOR.
THERE?
MORE IMPORTANTLY, HOW'S THE
FLOOR?
OKAY?
A GUY COLLAPSING IN THE OVAL
OFFICE, WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE NOT ME.
DON'T WORRY, HE'LL BE FINE.
DR. OZ IS ON THE CASE.
ANYWAY, ALL IN ALL A GREAT,
AWESOME WEEK
EXCEPT FOR
ELECTION.
THE DEMOCRATS WON.
THE LAMESTREAM MEDIA CALLED THE
ELECTIONS A REBUKE OF TRUMP'S
POLICIES.
JOKE'S ON THEM, THEY'RE STEPHEN
MILLER'S POLICIES, I DON'T READ
THAT STUFF.
NO LIKEE READEE.
CAN'T BELIEVE THEY ELECTED
MAMDANI.
WE LIKE TO SAY, MAMDANI.
I'M TORN BECAUSE I LIKE A WINNER
BUT I'M NOT CRAZY ABOUT A
MUSLIM.
MAYBE HE'LL CONVERT.
WE'LL PUT HIM IN LINE BEHIND
URSHA VANCE, AND I HOPE I'M
PRONOUNCING THAT WRONG.
OUR SIDE HAD SOME WINS THIS
WEEK, TOO.
THE SUPREME COURT SAID WE COULD
STOP FEEDING POOR PEOPLE.
YOU CAN DLAP FOR THAT.
S.N.A.P.!
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO CAN AFFORD
FOOD, NO, YOU CAN'T.
I PROMISED GROCERY PRICES WOULD
PLUMMET,
AND THEY DID, THEY
PLUMMETED STRAIGHT UP.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING, BUT SIR, HOW
WILL I AFFORD MY THANKSGIVING
TURKEY FOR MY FAMILY?
WELL, GOOD NEWS IS YOUR FAMILY'S
NOT COMING BECAUSE ALL THE
PLANES ARE GONE.
WE CALL THAT PROBLEM SOLVING
PROBLEM.
KILLING TWO BIRDS WITH ANOTHER
BIRD.
NOW YOU GOT A BUNCH OF CRAZY
BIRDS.
WE LIKE IT, WE LIKE IT, THAT'S
KIND OF OUR THING.
CAN'T AFFORD FOOD, HAVE SOME
CHEAP OZEMPIC.
NOW YOU'RE NOT HUNGRY AND YOU
GET TO TAKE ONE WEIRD, PAINFUL
POOP A WEEK.
HOW'S IT GOING BACK THERE?
IS HE DEAD?
THEY'RE DOING THE -- THEY GOT
THE LEGS UP, THAT MEANS DEAD IN
CARTOON.
ACTUALLY, DON'T TELL ME IF HE'S
DEAD, I WANT TO BE SURPRISED.
ANYWAY.
GOVERNMENT IS STILL SHUT DOWN.
ALL THANKS TO THE DEMOCRATS AND
SOME REPUBLICANS
AND ALL
REPUBLICANS AND ME.
PEOPLE SAY, JUST CAVE, DON, GIVE
THE DEMOCRATS WHAT THEY WANT,
END THIS.
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO DRAG IT
OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT SHUT DOWN.
WE'RE LOOKING INTO PERHAPS
STEALING CHRISTMAS.
WE'LL BE DOING GRINCH.
I LIKE THE GRINCH.
HE'S A GREAT GUY.
OUR WIVES ARE FRIENDS.
WE PLAY GOLF SOMETIMES.
IS HE OKAY?
HE'S OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IF YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE
HIM TO GET AN MRI,
USE THIS,
THIS IS MY PUNCH CARD.
ONE MORE AND THE NEXT ONE'S
FREE.
AND FOR ANYONE WORRIED ABOUT THE
STATE OF THE COUNTRY, I'LL SAY THE SAME THING
I SAID TO MELANIA
WHEN SHE TRIED TO HELP ME DO MY
HAIR.
GO AWAY, WHAT I'M DOING IS VERY
COMPLICATED,
AND ONLY I KNOW HOW
TO DO IT.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
HOST
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- NIKKI
GLASER!
>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HI, I AM NIKKI GLASER, AND I AM
SO HAPPY TO BE HERE TONIGHT.
THIS IS TRULY A DREAM COME TRUE.
I LOVE THIS SHOW SO MUCH.
AND HERE I AM IN NEW YORK CITY,
EPSTEIN'S ORIGINAL ISLAND.
OH, IT'S SUCH A SPECIAL NIGHT.
I GOT A SPRAY TAN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, IT DESERVES THAT,
THANK YOU.
THERE'S SO MANY PASTY WHITE
GIRLS WHO ARE TERRIFIED TO GET SPRAY TANS,
I'M GOING TO LOOK
ORANGE.
JUST -- BELIEVE ME, I PROMISE
YOU, I PROMISE YOU --
IT'S
BETTER THAN WHAT YOU ARE, OKAY?
DON'T BE SCARED.
THEY'RE ALWAYS LIKE, I'M GOING
TO LOOK LIKE TRUMP!
BITCH, THAT'S WHY HE WON.
YEAH, HE PICKED AN INSANE SHADE.
HE WENT PRETTY DARK.
HE DIDN'T GO KAMALA, BUT HE
PICKED A SHADE THAT
HALF OF
AMERICA WAS LIKE, OKAY, WE CAN
STILL TELL HE'S WHITE. SO,
I MEAN, IT IS KIND OF INSANE
THAT WHITE PEOPLE CAN JUST PAINT
THEIR SKIN A DIFFERENT COLOR
AND
THEY'RE LIKE, THIS IS COOL,
RIGHT?
I FEEL LIKE THAT'S CULTURAL
APPROPRIATION.
I DON'T KNOW. I MEAN,
IT'S NOT BLACKFACE, BUT
IT IS GUATEMALAN LEG.
THIS IS NOT MY LEG.
I'M LIKE, OH, MY GOD, ME, I'M
ALWAYS NIKKI,
LOOK AT THAT.
AM I SAYING THAT
RIGHT?
I GET SHE'S SPRAY TANS.
I BREATHE THE STUFF IN EVERY
WEEK.
I AM DEFINITELY GOING TO GET
SOME KIND OF RESPIRATORY ILLNESS
FROM IT.
IN 20 YEARS THERE'S GOING TO BE
SOME EPIDEMIC CALLED TAN LUNG.
I REALLY WANT TO BE ON THE
COMMERCIALS FOR THE CLASS ACTION
LAWSUIT.
I THINK THAT'S SUCH A GOOD GIG.
IT WILL BE SO FUN FOR YOU, TOO.
YOU'LL TURN ON YOUR TV IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT AND BE, WHO
IS THAT?
I'LL BE, LIKE, I'M NIKKI GLASER.
YOU MAY RECOGNIZE ME FROM THE
ROAST OF TOM BRADY.
IT WILL BE LIKE ME AND SNOOKI.
THAT'S FUN.
JUST TALKING THROUGH OUR TRACHS,
RFK JUNIOR'ing OUT.
HE'S GOT TAN LUNG. I MEAN,
HE'S STAGE 2, I DON'T
KNOW.
I'M NO HEALTH EXPERT, BUT
NOTWITHSTANDINGER IS HE.
IT'S JUST CRAZY WE HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT OUR LOOKS SO MUCH.
IT STARTS SO YOUNG AS A GIRL.
I SAW THIS GIRL THE OTHER DAY.
SHE WAS PROBABLY 6 YEARS OLD.
AND HER DAD WAS TRYING TO TAKE A
PICTURE OF HER.
McKENZIE, LOOK OVER HERE.
DAD, GET MY GOOD SIDE.
SHE'S LIKE, "GOOD SIDE."
6.
SO SAD, BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T HAVE
ONE.
IT'S LIKE, WHEN IS SHE GOING TO
FIND OUT?
SHE NEEDS TO LEARN A TRADE, YOU
KNOW?
HAND HER A WRENCH OR DO COMEDY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST THINK THERE'S SO MANY
THINGS WE DO FOR BEAUTY THAT ARE IMPORTANT,
BUT THERE'S OTHER
ONES I'M LIKE, WHY ARE WE DOING
THIS?
WHO CARES?
LIKE NAILS.
NO ONE CARES.
LIKE, I'VE BEEN WITH MY
BOYFRIEND FOR TEN YEARS.
HE'S NEVER ONCE NOTICED THAT
I'VE GOTTEN MY NAILS DONE.
AND THEY GO INSIDE HIM.
SO IF HE DOESN'T CARE,
WHO DOES?
THE ONLY TIME HE CARED WAS WHEN
I WAS THEM BEDAZZLED FOR HIS
PLEASURE.
THEN HE LOVED THEM.
GOING TO THE NAIL SALON, IT'S SO
BORING.
IT'S SUCH A WASTE OF TIME.
YOU JUST SIT THERE FOR TWO HOURS
JUST PARALYZED.
I FEEL LIKE MEN THINK WE GO TO
THE NAIL SALON WITH OUR GIRLFRIENDS
AND CHITCHAT THE
WHOLE TIME, BUT THAT'S NOT THE
CASE.
YOU CAN GO TO THE NAIL SALON
WITH A FRIEND,
BUT YOU GET
SEPARATED AT THE BORDER.
THEY DO NOT LET YOU SIT NEXT TO
EACH OTHER.
IT'S SO ANTISOCIAL.
WATCHING
ON MUTE
YOU CAN'T TALK TO THE WOMAN
DOING YOUR NAILS, BECAUSE
SLAVERY?
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
SHE SEEMS STUCK AND SAD.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I'M JUST PARANOID.
I'M JUST KIND OF OBSESSED WITH
SLAVERY RECENTLY, BECAUSE --
EVERY TIME YOU GO TO A WOMEN'S
RESTROOM, A PUBLIC WOMEN'S
RESTROOM, IN THE STALL
THERE'S A
POSTER ON THE BACK OF THE STALL
ASKING YOU IF YOU'RE BEING
TRAFFICKED.
WOMEN, WE HAVE THESE, RIGHT?
YES, YES.
IN EVERY STALL, IN EVERY WORLD
LANGUAGE.
ENGLISH IS REALLY TINY AND IT'S
LIKE, "YOU WISH."
BUT IT'S LIKE --
MEN'SEST
RESTROOMS DO NOT HAVE THESE
SIGNS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SIGNS YOU
HAVE. MAYBE YOU HAVE SIGNS LIKE,
"WANT
A SLAVE?
TEXT "TRAFFIC" TO 6969."
BUT IT'S REALLY A BIG FEAR OF
BEING TRAFFICKED.
MOSTLY FOR GEN-Z GIRLS.
I HAVE A LOT OF GEN-Z FRIENDS
THAT I BOUGHT.
THEY'RE TERRIFIED.
AND I DON'T RELATE.
I'M 41.
THAT WAS LIKE NOT A FEAR OF MINE
EVER IN MY 20s.
IN MY 20s I JUST FEARED GOOD
OLD-FASHIONED RAPE.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE A
CAREER.
WE DIDN'T THINK --
IT WAS ANYTHING MORE THAN A TEMP
JOB AT A FRAT HOUSE FUTON. BUT
IT'S REAL.
I'M GETTING SCARED.
IT'S RUBBING OUT WITH ME.
RECENTLY
WHAT IF WE GET TRAFFICKED?
THEY'RE LIKE, "YOU'RE GOOD."
THEY'RE LIKE, "WE'RE SAFER WHEN
YOU'RE WITH US
BECAUSE THEY
THINK YOU'RE OUR MADAM."
"YOU HAVE RESTING GHISLAINE"
FACE, SO KEEP THAT UP."
WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GET IT FIXED.
I'M GOING TO GET A FACELIFT
PRETTY SOON HERE.
MY BOYFRIEND DOESN'T WANT ME TO.
HE'S LIKE, NO, DON'T DO YOUR FACE,
I LOVE YOUR FACE, DO YOUR
TITS.
WHAT?
THAT'S ALL HE CARES ABOUT.
HE'S A SHORT GUY, THEY'RE ALL HE
SEES, I THINK.
I THINK THAT'S WHY HE'S FOCUSED
ON THEM.
I DO DATE A SHORT GUY, SHORTER
THAN ME, BUT REALLY HOT.
I THINK THAT'S WHY I GOT HIM,
BECAUSE I COULD NEVER GET HIS
FACE ON A TALLER MODEL.
LIKE, IF YOU WANT TO GET A 10 IN
THE FACE, YOU'VE GOT TO GO 5'7"
IN THE HEIGHT.
TRICK
GETTING A HOT GUY ON DISCOUNT.
HE'S MARKED DOWN.
I MET MY BOYFRIEND AT TJ MAXX,
CLEARANCE RACK,
HE WAS HIDING IN
IT.
IT'S CRAZY.
SOMETIMES I'LL POST A PICTURE OF US ONLINE
AND I'LL GET COMMENTS
OF, GIRL, HE'S HOT, HOW DID YOU
GET HIM?
I'M LIKE, IF YOU ZOOMED OUT,
YOU'D SEE HE'S SITTING ON MY
LAP.
THIS IS A TINY GUY.
WENT DIGGING IN THE BARGAIN BIN,
LADIES.
BUT -- YEAH, GIRLS DON'T LIKE
SHORT GUYS.
AND I GUESS IT'S BECAUSE YOU
WANT A TALL GUY
SO THAT YOU CAN
FEEL LIKE, HE CAN PROTECT ME,
AND MURDER ME SOMEDAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S IT.
BUT MY BOYFRIEND'S SHORTER THAN
ME.
I'VE NEVER FELT LIKE HE CAN'T PROTECT ME,
AND I AM CERTAIN HE
WILL MURDER ME SOMEDAY.
HE IS SO FILLED WITH RAGE THAT
HE'S SHORT.
I MEAN, HE IS JUST SIMMERING
WITH ANGER.
AND THAT'S WHY I KEEP OUR GUN ON
THE TOP SHELF.
I CAN'T RISK THAT.
I NEED HIM TO GO GET A
STEPLADDER AND THINK IT THROUGH,
YOU KNOW?
THE NUMBER OF TIMES I'VE WALKED
INTO OUR CLOSET AND SEEN HIM
LIKE --
AND I'M LIKE, "DOES SOMEONE NEED
TO GET UPPY-UPPY
TO GET THE
BANG-BANG TO MAKE NIKKI GO
BYE-BYE?"
THEN I GIVE HIM A JUICE BOX, AND
HE FORGETS WHY HE'S UPSET.
WE DON'T HAVE KIDS BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT TO PASS DOWN THAT
DNA.
BUT IT'S JUST -- I FEEL LIKE
IT'S TOO HARD TO BE A MOM.
I HAVE TOO MUCH ANXIETY ABOUT
IT.
IT'S HARD BEING AN AUNT.
I WAS STAYING AT MY SISTER'S
HOUSE RECENTLY,
AND AT ONE POINT
I WAS LIKE, "I'M GOING TO GO
TAKE A SHOWER."
MY NEPHEW COMES RUNNING IN, "I
TAKE A SHOWER WITH YOU!"
HE'S 18.
I'M LIKE, WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
HIS VOICE?
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
NO, NO.
HE WAS 4, AND IT WAS VERY CUTE.
MY SISTER'S LIKE, HE CAN TAKE A
SHOWER WITH YOU, IT'S FINE, HE
DOES IT WITH US.
OKAY, THAT'S FINE FOR YOU GUYS
BUT ARE YOU OKAY WITHN AN ADULT
SHOWERING WITH YOUR CHILD?
MAYBE IT'S OKAY IF YOU COME AND
SUPERVISE.
SHE WAS LIKE, WHY?
AND I WAS LIKE, WHAT AM.
I MOLEST HIM?
SHE WAS LIKE, WOULD YOU?
I WAS LIKE, NO!
I WOULD NEVER!
THAT'S DISGUSTING!
BUT THAT'S WHAT I'D SAY IF I WAS
GONNA.
THEY LIE!
DON'T TRUST ANYONE.
I DON'T EVEN TRUST MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO GO IN THERE.
HOW DO YOU BECOME A PEDESTRIAN
TILE?
YOU DON'T GET TO CHOOSE WHAT
YOU'RE INTO, DUDE.
WHAT IF IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS
YOU DON'T KNOW YOU LIKE TILL YOU
GET IN THERE AND YOU'RE LIKE,
WELL, THIS IS MY THING.
AND IT OPENS UP A PART OF MY
BRAIN.
NO, NO, NO.
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS CRAZY, BUT
THERE HAVE BEEN SO MANY THINGS IN MY LIFE
THAT I'VE BEEN, I
WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
AND NOW I'M LIKE, LOOKS KIND OF
FUN, ACTUALLY.
SO I DON'T KNOW.
THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
WE HAVE SUCH AN INCREDIBLE SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT.
SOMBR IS HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK!
>>> I TRIED TO TELL HER, BABE,
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE TO DO
THIS.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LOVE THAT YOU GUYS DO FAMILY
KARAOKE NIGHTS,
THAT'S SO SWEET.
>> AWW, PETEY, I LIKE HER
ALREADY.
>> THANKS FOR COMING TO OUR
LITTLE FAMILY TRADITION.
>> I KNOW IT'S SILLY, BUT WE
LOVE IT.
>> I'M JUST EXCITED TO MEET YOU
GUYS.
>> ALL RIGHT, PARTY PEOPLE,
DEEJAY FIG-A-LICIOUS ON THE MIC.
IF YOU ARE THE OWNER OF A 2004 COROLLA,
PLEASE TALK TO ME, I'M
CONSIDERING BUYING ONE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW GIVE IT UP FOR
BECKY AND PETEY!
>> WAIT, YOU PUT IN OUR SONG
ALREADY?
>> YOU KNOW I DID, LITTLE BRO,
GET UP THERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M SORRY, BABE, DUTY CALLS.
>> HAVE FUN!
>> THIS IS FOR MY BABY BROTHER.
I LOVE YOU, BUDDY.
SIS
¶ AND I'D GIVE UP FOREVER TO
TOUCH YOU
'CAUSE I KNOW THAT E
SOMEHOW ¶
OH, I FEEL IT TOO.
¶ YOU'RE THE CLOSEST TO HEAVEN
I'LL EVER BE
AND I DON'T WANT TO
GO HOME RIGHT NOW ¶
>> NEVER.
>> GO, KIDS!
¶ ALL I CAN SEE IS THIS MOMENT ¶
¶ AND ALL I CAN BREATHE IS YOUR
LIFE ¶
¶ AND SOONER OR LATER IT'S OVER
I JUST DON'T WANT TO MISS YOU
TONIGHT ¶
¶ AND I DON'T WANT THE WORLD TO SEE ME
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK THAT
SHE'D UNDERSTAND ¶
>> ME?
¶ WHEN EVERYTHING'S MADE TO BE BROKEN
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
WHO I AM ¶
¶ I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW WHO I
AM ¶
>> I DO.
>> I KNOW YOU DO.
KIDS
>> AND THEY'RE FULL SIBLINGS?
>> OH, YEAH.
VERY FULL.
>> GO, KIDS!
>> ALL RIGHT, GIVE IT UP FOR
BECKY AND PETEY.
AND NEXT UP, OH-OH --
IT'S PETEY AND BECKY.
>> WHAT?
OH, MY GOSH.
DID YOU PUT ONE IN TOO?
>> OF COURSE I DID, SIS, COME
ON.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT
¶ I'LL MAKE LOVE TO YOU
LIKE YOU WANT ME TO ¶
¶ AND I'LL HOLD YOU TIGHT
BABY ALL THROUGH THE NIGHT ¶
¶ I'LL MAKE LOVE TO YOU ¶
>> SO PETEY SAYS YOU'RE ON
WEGOVY.
>> WHAT?
SORRY, I'M A LITTLE DISTRACTED.
HE'S KIND OF HUMPING HIS SISTER.
>> WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHAT THE HELL DID YOU JUST
SAY?
>> BABE, WE WERE JUST DANCING.
>> NO, NO.
I GET IT, GIRL.
IT'S OKAY.
PETE AND I HAVE ALWAYS JUST BEEN
BEST FRIENDS.
AND WE JUST LOVE SINGING SONGS
THAT WE GREW UP LISTENING
TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, WE'VE ALWAYS
BEEN SUPER CHOSE.
WE SHARED A BEDROOM TILL SHE
LEFT FOR COLLEGE.
>> OH, THAT'S LATE, NO?
>> YEAH, IT WAS FINE.
WHEN I TURNED 17, WE GOT
SEPARATE BEDS.
>> THE WORST.
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
>> SPEAKING OF CLOSE, IT'S
DADDY-DAUGHTER TIME.
COME ON!
>> OH, MY GOSH, DAD, YOU DIDN'T
PICK THE SONG WE DANCED TO AT MY
WEDDING, DID YOU?
CRY
>> I SURE DID, SWEETHEART.
HIT IT, DEEJAY!
¶ BABY WHEN WE'RE GRINDING
I GET SO EXCITED ¶
¶ HOW I LIKE IT
I CAN'T HIDE IT ¶
¶ OH YA DANCING REAL CLOSE
AND SWAY IS REAL SLOW ¶
>> I MISS GRANDMA.
>> ME TOO.
¶ YOU'RE MAKING IT HARD FOR ME.
>> THIS IS MAKING ME FEEL WEIRD,
I'M JUST GOING TO GO.
>> WHY, WHY?
>> NO, NO, LET HER GO.
SHE JUST MAD THAT YOU TWO ARE SO
CLEARLY SEXUALLY SATISFIED AND
IN LOVE.
>> NO, NO, NO, WE'RE BROTHER AND
SISTER.
>> YOU THE HECK SAY WHAT, NOW?
>> OKAY, WAIT.
WHY DON'T I JUST DO A SONG,
JUST
ME, FOR MY BABY GIRL?
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
GET UP HERE.
HIT IT, DEEJAY.
>> THE SONG THAT YOU TOLD ME WAS
SPECIFICALLY RESERVED FOR YOU TO
SING TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND
AND NOT
YOUR FREAKY DEAKY SISTER?
>> YES, DEEJAY FREAK-A-LICIOUS.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GOT IT,
PLAYBOY.
¶ YOU'VE GOT A FRIEND IN ME ¶
>> WHAT?
NO, NO!
¶ YOU GOT A FRIEND IN ME ¶
>> YOU FEEL LIKE FAMILY ALREADY,
SIS.
>>> ARE YOU ANXIOUS,
OVERWHELMED?
HAVE YOU STOPPED FEELING LIKE
YOURSELF?
ARE YOU OVERCOME WITH AN INTENSE
FEELING OF FOREBODING AND DREAD?
IF SO, YOU MAY BE ONE OF THE
MANY CELEBRITIES
WHO ARE
SCHEDULED TO DANCE THROUGH THE
JENNIFER HUDSON SPIRIT TUNNEL.
>> I LOVE JENNIFER HUDSON.
BUT AS AN UNCOORDINATED WHITE
WOMAN, I FELT TRAPPED.
I'D TRIED PRACTICING, BUT
EVERYTHING I CAME UP WITH LOOKED
CAREER-ENDING.
POINTING.
SHOULDER SHRUG.
DRUNK AUNT AT A WEDDING.
I EVEN TRIED TO PUT MY ASS INTO
IT.
BUT I DON'T HAVE ONE.
I JUST KEPT IMAGINING MYSELF IN
THAT TUNNEL.
¶ COME ON NIKKI YOU'RE SO FINE
YOU'RE SO FINE YOU BLOW MY MIND
HEY NIKKI HEY NIKKI ¶
>> IT FELT LIKE THERE WAS NO WAY
OUT.
THAT'S WHEN MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
ABOUT HUDSICILLIN.
HUDSICILLIN IS THE
ONLY MEDICATION PROVED TO KILL
TUNNEL ANXIETY.
NOT BY MAKING YOUR BODY AWAY BIT
BY MAKING YOU SO VIOLENTLY ILL.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
CANCEL.
IT WORKS FAST, MAYBE TOO FAST.
30 SECONDS AFTER MY FIRST DOSE,
I WAS SHAKING ON THE BATHROOM
FLOOR.
NOT KNOWING WHICH END OF ME TO
AIM AT THE TOILET.
THAT'S BECAUSE HUDSICILLIN IS
MADE FROM A GENTLE BLEND OF E.
COLI, INFLUENZA, C. DIFF.
AND RANCID BUTTERMILK.
I FINALLY HAVE MY LIFE BACK.
AND NOW MY SPOT IN THE TUNNEL
CAN GO TO SOMEONE WHO REALLY
WANTS IT.
¶ HEY HEY HEY ¶
THANKS, HUDSICILLIN.
WHAT'S THE ALTERNATIVE?
LIGHTENING UP AND BEING FUN?
GOOD LUCK.
>> Announcer: NEXT WEEK, GLEN
AS TIME.
>> PAPA!
PAPA!
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE OKAY!
>> OH, BELLE, WHAT EVERY DOING
HERE?
YOU MUST LEAVE NOW.
>> I CAME TO RESCUE YOU.
>> OH, NO, BELLE, IT'S NOT SAFE.
THE PRINCE WHO OWNS THIS CASTLE
WAS CURSED TO BECOME A TERRIBLE
BEAST.
>> I'LL DO ANYTHING TO SAVE YOU,
FATHER.
I'LL TAKE YOUR PLACE.
>> OH, BELLE, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
HE'S NOT JUST ANY BEAST.
HE'S -- HE'S -- MR. BEAST!
>> I'M KEEPING HER DAD TRAPPED
IN A DUNGEON FOR 30 DAYS FOR A
CHANCE TO WIN OVER $300,000.
>> DISNEY'S "BEAUTY AND MR.
BEAST."
>> LET MY FATHER GO!
>> FOR EVERY POUND HE LOSES,
I'LL GIVE A TESLA TO A RANDOM
STRANGER.
>> WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
>> WHY, HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
HE USED TO BE A HANDSOME PRINCE
UNTIL HE WAS CURSED BY A WITCH.
>> HE WOKE UP THE NEXT MORNING,
RANTING AND RAVING ABOUT SENDING
THE WORLD'S LARGEST MAN TO THE
WORLD'S SMALLEST ISLAND.
>> AND YOU WERE CURSED TOO?
>> OUI, I WAS.
>> AND IF I LIVE FOR ONE YEAR AS
A CLOCK, I GET $2,500.
NOW -- WAIT A MINUTE, I'M JUST
REALIZING THAT'S NOT A LOT OF
MONEY.
>> MADEMOISELLE, DON'T JUDGE OUR
MASTER TOO HARSHLY.
HE IS A MAN OF TASTE.
LOOK AT HIS ART.
>> FROM THE EXECUTIVE PRODUCERS
WHO THOUGHT NOBODY SEES MOVIES
ANYMORE SO EFF IT, HAIL MARY?
AND THE DIRECTOR OF
KAI-SABLANCA.
>> WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THE LAST
PETAL FALLS?
>> A MAN IN ALBANY HAS TO EAT
500 SOFT SHELL CRABS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT I FEEL
LIKE I COULD SPEND EIGHT HOURS
LISTENING TO YOU.
>> WELL, THAT IS BECAUSE,
MADEMOISELLE --
¶ YOU'RE DEPRESSED YOU'RE
DEPRESSED WITH A LAPTOP ON YOUR
CHEST ¶
¶ WATCH YOUR GAME FORGET YOUR
STRESS YOU'RE DEPRESSED ¶
>> I DON'T GET IT, SAYS EVERY
PERSON OVER 25.
AND, I'M BUILDING THE LARGEST
LEGO TOWER IN THE WORLD, RAVES
MR. BEAST.
>> I JUST KNOW THERE'S A TENDER
HEART UNDER THERE.
I -- I THINK I LOVE YOU, BEAST.
>> REALLY?
EVEN THOUGH MY TOP HALF IS BEAST
AND MY BOTTOM HALF IS COMPLETELY
SMOOTH?
>> WELL -- I GUESS I DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
>> DANCE WITH ME, BELLE.
¶ TALE AS OLD AS TIME ¶
¶ SQUID GAME FOR THE TEENS ¶
¶ LIVE IN A CVS FOR A CHANCE TO
WIN A LAMBORGHINI ¶
>> OH, BEAST, I WANT TO MARRY
YOU.
>> OH, REALLY?
A BEAST LIKE ME?
OKAY.
I WILL MARRY YOU, BELLE.
IF YOU CAN LIVE FOR 30 DAYS IN A
SMART CAR WITH THESE TWO
GREASED-UP SUMO WRESTLERS.
>> HM.
AND YOU'RE A BILLIONAIRE, YOU
SAID?
>> SURE AM.
>> WELL, THEN I GUESS I'LL TRY.
¶ BEAUTY AND MR. BEAST ¶
>> DISNEY'S "BEAUTY AND MR.
BEAST."
>>> IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
YOU GREW UP TREASURING YOUR
AMERICAN GIRL DOLL.
I HELD ON TO SAMANTHA PARKINGTON
UNTIL I WAS ALMOST 12.
AS WE MATURE AS WOMEN, OUR DOLLS
DON'T MATURE ALONG WITH US.
UNTIL NOW.
INTRODUCING AMERICAN GIRL XL.
THE SAME HIGH-QUALITY, LOVINGLY
CRAFTED DOLLS, BUT LARGER AND
ALL GROWN UP.
JUST LIKE YOU.
>> MY TERESA DOLL HAS THE MOST
INSPIRING JOB OF ALL, TEACHER.
>> WITH SUZANNE BY MY SIDE, I
KNOW JUSTICE WILL ALWAYS BE
SERVED.
>> AND JESSICA HERE IS A NURSE.
HOW COOL IS THAT?
SHE TAKES SUCH GOOD CARE OF ME.
>> AND JUST LIKE OUR REGULAR
DOLLS, OUR XL DOLLS HAVE
INCREDIBLE ATTENTION TO DETAIL.
>> JUST LOOK AT THE STITCHING ON
MY DOLL'S SUIT.
>> AND ALL THE COOL PATCHES ON
MY ASTRONAUT DOLL.
>> AND MY DOLL'S FEET.
SO LIFELIKE.
>> WHAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT ARE
THEIR STORIES.
SUZANNE HERE WAS THE FIRST
FEMALE JUDGE IN MISSOURI.
>> I MADE UP MY OWN BACKSTORY
FOR JESSICA.
SHE'S FROM LITHUANIA.
>> NO, SHE'S AMERICAN.
>> WELL, SHE IS NOW.
>> MINE HATES HER DAD, AND SHE
WANTS TO BE A SINGER.
THAT'S WHY HER MOUTH IS ALWAYS
OPEN.
>> THE POINT IS, AMERICAN GIRL
XL DOLLS WILL INSPIRE WOMEN OF
ALL AGES.
AND YOU CAN EVEN DESIGN YOUR OWN
BASED ON HISTORICAL FIGURES.
>> MINE LOOKS LIKE ROSIE THE
RIVETER.
>> MINE LOOKS LIKE AMELIA
EARHART.
>> MINE LOOKS LIKE MY BROTHER'S
WIFE.
>> NO, THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
HISTORICAL FIGURES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
ABIGAIL HERE IS FROM COLONIAL
TIMES.
THAT'S WHY HER HANDS CHURN
BUTTER.
>> ARE YOU HERE WITH SOMEBODY?
MAYBE YOUR DAUGHTER OR --
>> CLOSE.
MY DAD.
>> MINE'S AN OLYMPIC SKIER.
>> I REALLY DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> AND THE BEST PART IS --
>> WAIT, WHO ARE YOU?
>> YOU CAN TAKE THE CLOTHING
FROM YOUR REGULAR AMERICAN GIRL
DOLL AND USE IT ON YOUR XL DOLL.
>> PLEASE, NEVER DO THAT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS TO HER?
>> BECAUSE IT'S FUN AND WE'RE IN
LOVE.
>> AND THEIR HAIR IS SUPER
STRONG.
>> YOU CAN MIX AND MATCH THEIR
PARTS.
I MADE MINE BIRACIAL.
>> IF YOU FOLD HER IN HALF, SHE
FITS RIGHT INTO THE DISHWASHER.
>> HEY, WANT TO TRADE FOR A
LITTLE WHILE?
>> I'D LOVE THAT.
>> THAT'S IT, WE'RE SHUTTING THE
STORE DOWN.
>> AMERICAN GIRL XL.
THEY MADE AN XL MISTAKE.
>> HONEY, SLOW DOWN, THAT'S YOUR
THIRD MARTINI.
HERE, HAVE SOME OF YOUR HOT DOG.
>>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, LET'S
HEAR IT ONE MORE TIME FOR
ALEXIS!
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT WAS SO
CRAZY.
>> WHAT'S CRAZY IS THAT I'M
GETTING MARRIED IN TWO WEEKS.
>> AHH!
>> I WISH IT WAS TO ME.
OOPS, I SAID THAT OUT LOUD.
I'LL BE LEAVING NOW.
>> OKAY.
BYE!
YOU GUYS, THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
WAIT -- WHERE ARE KAYLA AND
DELULAH?
>> OH, MY GOD, THEY'RE ON THE
BULL.
>> HI, GIRLIES!
>> YEE-HAW, YOU GUYS!
>> ONE AT A TIME, PLEASE, AND
YOU'RE MUCH TOO DRUNK.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
>> I ONLY HAD A MARTINI WITH A
TWIST.
>> AND THE TWIST, I HAD FOUR
MARGARITAS.
>> LET'S GET THIS DONKEY MOVING,
Y'ALL!
>> YEAH!
>> IT IS NOT A DONKEY.
ANDRE, DO NOT START THAT BULL.
>> HM.
ON THE ONE HAND, I KNOW I'M NOT
SUPPOSED TO DO THIS.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND -- I WOULD
LIKE TO SEE TWO BUXOM BABES
BEING BUCKED AROUND ON A BRONCO.
I CALL THIS "ANDRE'S DILEMMA."
DILEMMA SOLVED.
I WILL DO IT.
>> AAH!
>> ANDRE!
WHAT SETTING DID YOU PUT IT ON?
>> OH MY DEAR GOODNESS ME, I AM
AFRAID IN MY TITILLATED STATE I
ACCIDENTALLY SET IT TO "BON
VOYAGE."
>> NOOOOOOO!
>> WHOO!
¶ SO JUST LIKE THAT THEY STARTED
THEIR QUEST TWO BLOTTO BIMBOS
HEADED WEST ¶
¶ RIDING ACROSS THE USA WITH ALL
THE SIGHTS TO SEE ¶
>> THERE IT IS!
¶ COPS ON THE HIGHWAY COULDN'T
DECIDE IF THE SITUATION WAS A
DUI ¶
¶ JUST TWO DRUNK BITCHES ON A
RUNAWAY MECHANICAL BULL ¶
>> I'M HUNGRY!
>> OPEN OUR MOUTHS FOR SOME
BUGS.
>> GOOD IDEA.
OH, OH!
BEES!
AND A BIRD!
¶ SO THEY SAW THE OLD FAITHFUL
THEN SWALLOWED GRAND CANYON
DIRT ¶
¶ SAW USHER IN VEGAS AND GOT
SOILED PANTIES ¶
¶ ATE CHEESE IN WISCONSIN WHICH
THEY THOUGHT WAS DEMOLISH THEN
WENT TO NIAGARA GOT SLAPPED BY A
FISH ¶
¶ WHERE THE BIRD AND BEES AND
A BIG BLOCK OF CHEESE ¶
¶ JUST TWO DUMB BITCHES ¶
¶ ON A RUNAWAY MECHANICAL BULL ¶
>> WE'RE NOT DUMB, WE WENT TO
COLLEGE.
>> I WENT TO UTI.
WAIT -- I HAVE A UTI.
¶ THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW THEY
WERE CROSSING THE OCEAN ¶
¶ AND THE NAVY PICKED UP SOME
SUSPICIOUS MOTION ¶
AND THEIR SOFTWARE IDENTIFIED
THEM AS HOSTILE ¶
>> THIS IS U.S. SOUTHERN
COMMAND, WE'RE CLEAR TO FIRE ON
BOGEYS.
>> HI!
>> ROGER THAT, LAUNCHING
HELLFIRE MISSILES.
>> OOH!
¶ WITH THE MILITARY AND THE BIRD
AND THE BEES AND THE BIG BLOCK
OF CHEESE ¶
¶
¶ JUST TWO WORLD-TRAVELING
BITCHES AND A BULL GOING THE
SPEED OF LIGHT ¶
>> LOOK, TWO MINUTES AGO!
>> OH-OH, THINGS ARE GETTING
WEIRD.
¶ SO I WENT BACK IN TIME TO
ITALY AND MET GALILEO GALILEI ¶
¶ AND TOLD HIM THE EARTH
REVOLVES AROUND THE SUN ¶
>> YOU'RE COMING WITH US, BIG
FELLA.
¶ THEY TRAVELED BACK FARTHER
TO LINEAR SPACE AND COMMUNICATED
WITH ANOTHER RACE ¶
¶ THEN GOT HIT BY ANOTHER FISH
AND A BUCKET OF WATER ¶
>> THAT ISN'T NECESSARY.
>> COOL!
¶ GALILEO GALILEI AND THE
MILITARY AND THE BIRDS AND THE
BEES AND A BIG BLOCK OF CHEESE ¶
¶ JUST TWO TRAVELING BITCHES ON
AND A MAN WHO LOST HIS JOB
ANDRE ¶
¶ ANDRE ANDRE ¶
HA HA HA!
¶ I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE
FROM THE HOURS OF 12 TO 12
I AM NOT THE LEAST COMPELLED
BY ANYONE BUT YOURSELF ¶
¶ LOOK AT ME
IT MAKES ME MELT
I KNOW YOU WANNA
SEE ME IN HELL ¶
¶ MY LOVE I'M DEALING WITH
THE CARDS I'VE DEALT
WHILE YOU'RE DANCING
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE ¶
¶ WAS IT ALWAYS IN YOUR PLAN
TO LEAVE EVENTUALLY ¶
¶ BECAUSE TO ME
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
THAT COULD MAKE SENSE TO ME ¶
¶ THE LAST AND FINAL
PUZZLE PIECE ¶
¶ IN A ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE
I LOOK FOR YOU ¶
¶ WOULD YOU AVOID ME OR
WOULD YOU LOOK FOR ME TOO ¶
¶ TELL ME
IS OUR STORY THROUGH
OR DO OUR HEARTS
STILL BEAT IN TUNE ¶
¶ I'VE NEVER FELT ANYTHING
LIKE THE LOVE
FROM MY FINAL DAYS ¶
¶ WHY'D YOU WAIT
TO SHOW ME
YOU COULD DO IT THIS WAY ¶
¶ WHOO
I'LL NEVER LOOK AT YOU
LOOK AT YOU THE SAME ¶
¶ WE MET IN THE PARIS CAFE
I SAID CAN I SIT WITH YOU
COMMA CA SE FAIT
MY MISTAKE OHH ¶
¶ IF I'D KNOWN IT
WOULD HAVE BEEN THIS WAY
I'D NEVER LOOKED AT YOU
LOOKED IN THE FIRST PLACE ¶
¶ WAS IT ALWAYS IN YOUR PLAN
TO LEAVE EVENTUALLY ¶
¶ BECAUSE TO ME
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
THAT COULD MAKE SENSE TO ME ¶
¶ THE LAST AND FINAL
PUZZLE PIECE ¶
>> I SAID ONE, TWO, THREE, LET'S
GO.
¶ IN A ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE
I LOOK FOR YOU
WOULD YOU AVOID ME OR
WOULD YOU LOOK FOR ME TOO ¶
¶ TELL ME
IS OUR STORY THROUGH THROUGH
OR DO OUR HEARTS
STILL BEAT IN TUNE ¶
¶ MAYBE I'M DELUSIONAL
AND THE WAY YOU ACT IS USUAL
MAYBE IN ANOTHER WORLD
I WON'T FEEL SO UNLOVABLE ¶
¶ OHH-OH
OH OHH-OH OH ¶
¶ IN A ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE
I LOOK FOR YOU
WOULD YOU AVOID ME OR
WOULD YOU LOOK FOR ME TOO ¶
¶ TELL ME
IS OUR STORY THROUGH
OR DO OUR HEARTS
STILL BEAT IN TUNE ¶
¶ IN A ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE
I LOOK FOR YOU
WOULD YOU AVOID ME OR
WOULD YOU SEE ME THROUGH ¶
¶ TELL ME
IS OUR STORY THROUGH
OR DO OUR HEARTS
STILL BEAT IN TUNE ¶
COME ON!
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> A PHARMACEUTICAL EXECUTIVE
COLLAPSED IN THE OVAL OFFICE ON
THURSDAY, AND SPEAKING OF
PHARMACEUTICALS, WHATEVER
THEY'VE GOT TRUMP ON, I WANT
SOME.
JUST LOOK HOW CHILL HE IS DURING
ALL OF THIS.
HE'S JUST STANDING THERE.
HE'S LITERALLY THIS MEME.
THE CRAZIEST PART IS THAT DURING
THE COMMOTION, RFK JR. JUST RUNS
AWAY.
WATCH, WATCH THIS.
JUST HOW SUSPICIOUS IS THAT?
SUCH A WEIRD MOVE.
DON'T WORRY, BY THE WAY.
THE MAN WHO COLLAPSED IS TOTALLY
OKAY.
YOU CAN TELL BECAUSE IF THERE'S
SOMETHING DEAD ON THE GROUND,
RFK EATS IT.
>>> ON TUESDAY, ZOHRAN MAMDANI
WAS ELECTED MAYOR OF NEW YORK
CITY.
HE WAS ELECTED -- LOT OF SLIWA
FANS?
HE WAS ELECTED MAYOR DESPITE HIS
OPPONENT, ANDREW CUOMO,
RECEIVING ENDORSEMENTS FROM
DONALD TRUMP AND ERIC ADAMS.
WHICH IS LIKE TRYING TO BRING A
GIRL HOME BY SAYING, "NOT TO
BRAG BUT I HAVE HELP SITE "B"
AND "C."
>>> ANDREW CUOMO SPENT THE LAST
DAY BEFORE THE ELECTION
CAMPAIGNING AROUND THE CITY IN A
WHITE FORD BRONCO.
WHICH IS WHAT O.J. SIMPSON USED
TO GET AWAY FROM POLICE.
PLEASE O.J. WAS AHEAD IN THE
RACE FOR A WHILE.
>> OH, STOP.
>>> REPUBLICAN CURTIS SLIWA
CONCEDED THE MAYORAL RACE ON
TUESDAY IN FRONT OF A CROWD OF
HIS MOST LOYAL SUPPORTERS,
SQUIRRELS.
CONSERVATIVE CRITICS HAVE BEEN
CALLING ZOHRAN MAMDANI A
FAR-LEFT RADICAL AS WELL AS A
JIHADIST.
BUT HE CAN'T BE FAR-LEFT AND
WHAT DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO
DO, TURN ISIS INTO THEYSIS?
I WORKED REALLY HARD ON THAT,
COLIN.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS GOOD, I LIKED
THAT.
>>> THE SUPREME COURT ON FRIDAY
TEMPORARILY ALLOWED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TO WITHHOLD
S.N.A.P. BENEFITS, INCLUDING
FOOD STAMPS.
AND WE ACTUALLY HAVE FOOTAGE OF
TRUMP FINDING OUT HE DOES NOT
HAVE TO PAY THE BENEFITS.
>> SO STUPID.
>>> DEMOCRAT ABIGAIL SPANBERGER
HAS BEEN ELECTED AS VIRGINIA'S
FIRST-EVER FEMALE GOVERNOR --
DEFEATING REPUBLICAN WINSOME
EARLE-SEARS.
WHO WILL NOW HAVE TO CHANGE HER
NAME TO LOSESOME EARLE-SEARS.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID THAT HE
WILL ONLY NEGOTIATE WITH
DEMOCRATS WHEN THEY AGREE TO
REOPEN THE GOVERNMENT, ADDING
THAT HE WOULD NOT BE EXTORTED.
EXCEPT THAT ONE TIME HE FAMOUSLY
GOT EXTORTED BY THAT MATTRESS
ACTRESS STORMY DANIELS.
>>> TRUMP ALSO REACTED TO NEWS
THAT PRINCE ANDREW LOST THE
TITLE OF PRINCE OVER TIES TO
JEFFREY EPSTEIN, SAYING HE FEELS
BADLY FOR THE ROYAL FAMILY.
TRUMP EVEN SENT PRINCE ANDREW A
CARD TO CHEER HIM UP, AWW.
HANG IN THERE.
POOR EPSTEIN.
>>> NEW MEXICO HAS BECOME THE
FIRST STATE IN THE COUNTRY TO
OFFER ITS RESIDENTS FREE
CHILDCARE, WHICH WILL BE
PROVIDED BY NANNIES FROM OLD
MEXICO.
>>> A VIDEO HAS GONE VIRAL OF A
MAN IN MEXICO COMING UP BEHIND
PRESIDENT CLAUDIA SHEINBAUM AND
TRYING TO KISS AND GROPE HER.
SO NO, HE'S NOT TAKING THE LOSS
WELL.
>>> STARBUCKS HAS BEGUN SELLING
THE NEW GLASS "BEARISTA" COLD
CUP, WHICH IS THE MOST ADORABLE
WAY TO SMOKE CRACK IN THEIR
BATHROOM.
>>> TOM BRADY ANNOUNCED THAT HIS
CURRENT DOG IS ACTUALLY A CLONE
OF HIS PREVIOUS DOG, WHO PASSED
AWAY TWO YEARS AGO.
BRADY ALSO REVEALED THAT DURING
HIS CAREER, HE WENT THROUGH
EIGHT GRONKS.
>>> SCIENTISTS HAVE POSTED A NEW
VIDEO OF A POD OF ORCAS
ATTACKING AND KILLING A GROUP OF
BABY SHARKS.
SO I GUESS WE WERE RIGHT TO PUT
THEM IN PRISON.
>>> A NEW POLL FINDS THAT NEARLY
30% OF GEN-Zers THINK THAT
PAYING WITH CASH IS CRINGE.
EVEN WHEN I CRUMPLE IT UP FOR
THEM.
>> DON'T CLAP.
>>> A HUSBAND AND WIFE FROM
MIAMI HAVE BEEN NAMED THE
WORLD'S OLDEST MARRIED COUPLE
WITH A COMBINED AGE OF 216
YEARS.
WHICH SOUNDS REALLY SWEET UNTIL
YOU REALIZE THE HUSBAND IS 200.
>>> LIONSGATE HAS RELEASED THE
FIRST TRAILER FOR "MICHAEL," THE
UPCOMING BIO-PIC ABOUT MICHAEL
JACKSON.
AND LIKE JACKSON, IT STARTS OUT
VERY DARK BUT ENDS IN A MUCH
LIGHTER TONE.
THESE SOME ARE THINKERS.
>> YEAH.
>>> OFFICIALS IN IRELAND ARE
SAYING THERE ARE REPORTS OF A
LION WANDERING IN THE WOODS --
ACTUALLY JUST A DOG WITH A NEW
HAIRCUT.
IRELAND, I GUESS WE ARE PRETTY
DRUNK.
>>> "THE NEW YORK TIMES"
RECENTLY RAN AN ARTICLE CALLING
THE STATEN ISLAND FERRY THAT I
PURCHASED WITH PETE DAVIDSON --
CALLED IT A MONEY-LOSING FIASCO.
WITH MORE ON THIS, PETE
DAVIDSON.
>> WHAT'S UP?
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
>> WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> THANK YOU, COLIN.
COLIN, YOU'RE LOOKING GREAT AS
EVER.
CHE, STARTING TO CRACK.
>> WHOA!
>> SORRY.
SO YEAH, IN CASE YOU'RE
WONDERING WHY I HAD TO DO A SHOW
IN SAUDI ARABIA, WE'RE LOSING
MILLIONS ON THIS FERRY.
I ASSUME THAT'S WHAT THE ARTICLE
SAYS.
I CAN'T SPEND $5 ON A PAYWALL
WHEN I GOT A KID ON THE WAY.
>> OH, THAT'S RIGHT, CONGRATS,
PETE.
>> YES, YES.
THANK YOU, YEAH.
I'M JUST -- I'M JUST EXCITED TO
BE A DAD, YOU KNOW, AND GIVE IT
ALL THE ENERGY AND ENTHUSIASM I
NEVER HAD FOR THIS SHOW.
>> COME ON.
I WILL TELL YOU ON THE OTHER
SIDE, I DEFINITELY PREFER HAVING
A KID TO A FERRY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT?
YOU HAVE A GREAT JOB AND YOUR
UNCLE ROBERT IS THE HHS
SECRETARY, RIGHT?
>> FOR THE LAST TIME, PETE, I'M
NOT A KENNEDY.
>> OKAY.
LOOK, I ACTUALLY -- I UNDERSTAND
RFK.
I WOULDN'T BE FAMOUS WITHOUT MY
DAD DYING, EITHER.
THANK GOD THAT HAPPENED.
WOULDN'T TRADE IT.
>> GOOD LORD.
>> NO?
ALL RIGHT.
WE EVEN GAVE THE BOAT A NEW
NAME.
WE THOUGHT "THE STATEN ISLAND
FERRY" SOUNDED TOO DEPRESSING.
NOW IT'S CALLED "THE TITANIC 2."
>> IT'S GOING VERY WELL.
WE GOT PAID BY NIKE TO PUT AN AD
ON IT FOR THE NEW YORK CITY
MARATHON.
>> EXACTLY.
IF LORNE MICHAELS HAS CAUGHT US
ANYTHING, IT'S THAT YOU NEVER,
EVER GIVE UP.
EVEN IF EVERYONE SAYS THE TIME
HAS COME AND TINA FEY IS READY
TO TAKE OVER.
NO, I ACTUALLY HAVE A GREAT IDEA
TO MAKE THIS FERRY MORE OF A
SUCCESS.
>> OH, GREAT.
>> AS YOU KNOW, WE JUST HAD A
MAYORAL ELECTION, WHICH IS MY
LEAST FAVORITE KIND OF ORAL.
THAT'S A CLASSIC PETE!
PETE'S BACK, BABY!
>> YOU'RE ADDING NEW BITS NOW?
YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOR YEARS.
>> YEP, IT'S NOW THIS AND CHAD.
>> YEAH.
>> SO ANYWAY, WE JUST HAD AN
ELECTION.
IF YOU DON'T MIND, I HAVE A
MESSAGE FOR EVERYONE WHO DID NOT
VOTE FOR OUR NEW MAYOR.
HEY, STATEN ISLANDERS!
DID YOU PROMISE TO MOVE OUT OF
NEW YORK IF MAMDANI WON BUT HAVE
TOO MANY WARRANTS IN NEW JERSEY
AND NOT ENOUGH GUNS FOR FLORIDA?
WELCOME TO NEW STATEN ISLAND!
YEAH!
IT WILL HAVE EVERYTHING THAT
MAKES STATEN ISLAND GREAT.
THE PIZZA.
>> THAT WAS THE WHOLE LIST?
>> YEP.
NEW STATEN ISLAND.
WE CAN'T CALL IT THE TITANIC
ANYMORE SINCE THE PEOPLE ON THIS
SHIP WILL ACTUALLY LOVE RUNNING
INTO ICE.
THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
GOT IT GOING, YEP.
STILL GOT IT.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE IT'S GOING
TO BE A BIG YEAR FOR US.
>> I THINK SO TOO, I COULDN'T BE
MORE EXCITED.
MY POINT IS, LOOK, THE FERRY,
IT'S FINE.
SOMETIMES THE NEWS JUST MAKES
THINGS SEEM WORSE THAN THEY ARE.
LIKE HOW EVERYONE WAS SURE
CERTAIN PEOPLE WOULD BE EXPOSED
AND RUINED FOR PEOPLE ON THE
EPSTEIN LIST.
IT'S 2025 AND ALL THREE OF US
ARE STILL UP HERE.
>> PETE DAVIDSON, EVERYONE.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I'M MICHA
THE THEME OF OUR DELTA GAMMA
THANKSGIVING PARTY WILL BE, PILL
GRIM HOS AND RESPECTFUL
REPRESENTATION OF INDIGENOUS
PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
NEXT ACTION ITEM.
THIS IS PRETTY SERIOUS, OKAY?
I GOT AN EMAIL FROM THE GREEK
LIFE ADVISER, AND APPARENTLY
ANOTHER SORORITY JUST LEARNED
ONE OF THEIR PLEDGES WAS
ACTUALLY A FRAT GUY IN A
HYPER-REALISTIC GIRL MASK.
>> NO WAY.
>> WHAT?
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT'S SO WEIRD.
>> YEAH, THAT IS SO WEIRD!
>> I KNOW.
WELL, THEY ASKED US TO JUST STAY
VIGILANT, OKAY?
I'M JUST ASKING YOU, IF YOU SEE
ANYTHING, JUST SAY SOMETHING,
OKAY?
>> UM, SO I DON'T WANT TO, LIKE,
CALL SOMEONE OUT OR WHATEVER.
BUT I THINK SOMEONE IN OUR
SORORITY HEAT BE A FRAT GUY IN A
HERE REALISTIC MASK.
>> WHAT?
>> WHAT, NO WAY.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> I THINK IT'S ALYSSA.
>> WAIT.
ME?
>> ARE YOU CRAZY?
>> SO MEAN.
>> SHAME ON YOU, MADDIE.
>> THAT'S MESSED UP.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT THE HELL, MADDIE?
HAVE SOME RESPECT FOR YOUR
SISTER.
>> SORRY.
YOU SAID SAY SOMETHING IF YOU
SAW SOMETHING STRANGE.
>> JUST SAY IT, MADDIE.
YOU THINK ALYSSA'S UGLY.
HOW TO THE ABSOLUTE DARE YOU!
DELTA GAMMAS DON'T JUDGE
PEOPLE'S LOOKS.
DID YOU FORGET OUR MOTTO?
DON'T JUDGE PEOPLE'S LOOKS.
WE JUDGE PEOPLE BY HOW MUCH
MONEY THEIR PARENTS MAKE.
>> OKAY, YEAH.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT ALYSSA, MADDIE,
IT'S ABOUT YOU.
YOU ALWAYS GET ON NEW SISTERS.
YOU WERE AWFUL TO ME LAST YEAR,
NOW YOU'RE ACCUSING HER OF BEING
A FRAT GUY IN A MASK?
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> DISGUSTING!
>> OKAY, DO YOU SEE HOW SHE
EATS?
THAT IS NOT NORMAL.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS OF WHAT
AN AMAZING PERSON ALYSSA IS.
HER CONTRIBUTION TO DELTA GAMMA
IS UNMATCHED.
SHE'S JUST A FIRST YEAR AND
SHE'S ALREADY PLANNED NOT ONE,
NOT TWO, BUT 15 BIKINI CAR WASH
FUND-RAISERS.
>> YEAH, GIRL POWER!
>> DON'T YOU THINK IT'S
SUSPICIOUS THAT SHE NEVER
PARTICIPATES?
>> SHE'S ALLERGIC TO THE SUN.
IT'S JUST SAFER FOR HER TO WATCH
FROM THE GARAGE, WEARING
SUNGLASSES, WITH A PILE OF
TOWELS ON HER LAP.
I'M SORRY, MADDIE, BUT YOUR
THEORY IS REJECTED DUE TO LACK
OF PROOF.
>> CAN MY PROOF BE HER VAPING
RIGHT NOW?
THE SMOKE IS COMING OUT OF HER
EYEHOLES.
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THIS?
>> IT JUST DOES THAT!
>> MADDIE, STOP.
YOU'RE MAKING ALYSSA SAD.
LOOK.
>> SO SAD.
>> MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GO.
>> NO!
>> DON'T GO!
>> CAN WE JUST TAKE A MOMENT AND
LOOK AT WHAT'S INSIDE HER PURSE?
A HUGE UNOPENED BOX OF MAXI
PADS.
>> WHAT?
>> A BEANIE BABY.
>> AND A FRAMED PHOTO OF HILLARY
CLINTON.
>> AND?
>> AND THAT LOOKS LIKE A STUPID
GUY WOULD THINK GIRLS HAVE IN
THEIR PURSE.
>> I'MA SLAP THIS BITCH.
>> CALM DOWN, JESUS.
THIS DISCUSSION IS OVER.
ALL RIGHT?
MEETING ADJOURNED.
>> GIVE ME MY PURSE.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M SO SORRY FOR ALL OF THIS,
ALYSSA.
>> IT'S OKAY.
BYE!
OH, MY GOD.
I'M GOING TO PASS OUT IN THIS
THING.
>> ALYSSA?
>> UH -- I CAN EXPLAIN.
>> NO NEED.
SECRET'S SAFE WITH ME, MAN.
BRAD.
DON'T SIT IN YOUR ROOM, PLAY
VIDEO GAMES ALL WEEKEND.
ALL RIGHT?
COME ON, LET'S GO OUTSIDE.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M SERIOUS, BUD, COME ON.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR FRIENDS.
>> OKAY, I JUST LITERALLY NEED
ONE SECOND.
>> ONE.
>> ANYONE HAVE A SHIELD JACK?
>> ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME THE --
SORRY, FELLOWS.
BRAD'S GOT TO GO.
HEY!
FIRST OF ALL, YOU NEVER CALL
SOMEONE THAT WORD.
SECOND OF ALL, IT MAKES NO SENSE
'CAUSE I'M WHITE.
LITTLE JACKASS.
GET YOUR SHOES ON, BUD.
TAKING YOU SOMEPLACE FUN.
>> WHERE?
>> WHY DO I KEEP GETTING THIS
STUFF?
>> DAD, I'M TOO OLD FOR THE
PLAYGROUND.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT, YOU'RE 10.
>> I'M 11, THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
BUT COME ON, GO DOWN THE SLIDE.
HEADFIRST!
ALL RIGHT, FEETFIRST IS GOOD,
FEETFIRST IS FINE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> COMING.
SCRAPING MY SKIN.
>> SCOOT, BRAD.
SCOOT.
YEAH, MAYBE YOU ARE TOO BIG FOR
THIS, ALL RIGHT.
>>> LOOK WHAT I FOUND, BUD.
RUN OUT 10 YARDS, FAKE RIGHT, GO
LEFT, I'LL HIT YOU ON THE CROSS.
YOU READY?
>> ONE SEC.
OKAY.
>> HUT, HUT, HIKE!
GOT TO GO ON HIKE, BUD.
HIKE!
BRAD, LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME.
OH!
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
>>> OH-OH!
BRAD, WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
>> WHOA, IS THAT A DRONE?
>> YEAH.
I GOT IT FOR YOU.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
JUST REMEMBER, GENTLE MOVEMENTS
ON THE CONTROLLER, OKAY?
>> I KNOW.
>> GODDAMMIT.
>>> THERE'S A GUY ON YOUR LEFT.
ON MY HILL.
NICE.
OH, THAT'S YOUR MOM.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO, DAD.
>> I LOVE YOU MORE THAN YOUR MOM
DOES.
DON'T TELL HER I SAID THAT, BUT
IT'S TRUE.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
BYE, DAD.
>> BYE, SON.
OH, SON OF A BITCH!
¶ BRAD ¶
>> I KNOW, WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
TAKE OFF A HALF-HOUR AGO.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WE DO
APOLOGIZE FOR THE DELAY.
AS YOU KNOW, THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN HAS AFFECTED THE
FLIGHTS AROUND THE COUNTRY.
I'M NOT BLAMING ANYONE, MAMDANI,
BUT WE'RE DOING OUR BEST TO MOVE
YOU GUYS AROUND ONCE AGAIN.
WE DO APOLOGIZE, AND THANK YOU.
>> GOD, THIS ABSOLUTELY STINKS.
>> HEY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
FROM THE FLIGHT DECK, THIS IS
YOUR CAPTAIN SPEAKING.
JUST GOT WORD FROM THE TOWER.
IT'S GOING TO BE A BIT LONGER
HERE ON THE TARMAC.
PROBABLY IN ABOUT 15 MINUTES,
I'LL COME BACK ON AND TELL YOU
IT'S GOING TO BE TWO MORE HOURS.
GOOD NEWS IS, FINE WEATHER
COMING OUT OF CLEVELAND.
SHOULD BE A SMOOTH FLIGHT ONCE
WE GET UP IN THE AIR.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BE HERE
FOREVER.
>> TRUTH BE TOLD, CAN'T WAIT TO
GET TO CLEVELAND MYSELF.
GOING TO BE MEETING UP WITH A
YOUNG LADY OUT THERE.
I MET HER ON THE APPS.
ALWAYS SAID I WOULDN'T DO THE
APPS BUT LAST NIGHT I GOT A
LITTLE RUM IN MY, WHAT THE HELL.
COPILOT RITCHIE HERE SET ME UP
WITH A PROFILE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU FOLLOW MY LEAD, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE SWIMMING IN IT.
>> THAT'S WONDERFUL, RITCHIE.
ALREADY MATCHED WITH A CUTE,
YEAH, A CUTE ABOUT 7.5 GIRL,
SORT OF MY SWEET SPOT.
WELL, OUT OF MY RANGE, BUT
ATTAINABLE.
JUST SENT HER A RISKY TEXT.
SHE SAID, HOPPING IN THE SHOWER.
AND I SAID, WITHOUT ME?
HA HA.
MONKEY COVERING EYES.
BEEN ABOUT 20 MINUTES, NO
RESPONSE.
GET YOU AN UPDATE SOON.
SIT BACK AND ENJOY THE FLIGHT.
>> OKAY, WELL, THAT'S INSANE.
>> I KNOW.
SHE'S TOTALLY LEADING HIM ON.
HOPPING IN THE SHOWER!
OOH, I'M A LITTLE NAKED LADY,
HOPE I DON'T GET BUBBLES ON MY
BOOBIES!
WHORE.
>> CAPTAIN DAVE.
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT ABOUT 576
PLANES IN FRONT OF US.
BUT GOOD NEWS IS MAN IN THE
TOWER SAYS HE'S ON TOP OF IT.
BAD NEWS IS, BY IT, I MEAN THE
TOWER ITSELF.
A COUPLE OF PEOPLE TRYING TO
TALK HIM DOWN.
BUT WE SHOULD HAVE YOU IN
CLEVELAND BY CHRISTMAS.
>> IT'S NOVEMBER 8th!
>> AND EVEN WORSE NEWS, I
DECIDED TO DOUBLE TEXT.
NOT GOING TO LIE, IT'S PRETTY
BAD.
SENT A GIF OF JACK NICHOLSON
KNOCKING DOWN THE DOOR IN "THE
SHINING."
POKING HIS HEAD IN, CAPTIONED
IT, "ME IF I WAS THERE RIGHT
NOW."
HATED IT AS SOON AS I SENT IT.
>> I TOLD YOU WHAT YOU NEED TO
SAY TO THIS GIRL IS --
>> YEAH, OKAY, WELL, THAT'S
COLORFUL.
FOLKS, FROM THE FLIGHT DECK,
BASICALLY THE GIST OF RITCHIE'S
PITCH WAS SOMETHING ABOUT
SLATHERING A CERTAIN PART OF HER
BODY IN BUTTER, THEN CRACKING
HER OPEN LIKE A CRAB LEG.
DON'T THINK I'LL TEXT THAT.
IF YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS, PLEASE
LET A FLIGHT ATTENDANT A
CALIFORNIA KNOW.
HIT THAT CALL PUT TON.
SIT BACK AND ENJOY THE FLIGHT.
>> THIS GUY'S UNRAVELING.
>> WOULDN'T MIND YOU CHOPPING
DOWN THE DOOR TO SEE ME IN THE
SHOWER.
>> TO SEE WHAT, SOMETHING I SEE
FOR FREE EVERY DAY?
NO THANK YOU.
>> FOLKS, CAPTAIN DAVE HERE.
UPDATE FROM THE TOWER.
NO NEWS.
NO NEWS FROM THE TOWER.
UPDATE FROM MY TEXT SAGA.
SHE JUST POSTED ON HER STORIES,
SO SHE IS ON HER PHONE.
AND -- I AM IN HELL.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, ALL YOU NEED
TO SAY IS, WORD FOR WORD --
>> UH-HUH.
RIGHT.
UH-HUH.
I CAN'T SAY ANY OF THOSE WORDS.
YOU KNOW, I WOULD LOVE TO HEAR A
WOMAN'S PERSPECTIVE.
MAYBE EVEN A GAY GUY.
ONE OF THE NICE ONES, THOUGH.
NOT A GYM GAY.
SORT OF ALL ABOUT HIS BODY.
I WANT A NICE ONE.
A "MODERN FAMILY" TYPE.
MAYBE EVEN AN OLDER AFRICAN
AMERICAN GENTLEMAN.
THAT MIGHT BE NICE.
KIND OF A GROWN-ASS MAN TYPE,
SEEN IT ALL FROM BOTH SIDES NOW.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THE
CAPTAIN HAS REQUESTED THE HELP
OF A WOMAN, A NOT-MEAN GAY, OR A
GROWN AND SEXY BLACK MAN.
ONCE AGAIN, ANY WOMAN, KIND
GAYS, OR BILLY DEE WILLIAMS
TYPES, PLEASE HIT YOUR CALL
BUTTON NOW.
THANK YOU.
>> CAN WE PLEASE JUST GO
ALREADY?
>> CAPTAIN DAVE, BIG NEWS.
SHE TEXTED BACK, AND GET THIS,
SHE LOVED MY TEXT, AND YEAH SHE
POPPING.
SO I THINK I'M JUST GOING TO
TAKE THIS THING ON THE HIGHWAY.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, SOMBR.
¶ TOUCH MY BODY TENDER
'CAUSE THE FEELING
MAKES ME WEAK ¶
¶ KICKING OFF THE COVERS
I SEE THE CEILING
WHILE YOU'RE LOOKING
DOWN AT ME ¶
¶ HOW CAN WE GO
BACK TO BEING FRIENDS
WHEN WE JUST SHARED A BED ¶
¶ HOW CAN YOU LOOK
AT ME AND PRETEND
I'M SOMEONE
YOU'VE NEVER MET ¶
¶ IT WAS LAST DECEMBER
YOU WERE LAYIN'
ON MY CHEST ¶
¶ I STILL REMEMBER
I WAS SCARED TO TAKE A BREATH
DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO MOVE YOUR HEAD ¶
¶ HOW CAN WE GO
BACK TO BEING FRIENDS
WHEN WE JUST SHARED A BED
YEAH ¶
¶ HOW CAN YOU LOOK
AT ME AND PRETEND
I'M SOMEONE
YOU'VE NEVER MET ¶
¶ THE DEVIL IN YOUR EYES
WON'T DENY THE LIES
YOU'VE SOLD ¶
¶ I'M HOLDING ON TOO TIGHT
WHILE YOU LET GO
THIS IS CASUAL
OHH-OH OH ¶
¶ HOW CAN WE GO
BACK TO BEING FRIENDS
WHEN WE JUST SHARED A BED
YEAH ¶
¶ HOW CAN YOU LOOK
AT ME AND PRETEND
I'M SOMEONE
YOU'VE NEVER MET ¶
¶ HOW CAN WE GO
BACK TO BEING FRIENDS
WHEN WE JUST SHARED A BED
YEAH ¶
¶ HOW CAN YOU LOOK
AT ME AND PRETEND
I'M SOMEONE
YOU'VE NEVER MET
¶ OOH
SOMEONE YOU'VE NEVER MET
YEAH
SOMEONE YOU'VE NEVER MET ¶
BIG OAK TREE TO RIFT HER FRIENDS
IN BLAKE-BELIEVE MEADOW.
AS SHE GREW OLDER, SHE VISITED
LESS AND LESS.
WHEN ANNA WAS GROWN, SHE MADE
ONE LAST VISIT TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
>> MY SPECIAL FRIENDS, I'M GOING
TO MISS YOU ALL SO MUCH.
>> WE'LL MISS YOU TOO, ANNA.
BUT WE'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
>> IN HERE.
>> YEAH!
>> THANK YOU, BEVIN.
BEFORE I GO, I WANT TO GIVE EACH
OF YOU A GIFT JUST AS A THANK
YOU FOR ALL OF OUR ADVENTURES.
>> YES, ANNA?
>> YOU TAUGHT ME TO LOOK AT THE
WORLD WITH A SENSE OF WONDER, SO
I GOT YOU THIS THING CALLED A
PINWHEEL.
>> WOW!
>> OH!
PINWHEEL!
>> ANNA, WOW!
>> WOW, PINWHEEL!
>> ANNA!
>> IT'S SPINNING, ANNA!
>> LOOK, IT'S A PINWHEEL!
>> I KNOW, I GET IT, IT'S NEAT.
>> WOW, THE PINWHEEL HAS SO MANY
COLORS, ANNA.
>> ANNA!
YOU CAN HOLD IT WITH YOUR HANDS,
ANNA!
>> I LOVE THE PINWHEEL SO MUCH,
ANNA.
>> PINWHEEL, ANNA!
>> I'M SO GLAD YOU LIKE THEM.
SO MUCH MORE THAN I THOUGHT YOU
WOULD.
>> THANK YOU, ANNA!
>> BEVIN AND PIFF.
>> YES, ANNA?
>> YOU TAUGHT ME TO SEE THE
BEAUTY IN OTHERS, SO I GOT YOU
SOMETHING THAT IS BEAUTIFUL NO
MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT.
>> A PINWHEEL!
>> NO, NOT A PINWHEEL.
OKAY?
>> OKAY, ANNA.
>> I GOT YOU KALEIDOSCOPES.
>> OH!
>> OH, WOW!
IT'S AMAZING, ANNA.
>> I'LL LOOK THROUGH IT EVERY
DAR.
>> AND FINALLY, MR. BUNSY --
>> OH, ANNA, MY VERY BEST
FRIEND.
>> YOU ALWAYS ENCOURAGED ME TO
BE AN ARTIST, SO -- I DREW A
PICTURE FOR YOU.
I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
>> EVERYONE, PLEASE LOOK AT
THIS!
>> PINWHEEL!
>> I FELL ASLEEP FOR A LITTLE
BIT.
>> ANNA!
>> GUYS, MAYBE WE TAKE THE
WONDER DOWN A LITTLE.
>> FOR REAL, IT'S TOO MUCH
WONDER.
>> BUT YOUR PICTURE'S BEAUTIFUL,
ANNA.
I'LL TREASURE IT FOREVER.
BEFORE YOU GO, WE GOT YOU A
GIFT --
>> A PINWHEEL!
>> NO, NO!
GO PLAY WITH YOUR PINWHEEL.
GIVE US SPACE.
GO.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE PINWHEEL?
>> GO!
I'M BEGGING BOTH YOU, GO OVER
THERE.
>> NO --
>> ENOUGH, ENOUGH!
ENOUGH OF IT!
>> WHEN YOU WERE JUST A LITTLE
MITE, YOU WROTE THIS LETTER TO
YOUR GROWN-UP SELF.
AND WE KEPT IT THROUGH ALL THIS
TIME TO BE READ ON YOUR LAST
VISIT.
>> "DEAR GROWN-UP ME.
I HOPE YOU STILL DO WHAT MAKES
US HAPPY.
I HOPE YOU STILL LOOK AT CLOUDS
AND SEE KINGDOMS.
I HOPE YOU STILL DANCE AND MAKE
UP STORIES.
MOST OF US, I HOPE YOU DON'T
FORGET ME."
>> TREMENDOUS.
THAT LITTLE GIRL IS NEVER DONE.
SHE'LL ALWAYS BE A PART OF YOU,
ANNA.
>> ANNA!
>> HE'S TELL ME THIS IS NOT
ABOUT THE PINWHEEL.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
WE PROMISE.
>> TELL HER, TELL HER!
>> ANNA, ANNA.
WHEN YOU -- IF YOU -- IF YOU --
WHEN YOU -- WHEN YOU -- IF
YOU -- WHEN -- WHEN -- WHEN --
WHEN YOU -- IF YOU -- WHEN YOU
BLOW A PINWHEEL, IT HAS
COLORS --
>> GIVE ME THIS.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS WORSE THAN
WHEN I BOUGHT THOSE PUPPETS.
>> PUPPETS!
>> ANNA, ANNA!
>> IT'S ANNA.
IT'S A HARD VOWEL.
OKAY?
GOD.
I LOVE YOU ALL SO MUCH.
BUT I GOTTA BOUNCE.
>> ANNA!
>> AND IT WAS ON THAT DAY ANNA
DECIDED TO NEVER HAVE CHILDREN.
>>> THANKS TO SOMBR, PETE
DAVIDSON, LORNE MICHAELS, THIS
AMAZING CAST AND CREW.
THIS WAS ONE OF THE BEST WEEKS
OF MY ENTIRE LIFE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!