>>> YOU'RE WATCHING C-SPAN,
LATER IS TAYLOR SWIFT NOW DATING
MARCO RUBIO?
BUT FIRST, TESTIMONY FROM THREE
UNIVERSITY PRESIDENTS
ON THE
SUBJECT OF ANTI-SEMITISM ON
COLLEGE CAMPUSES.
>> ORDER, PLEASE.
ORDER, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE JOINED TODAY BY THE HEADS
OF THREE OF OUR MOST ESTEEMED
UNIVERSITIES,
THE PRESIDENT OF
M.I.T. SALLY KORNBLUTH.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN MORE AFRAID
TO BE ANYWHERE.
>> THE PRESIDENT OF UPENN,
ELIZABETH MAGILL.
>> CAN I JUST RESIGN NOW?
>> NOT YET.
AND THE PRESIDENT OF HARVARD,
DR. CLAUDINE GAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> DR. GAY, WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO
A QUICK JOKE ABOUT YOUR NAME TO
GET IT OUT OF THE WAY?
>> I WOULD.
DR. GAY SOUNDS LIKE A MOLLY
TEALER ON FIRE ISLAND.
>> THANK YOU.
NOW, I'LL TURN IT OVER TO MEG
SUPERSTAR ELISE STEFANIK FROM NEW YORK
WHO'S BEEN PACING THE
HALLWAYS LISTENING TO LOSE
YOURSELF BY EMINEM.
MS. STEFANIK.
>> THANK YOU, CHAIRWOMAN.
I'M GOING TO START SCREAMING
QUESTIONS AT THESE WOMEN LIKE
I'M BILLY EICHNER.
ANTI-SEMITISM, YEA OR NAY.
>> I'M SORRY.
WHAT?
>> YES OR NO, IS CALLING FOR JEWS
AGAINST THE CODE OF CONDUCT
FOR HARVARD?
>> WELL, IT DEPENDS ON THE
CONTEXT.
>> THAT CAN'T BE THE ANSWER.
UPENN LADY, YES OR NO?
>> WE ARE INTERESTED IN STOPPING
ALL FORMS OF HATRED,
ANTI-SEMITISM, ISLAM PHOBIA.
SECOND
CHANGE
KEEP IN MIND:
IF YOU DON'T SAY YES, YOU'RE
GOING TO MAKE ME LOOK GOOD,
WHICH IS REALLY HARD TO DO.
SO I'LL ASK YOU STRAIGHT UP.
DO YOU THINK GENOCIDE IS BAD?
>> COULD I SUBMIT AN ANSWER IN
WRITING AT A LATER DATE?
>> AM I WINNING THIS HEARING?
SOMEBODY PINCH ME.
>> MS. STEFANIK, YOUR TIME IS
UP.
>> OH, THANK GOD.
>> THE CHAIR RECOGNIZES
GENTLEMAN FROM MICHIGAN.
>> THANK YOU.
I YIELD MY TIME BACK TO
MS. STEFANIK.
>> DAMN IT.
>> I AM HERE TODAY BECAUSE HATE
SPEECH HAS NO PLACE ON COLLEGE
CAMPUSES.
HATE SPEECH BELONGS IN CONGRESS,
ON ELON MUSK'S TWITTER,
IN PRIVATE DINNER WITH MY DONORS
AND IN PUBLIC SPEECHES MY BY
WORK HUSBAND, DONALD TRUMP.
SO DR. GAY, SIMPLE QUESTION,
IS IT ACCEPTABLE FOR STUDENTS TO
USE ANTI-SEMITIC LANGUAGE?
>> ON THIS SUBJECT, I WOULD LIKE
TO SPEAK NOT FROM THE HEART BUT
FROM THE THESAURUS.
THAT TYPE OF HATEFUL SPEECH IS
PERSONALLY ABHORRENT TO ME.
>> COULD YOU PHRASE THAT IN AN
EVEN MORE ACADEMIC WAY?
>> SURE.
THAT VARIETY OF ODIOUS
IS
SLOW
RATION IS REPUGNANT.
PROTECT
WE'RE TALKING PRECAUTIONS TO
PROTECT ALL STUDENTS,
JEWISH
STUDENTS, MUSLIM STUDENTS.
>> AGAIN, UGH, JUST THE FIRST
ONE.
THIS IS PERSONAL FOR ME.
WHILE I AM NOT JEWISH, I'M ROMAN CATHOLIC,
SOME OF MY CLOSEST
FRIENDS ARE ALSO ROMAN CATHOLIC.
SO UPENN LADY, WOULD YOU SAY
THAT YOU ARE
ANTI, ANTI, ANTI, ANTI
ANTI-SEMITIC?
>> I'M SORRY.
CAN YOU TELL ME HOW MANY ANTIS
THAT WAS?
>> I WILL NOT.
>> YOU'RE ASKING US QUESTIONS
THAT SEEM VERY UNFAIR.
>> OH.
THANK YOU.
>> THE CHAIR RECOGNIZES
MR. TAKANO FROM CALIFORNIA.
>> THANK YOU, CHAIRWOMAN.
SO TO CLEAR THINGS UP, WHAT DOES
VIOLATE THE CODE OF CONDUCT AT
YOUR SCHOOLS?
WHAT ABOUT IF SOMEONE ON CAMPUS
YELLED, I POISONED THE WATER
SUPPLY?
>> IF THEY POISONED IT WITH
DIVERSITY, THAT COULD BE
WONDERFUL.
>> MM, DIVERSE WATER, IT SOUNDS
DELICIOUS.
>> OKAY.
AND WHAT IF THEY YELLED, I'VE
GOT A KNIFE?
>> WELL, MAYBE THEY HAVE A LISP,
AND THEY'RE SAYING,
I HAVE A
KNIFE BOUQUET OF FLOWERS FOR
YOU.
>> AS LONG AS THE FLOWERS ARE
DIVERSE, I ACCEPT.
>> AND WHAT IF THEY YELLED FIRE
IN A CROWDED THEATER?
>> I WOULD BE EXCITED THE
THEATER WAS CROWDED BECAUSE I
SUPPORT THE ARTS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CAN YOU TAKE A MORAL STANCE ON
ANYTHING?
CAN ANYONE HERE SAY YES TO A
SINGLE QUESTION?
>> YES, HELLO.
I AM THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX ONLINE.
AND I AM WILLING TO SAY YES TO
ANYTHING.
>> SEE?
SEE, FINALLY,
A REAL PRESIDENT
OF A REAL UNIVERSITY.
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY OUR SCHOOL
MOTTO.
U OF P, WE ARE A REAL
UNIVERSITY.
>> AND WILL YOU PROMISE TO
ELIMINATE ALL ANTI-SEMITISM FROM
YOUR CAMPUS?
>> WELL, MY CAMPUS IS THE INTERNET,
SO ANTI-SEMITISM IS
KIND OF OUR MOST POPULAR MAJOR.
AND OUR MASCOT IS PORN.
>> OKAY.
THEN WILL YOU OFFER A COURSE
EXPLAINING WHY ANTI-SEMITISM IS
WRONG?
>> LADY, WE'LL OFFER A COURSE ON
ANYTHING.
OUR ONLY MANDATORY COURSES ARE
HOW TO LOG INTO THE UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX ONLINE
AND HOW TO SET
UP AUTOPAY.
>> THANK YOU.
SOMEHOW THAT WAS THE ONLY
STRAIGHT ANSWER I GOT ALL DAY.
>> WELL, PLEASE DON'T SAY THE
ANSWER WAS STRAIGHT.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE ANSWER'S
SEXUAL ORIENTATION IS.
>> THANK YOU.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE.
THIS WAS ALL VERY USELESS.
>> NOT FOR ME.
FOR ME, IT WAS VERY USEFUL.
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
I'M THE HANUKKAH GIFT NO ONE
WANTED.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ADAM
DRIVER!
>>> HELLO.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE BACK!
ESPECIALLY DURING THIS TIME OF
YEAR.
I LOVE CHRISTMAS.
IT'S MY FAVORITE HOLIDAY.
THE FOOD, THE MUSIC, THE FAMILY.
BUT LARGELY, IT'S BECAUSE I HAVE
A VERY DEEP
AND PERSONAL
RELATIONSHIP WITH SANTA.
AND EVERY YEAR, I MAKE MY
CHRISTMAS LIST AND I TELL IT TO
HIM.
IT'S KIND OF OUR RITUAL.
USUALLY I DO IT IN PRIVATE,
BUT
SINCE WE'RE HERE AND I KNOW
SANTA WATCHES SNL.
HE HASN'T LIKED IT SINCE KATTAN
LEFT.
BUT IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I WOULD LIKE TO MAKE MY CHRISTMAS LIST
RIGHT NOW IF THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
THE PIANO IS PART OF THE RITUAL.
HE LOVES HEARING ME PLAY,
AND
IT'S ACTUALLY ME PLAYING.
CAN WE GET A CLOSEUP OF MY
HANDS?
SEE, THEY'RE VERY BIG.
VERY BIG HANDS.
I MEAN, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
IF YOU DON'T MIND, I WOULD LIKE
TO TALK TO SANTA NOW.
HEY, SANTA!
OH, RIGHT.
WE'RE ON TV.
HEY, SANTA.
IT'S ME, ADAM.
DRIVER.
FROM THE NICE LIST.
AND ALSO GIRLS.
I TURN 40 THIS YEAR, SANTA.
SO I WOULD LIKE FIVE PAIRS OF
CHINOS.
I ALSO WANT ONE OF THOSE GIANT
METAL TESLA TRUCKS.
I THINK IT WOULD PAIR PERFECTLY
WITH MY TEENY TINY MICRO PENIS.
OH, AND I WOULD LIKE PEOPLE TO
STOP COMING UP TO ME ON THE
STREET SAYING YOU KILLED HAN
SOLO.
I DIDN'T KILL HIM, WOKENESS
KILLED HAN SOLO.
LET'S SEE.
WHAT ELSE DO I WANT?
OH, YOU KNOW THOSE TIKTOKS
THAT'S LIKE THOSE COUPLES THAT
DO PRANKS ON EACH OTHER?
CAN YOU KILL THOSE PEOPLE?
I KNOW.
OKAY.
NOW IT'S PART OF THE RITUAL
WHERE I PLAY OH HOLY NIGHT
WHERE MAKING UNBREAKABLE EYE CONTACT
WITH THE CAMERA.
ACTUALLY, THAT'S REALLY HARD.
I'M NOT GOING TO DO THAT
ANYMORE.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS
IS A GINGER BREAD
HOUSE.
DO YOU THINK A GINGER BREAD MAN
GETS SCARED
WHEN HE REALIZES THE
HOUSE IS MADE OF HIS OWN SKIN?
THAT'S A CUTE ONE.
YOU CAN TELL YOUR KIDS THAT ONE.
I SHOULD ALSO SAY ANOTHER THING
I LOVE ABOUT CHRISTMAS IS
EGGNOG.
IT'S MY FAVORITE WAY TO HAVE
EGG.
WHENEVER I GO TO A DINER AND
THEY SAY HOW WOULD YOU LIKE YOUR
EGGS, I SAY NOGGED.
OKAY, SANTA.
THANK YOU FOR LISTENING.
I LOOK FORWARD TO YOU BREAKING
INTO MY HOUSE.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
I GOT YOU A GIFT THIS YEAR.
IT'S MY NEW MOVIE "FERRARI"
WHICH OPENS CHRISTMAS DAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, SANTA.
BIG FINISH.
IT'S ALMOST DONE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, SANTA!
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
OLIVIA RODRIGO I HERE!
STICK
IS.
>> YEAH.
WE GOT TO DO THESE ADULT ONLY
SKI TRIPS MORE OFTEN.
>> NOT GOING TO CHECK MY PHONE.
SHE'S WITH THE SITTER.
SHE'S FINE.
>> HONEY, HOW ARE YOU GOING TO
COPE WHEN THERE'S TWO OF THEM?
>> OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU PREGNANT AGAIN?
>> WE'RE NOT PREGNANT YET, BUT
WE'RE TRYING FOR ANOTHER ONE.
>> THAT'S SO GREAT, GUYS.
>> YEAH.
DON'T COME NOTHING ON OUR DOOR
TONIGHT.
>> AWW.
>> DANIEL, SINCE WE'RE ON THE
TOPIC, SHOULD WE TELL THEM?
>> OH, WELL, WE WEREN'T GOING TO
SAY IT, BUT LET'S JUST TELL
THEM.
>> WE'RE TRYING TO HAVE A BABY
TOO.
>> OH, THAT'S GREAT.
>> SO EXCITING.
>> I'M SO, SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
SO TELL ALL NOW.
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
ARE YOU GOING TO ADOPT?
>> NO.
WE'RE JUST GONNA TRY.
>> SO THEN YOU'RE DOING THE
SURROGATE ROUTE.
THAT'S GREAT.
>> HUH, SURROGACY, WELL, MAYBE
DOWN THE LINE, BUT FOR NOW,
WE'RE JUST GONNA TRY.
>> SO DON'T COME KNOCKING ON OUR
DOOR EITHER.
>> AWW.
>> SO ARE YOU TWO JUST STRAIGHT
UP HAVING SEX?
>> I MEAN, WE'RE NOT JUST HAVING
SEX.
WE'RE GETTING A LITTLE HELP.
AFTER JACOB IS DONE, I'M
THROWING MY LEGS UP, HANGING OFF
THE BAR AND LETTING GRAVITY DO
ITS THING.
>> NOBODY ASK ME TO GO INTO THE
HOT TUB TONIGHT, I'M NOT BOILING
MY BALLS.
>> RIGHT.
SO HOW IS THE TRYING GOING?
>> GOOD.
GOOD.
I THINK WE'RE GETTING REALLY
CLOSE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, MY BODY IS
ALREADY CHANGING.
THIS COULD BE IN MY HEAD, BUT I
JUST NEED CERTAIN FOODS.
WHEN YOU WERE PREGNANT, WERE YOU
RANDOMLY CRAVING HAM AND
COCAINE?
>> NO.
BUT THAT DOES BRING UP MORE
QUESTIONS FOR ME.
>> OKAY.
FINE.
LADY, WE KNOW.
THE ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM.
>> WHOO, OKAY.
WE THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T GOING TO
MENTION IT.
>> DANIEL IS 34, SO THE
PREGNANCY WOULD TECHNICALLY BE A
GERIATRIC.
>> I GUESS THE PREGNANCY PART IS
WHAT'S CONFUSING.
>> LET ME EXPLAIN.
FOR NOW, FOR US, IT'S ABOUT WHAT
FEELS GOOD FOR US.
AND FOR NOW, FOR US, WHAT FEELS
GOOD FOR US IS FOR US TO TRY.
>> BECAUSE FOR US, FOR NOW, WHAT
FEELS GOOD FOR NOW IS TRYING,
FOR US.
>> FOR NOW.
>> GOT IT.
SO WHY DID YOU GUYS DECIDE TO
START TRYING NOW?
>> WELL, FUNNY ENOUGH I HAD A
DREAM WHERE MY SON CAME OUT OF
MY ASS, WHICH DIDN'T MAKE ANY
SENSE.
>> NO.
NO.
>> NO, IT DOESN'T.
>> RIGHT.
BECAUSE THE BABY IS OBVIOUSLY
GOING TO COME OUT OF MY ASS.
>> NO.
THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
>> CAN YOU JUST EXPLAIN EXACTLY
HOW YOU THINK YOU'RE TRYING FOR
A BABY?
>> OKAY.
GOD GOD, THIS IS SO INVASIVE.
PEOPLE THINK THEY CAN JUST ASK
GAY PEOPLE ANYTHING.
IT'S CRAZY.
>> LOOK, ALL WE FEEL COMFORTABLE
SHARING IS WE'VE TRIED THREE OUT
OF SEVEN HOLES.
>> SEVEN HOLES?
>> WE ARE NOT GOING TO HOLD YOUR
HAND THROUGH THAT.
>> EARS, EYES, PITS, CRACK --
>> BABY, DON'T.
THEY CAN GOOGLE.
>> GUYS, WE LOVE YOU, BUT YOU
TWO CAN'T HAVE A BABY.
YOU BIOLOGICALLY CANNOT.
>> OH, REALLY?
WELL, YEARS BEFORE THERE WERE
PHONES, I'M SURE SOMEONE SAID WE
CAN'T HAVE PHONES, WE'LL NEVER
HAVE PHONES, AND NOW WE HAVE
PHONES.
GIRL.
>> THINGS IN THE SCIENCE
COMMUNITY CHANGE SO FAST.
YEARS FROM NOW, YOU'RE GOING TO
FEEL SO SMALL-MINDED.
IMAGINE GOING BACK TO THE
PILGRIMS AND TRYING TO EXPLAIN
ANDY MILLINACAS.
BY THE WAY, MY BIRTHDAY IS
TOMORROW, AND NO ONE HAS
MENTIONED IT.
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
>> OKAY.
NOW I'M EMBARRASSED
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
>> SO EMBARRASSED.
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEAR DANIEL ♪
>> THIS REALLY SUCKS.
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
>> HONEY, BLOW YOUR CANDLES OUT.
WHAT DID YOU WISH FOR BABY?
>> I WISHED THAT WE GET PREGNANT
AND THEY NEVER DO.
>> HEY!
THAT'S NOT NICE.
>> YOU ALREADY HAVE ONE AND HE'S
AWFUL.
>> SHE'S A GIRL.
>> WELL, THEN SHE LOOKS GAY.
EWW.
>> EVERYONE, I ACTUALLY HAVE
ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE.
>> OH, WHAT IS IT, SWEETIE?
>> I'M EXPECTING.
>> YOU'RE PREGNANT?
>> NO.
I'M JUST EXPECTING TO HAVE A
BABY SOME DAY.
>> SEE, NOW THAT'S CONFUSING.
>> GIRL.
>> HE JUST FELL ASLEEP.
OLD
>> OH, MY GOD.
MY MOM HAS NOT CHANGED THIS ROOM
SINCE I LEFT FOR COLLEGE.
>> OH, LOOK AT YOU.
WHO'S THIS?
>> OH, THAT'S KEITH.
HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND GROWING
UP.
HE LIVED A FEW DOORS DOWN.
MAN, I HAVEN'T SEEN KEITH IN
LIKE 15 YEARS.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD REACH OUT.
IT'S ALWAYS NICE TO HEAR FROM AN
OLD FRIEND AT CHRISTMAS.
>> HEY, KEITH, IT'S JAKE.
IT'S BEEN FOREVER, MAN.
WANNA GRAB A BEER TONIGHT?
>> JAKE MITCHELL?
WOW.
I WOULD LOVE THAT.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
>> FENNIGAN'S?
>> SEE.
IT ALWAYS PAYS TO REACH OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT A GAY BAR, RIGHT?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
IT'S JUST A BAR.
>> IS IT MORE THAN A THOUSAND
FEET FROM A SCHOOL?
>> KEITH.
LOL.
>> SILLY FACE EMOJI.
>> OKAY.
>> FOR REAL, THOUGH, IS IT MORE
THAN 1,000 FEET FROM A SCHOOL?
>> PROBABLY.
>> I'M IN.
HEY, IT MEANS A LOT THAT YOU
REACHED OUT, MAN, FOR REAL.
>> OF COURSE.
>> MOST OF MY FRIENDS CUT TIES
AFTER ALL THAT STUFF WENT DOWN
LAST YEAR.
>> WHAT STUFF?
>> BUNCH OF BS.
A NETFLIX DOC MADE IT SEEM WORSE
THAN IT WAS.
>> BABE, GO ON NETFLIX AND
SEARCH KEITH LONDALE.
THE MAN WITH 600 KIDS.
HOW A SPERM BANK JANITOR
SECRETLY SWITCHED HUNDREDS OF
DONOR SAMPLES WITH HIS OWN
AND
GOT AWAY WITH IT.
GOD
>> ANYWAY, I'VE BEEN PRETTY
LONELY.
I LOST THE LOVE OF MY LIFE LAST
YEAR.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> HERE'S MY FAVE PIC OF US.
IT'S CRAZY THEY CAN JUST TAKE A
GUN AWAY FROM YOU BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU SAY ONLINE.
>> YOU SENT A THUMBS UP TO THAT?
>> WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
>> ANYWAY, CAN'T WAIT TO HANG.
I HAVE SO MUCH TO TELL YOU
ABOUT.
PICK YOU UP IN A FEW.
HAVE TO UBER, THOUGH.
NO LICENSE.
>> OH, DUI?
>> NAH, CAN'T RENEW IT.
DMV IS WITHIN 1,000 FEET OF A
SCHOOL.
>> DUDE.
>> OKAY.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
>> WE?
>> ME AND BIG FILTHY.
>> WHO IS BIG FILTHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HIS FRIEND, I GUESS?
>> CALL ME.
I HAVE A WAY WE CAN MAKE 30 K
TONIGHT.
YOU ALLERGIC TO LATEX?
>> WHO IS BIG FILTHY?
>> NOT TO BE CORNY, BUT SOME OF
MY BEST MEMORIES
ARE HANGING OUT
WITH YOU AT YOUR MOM'S.
BY THE WAY, DOES SHE STILL HAVE
BIG ONES?
OH, MY GOD.
SORRY.
TYPO.
BIG TITTIES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
HOW DID I NOT KNOW KEITH'S A
FULL PSYCHO NOW.
>> BECAUSE YOU NEVER GO ON --
>> FACEBOOK.
STILL THE BEST WAY TO SEE
WHICH
OLD FRIENDS ARE CRAZY NOW.
JACKSON
>> OH, THEY'RE FINE.
>> HEY, GENIE, NOT TO BE A PIG,
BUT YOU GOT AN ETA ON DINNER
TIME?
>> EVERYTHING LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> WHEN CAN WE EAT?
>> DON'T ASK ME.
THAT'S MARK'S DEPARTMENT.
>> OH, BEEP BEEP.
LET ME GO RIGHT PAST YOU.
>> SORRY, MARK.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
ALL GOOD.
>> HOW MUCH LONGER DO YOU THINK
UNTIL WE EAT?
>> ALL THE FOOD IS HERE, SO AS
SOON AS BETTY AND CARL GET HERE,
WE CAN GET STARTED.
OKAY?
>> WELL, IF THAT HAM GOES
MISSING, GREGG DID IT.
>> HO, HO, HO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO ALL.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
>> OH, DON'T BE.
YOU DIDN'T MISS NOTHING.
WE WERE JUST ABOUT TO START.
>> OH, BEEP BEEP.
LET ME GET RIGHT BY.
>> SORRY, CARL.
>> IT'S OKAY.
JUST GOING TO GRAB ONE MORE OUT
THE CAR.
>> OKAY.
GOOD.
WELL, LET ME GET YOU A DRINK,
BETTY.
OVER HERE.
>> OH, BEEP BEEP.
BEEP BEEP, LET ME JUST SCOOT
RIGHT PAST YA.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M IN TRAFFIC.
HEY, BETTY, GIRL, LET ME TELL
YA, BEST PART OF THE HOLIDAYS IS
DRINKING DURING THE DAY.
>> HONEY, WHY WAIT UNTIL THE
HOLIDAYS?
>> CHEERS TO THAT.
>> AND -- OH.
BEEP BEEP.
>> OH, BEEP BEEP.
>> BEEP BEEP.
JUST GOING TO GO RIGHT IN THERE.
LET ME JUST SCOOT RIGHT PAST YA
REAL QUICK.
>> UM, I'M SORRY, BOYS.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> EVERYTHING'S FINE, SWEETIE.
I SAID, BEEP BEEP.
>> NAH, NO, NO, NO.
I SAID BEEP BEEP.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND.
SEE, I'M A LITTLE CAR RIGHT NOW,
AND I'M HONKING AT YOU WITH MY
LITTLE HORN.
BEEP BEEP.
>> WELL, THAT'S INTERESTING
BECAUSE I'M IN A LITTLE CAR TOO.
A CARRAWAY LITTLER THAN YOURS.
I'M SO LITTLE, I GOT MY KNEES UP
TO MY CHEST, LITTLE TIRES THE
SIZE OF BUTTONS.
>> NO, STOP.
>> BOUGHT IT USED TOO FROM
STEWART LITTLE.
>> OH, I SEE.
SO YOU WANNA DIE TONIGHT?
>> BOYS, PLEASE, THIS IS INSANE!
>> OTHER MEN IN THE ROOM, PLEASE
DO SOMETHING!
THEY'LL KILL EACH OTHER!
>> WE CANNOT GET INVOLVED.
>> WHEN TWO GUYS WHO GO BEEP
BEEP GET IN EACH OTHER'S WAY,
GETTING IN BETWEEN THEM IS A
SURE FIRE WAY TO LOSE A HAND.
IT'S LIKE GETTING BETWEEN TWO
FALCONS, TWO WOLVES, TWO
CONDORS, THEY'LL BITE YOUR HEAD
CLEAN OFF.
>> ONE OF THEM MUST YIELD TO THE
OTHER'S BEEP BEEP OR --
>> OR WHAT?
>> FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
>> OH!
>> YOU SEE, THIS IS MY HOUSE,
SON, AND IN MY HOUSE, WHEN I SAY
BEEP BEEP, EXCUSE ME, COMING
THROUGH, LET ME JUST SCOOT RIGHT
PAST YA, YOU BETTER MOVE.
>> WELL, MY DADDY DIDN'T RAISE
NO MOVER.
HE RAISED A BEEP BEEP WATCH OUT
COMING UP BEHIND YOU LET ME JUST
SQUEEZE RIGHT BY YA REAL QUICK.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I WANT YOU TO
SAY BEEP BEEP.
I WANT YOU TO SAY IT ONE MORE
TIME SEE IF I DON'T DRIVE MY CAR
RIGHT UP YOUR ASS LIKE
MS. FRIZZLE.
>> SHOOT.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
I INVITED THE NEIGHBORS.
>> HEY, FOLKS.
I BROUGHT SOME YAMS.
>> HIS YAMS ARE AMAZING.
>> BEEP BEEP, LET ME JUST
SCOOT --
>> WHOA.
>> HEY.
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
>> WHERE YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
>> I SAID BEEP BEEP.
BECAUSE FIRST I SAY BEEP BEEP,
BUT I COULD GO BANG BANG.
WE COOL?
>> YEAH, WE COOL.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
BEEP BEEP.
SEASONS GREETINGS, HOME
SHOPPERS.
>> HEY, Y'ALL.
>> RHETT AND LINDY LIVE HERE.
MISTING TOE CHECK.
THERE ISN'T ANY.
>> HE WISHES.
>> I'M SILLY TODAY.
IT'S 5:00, AND THAT MEANS IT'S
TIME FOR SOME HOLIDAY SQUEAL
DEALS.
>> AHH!
>> OH, DALE, WHAT IS THAT SOUND
EFFECT?
>> WE ASKED FOR SOMETHING LIGHT
AND FESTIVE, ODELL.
>> THAT'S HORRIBLE, ODELL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WELL, WE GOT FA LA LA LA LOTS OF
HOLIDAY ITEMS FOR Y'ALL TODAY.
>> LATER ON, THE CRAFTY
CHRISTIAN HIMSELF, TIM TUCKER
NEEBS SELLING HIS PATRIOTIC
NATIVITY SET.
>> WOW.
THAT IS GORGEOUS.
>> LOTS OF PATRIOTIC COLORS AND
BABY JESUS IS SWADDLED
TASTEFULLY IN THE AMERICAN FLAG.
>> OH, THAT'S CLEVER.
>> THAT SENDS A SWEET MESSAGE.
>> YES, IT DOES.
NOW SPEAKING OF SWEET, OUR FIRST
SELLER TODAY IS THE OWNER OF
DELANEY CHOCOLATES, MR. DEAN
DELANEY.
>> THIS HERE IS A REAL LIVE
CHOCOLATEER, FOLKS.
>> I'M OFTEN CALLED THE WILLY
WONKA OF CENTRAL INDIANA.
>> WOW.
I NEVER LIKED THAT WILLY WONKA
MOVIE.
WHAT YOU SELLING TODAY, DEAN?
>> IT'S A DELANEY'S CHOCOLATE
HOLIDAY FAVORITE, OUR DELUXE
CHOCOLATE SANTA.
>> THAT'S ALL CHOCOLATE?
NO.
>> I'M A CHOCOHOLIC, AND MY
MOUTH IS WATERING RIGHT NOW.
>> THIS LOVELY GUY IS JUST
25.99.
>> NO, THAT'S IT?
>> YEP.
PHONE LINES ARE ALREADY GOING
OFF.
YOU'RE A HIT, DEAN.
YOU'RE ON SHOP TV.
>> MY NEPHEW WOULD LOVE THAT.
WHAT KIND OF CHOCOLATE IS THAT?
>> IT'S FLAVORED MILK CHOCOLATE
MADE WITH 100% COCOA BUTTER, AND
YOU CAN JUST LOOK HOW SHINY AND
BEAUTIFUL THIS CHOCOLATE IS.
>> NEAT.
WOW.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHOA!
WHY DOES IT LOOK LIKE THAT?
>> WHY DOES IT LOOK LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE A BIG PEE --
>> HANG UP, ODELL.
>> IS HE OKAY?
HE SOUNDED A LITTLE RATTLED?
>> I JUST THINK THIS RIDGE
AROUND THE TOP MAKES IT LOOK A
LITTLE ICKY.
>> YOU NEED THE RIDGE.
THE RIDGE GIVES DIMENSION TO
SANTA'S HAT WHEN IT'S IN THE
FOIL.
THAT'S JUST CHOCOLATEERING 101.
>> I'M SURE IT IS.
YOU SAID IT'S FLAVORED MILK
CHOCOLATE?
>> YES, IT IS.
HAZELNUT.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GIVE IT A
SNIFF?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> GIVE IT A SNIFF.
>> I SNIFFED IT.
I SMELLED IT.
YUM.
>> DEAN, IT CERTAINLY LOOKS
DELICIOUS.
>> WELL, YEP.
AND WE HAND TEMPER OUR CHOCOLATE
WHICH GIVES IT THIS SMOOTH SHINE
HERE.
>> OH.
>> DON'T -- I DON'T LOVE THAT
CLOSEUP, ODELL.
>> MAYBE WIDEN OUT, ODELL.
>> LET'S MAYBE -- DON'T HAVE TO
STROKE IT SO MUCH.
LET'S TAKE A CALLER.
HI THERE, YOU'RE ON SHOP TV.
>> HI.
THAT THING VIBRATE?
>> HANG UP, ODELL.
HANG UP.
>> SHAME ON YOU.
>> WELL, NO, IT DEFINITELY
DOESN'T VIBRATE.
SANTA HERE IS SOLID CHOCOLATE,
AND IT'S AS SOLID AS A ROCK.
BUT IT TASTES A WHOLE LOT BETTER
THAN ONE.
SOMETIMES I JUST WANT TO GOBBLE
IT DOWN.
>> OH.
>> DEAN!
>> LET'S NOT DO THAT.
>> ODELL, ODELL, ODELL, I'M
WONDERING DO WE HAVE ANOTHER ONE
OF THOSE SANTAS AROUND THAT'S IN
THE FOIL?
WE DON'T?
OKAY.
>> 25.99, AND IF YOU ORDER IN
THE NEXT HOUR, DEAN'S GOING TO
THROW IN A COUPLE OF BONUS
GOODIES FOR FREE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S A VERY SWEET DEAL.
>> OH, THAT A LITTLE JOKE THERE,
DEAN?
>> OH, A GOT A CHOCO-LOT OF
THEM.
>> HE DID IT AGAIN.
TELL FOLKS ABOUT THESE BONUS
GOODIES.
>> I'M THROWING IN TWO OF OUR
FAMOUS DELANEY CHOCOLATES CRISPY
CLUSTERS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OH, NO.
I'M JUST GONNA -- OOPS!
SORRY, DEAN.
JUST WANT TO GET THOSE OUT OF
THERE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT, DEAN.
>> WHAT A DEAL THAT WE GOT HERE.
CALLER, DO YOU AGREE?
>> MOST DEFINITELY.
I'M DYING TO KNOW HOW THEY
TASTE.
>> OH, WELL, DELISH, BUT I AM
BIASED.
I'LL ASK OUR CHOCOHOLIC HERE.
HERE YOU GO.
>> AGAIN, BETTER NOT.
I'M STUFFED FROM LUNCH, AND I'M
A MOTHER, SO.
>> OWEKY DOEKY, ALL YOURS THEN,
RHETT.
>> OKAY, FUN.
JUST TRYING TO WORK OUT HOW TO
COME AT THIS WITHOUT BECOMING A
MEME.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST TAKE A LITTLE BITE
HERE.
DON'T BLUR IT, ODELL!
MAKES IT LOOK LIKE I'M DOING
SOMETHING NAUGHTY.
COME ON NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
>> COME ON.
DON'T FEEL GUILTY.
IT'S THE HOLIDAYS.
>> YEAH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EAT THE WHOLE
THING.
JUST THE TIP.
>> OKAY, DEAN.
OKAY.
LITTLE NIBBLE HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S IT.
>> NO!
>> YUCK!
YUCK!
>> SHAME ON YOU!
>> YUCKY!
>> SHAME.
>> EWW.
NOW DEAN'S OFFERING FREE
SHIPPING.
HOW SOON CAN FOLKS GET THEIR
HANDS ON ONE OF THESE YUMMY
SANTAS?
>> I HANDLE ALL THE PACKAGES
MYSELF, SO IT SHOULD COME PRETTY
QUICK.
>> OKAY.
>> NO, NO, NO.
STICK AROUND BECAUSE AFTER THE
BREAK, WE GOT MORE HOLIDAY
SQUEAL DEALS.
>> AHH!
>> ODELL!
>> FIX THE DAMN SOUND EFFECT,
ODELL.
CHANGE THAT!
♪
♪ HATE TO GIVE THE
SATISFACTION, ASKING
HOW YOU'RE DOING NOW
HOW'S THE CASTLE BUILT ♪
♪ OFF PEOPLE YOU PRETEND
TO CARE ABOUT
JUST WHAT YOU WANTED
LOOK AT YOU, COOL GUY ♪
♪ YOU GOT IT
I SEE THE PARTIES AND THE
DIAMONDS SOMETIMES
WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ SIX MONTHS OF TORTURE
YOU SOLD AS SOME
FORBIDDEN PARADISE
I LOVED YOU TRULY ♪
♪ YOU GOTTA LAUGH AT
THE STUPIDITY
'CAUSE I'VE MADE SOME
REAL BIG MISTAKES ♪
♪ YOU MAKE THE WORST
ONE LOOK FINE
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN
IT WAS STRANGE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT
I USED TO THINK
I WAS SMART
YOU MADE ME ♪
♪ LOOK SO NAIVE
THE WAY YOU SOLD
ME FOR PARTS
AS YOU SUNK YOUR TEETH ♪
♪ INTO ME, OH
BLOODSUCKER, DREAM CRUSHER
BLEEDIN' ME DRY
LIKE A DAMN VAMPIRE ♪
♪ AND EVERY GIRL I EVER
TALKED TO TOLD ME
YOU WERE BAD, BAD NEWS
YOU CALLED THEM CRAZY ♪
♪ GOD I HATE THE WAY I
CALLED THEM CRAZY TOO
YOU'RE SO CONVINCING
HOW DO YOU LIE ♪
♪ WITHOUT FLINCHING
OOH, WHAT A MESMERIZING
PARALYZING
TRAGIC LITTLE THRILL ♪
♪ CAN'T FIGURE OUT
JUST HOW YOU DO IT
AND GOD KNOWS I NEVER WILL
WENT FOR ME, AND NOT HER ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GIRLS YOUR
AGE KNOW BETTER
I'VE MADE SOME
REAL BIG MISTAKES ♪
♪ YOU MAKE THE WORST
ONE LOOK FINE
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN
IT WAS STRANGE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT
I USED TO THINK
I WAS SMART
YOU'VE MADE ME ♪
♪ LOOK SO NAIVE
THE WAY YOU SOLD
ME FOR PARTS
AND YOU SUNK YOUR ♪
♪ TEETH INTO ME, OH
BLOODSUCKER, DREAM CRUSHER
BLEEDIN' ME DRYE
LIKE A DAMN VAMPIRE ♪
♪
♪ YOU SAID IT WAS TRUE LOVE
BUT WOULDN'T THAT BE HARD
YOU CAN'T LOVE ANYONE
'CAUSE THAT WOULD MEAN ♪
♪ YOU HAD A HEART
I TRIED YOU HELP YOU OUT
NOW I KNOW THAT I CAN'T
'CAUSE HOW YOU THINK'S ♪
♪ THE KIND OF THING
I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND
OH
I'VE MADE SOME ♪
♪ REAL BIG MISTAKES
YOU MAKE THE WORST
ONE LOOK FINE
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN ♪
♪ IT WAS STRANGE
YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT
I USED TO THINK
I WAS SMART ♪
♪ YOU MADE ME
LOOK SO NAIVE
THE WAY YOU SOLD
ME FOR PARTS ♪
♪ AND YOU SUNK YOUR
TEETH INTO ME, OH
BLOODSUCKER, DREAM CRUSHER
BLEEDIN' ME DRY ♪
♪ LIKE A DAMN VAMPIRE ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
A FEDERAL INDICTMENT ISSUED THIS
WEEK AGAINST HUNTER BIDE AN LEDGES
THAT HE EVADED PAYING
OVER $1 MILLION OF TAXES BETWEEN
2016 AND 2020,
AND THEY'RE ONLY
CATCHING HIM NOW?
MAN, THIS IS SUPER EMBARRASSING
FOR WHOEVER WAS PRESIDENT FROM
2016 TO 2020.
THE INDICTMENT CLAIMS THAT
INSTEAD OF PAYING TAXES,
HE
SPENT HIS MONEY ON DRUGS AND
ESCORTS.
HONESTLY, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE SURPRISING IF HE REMEMBERS
TO DO HIS TAXES DURING THAT
TIME.
NO ONE FINISHES DOING COCAINE
WITH A HOOKER
AND IS LIKE, CAN I
GET A RECEIPT?
>> SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
IF CONVICTED, HE COULD BE
SENTENCED TO UP TO 17 YEARS IN PRISON,
WHICH WOULD BE THE FIRST
TIME ANY BIDEN HAS SUCCESSFULLY
COMPLETED A SENTENCE.
HOUSE SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON SAID
THAT HE IS BLURRING THE FACES ON
THE FOOTAGE OF JANUARY 6th RIOTERS
SO THAT NONE OF THEM
WOULD BE CHARGED WITH A CRIME.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'LL NEVER KNOW
WHO THEY ARE.
>> THAT'S PHOTO SHOPPED.
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNIVERSITY
OF PENNSYLVANIA HAS RESIGNED
AFTER APPEARING TO DODGE
QUESTIONS ABOUT GENOCIDE
DURING
A CONGRESSIONAL HEARING ON
CAMPUS ANTI-SEMITISM.
SHE WILL BE REPLACED BY
LITERALLY ANYONE
WHO KNOWS YOU
SAY GENOCIDE IS BAD.
THE WHOLE CRAZY PART IS THAT THE
WHOLE POINT DURING HER SPEECH
WAS THAT FREE SPEECH ON CAMPUS
SHOULD NEVER BE PUNISHED, AND
SHE WAS IMMEDIATELY PUNISHED FOR
HER SPEECH.
VICTOR MANUAL ROCCA HAS BEEN
CHARGED WITH SPYING FOR CUBA
SINCE 1981, AND THAT'S WHY CUBA
IS THE UNSTOPPABLE SUPERPOWER
THEY ARE TODAY.
>> A NEW POLL FINDS THAT NEW
YORK MAYOR ERIC ADAMS' APPROVAL
RATING IS JUST 28%.
NOW, THAT SOUNDS LOW.
INDEPENDENT PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE ROBERT F. KENNEDY
ADMITTED HE FLEW TWO TIMES TO
JEFFREY EPSTEIN'S ON HIS PRIVATE
JET, BUT ON TO MAKE SURE NONE OF
THEM WERE VACCINATED.
>> MITCH McCONNELL, SEEN HERE
BRINGING PEANUTS INTO A
PRESCHOOL CAFETERIA, SAID HE
WILL TELL REPUBLICAN SENATORS TO
VOTE AGAINST ADDITIONAL AID FOR
UKRAINE UNTIL THERE ARE MEDIATE
CHANGES TO THE BORDER.
BUT THE WAY IT CAME OUT WERE
BRAINS.
ON HIS WEBSITE, TRUTH SOCIAL
DOT -- I'M GOING TO GUESS
SCAM -- DONALD TRUMP DENIED
REPORTS HE WAS SO DEPRESSED
AFTER THE 2020 ELECTION THAT HE
STOPPED EATING SAYING, QUOTE, IT
WAS NOT THAT I WAS NOT EATING.
IT WAS THAT I WAS EATING TOO
MUCH.
WOW, GOOD SAVE.
THAT'S LIKE WHEN A RUMOR WENT
AROUND MIDDLE SCHOOL THAT I PAID
MY PANTS AND I WAS LIKE JOKE'S
ON YOU BECAUSE I ACTUALLY POOPED
THEM.
>> THE DODGERS HAVE SIGNED
SHOHEI OHTANI TO A TEN-YEAR
CONTRACT WORTH $700 MILLION,
WHICH IS ALMOST AS MUCH AS HIS
SISTER ON ONLYFANS, SHOW FEET
OHTANI.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS A REAL SMART
JOKE MP McDONALD'S HAS ANNOUNCED
A NEW SPINOFF RESTAURANT CALLED
COSMCS.
THE MASCOT IS -- OH, NO, COSBY
McDONALD?
>> ACCORDING TO A NEW STUDY, THE
RATE OF DEPRESSION AMONG MEN IN
AMERICA IS AT AN ALL-TIME HIGH.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR VERY OWN
MARCELLO HERNANDEZ.
>> COLIN, GREAT TO SEE YOU.
YOU LOOKING GOOD, COLIN.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S ALWAYS GREAT TO SEE YOU.
WHY DO YOU THINK MEN ARE
DEPRESSED?
>> COLIN, TO UNDERSTAND WHY MEN
ARE DEPRESSED, WE HAVE TO FIRST
TALK ABOUT WOMEN, AND I
UNDERSTAND WOMEN.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU WANT TO
START WITH THAT, BUT --
>> NO, COLIN.
I GREW UP WITH ONLY WOMEN IN MY
HOUSE.
IT WAS ME, MY MOM, AND MY
SISTER.
IN HIGH SCHOOL, MY MOM'S BEST
FRIEND AND HER DAUGHTER MOVED
IN, SO IT WAS JUST ME AND FOUR
WOMEN.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS TO YOU,
COLIN, WHEN IT'S JUST YOU AND
FOUR WOMEN, YOU HAVE NO
CHOICE --
>> BUT TO BECOME THE MAN OF THE
HOUSE?
>> WRONG.
TO BECOME A WOMAN.
I WAS A WOMAN FOR MANY YEARS,
COLIN.
A PROUD LATINA WOMAN.
I WAS LIVING A DOUBLE LIFE.
AT SCHOOL, I WAS CAPTAIN OF THE
SOCCER TEAM YELLING YOU BETTER
PLAY DEFENSE TODAY.
AND AT HOME, MY MOM WOULD BE
LIKE, HOW DO I LOOK.
AND I WOULD BE LIKE, YOU LOOK
AMAZING MOMMY.
GO INTO YOUR ROOM AND WALK OUT
AGAIN.
I WANT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THE WHITE HOUSE?
IS MY MOM GOING TO MEET THE
PRESIDENT?
>> AND HOW DOES THIS RELATE TO
MEN BEING DEPRESSED?
>> BECAUSE, WOMEN SUPPORT EACH
OTHER.
MEN DON'T SUPPORT EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE DEPRESSED.
A GIRL CAN TELL HER FRIEND
ANYTHING, AND SHE'LL SUPPORT IT
NO MATTER WHAT.
SHE'LL BE LIKE, I'M DATING THIS
GUY, AND HE ROBS BANKS.
AND THEN HER FRIEND WILL BE
LIKE, AT LEAST HE HAS A PASSION.
>> AND YOU DON'T THINK THAT MEN
ARE AS SUPPORTIVE?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T GO TO THE
BARBERSHOP ANYMORE, COLIN.
IT'S A NEGATIVE ENERGY IN THERE.
NO ONE IS HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
EVERY TIME I GO, THE GUY'S LIKE,
LOOK WHO IT IS.
WE ALREADY TOLD YOU, BUDDY, WE
CAN'T MAKE YOU TALLER.
THAT'S WHY A LITTLE PRINCE LIKE
ME GOES TO THE SALON, COLIN.
I GET TO THE SALON, COLIN, AND
THE LADY IS LIKE, WHERE HAVE YOU
BEEN?
AND I'M LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
I MISSED YOU.
>> OKAY.
THE SALON DO BE SOUNDING KIND OF
FIRE.
>> IT DO, IT DO, COLIN, IT DO!
I'M JUST TRYING TO SAY THAT
WOMEN HAVE SUPPORT, OKAY.
WHEN A WOMAN GOES THROUGH A
BREAKUP, ALL HER FRIENDS SHOW
UP.
WHEN A GUY GOES THROUGH A
BREAKUP, HIS BOYS JUST ACT LIKE
HIS FLIGHT GOT DELAYED.
YOU'LL BE LIKE, YO, I WAS IN
LOVE WITH HER MAN, AND OUT OF
NOWHERE, SHE LEFT ME.
AND MY BEST FRIEND WILL BE LIKE,
DAMN.
THAT SUCKS, BRO.
JUST GO TO CHILI'S AND WAIT FOR
THE NEXT ONE, MY BOY.
>> AND YOU WOULD SAY THIS IS THE
REASON MEN ARE THE MOST
DEPRESSED THEY'VE EVER BEEN IN
HISTORY?
>> YES.
AND ALSO A VARIETY OF OTHER
DIFFERENT ISSUES, BUT THEY'RE
NOT AS FUNNY, AND I DON'T HAVE
STANDUP ON THAT.
>> MARCELLO HERNANDEZ, EVERYONE.
>> ISN'T HE GLOWING?
>> SYLVESTER STALLONE TRAVELED
TO PHILADELPHIA TO CELEBRATE THE
CITY'S FIRST EVER ROCKY DAY.
ALTHOUGH, I WOULD SAY THAT IF
YOU LIVE IN PHILADELPHIA, EVERY
DAY IS A PRETTY ROCKY DAY.
>> ALASKA AIRLINES HAS ANNOUNCED
PLANS TO BUY HAWAIIAN AIRLINES
FOR NEARLY $2 BILLION.
ALASKA AND HAWAIIAN COMBINED
WILL BE CALLED TECHNICALLY
AMERICAN AIRLINES.
>> IT WAS REPORTED THE INMATE
WHO ATTACKED DEREK CHAUVIN, THE
POLICE OFFICER WHO KILLED GEORGE
FLOYD STABS CHAUVIN 22 TIMES,
BUT CHAUVIN STILL WOULDN'T STOP
CHOKING HIM.
ALL RIGHT.
NICK CANNON REVEALED THAT HE
SPENDS UP TO $200,000 EVERY YEAR
TAKING ALL 12 OF HIS CHILDREN TO
DISNEYLAND.
THAT'S HOW BAD CONDOMS FEEL.
>> SOME GOOGLE USERS ARE UPSET
AFTER THE COMPANY'S AI SOFTWARE
MISTAKINGLY LABELED INNOCENT
PICTURES OF THEIR CHILDREN AS
CHILD PORN.
THIS IS COMPLETELY UNACCEPTABLE,
SAID PEOPLE WHO WERE LOOKING FOR
REAL CHILD PORN.
A WOMAN IN OHIO CONVICTED OF
THROWING A BURRITO BOWL AT A
CHIPOTLE WORKER HAS BEEN
SENTENCED TO SPEND TWO MONTHS
WORKING IN FAST FOOD
RESTAURANTS.
FAST FOOD, WHERE YOUR JOB IS
OTHER PEOPLE'S JAIL.
>> A SIF-DESCRIBED ANTI-WOKE
BEER COMPANY HAS CREATED A
CALENDAR WHICH FEATURES, QUOTE,
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL CONSERVATIVE
WOMEN IN AMERICA, WHICH IS JUST
A POLITE WAY OF SAYING FLAT
ASSES.
ALL RIGHT.
>> BUFFALO BILLS COACH SEAN
McDERMOTT APOLOGIZED AFTER
GIVING A SPEECH TO HIS PLAYERS
WHERE HE USED 9/11 TERRORISTS AS
A GOOD EXAMPLE OF TEAMWORK,
WHICH IS KIND OF A FULL CIRCLE
MOMENT BECAUSE WHEN OSAMA BIN
LADEN WAS GIVING THE TERRORISTS
A PEP TALK, HE TOLD THEM NOT TO
BE LIKE THE BILLS.
>> A GYM TEACHER IN FLORIDA WAS
ARRESTED AFTER HE THREW A
BASKETBALL AT A SIXTH GRADER AND
THEN ELBOWED HIM IN THE MOUTH
KNOCKING OUT HIS FRONT TOOTH.
THE TEACHER WAS FORCED TO RESIGN
AND RETURN TO THE GOLDEN STATE
WARRIORS.
>> WELL, GUYS, THE HOLIDAYS ARE
COMING UP.
HERE WITH SOME INTIMATE GIFT
IDEAS FOR THAT SPECIAL SOMEONE
IS OUR VERY OWN CHLOE FINEMAN.
>> HI, COLIN.
HI, MICHAEL.
>> HI, CHLOE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN FRONT OF
THE DESK?
>> WELL, I ONLY HAVE ONE SEXY
GIFT IDEA, AND I KIND OF HAVE TO
DEMONSTRATE IT.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I'M CURIOUS.
>> THE SEXIEST GIFT YOU CAN GIVE
YOUR PARTNER IS TRYING SOMETHING
NEW IN THE BEDROOM.
>> WHAT ARE YOU ABOUT TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I'M GETTING MY POPCORN OUT
FOR THIS ONE.
>> THE PERFECT HOLIDAY GIFT THIS
YEAR IS THE DANCE THAT JULIA
STYLES DOES AT THE END OF THE
2001 MOVIE "SAVE THE LAST
DANCE."
>> CHLOE, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
>> HIT IT!
♪
TO GIVE YOUR PARTNER?
>> DON'T YOU.
>> I MEAN, NOT REALLY.
>> IT'S WORKING FOR ME.
>> WHAT STYLE OF DANCE EVEN IS
THIS?
>> STREET BALLET.
>> STREET BALLET?
>> YEAH.
BASICALLY, JULIA STILES'
CHARACTER SARAH IS AN UPTIGHT
BALLERINA WHO AUDITIONS TO GET
INTO JULIARD BUT DOESN'T GET IN,
AND HER MOM ON THE SAME DAY DIES
IN A CAR CRASH.
>> OKAY.
SO WHERE DOES THE STREET ELEMENT
COME IN?
>> COLIN, COME ON.
SARAH MOVES TO THE SOUTHSIDE OF
CHICAGO AND GOES TO A MORE URBAN
HIGH SCHOOL WHERE SHE LEARNS HIP
HOP.
DUH.
>> EXACTLY.
SO SARAH COMBINES HIP HOP WITH
BALLET TO CREATE AN ENTIRELY NEW
STYLE OF DANCE LIKE THIS, HIP
HOP, HOP, HIP HOP, HOP, HOP.
>> OKAY.
AND THEN WHAT HAPPENS?
>> SHE GETS ANOTHER AUDITION,
AND HER CRUSH DEREK SKIPS A
DRIVE-BY SHOOTING TO COME
SUPPORT HER.
HE SHOWS UPHOLDING A JACKET OVER
HIS SHOULDER AND GIVES A NOD OF
APPROVAL.
>> SO DOES SHE GET INTO JULIARD?
>> YES!
>> SARAH DID GET INTO JULIARD.
>> HOW?
>> WELL, YOU DIDN'T SEE THE END
OF THE DANCE.
>> HIT IT.
♪
>> OKAY.
SO, COLIN, WHAT DID YOU THINK?
>> WELL, I CAN'T SAY THIS ON THE
RECORD YET, BUT WELCOME TO
JULIARD.
CHLOE FINEMAN AND JULIASTILES
ALTITUDE AND WILL BE TURNING OFF
THOSE SEAT BELT SIGNS.
ENJOY YOUR FLIGHT.
>> HEY, Y'ALL.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY IT'S MY
BABY'S FIRST TIME FLYING, SO I
APOLOGIZE IN ADVANCE FOR LITTLE
EDDIE HERE.
I'M FLYING WITHOUT MY HUSBAND,
SO BEAR WITH ME, PLEASE.
>> I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE.
RAISED THREE ON MY OWN.
HOW OLD IS HE?
>> I'M 11 MONTHS.
>> OH, WOW.
>> YOU MEAN 11 MONTHS AND LIKE
15,000 DAYS?
>> MY EARS FEEL STRANGE.
>> AWW.
IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
THAT'S JUST THE PRESSURE FROM
BEING UP HIGH.
>> MY EARS, THEY FEEL DIFFERENT.
I DON'T LIKE IT!
>> IT'S OKAY.
HERE.
DO YOU WANT YOUR iPAD, SWEETIE?
>> THE PEPPA PIG DEVICE?
THAT IS THE ONLY THING I WANT.
>> HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
KIDS AND THEIR iPADS, RIGHT?
>> DON'T ENGAGE.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE DOES IT.
PEPPA IS FANTASTIC.
I JUST LIKE THIS SO MUCH, I JUST
WANT TO SHAKE IT.
>> AW, YOU ARE THE SWEETEST
LITTLE BABY.
>> CAN YOU GET ANYTHING TO DRINK
FOR -- BABY MONSTER.
SORRY.
OH, MY GOD.
>> NO WORRIES.
I'LL DO THE DIET COKE, PLEASE.
>> AND FOR THE LITTLE ONE?
>> WHO IS THAT WOMAN?
SHE'S NOT MY MOTHER.
NOW I'M FEELING CONFUSED AND
UNCOMFORTABLE, AND FRANKLY I
MISS THE WOMB!
WAHH!
>> SWEETIE --
>> WAHH!
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'LL GET YOUR BABA.
HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
I FEEL MUCH BETTER.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
>> OH, ISN'T HE DARLING?
I WAS WORRIED HE WOULD COME OUT
OVERCOOKED CONSIDERING I WAS
PREGNANT WITH HIM FOR TWO FULL
YEARS, BUT HERE HE IS, A PERFECT
LITTLE ANGEL.
AND HE LOOKS JUST LIKE HIS
FATHER.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE A FATHER.
>> YOU WANT TO PLAY A GAME, BUD?
>> NOT RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO SEE IF I CAN FIT MY
WHOLE ARM IN MY MOUTH.
>> SWEETIE, NO.
SWEETIE, NO.
NO.
HEY, HOW ABOUT WE PLAY WITH YOUR
POOKIE BEAR, HUH?
>> I LOVE HIM!
>> AND WHERE DID HE GO?
>> AHH!
HE VANISHED!
NO, POOKIE!
OH, HEY, POOKIE HAS RETURNED.
I FEEL SUCH ELATION!
>> WHERE DID HE GO?
>> NO, CHRIST, HE'S GONE!
YOU KILLED HIM, YOU BITCH!
>> HERE HE IS.
>> AND ONCE MORE, HE HAS
RETURNED.
>> IT'S JUST A GAME, SWEETIE.
SORRY AGAIN, Y'ALL.
FIRST TIME FLYING.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
>> STOP LOOKING AT US.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
IS HE POOPING?
I DON'T LIKE THAT HE'S STARING
AT ME.
>> I'M DONE.
I DON'T LIKE THE WAY IT FEELS.
AHH!
>> NEXT TIME, USE BABY PLANE,
FLY YOUR BABY SEPARATELY ON BABY
PLANE.
♪
♪ I AM LIGHT AS A FEATHER
AND AS STIFF AS A BOARD
I PAY ATTENTION TO THINGS
THAT MOST PEOPLE IGNORE ♪
♪ AND I'M ALRIGHT WITH THE
MOVIES THAT MAKE JOKES
'BOUT SENSELESS CRUELTY
THAT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ AND I AM BUILT LIKE A
MOTHER AND A TOTAL MACHINE
I FEEL FOR YOUR
EVERY LITTLE ISSUE ♪
♪ I KNOW JUST WHAT YOU MEAN
AND I MAKE LIGHT
OF THE DARKNESS
I'VE GOT SUN COMING ♪
♪ OUT OF MY POCKET
BEST BELIEVE
YEAH, YOU KNOW ME, I
FORGIVE AND I FORGET ♪
♪ I KNOW MY AGE AND
I ACT LIKE IT
GOT WHAT YOU CAN'T RESIST
I'M A PERFECT ALL-AMERICAN ♪
♪ I AM LIGHT AS A FEATHER
I'M AS FRESH AS THE AIR
COCA-COLA BOTTLES THAT I
ONLY USE TO CURL MY HAIR ♪
♪ I GOT CLASS AND INTEGRITY
JUST LIKE A
DAMN KENNEDY
I SWEAR ♪
♪ WITH LOVE TO SPARE, I
FORGIVE AND I FORGET
I KNOW MY AGE AND
I ACT LIKE IT ♪
♪ GOT WHAT YOU CAN'T RESIST
I'M A PERFECT
ALL-AMERICAN BITCH
WITH PERFECT ♪
♪ ALL-AMERICAN LIPS
AND PERFECT
ALL-AMERICAN HIPS
I KNOW MY PLACE ♪
♪ I KNOW MY PLACE
AND THIS IS IT
I DON'T GET ANGRY
WHEN I'M PISSED ♪
♪ I'M THE ETERNAL OPTIMIST
I SCREAM INSIDE
TO DEAL WITH IT
LIKE, AH ♪
♪ LIKE, AH
AH-HA-HA-HA-HA
ALL THE TIME
I'M GRATEFUL ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ I'M SEXY AND I'M KIND
I'M PRETTY WHEN I CRY
OH, ALL THE TIME
I'M GRATEFUL ♪
♪ GRATEFUL ALL THE TIME
I'M SEXY AND I'M KIND
I'M PRETTY WHEN I CRY ♪
LIKE GETTING PRANKED.
>> I'M RUTH.
I'M 67.
I GET PRANKED ALL THE TIME.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> MY NAME IS WALTER.
I'M VERY PROUD TO BE A UNITED
STATES VETERAN, AND I DO NOT
ENJOY GETTING PRANKED.
>> EVERY DAY, THOUSANDS OF
SENIORS FALL VICTIM TO TIKTOK
PRANKS.
>> IT HAS TO STOP.
>> IT'S GOTTA STOP.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
>> I'M IN THE MARKET LOOKING FOR
CAT FOOD, THE DRY KIND, JUST
MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS.
NEXT THING I KNOW, SOMEBODY
THROW A DAMN BLANKET OVER MY
HEAD.
NO!
I THOUGHT I DIED.
>> MANY SENIORS ARE EVEN BEING
PRANKED IN THEIR OWN HOMES BY
THEIR OWN FAMILIES.
>> THIS LITTLE HEFFER GONNA TELL
ME, GRANDMA, SOMEBODY IN CHURCH
IS POSSESSED BY AN OWL.
SO NATURALLY, I SAID, WHO?
WHO, CHILD?
WHO?
>> I CAN'T STAND HER ASS.
>> I SERVED MY COUNTRY.
I'VE EARNED RESPECT.
I DON'T DESERVE BEING DUNKED ON
BY CHILDREN AT WALMART.
I'M TRYING TO BUY A PICTURE
FRAME FOR MY WIFE!
I HAVE 81 CONFIRMED KILLS.
>> I'VE WORKED VERY HARD TO
PREPARE A NICE PERFECT HOLIDAY
DINNER FOR MY ENTIRE FAMILY TO
ENJOY.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE GAY JUST TO
SEE MY REACTION.
I DON'T THINK I QUITE
UNDERSTAND.
>> IT'S A PRANK!
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU GAY?
I CAN'T HANDLE THAT.
>> AND DON'T TELL ME JESUS HAS
COME BACK IF YOU KNOW HE HAS
NOT.
>> TELLING YOUR GRANDMA JESUS IS
RETURNING.
>> YOU WANT TO PRANK ME, PUT
ITCHING POWDER IN MY SHORTS.
DON'T ASK ME TO JUST WATCH YOUR
KID AND JUST LEAVE.
IT'S NOT MY KID.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I CAN'T HANDLE THAT.
I'M A DECORATED VETERAN.
I BLOCKED DOORS WITH GOVERNOR
WALLACE.
>> AND FOR CHRISTMAS SAKES, I
DON'T WANT TO PLAY YOUR SURPRISE
GAME SHOW.
>> HEY.
QUICK, FOR 20 BUCKS, JUST NAME
ONE WOMAN.
>> JIMMY -- OH, NO.
>> OH!
>> OH, NO.
>> HE PEEED HIS PANTS.
>> SO THE NEXT TIME YOU THINK
ABOUT PRANKING SOMEONE OVER THE
AGE OF 60 --
>> DON'T.
>> DON'T DO IT.
>> PLEASE, DON'T DO IT.
ALL RIGHT?
HEY!
GET!
OH!
I'M GOING TO GET YOU.
GET O
AROUND A BIG BAG LOOKING LIKE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO DONATE STUFF TO
GOOD WILL?
>> DOES YOUR BIG BAG MAKE YOU
LOOK LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS COMING
HOME FROM SLEEP AWAY CAMP OR
SERVING IN THE ARMY?
>> WELL, TRY --
>> TINY ASS BAG.
>> MY ASS IS SMALL, BUT I AM
BIG.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
KISS MY REAR.
>> WE ARE ROGELIO.
>> MARIE JOSE.
>> AND KEVIN.
AND WE'RE HERE TO TELL YOU THAT
RIGHT NOW TINY IS HUGE.
>> TINY ASS BAG IS PER IF HE CAN
FOR CARRYING --
>> ONE AIR POD, AND DASSIT.
>> ONE ALTOID, AND DASSIT.
>> HALF SMOKED CIGARETTE, AND
DASSIT.
>> LOOKING FOR A DAMN DUFFEL?
GO TO WALMART, PIG.
THIS IS --
>> TINY ASS BAG.
NOW AVAILABLE IN MEDIUM.
>> IN THIS BAG, YOU CAN FIT --
>> ONE THONG, AND DASSIT.
>> THE KIDS FROM HONEY I SHRUNK
THE KIDS, AND DASSIT.
>> CLOTHES FOR A WORM, AND
DASSIT.
>> AND FOR YOU, THAT WOULD BE
LIKE IN FASHION IN NATURE, WE
PRESENT TO YOU TINY ASS HIKING
BACKPACK.
>> I WAS GONNA MAKE S'MORES, BUT
WITH THIS TINY ASS BAG, I'M
MAKING SM'LESS.
>> THAT'S AMAZING, KEVIN.
>> YES, KEVIN.
WE LOVE YOU, KEVIN.
>> YOU WANT TO LOOK FASHION
WHILE YOU GO ON A TRIP, WE
PRESENT TO YOU, TINY ASS
LUGGAGE.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO BRING
ANYTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU, A BELLBOY?
THERE WILL BE STUFF THERE.
>> TINY ASS LUGGAGE IS PERFECT
FOR CARRYING --
>> A REASONABLE AMOUNT OF
COCAINE.
AND DASSIT.
>> AND MITOCHONDRIA, AND DASSIT.
>> MY BAG IS LITTLE, AND MY ASS
IS FAT, I'M THE KING OF THE
WORLD.
>> TINY ASS BAGS HAS SOMETHING
FOR EVERYBODY.
JUST ASK OUR ASSOCIATE GEORGINA.
>> MY NAME IS GEORGINA, AND I
DON'T HAVE A LAST NAME.
IT'S GEORGINA, AND DASSIT.
WE ALSO HAVE A CARRY-ON OPTION.
THIS ONE IS SO SMALL, IT CAN
ONLY FIT YOUR SECRETS.
LIKE THIS --
>> PSPSPS -- AND DASSIT.
THE ONLY THING BETTER THAN THE
PASSION IS THE PRICES.
>> $10,000, AND DASSIT.
>> $14,099, AND DASSIT.
>> THE TINY ASS HIKING BACKPACK,
$25,650 PLUS TAX, AND DASSIT.
>> SO LEAVE YOUR HOUSE AT HOME,
AND COME ON DOWN TO --
>> TINY ASS BAG.COM THE STORE.
>> AND THAT'S ALL.
>> KEVIN!
>> I MEAN THAT'S IT!
LAUREN MICHAELS, THE CAST, THE
CREW, THE WRITERS, DONNA,
WALLEY, JERRY, AND MOST
IMPORTANTLY, SANTA!
SANTA!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD NIGHT!