MESSAGE
Well,
tomorrow is Mother's Day,
and in the SNL tradition,
we'd like to take this time
to celebrate our moms.
The women who made us, cared
for us
and bit their tongues
when we told them we wanted
to go into show business.
They've done so much for us.
So moms, this is for you.
You cut the crust.
Off my. Bread.
And tucked me into bed.
But how often have we said
we love you, mom?
I can always count on mom.
You took me to the prom.
You bought me my first bong.
Just kidding. Mommy.
Moms, you never bore us.
You were always there for us.
Now it's
time to sing the chorus.
Or not.
Hello?
It's me again.
Invading
all aspects of your life.
All right,
go on.
I got the right idea.
Just move it
along.
Bye bye, moms.
Don't worry.
Those aren't even the real moms.
Those are. actors
Can you believe that?
SNL wouldnt
spring for the flights.
What the hell am I doing here?
There's a new pope from Chicago.
Why are we doing
da pope? Right?
Like da bears, but da prayers.
You know what the
first thought.
Whatever.
Instead, you get me.
Is it that exciting?
Oh, it's so exciting.
We have an American Pope
Chicago style.
No ketchup
but we like Pope Leo.
We hope he does what we want.
That's what you want the Pope
to do what you want right now.
Otherwise, I'll have to send
J.D. back to do his thing.
Last time
J.D. met the Pope.
He's got the Midas touch.
But for bad things,
he meets the Pope dead,
goes to India War
and joins my campaign.
Trump wins.
Incredible
Bad things happen in threes.
But we like the way
they elect Mr. Pope.
We like the smoke.
It's wonderful
what they're doing with smoke
and phallic hats
and the popemobile.
We like that as well.
One of my favorite mobiles.
After Weiner and Bat.
But we love Catholic.
It's one of these stronger
Christian organizations,
along with Salvation Army.
And I want to say Chick-Fil-A.
And we love Catholic Mass.
The only thing I don't like
is that holy water.
Why does that stuff burn so bad
when it hits your skin?
What's in this?
We gotta figure that out.
We'll be looking into that.
What else was going on?
The debt is piling up,
and we've got no trade deals.
Well, you know what?
We've got one with the UK,
but they don't have anything
we want. Right.
Sir, how many Cadbury fruit
and nut bars?
Zero.
So not going to be doing trade
more.
Question.
Can a country
go out of business.
We're going to find out.
It's that news
I just appointed one of
the loudest people
I know
to be the U.S.
attorney in D.C., Jeanine Pirro.
Come on out, Jeanine.
Come on
Honor
Look at this.
This is Jeanine has brought her
files, and she's ready to work.
Oh, no.
This is too cozy for merlosy
See, she always comes prepared,
and that rhymed, I like that.
Thank you.
Sweet justice.
Oh, Jeanine will be the newest
addition to my incredible team
in my administration.
And what a team, Mr. President.
I'm so proud to be part
of this group
full of Russian assets,
booze hounds
and people famous for the little
baby animals they've killed.
Proud to you.
I personally, Big Jeanine,
to be the U.S.
attorney in Washington, D.C..
Isn't that right?
That's right. The district,
or as the locals
call it, Chocolate City.
So all you soul
sisters and brothers
put the word out on the street.
There's a bad new mama
Jamal laying down the law.
Gotten down and funky town
looking fine
and sipping wine.
Now I'm so glad we can
Talk like this again,
Mr.. President.
Oh, we love Jeanine.
She's a great legal mind,
and she has the most important quality.
I look for in a lawyer.
She's on TV.
She's on the five,
which is a show on Fox.
And I like The View. I'm a.
Here are indeed the Whoopie
You're very Whoopie, but
you're also very, very tough.
Yes, especially on immigration.
I don't have any reservations
about sending things back.
My friends know I've sent back
every salad I've ever ordered
at a restaurant.
One.
No, I've never eaten one.
Wow.
I know what
hiring people from Fox News,
they all do an incredible job.
Just look at Pete Hegseth
There's not one mistake.
Oh, I. Love Pete Hegseth.
He's my own drinking buddy.
Surprise!
What?
Here
Yes. But, you know, I asked Pete
to give us a little
rundown
on one of our F-18
fighter planes.
Oh, is it bombing the houties?
Close.
It fell off the aircraft carrier
into the ocean.
What? Again?
Hey, Pete.
You're not drinking again,
are you?
No.
Absolutely not, sir.
I promised I would never have
a bottle touch my lips,
but I do have some news to share
before I do.
Janine,
you want to take a swig of this?
Oh, yeah. Oh, there.
You know I do. Oh, yeah.
Anyway,
I accidentally added Kim Jong un
to the group chat.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. That's the.
That's the stuff,
folks.They're not the A-Team.
They're the AA-Team. Right?
Anyway, in conclusion,
happy Mother's Day.
AND LIVE
FROM NEW YORK, IT'S SATURDAY
NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- WALTON
GOGGINS!
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very, very, very much.
I am so excited to be here.
Now, most of you
probably know me from the show
White Lotus.
No spoilers, but I die
my character in White Lotus
is pretty brooding,
which the internet
seemed to find attractive.
Some of my friends
have even asked me
What's it like
to become a sex symbol?
At 53 years old?
And you know what?
If I'm being honest,
it feels fantastic.
At least it did
until I googled myself
and read some of the headlines.
Take a look.
Are we all horny?
Are we all horny
for Walton
Goggins receding hairline?
I've had the same hairline
since I was seven.
It's not receding.
It's holding its ground.
How about this one?
His hair is greasy,
his eyes are bulging.
I think I'm in love.
Wow. Beautiful journalism.
How about this one?
It's my favorite.
Hollywood's newest
heartthrob is a greasy,
depressing little man
who no one saw coming.
Thank you.
For some reason,
the part of that headline
that offends me the most
is the word whom
It just sounds pretentious.
But you know
what isn't pretentious?
My upbringing.
I was raised in Atlanta,
Georgia, by my mother,
with the help of her three
sisters and my grandmother.
And my mama
is the most important person
in my life.
Going, growing, going up.
Whenever my mama, she couldn't
afford a babysitter,
she would take me with her
to honky tonks.
My mother taught me how to clog,
told me how to 2-step
And luckily enough for
me, my mama's here tonight.
We've got, we've.
We've come a really long way,
haven't we, mom?
Absolutely.
And since his Mother's Day
tomorrow.
Mama, would you dance with me?
You know what?
Yeah. Hold on.
Let's kick
this up a notch,
fellas. If you don't mind.
Oh, we got a great show for you
tonight.
Arcade fire here.
Happy Mother|s Day.
Stick around.
We|ll be right back
And so we are resolved.
The First Amendment to
our Constitution is as follows.
Congress
shall make no law respecting
an establishment of religion,
of abridging
the freedom of speech,
or of the press,
or of the right of the people
peaceably to assemble,
and to petition the government
for a redress of grievances.
Well done, gentlemen.
The First Amendment,
All right.
Now, what shall we discuss next?
What is the second
most important
principle of our nation? Gun.
Excuse me. Gun.
I don't hate that.
Well, I do. It's ridiculous.
So, what is your name?
Matt.
Matt. What?
That.
Don't you worry about it.
Well, Matt,
what will posterity say of us
if the second rate
we enshrined in this document
is simply
guns that we don't play?
Damn,
that's
actually kind of sick. Yes.
No, no, no.
The idea is ludicrous.
Wait, now hold on.
I mean, we did just make a law
that said anyone can say
whatever crazy stuff
they want, right?
Maybe this gun thing
would kind of balance that out.
Bingo.
Okay. Yes.
But by the same token, wouldn't
having a gun embolden people
to say crazy stuff as well?
Bro. What?
Yeah. Yeah.
What makes that makes sense?
Gentlemen, we cannot just have
an amendment that says guns.
But what about guns?
Having them.
That smart?
Like, who is this guy?
Why isn't he running this?
Matt, I am open to discussing
guns for a later amendment,
but I must insist we move on
to a more pressing concern.
You are screaming. So angry.
So, where are you from exactly?
America?
Yes, but where in America?
Which state are you?
A united one
Oh, wow. Well said. So.
Can this guy, like,
be on our money?
Who is this guy?
Have guns. Really, gentlemen?
That's what we want
the Second Amendment to be.
Have guns.
That sounds idiotic.
Just chill. Not have guns.
Bear Arms
Oh, that is so good.
Yeah, that sounds smart as hell.
Yeah. Okay. I'm freaking sold.
I'm writing an amendment
to the right to bear arms.
I just got chills.
Yeah,
well, my work here is done.
Wait, Matt,
will we ever see you again?
Depends on where you look.
ZOO
>>> I JUST HAD TO GET OUT OF THE
APARTMENT.
>> OF COURSE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I GOT FIRED.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN GIVE ME A
WARNING.
HELEN, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> WHAT?
OH -- YEAH SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GO ON WITHOUT ME.
* THE TINY BABY SHOE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE ZOO *
* I CAN'T KEEP WALKING AND
PRETEND I DIDN'T SEE IT WHEN I
DID *
* AND IT'S CHANGING ME INSIDE *
* NOW I'VE FOUND THIS TINY BABY
SHOE *
* PUT A FOOTPRINT ON MY HEART I
CAN'T UNDO *
* CAN'T THROW IT AWAY
IT'S NOT TRASH *
* A PIECE OF MY FUTURE A PART OF
YOUR PAST *
* A BABY
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO *
* SOMEWHERE THERE'S A TINY
CINDERELLA *
* WELL I'M COMING FOR YOU
LITTLE BELLA *
* I GOT YOUR SHOE
SO PUT IT ON *
* NICE TO MEET YOU
NOW I'M YOUR MOM *
* YOU'VE GOT A MOM, WELL NOW
YOU'VE GOT TWO *
* IS IT YOUR BABY
BIT TOO SKINNY *
* IS IT YOURS
BIT TOO FAT *
* HOW ABOUT YOU
BIT TOO LONG AND ALSO FLAT *
* WELL, THESE ARE THE ONLY
BABIES I SEE *
* ACTUALLY THE SHOE BELONGS TO
ME *
* I'M A FULLY GROWN-ASS MAN
WITH TINY BABY FEET *
* AND I'D REALLY BE SO GRATEFUL
IF YOU GIVE MY SHOE BACK TO ME *
* IT'S YOU *
* IT'S ME *
* I FOUND THIS TINY BABY SHOE *
* AND THE MAN IT BELONGS TO *
* SURELY THIS CAN'T FADE
AND YOU AND I WILL DATE *
>> OH, NO, SORRY, WHAT?
>> YOU AND I ARE GOING TO DATE
NOW, RIGHT?
'CAUSE YOU FOUND MY SHOE.
>> I WAS LOOKING FOR A BABY.
>> NO, YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR A BABY, BUT YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR ME.
DING DONG BING BONG, HERE I AM.
* SHE FINALLY FOUND HER MAN
AND THEY MADE LOVE ON THE CAROUSEL *
>> NO, WE'RE NOT A COUPLE.
>> WELL, DAMN.
I'M BEING STRAIGHT-UP GASSED
WITH IT RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
HE HAS SMALL FEET, IS HIS OTHER
PART SMALL TOO?
>> I WAS NOT THINKING THAT.
>> WELL, I'LL ASK YOU THIS.
IS TWO INCHES SMALL?
>> YEAH.
OH, OH, MY GOD, I DIDN'T MEAN TO
UPSET YOU.
>> WELL, YOU DID.
YOU LEAVE ME BE.
I'D WALK AWAY MYSELF, BUT I'M
TIRED.
I'VE ALREADY WALKED LIKE 45,000
STEPS TODAY.
I'VE ONLY BEEN AWAKE FOR 20
MINUTES.
>> HEY, I'M SAM ROCKWELL.
I THINK WE'VE ALL LEARNED A VERY
VALUABLE LESSON TODAY.
CINDERELLA RULES AREN'T
REAL-LIFE RULES.
>> HEY, MAN, MIND YOUR BUSINESS.
>> HEY, MAN, EXCUSE ME?
>> YOU JUST WALK AROUND THE
PARK, INTERRUPTING CONVERSATIONS
WITH NUGGETS OF WISDOM?
>> NO, WHAT I DO IS MAKE BALLOON
ANIMALS.
I THINK WE'RE ALL SET.
>> EXCUSE ME, I'M TALKING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I DON'T NEED
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF TO YOU, TO
YOU.
I'M LEAVING, I'M OUT OF HERE.
>> I GUESS THE LESSON HERE IS --
* WHEN YOU FIND A BABY SHOE *
>> NOT SO TINY.
* THAT FITS JUST LIKE A GLOVE *
* JUST GO ABOUT YOUR DAY *
* YOU DON'T NEED TO DO THAT
GIRL *
* IT WON'T BE YOU'RE IN LOVE *
* NO, NO IT DON'T MEAN THAT AT
ALL *
Mother's day
brunch at Lillard's in the park.
I am so impressed.
How did you boys
get a reservation?
A little trade secret called
booking at five months ago.
And a little surprise
after this,
we got tickets
to the Botanical Gardens exhibit
and flowers of the 19th century.
I have wanted to go to that.
You boys are so sweet.
Oh. Hello there.
My name is Alby,
and I'll be your server
I am sad to say,
a happy Mother's Day, but
all I see a two young men out
with their much younger sisters.
Oh, you're a big.
tip, mister.
No need.
I already have one. Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh. Okay,
go get some menus.
I should warn you, ladies,
I am a big old flirt.
Oh, baby.
You do not want to flirt
with a couple of old moms.
Oh, yes, I do.
I've always been attracted
to mothers.
Perhaps it's because my own
mother was such an angel.
Or possibly
because once I came of age,
I slept with every single
one of her friends. Oh,
love to peek at some menus.
Needless to say, it's
my lucky day to wait on not one,
but two mature goddesses
dripping in Talbots.
Now please tell me
you all have those comfy kids.
Do you have them on?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, how did you know? Oh.
Oh, y'all
making a boy sweat over here?
Oh, no.
No. Oh.
All right.
I think we're good
on the flirting with our moms.
Are you Lord Jesus?
No. Then don't be cross.
Just cause your mama baked you
just because you're mama baked
you doesn't mean other men
don't want to see the oven. Oh.
You're hysterical.
Oh, we going to have so much fun
out of here.
Okay, how about some menus?
Oh. Thank you.
Alby,
This one's for. You.
Can we snag a couple of those?
Now, can
I start you with some drinks?
Oh, or is the mimosa bottomless?
Yes, ma'am.
And maybe after you've
had a couple, you'll be two.
Here.
I'll be two mimosas for us.
How is your sangria?
No idea.
And, I just got a coffee.
I don't know, can you.
I'll get those mimosas for you.
Okay.
Do you want us to ask
for a different server?
Oh, stop. Alby's harmless.
He's harmless.
Look at him.
You guys,
this is an expensive brunch, and
I just want to make sure it's
a good experience for everybody.
Well, if you stop
being so uptight, it will be.
Here are your mimosas.
Did you unbutton your shirt
more?
Yes, I did.
Your turn. Ladies.
Oh, my God, I'm so silly today.
Dude. For real?
Stop! You're being. Gross.
Calm down boy.
You've got to spend
nine months inside your mom.
I'm just
trying to get 20 minutes.
You know, Ali, do
you have any butter substitute?
Like a margarine.
You know, if I have dairy,
I will be gassy
for the whole rest of the day.
So I've never complained about
a breeze
blowing through my hair. Oh.
Jesus, dude.
Oh, I'm a handful today.
Then I have.
Oh, I'm getting a rush of blood
somewhere as well.
Thank the Lord
I'm wearing this apron
because I'm about to have a hat
rack down here.
Prove it
Mom, what?
Everyone just order, please.
Okay, we'll all have the brunch
special.
I'll go put that in now
and maybe later.
Wait, let me guess.
And maybe later
I'll put something else in.
Hey, watch your tongue.
How dare you talk about that way
around your mama?
Don't ruin today for me, son.
Yeah,
I'll do
all the ruining around him.
Oh, your trouble
Good afternoon, everyone, and
thank you so much for attending
this preview of our upcoming
production, handful of Hope.
You may notice
we have some unusual guests
in the audience today, 20 dogs
from Canine Companions who,
as part of their service dog
training, must learn how to sit
through a full length play.
And again,
welcome people and dogs.
I think you'll all really enjoy
hand full of Hope.
It was 1958.
Chuck Berry taken over the radio
with Johnny B good.
Nothing would be good for this
Johnny that's similar.
Not as my alcoholic half sister
Janelle
had anything to say about it.
Dinah, what are you doing here?
I'm pretty sure daddy told
you never to come back here.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I know he told me never
to come back here. You hear
the back here?
You hear I came.
I'm sorry.
I really hate
to break character,
but I do notice that dogs
keep leaving the,
It's very hard to act
when that's happening.
I'm. I'm so sorry.
I'm one of the dog trainers.
Please don't be offended.
This is their first time
at a bad play.
Well, I like the show,
and I think my dog does too.
Well, we are going to.
Ask the dog.
Stay as still as possible,
please,
so the actors can concentrate.
Absolutely. So sorry.
be good? be good?
You see, my sisters better days
inside a bottle of cheap
champagne.
Said she loved how the bubbles
tickled her nose.
But one day the bubbles began
to tickle her
brain.
My brain?
Fine, I tell you.
Finer
than the softest silks in China.
Now I just need to put a bird,
pick me up and carry me there.
Oh, how? Stop it!
Oh my
God, what what what what now?
I'm sorry.
My dog
keeps hitting me in the ribs
and then pointing at the stage,
kind of like.
You see?
And this.
Yeah.
And my dog
keeps looking at the program
to see who the producers are.
Okay, you know what?
Let's just skip
to the end of the first act
and we can get this
all sorted out.
I didn't go to Juilliard, so
I can act with a bunch of dogs.
Okay, well,
you didn't go to Juilliard
for any reason, Daniel,
because you didn't get it.
Wait a second.
I'm sorry. Is your dog asleep?
Oh, no.
wide awake
Can I ask a question?
Is. Yes, I have a question.
I'm sorry.
Is this for
I shouldn't have brought the
button mat treat treat, treat.
Okay, just skip to the end.
Johnny.
No, don't leave me again.
I know
that's not what she wants.
You have no clue what I want,
Joel.
No. Now, don't ask.
Oh, he kissed his sister.
Rose.
You kissed me.
That's different.
I guess my train can wait.
I guess that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
But what will you say to me.
In act two?
Guys, it's not over.
Oh my God, who gave you M+M|s?
I knew he should
have gone to Oh Mary.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ARCADE
FIRE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
**
* NOW IT'S ALL IRRELEVANT
PINK ELEPHANT
PINK ELEPHANT *
**
* ALWAYS NERVOUS
WITH THE REAL THING *
* MIND IS CHANGING
LIKE A MOOD RING *
* JUMPING EVERY TIME
THE PHONE RINGS *
* 'CAUSE YOUR MIND'S
OFF OF ME *
**
* FAMILIES FAKING ON THE TV
LIVE IN THE SPECTRUM
THAT WE CAN'T SEE *
* CRYING TEARS
WE DON'T BELIEVE
KEEPS YOUR MIND OFF OF ME *
* TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME
A LITTLE WHILE *
* IN THE DARKEST PLACE
I SAW YOU SMILE *
* AND THE WAY IT ALL CHANGED
MAKES ME WANNA CRY BUT
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH *
**
* YOUR FAKE FRIENDS
THEY GO OUT DANCING *
* BUT YOU'RE TOO BUSY
NEUROMANCING *
* EVERY CIRCUIT IN
YOUR HEART SINGS
KEEPS YOUR MIND OFF OF ME *
* TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME
A LITTLE WHILE *
* IN THE DARKEST PLACE
I SAW YOU SMILE *
* AND THE WAY IT ALL CHANGED
MAKES ME WANNA CRY BUT
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH *
* I DON'T THINK ABOUT YOU
THE WARM RAIN IN JUNE *
* THE FEELING THAT MY LIFE
HAD FINALLY FOUND
SOME MEANING *
* I DON'T THINK ABOUT YOU
WELL WHAT CAN I DO *
* NOW IT'S ALL IRRELEVANT
DON'T THINK ABOUT
PINK ELEPHANT, NO *
* TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH *
* THE WAY IT ALL CHANGED
MAKES ME WANNA CRY BUT
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH *
**
* YEAH
YEAH *
**
* THE WAY IT ALL CHANGED
MAKES ME WANNA CRY BUT
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF ME YEAH *
It's Weekend Update
with Colin Jost and Michael Che.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thanks. Good evening everyone.
Welcome to Weekend
Update I'm Michael che.
I'm Colin Jost.
Well, the Catholic Church
has elected the first ever pope
from America.
And as an American Catholic,
I could not be more proud.
Which is a sin.
And now I'm ashamed.
The Vatican has selected
Cardinal Robert Francis Prevost,
who is from the South side
of Chicago, to be the new pope.
And you can tell
he's from the South Side,
because he's got his hands
up.
This pic was actually
a welcome surprise for me,
because when I heard the Pope
was a super religious guy
from Chicago in a funny robe,
I was worried it was Kanye.
I also love that conservatives
are already complaining
that this pope is too woke.
How woke can a 69 year
old man from Chicago be?
It's not like he came out
and was like,
hey, I'm Pope Leo the 14th.
He him.
The reality is,
there are no woke Catholics.
If you're a woke Catholic, you're
just not Catholic anymore.
Joe Biden appeared on The View,
where he said he wasn't surprised
Kamala Harris lost the election,
because the only thing
that surprises
Joe Biden are the words
that come out of his own mouth.
President
Trump says he will appoint
Fox News host
Jeanine Pirro
as interim U.S.
attorney for Washington, D.C..
Pirro celebrated the news
with a bottle of wine
every day
for the last 50 years.
President Trump also announced
a new trade deal with the U.K.
that will reopen British markets
for American companies.
All that
Britain demands in return
is that we keep these two.
Insiders are saying
that President Trump
is trying to create tension
between his potential
successors -
Marco Rubio and JD Vance,
mostly
by pointing at them
and saying, kiss.
President Trump
announced plans
for a 100% tariff
on movies
made outside the U.S.,
which is no problem for me
because all the movies I watch
were filmed in a Florida condo
on a leather couch.
If you laugh, you're a fan too.
President Trump said he was
interested in reopening Alcatraz
because it represents something
horrible
and beautiful and strong
and miserable and weak.
What's also his nickname
for his five children?
A new report shows that
there have been at least nine
incidents at Newark Airport,
where air traffic controllers
have lost contact with planes
that were about to land.
But
luckily, it's Newark, so planes
can just follow the smell.
Insiders at the FBI are concerned
that Director
Kash Patel is not at work enough,
and is often seen
attending sporting events
with celebrities.
But like his eyes, Patel
can be in two places at once.
The white House marked Star Wars
Day by posting an AI
generated picture
of President
Trump as a musclebound Jedi.
And they also posted
a picture of JD the Hutt.
The first week of jury selection
in the Sean Combs trial
has ended
without a jury being selected.
Well, yeah,
I mean, where are you going
to find 12 people
who
haven't had sex with Diddy.
In New York City?
Big city Mayor Eric Adams met
with President Trump yesterday
to discuss the city's
concerns,
namely that Trump's deportations
have dramatically cut
New York's
supply of thick shorties
I love that man
President, Trump
says Catholics loved
an image he posted of him
dressed as the Pope last week.
But I just find it
hard to believe that
anyone in the Catholic Church
would be into something
so juvenile.
Well, with box office
hits like sinners,
Thunderbolts, and Minecraft.
Summer movie
season is in full swing
here with his preview of the upcoming
summer blockbusters.
Is the movie guy.
Hope the movie God.
And you're
not going to believe it.
But I'm here
to talk about the movies.
That's great. Yes.
Well, first off, I got to know
what is your take on sinners?
Yes. Sinners.
This is an amazing movie
about people who are doing sins.
But I
do have one sin to confess.
I did not see that one yet.
Okay.
All right, well,
what movies can
we look forward to this summer?
Oh, thank you
for asking that one.
The first movie that's coming up
is Jurassic World The Rebirth.
They gave me early access
to this movie,
and I have to tell you,
I did not see that one yet.
But I can guess what
going to happen
in the beginning of this movie.
Everything. That's okay, guys.
No problem here.
The dinosaur is in jail.
Hey, everybody,
don't worry about it.
But then the dinosaur escaped,
and the only person
that can stop them
is Scarlett Johansson
I'm sorry. Who?
Scarlett Johansson
Yeah.
You know.
You know where you see Avengers?
Yes. Oh, Scarlett Johansson.
Yes. That's my wife.
Yeah, yeah.
And my wife is Rihanna.
To the umbrella.
I don't like
how hard you guys are laughing.
Let's just move on
to the next summer movie.
And remember, you don't have to
guess what the plot is.
You must not know about me.
I'm going to do exactly the.
The next movie from
the summer is Fantastic Four.
I imagine this movie
going to be about
three, maybe four people.
And they probably fantastic.
Yeah.
But you know
somebody who not fantastic.
Gary Fields.
Who is Gary Fields?
You know Gary Fields.
He hate Monday
even though he don't have a job
every day. The same for a cat.
Am I right, guys?
I'm on.
You're wrong. No.
Did you like ball field
material now? Yes,
but we got to talk about karate,
Keith.
Oh, yes.
If I had to guess,
it would be like the first one
where a Chinese guy
teach a little boy to wack off.
And I'm sorry.
You know, waCk on, wack off.
it|s wax
not sure if he had the kid wax
before.
Can we.
Just get back to the movies?
What about Superman?
I don't know who that is, but.
But you know who
the real superhero.
Single mothers of
Can't do that.
All right.
Movie guy, anything
you want to cover before we go.
Yes, I have a joke.
A joke? Yeah.
The joke is.
Gatorade zero zero.
What's in there?
Am I right, guys?
Movie guy everyone
Weight watchers said that
it is filing for bankruptcy protection
to eliminate
more than $1 billion in debt.
But, you know, they're
just going to gain it all back.
American Airlines has introduced
a new first class option
called Flagship Suites
that features privacy doors,
a cool touch pillow, and a lie
flat bed.
American Airlines
get pregnant with us.
K-pop star Lisa
is being criticized
for her Met Gala outfit
that appeared to feature images
of Rosa Parks on the crotch.
But at least
they put her in the front.
Am I right?
A Lamborghini yacht off
the coast of Miami Beach sank
while carrying more than 30
social media influencers
like.
The U.S. Navy said that for the second
week in a row,
F-18
fighter jet fell off an aircraft
carrier into the ocean.
Well, thankfully,
there's nobody at the bottom
of the ocean
who could use two airplanes.
Oh, God.
Experts are noting
that the R-word has become
more commonplace
due to its use
by people like Elon Musk.
And yay!
Yeah, well,
they can say it because they're.
Rich.
They're rich.
Oh. Just get me.
President Trump's tariffs are
having massive cascading effects
on global trade.
Here to unpack
how this will affect you
The consumer
is a guy who just
walked into a spiderweb. Oh.
Oh oh, I'm so sorry.
I just walked into a spider web.
Oh, there was a spider in it.
I felt something like, hit
my shoulder.
Is there anything on me?
Oh, I really
I don't see anything.
I'm sorry.
Why don't
we just take us through
what's going on
with these tariffs?
Because the more I hear
about the tariffs,
the more confused I get.
Yeah.
Well, I like to tell
I feel something.
There's a spider on there.
on me
and I'm feeling okay.
I feel I feel good.
Where
Know
It's there.
Oh, God.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
I felt it on my skin.
On my skin?
I'm so sorry.
Feel sorry.
Should I still talk about
tariffs?
Get out
You just walk into a spider web.
What?
What is the show?
85 year old Motown legend Smokey Robinson
has been accused
of sexual assault
by four of his former
housekeepers.
Robinson plans to beat
the charges by being dead soon.
After a spider
and a new report lists
the happiest city in the U.S.
as New York.
Yeah.
I don't know who took that
survey.
The happiest city in the U.S.
was New York.
While the least happy
Dick splinter North Dakota.
- It's rough city, man.
- That's
the makers of the Grand
Theft Auto video game series
Announced
that the release of the
newest version of the game
will be delayed until May 2026.
And you know what? Good.
Maybe kids will finally turn off
their PlayStations,
go outside and slap
a real prostitute.
A doctor in Scotland
who secretly hid cameras
in his bathroom
so he could compare the size
of his penis
to other men,
has been sentenced
to 18 months in prison,
where his studies continue.
Well, it is Mother's Day.
No good transition.
It's Mother's Day
and spring has sprung here
in New York City,
which means more tourists
than ever.
Here, with her
tips on how to survive the Big Apple
is Diane,
the mom who's only read
about New York on Facebook.
I love New York. Yay!
Hello. Hello, Diane. Welcome.
Do you want to?
You want to put your bag down?
Oh. Nice try guy.
All right.
Any any tips from your visit
so far?
Yes.
New York is a beautiful city.
You can go to Central Park,
home of the Mets,
and, yeah, a thousand crackheads and that.
Thanks.
I'll stay in my hotel room with
my QVC and my deadbolt locks.
Okay. Well, Dan, sorry.
New York is really not that bad.
No, Colin.
It is.
Okay,
so I read a post, all right,
about a woman,
my neighborhood, my
age, white.
Mother of four.
She is in New York. Okay.
Takes the subway.
Two stops later,
her AirPods are missing.
She's got two face tattoos,
and she's a Crip
showing up currently
at the Marriott Fitness Center.
I really can't believe that's
true, Diane,
I'll say. You seem a little on edge.
I'm on edge.
I'm not on anything.
I'm not smoking,
not chopped cheese.
Okay? I'm high.
I'm high on two things.
Jamba Juice or.
Oh, okay.
Do you do
you have any other tips?
Yeah.
Hey, don't buy a single thing,
okay?
Cause listen to this, all right?
I read it, I read a post.
Oh, about a woman.
Same school district.
Okay. My age. White.
This is New York. Okay.
What's a pair of sunglasses?
Oh, okay.
Vendor seems nice.
Cuts her deal. She puts them on.
What does she see?
Porn everywhere.
- She sees.
- Yes. Okay.
It erased all of her memories.
And now all
she remembers is porn.
All she remembers is porn.
Sorry, kids.
Mommy just knows porn now.
She can't come to your site.
Oh, cause she's on the bank,
boss.
Oh, my God.
Okay, here's another tip.
Do you not have your picture
taken?
Don't
have your picture taken? Why?
So
I read a
post about a woman about my age.
Beautiful mother of four.
Mixed.
- It took me to say that.
- Well, I want to.
She had just gotten out of
a fabulous matinee of Mamma mia!
When this man offered
to take her photo.
He takes out his camera, clicks
it, boom.
She passes out, wakes up in Abu
Dhabi, chained to a bed.
No way, no way.
Sorry kids.
Mommy's last name is.
I'm dual now.
- They come down.
- Okay. What?
Just put down your bag.
No one is trying to
take your money.
Oh, yeah?
Like I would keep money
in my bag in New York. Right?
Well,
where do you keep it?
In my butt?
You keep money in your butt?
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
I have 2000 cash plus my jewelry
plus tickets
- Are Lion King tickets online?
- I'm calling.
You should know that.
So I write a post about a woman
my age.
Same shirt she was.
What was. Mona? No. No.
Go on for not doing it,
Diane.
Everyone.
Poke
What was the weekend
update on college?
Yes, I'm Michael J tonight.
Knicks in five
Look, kids were at the
deathly diner
because this part of the park
is for a themed, fun ride.
It's so fun.
I love. Scary stuff.
Rides were great today,
but I'm ready to eat.
Greetings, diners.
Is this your first time
dining with us this afternoon?
I hope you enjoy your meal.
It might be your last. Ooh.
Kids. You scared?
I am. Fun. Right, guys?
We're looking for a table
for four. Right this way.
But watch your step.
There is blood on the floor.
Enjoy your meal.
It's might be your last.
Yes. You said that.
Fun kid.
Fun. Right, kids?
Hello, diners.
I'll be your evil server
tonight.
I'll be back to take your order.
But be careful.
It might be your last.
Honey, does.
The staff is sort of bad
at this.
Sort of.
I feel like
there should be more of a story.
But the theme park
did just open this week,
so maybe
they're still ironing it out.
I've got two waters for you.
But be careful.
They might be
your last
Do we not get more water?
No. You do.
But enjoy it and be careful.
It may be your last
drink.
You guys have said
it might be our last a lot. Now.
Oh, wait wait wait.
Wait wait wait.
Actually.
We'd love to hear more of the
story of your scary restaurant.
Is the theme of this place
just dying?
No, no.
It's also.
Can't think of what to say.
Dan. Dan?
Yes, yes.
Tell these corpses
the scary back story
that I can't quite remember.
Well, right now
there's, witch in our basement.
And, vampire in our attic.
Okay.
And, there's a woman being
slapped around in our kitchen.
Excuse.
No no no no no no no
no, not like that.
What that means is
she is getting hurt physically.
But don't
worry, she's turned on by it.
It was her idea.
Okay, okay. Stop.
Our kids are ten and 12.
You know what?
I'm just going to get
the bloody steak.
But can I sub the salad
for fries?
Yes, but be careful.
It cost $2 extra.
And I'll have the chicken.
Terry. Scary. What?
Why wouldn't
you just call it the chicken?
Scary-aki
Because we didn't think of that.
It's our first day.
Oh, and it might be our last.
Okay, so it's your first day.
All right, well,
that explains a lot. Yes.
The rest of the staff
was poisoned.
Wait, is that real?
By the food?
No. No.
Oh. Oh, well,
I don't know what to say.
Okay.
Where's the bathroom?
Oh, it's around the corner
to the left.
But, it's occupied
due to the kitchen.
Woman is being killed in there.
The woman stuff
is actually kind of upsetting.
No, no. It's okay. She's safe.
But right now,
there's a bunch of guys in there
hitting her on the head.
Yeah,
but it was her idea, remember?
She's so horny.
Oh my God.
Never mind,
kids, let's. Let's go.
Excuse us, waiters,
can we please put it in order?
It's my 100th birthday.
Oh. Well, then,
Be careful.
This meal may be your,
First of many more to come.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, ARCADE FIRE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
**
* IT'S THE TIME
OF THE SEASON
WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT LEAVING *
* OH-OOH
I KNEW THAT YOU WOULD
I KNEW THAT YOU WOULD *
**
* IN THE SEASON OF STRANGERS
WHEN WE WERE IN DANGER
OH-OOH *
* I REACHED OUT TO YOU
LIKE YOU KNEW THAT I WOULD
LIKE YOU KNEW THAT I WOULD *
* IT'S THE SEASON OF CHANGE
AND IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD *
* IN THE YEAR OF THE RABBIT
I PICKED UP THE HABIT
OF WAITING ON YOU *
* IN THE YEAR OF THE SNAKE
I MADE A CLEAN BREAK
AND TRIED SOMETHING NEW *
* I FLY IN MY AEROSTAR
I PICKED UP A NEW SCAR
I TRIED TO BE GOOD *
* BUT I'M A REAL BOY
MY HEART'S FULL OF LOVE
IT'S NOT MADE OUT OF WOOD *
* SO DO WHAT IS TRUE
DON'T DO WHAT YOU SHOULD *
* IT'S THE SEASON OF CHANGE
AND IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD *
**
* SEASON OF CHANGE
IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD *
* SEASON OF CHANGE
IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD
OH *
* LET YOUR HEART BREAK
LET THE EARTH QUAKE
LET THE STARS OF TEXAS
FALL IN THE LAKE *
* JUST DO WHAT IS TRUE
YOU AIN'T GOTTA BE FAKE *
* LET THE FIRE BLAZE
LET THE LIGHT CHANGE
LET THE HEAVENLY BODY
FALL OUT OF PHASE *
* IT'S THE NEW AGE
DON'T DO WHAT YOU SHOULD *
* IT'S THE SEASON OF CHANGE
AND IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD
WOO *
* SEASON OF CHANGE
IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD *
* SEASON OF CHANGE
IF YOU FEEL STRANGE
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD *
**
* IT'S THE YEAR OF THE SNAKE
SO LET YOUR HEART BREAK *
**
* IT'S THE YEAR OF THE SNAKE
SO LET YOUR HEART BREAK *
**
* IT'S THE YEAR OF THE SNAKE
SO LET YOUR HEART BREAK **
**
>>> IT'S BEEN SUCH A GREAT
NIGHT.
I REALLY CAN'T THANK YOU GUYS
ENOUGH.
>> INCOME.
YOU'RE LIKE FAMILY.
>> LISTEN, NICK, I DIDN'T ASK
YOU HERE TONIGHT JUST FOR THE
PLEASURE OF YOUR COMPANY.
THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO TELL
YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> I'VE DECIDED TO MAKE YOU
PARTNER.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> VERY MUCH SO.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, NICK.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
MR. PATTERSON, I WON'T LET YOU
DOWN.
>> I KNOW YOU WON'T.
HOW ABOUT WE CELEBRATE WITH SOME
CHAMPAGNE?
>> YES, SOUNDS GREAT.
YOU MIND IF I USE YOUR BATHROOM
REAL QUICK?
>> SURE, YEAH.
IT'S RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER.
>> WHOO.
PARTNER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> NOW, IT'S GOING TO BE A LOT
OF WORK.
>> I'M READY FOR THAT, SIR.
>> I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT ON YOUR
PLATE, SO THINGS COULD GET
MESSY.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU
JUST HAVE TO PUSH.
>> COME ON, NOW.
COME ON, NOW.
>> SOMETHING WRONG, NICK?
>> NO, NO.
JUST FEELING GRATEFUL.
>> NO, NO, I'M GRATEFUL TO YOU.
FRANKLY, I'VE BEEN DESPERATE FOR
A SOLID NUMBER TWO.
>> EVERYTHING OKAY, NICK?
>> YEAH.
YEP.
EVERYTHING'S GREAT.
>> LOOK, IT'S GOING TO BE A
STRUGGLE AT FIRST, BUT JUST
FIGHT THROUGH IT, AND I KNOW
YOU'LL MAKE A BIG SPLASH.
NICK, COULD YOU GET US ANOTHER
BOTTLE OF CHAMPAGNE?
>> SURE, MRS. PATTERSON.
>> OVERWHELMING, ISN'T IT?
SO MUCH TO TAKE IN.
YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE
THE WET WIPES OVER THE TANK.
>> WATER!
OH!
OH, OH!
>> WET WIPES GOOD.
>> HELLO.
>> HELP ME.
>> AAHHH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MAYBE NOW I'LL BE PARTNER.
>> AAHHH!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
**
>>> I WANT TO THANK ARCADE FIRE,
CECILY STRONG, MAMA, LORNE
MICHAELS, THIS AMAZING CAST AND
CREW AND ONE OF THE GREATEST
WEEKS OF MY ENTIRE LIFE.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
**