>>> AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR
CHURCH CHAT.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, AND WELCOME TO
CHURCH CHAT.
I'M THE CHURCH LADY.
THANK YOU.
SO SWEET, SO SWEET.
YOU KNOW, IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK
TO RING OUT THE END OF 2024.
THE MOST SATANIC YEAR IN
HISTORY.
INSTEAD OF MOTHER MARY,
LITTLE GIRLS ARE LOOKING UP TO THE
HOPTOEE GIRL.
YOU KNOW WHAT I SAY?
INSTEAD OF HOPTOEE
YOU NEED TO
WALKTOEE A CHURCH.
HAVE YOU SEEN "WICKED"?
YEAH, JUST LIKE "THE WIZARD OF OZ",
BUT INSTEAD OF SAYING
LIONS, TIGERS AND BEARS, OH MY,
THEY SAY LIONS, TIGERS, AND
SLUTS, OH YES!
A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK, YOU'VE GOT
11-YEAR-OLDS
DRESSING UP LIKE
THAT VIXEN, SABRINA CARPENTER.
YOU KNOW WHO WAS THE BEST
CARPENTER?
JESUS.
¶ HE'S WORKING LATE'
CAUSE HE'S A SAVIOR ¶
NOW IT'S TIME FOR MY FIRST
GUEST.
PLEASE WELCOME MATT GAETZ.
HELLO, DEAR.
>> THANK YOU.
HELLO, CHURCH LADY.
>> ARE YOU OKAY, MATT?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE SURPRISED TO
BE HERE.
>> NO.
THIS IS JUST HOW MY FACE IS.
>> I CAN SEE THAT.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR FOREHEAD'S
TRYING TO GO TO HEAVEN WITHOUT
YOU.
WHAT A -- WHAT A PUSS, WHAT A
PUSS.
I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE ANY HUBBUB,
BUT YOU DO LOOK A LITTLE
LIKE SOMEONE WHO COULD BE --
>> LEONARDO DiCAPRIO?
>> NO, IT'S NOT LEONARDO --
>> BRAD PITT?
>> NO, JUST TRYING TO KNOCK ON
MY NOGGIN.
COULD IT BE -- SATAN?
CAUGHT YOU OFF GUARD, DIDN'T I?
NOW MATT, LET'S SEE IF I HAVE
THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU WERE INVOLVED IN SOME LITTLE
SEXUAL PECCADILLOS?
THEY WROTE A WHOLE REPORT ABOUT IT,
BUT SOMEHOW WE NEVER GOT TO
SEE IT, DID WE?
ISN'T THAT CONVENIENT?
>> FOR ME IT IS, YES.
>> POOR LITTLE MATT GAETZ.
YOU BETTER REPENT, MATT.
THERE'S ONLY 17 DAYS LEFT TO
CHRISTMAS.
>> YOU HAD ME AT 17.
>> OKAY, OFF YOU GO.
DON'T LET THE DOOR HIT YOU ON
THE FOREHEAD ON YOUR WAY OUT.
GOOD-BYE, MATT GAETZ, GOOD-BYE.
ALL RIGHT.
MOVING RIGHT ALONG,
MY NEXT
GUEST IS SOMEONE WHO ACTUALLY IS
A LOT LIKE JESUS.
BECAUSE HE ALSO HAS A DAD NAMED
JOSEPH.
WHOSE LIFE IS MADE WAY MORE
COMPLICATED BECAUSE OF HIM.
PLEASE WELCOME THE ONE AND ONLY
HUNTER BIDEN.
>> HI, THERE.
CHURCH LADY.
HAVEN'T BEEN HERE IN A WHILE,
I'VE BEEN LAYING LOW A LITTLE
BIT.
>> OH, I THINK THAT'S OKAY.
AT LEAST YOU HAVEN'T BEEN DOING
A PODCAST.
>> EASY, CHURCH WOMAN.
>> OH, HUNTER, IT'S ACTUALLY
CHURCH LADY.
>> OH, WELL PARDON ME.
>> PARDON YOU?
WHO DO YOU THINK I AM, YOUR
DADDY?
>> OH, YES, MY FATHER DID PARDON
ME.
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS A GOOD
THING FOR THE FATHER TO FORGIVE THE SON,
RIGHT, CHURCH LADY?
>> OH.
LAST TIME I CHECKED, JESUS
WASN'T WALKING AROUND IN A ROBE
WITH NO UNDERWEAR,
HANGING OUT
WITH PROSTITUTES.
>> I THINK HE WAS.
>> WELL, JESUS CERTAINLY DIDN'T
TURN WATER INTO CRACK.
>> WAIT, YOU CAN DO THAT?
>> HUNTY, LET'S MOVE ON, OKAY?
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE ON
THE RIGHT AREN'T TOO HAPPY ABOUT
YOUR PARDON.
>> WELL, THEY SINGLED ME OUT
JUST BECAUSE OF WHO I AM.
MUCH LIKE TRUMP, THEY WENT AFTER
ME BECAUSE OF MY LAST NAME
AND
ALL THE ILLEGAL THINGS I DID.
>> WELL, ISN'T THAT SPECIAL.
>> CAN I SAY ONE THING BEFORE I
GO?
I'VE GONE THROUGH A LOT, BUT MY
DAD LOVES ME UNCONDITIONALLY
AND THAT'S THE GREATEST GIFT OF ALL.
ALSO, TO ANYONE WHO'S SEEN ANY
OF THOSE LAPTOP PHOTOS,
JUST
REMEMBER, THE CAMERA TAKES OFF
TWO INCHES.
>> ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
BYE-BYE, NOW.
BYE-BYE.
GO AWAY.
ALL RIGHT.
HUNTER BIDEN, EVERYBODY.
WELL.
MY NEXT GUEST IS A BASEBALL FREE AGENT
ABOUT TO SIGN THE BIGGEST
CONTRACT IN ALL OF TIME.
PLEASE WELCOME JUAN SOTO.
>> HELLO, CHURCH LADY, OR AS I
LIKE TO SAY --
>> WELCOME TO "CHURCH CHAT."
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO CHURCH
BEFORE?
>> WELL, I AM LATIN.
WHEN I WAS A KID, WE WENT TO
CHURCH
ONCE ON CHRISTMAS,
ONCE ON EASTER,
AND TWICE EVERY OTHER
DAY.
>> WELL, AREN'T YOU A MUSCULAR
MAN WITH A FESTIVE ACCENT.
>> OKAY.
>> I LIKE IT, I CAN'T HELP IT.
>> WELL, MY FAITH IS ACTUALLY A
PART OF MY GAME.
>> WELL, ISN'T THAT SPANISH.
SO I HEAR THEY'RE GOING TO PAY
YOU $700 MILLION
TO SMACK SOME
BALLS AROUND WITH YOUR BIG
STICK.
WE LIKE TO HIT A BASEBALL, DON'T
WE?
MAKE MORE MONEY THAN JESUS.
YOU KNOW, MONEY IS THE ROOT OF
ALL EVIL.
>> HA HA.
WELL, IT'S NOT TRUE, THEN I'M
GOING TO BECOME
THE MOST EVIL
BASEBALL PLAYER IN THE WORLD.
>> OH, SO FUNNY.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL TELL US,
WHAT
TEAM DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO PICK?
>> YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
RIGHT NOW, I HOPE THE YANKEES
MAKE ME THE BEST OFFER.
>> WELL, AS A CHRISTIAN, I HAVE TO ASK YOU --
WHY NOT SPEND YOUR
TIME HELPING --
AND MONEY
HELPING THE NEEDY AND THE LESS
FORTUNATE?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE I SIGN WITH THE METS.
>> WELL, THAT'S TERRIFIC.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S TIME FOR MY SONG.
COME ON OUT, "CHURCH CHAT" SINGERS,
COME OUT, DON'T BE SHY.
HERE WE GO.
¶ SATAN HAD A GOOD YEAR ¶
¶ WITH HOPTOEE AND P. DIDDY ¶
¶ SATAN IS A REAL KIND OF
GIDDY ¶
¶ SATAN HAD A GOOD YEAR ¶
¶ WILL CHRISTMAS BE ABOUT JESUS
NOBODY KNOWS ¶
¶ OR WILL IT BE ABOUT SANTA
HANGING WITH THE ¶
¶ HO HO HO ¶
¶ SATAN HAD A GOOD YEAR ¶¶
LET'S DANCE!
>> LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- PAUL
MESCAL!
>>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK
YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M PAUL MESCAL, AND IT IS GREAT
TO BE HERE.
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED "SNL"
THIS PLACE HAS SUCH HISTORY.
AND GROWING UP BACK HOME, I
NEVER IMAGINED I'D BE STANDING
HERE.
I'M ALSO EXCITED TO BE HERE
BECAUSE I'M NOT REALLY KNOWN FOR
COMEDY.
WHICH IS CRAZY TO ME.
BECAUSE I THINK I'VE GIVEN A LOT
OF REALLY FUNNY PERFORMANCES,
AND I THINK WE HAVE SOME
HIGHLIGHTS HERE.
>> SORRY.
>> I MEAN, IT'S FUNNY, NO?
BUT I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR
I'M NOT AFRAID TO DO EMOTIONAL SCENES
OR NUDE SCENES
OR NUDE EMOTIONAL SCENES.
RECENTLY I DID PIVOT TO
SOMETHING NEW IN "GLADIATOR 2."
IT'S A BIG ACTION-PACKED
BLOCKBUSTER.
HERE'S A LOOK.
IT'S SAFE TO SAY THERE'S NOT A
LOT OF COMEDY ON THE RESUME.
ANYWAY, I DO TAKE GREAT PRIDE IN
BEING IRISH.
AND THE IRISH PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT.
CENTURIES OF BRITISH OCCUPATION.
THE GREAT FAMINE.
MASS EMIGRATION.
THAT U2 ALBUM THAT AUTOMATICALLY
GOT DOWNLOADED.
SO BEFORE WE START THE SHOW, I
JUST WANT TO CLEAR UP
SOME UGLY
STEREOTYPES ABOUT THE IRISH.
FOR EXAMPLE, THERE'S A NASTY RUMOR
THAT IRISH PEOPLE HAVE SEX
WITH OUR COUSINS, RIGHT?
THAT'S OFFENSIVE, AND IT'S
RIDICULOUS.
WE HAVE SEX WITH OUR SECOND
COUSINS.
PEOPLE ALSO THINK THE IRISH HATE
BRITISH PEOPLE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE, WE JUST DON'T
CONSIDER THEM PEOPLE.
AND SOMETIMES PEOPLE ASK ME IF I
THINK
NOTRE DAME'S MASCOT THE
FIGHTING IRISH IS OFFENSIVE.
NOT AT ALL.
WE DO THE SAME THING WITH THE
AMERICANS.
MY HIGH SCHOOL'S MASCOT WAS THE
FIGHTING FAT-ASSES.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ASK IF WE WEAR
KILTS.
NO, THAT'S THE SCOTTISH.
TRADITIONALLY, THE IRISH WEAR
SHORT-SHORTS.
>> DID SOMEONE SAY SHORT-SHORTS?
HI
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> TRYING TO BE LIKE YOU, MAN.
YOU LIKE WHEN YOU SEE, HUH?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
BY THE WAY, THOSE ARE WAY TOO
SHORT.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
PAUL.
THE SHORTER THE SHORTS, THE
TALLER YOU LOOK.
>> DON'T THINK IT'S WORKING,
BUD.
>> AGREE TO DISAGREE, MY
BROTHER.
GOOD-BYE, PAUL.
GOOD-BYE, AMERICA.
BYE
>> YOU KNOW, PEOPLE OFTEN TALK
ABOUT THE LUCK OF THE IRISH.
AND TONIGHT, I HAVE TO SAY,
I DO FEEL VERY, VERY LUCKY TO BE
HERE.
I'M IN NEW YORK CITY.
I'M HOSTING "SNL."
AND THIS FEELS TOTALLY, TOTALLY
INSANE TO ME.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW TONIGHT.
SHABOOZEY IS HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK!
AND HE SAID, "YOU KNOW YOU'RE AT
CHIPOTLE, RIGHT?"
>> THIS CHICKEN IS DELICIOUS,
MOM.
I REALLY MISSED YOUR COOKING.
>> AND WE REALLY MISSED YOU.
>> COLLEGE HAS REALLY DONE YOU
WELL, SON.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> SWEETHEART?
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
NO HATS AT THE TABLE.
>> RIGHT, SORRY.
>> HONEY?
YOU GOT SOMETHING ON YOUR EAR.
>> OH, YEAH, GOT MY EAR PIERCED.
>> STEVEN, DO SOMETHING.
>> SORRY, BUT FOR A SECOND I
THOUGHT YOU HEARD YOU SAY YOU
GOT YOUR EAR PIERCED.
>> I DID, YEAH.
>> LIKE AS A JOKE?
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE A JOKE?
>> NO, I JUST THOUGHT IT LOOKED
GOOD, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
>> WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
LET ME ANSWER THAT QUESTION WITH
ANOTHER QUESTION.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL IF I CAME
HOME ONE DAY WITH SKELETON HANDS
TATTOOED AROUND MY NECK!
>> YEAH, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
MAYBE I'LL SHOW UP TO WORK
TOMORROW NAKED.
TELL ME BOSS, "IT'S OKAY, MY SON
HAS AN EARRING, WE'RE ALL FREE,
MAN."
>> IT'S AN EARRING, MOST PEOPLE
THINK THEY'RE, LIKE, COOL.
>> OH, OH, IT'S COOL.
WE'RE BEING COOL?
HEY, I WANT TO BE COOL.
WOULD IT BE COOL IF I START
PEEING ON THE FLOOR?
I'LL PEE ON THE FLOOR NOW, THAT
WORK FOR YOU?
>> YEAH, I WANT TO BE COOL TOO.
MAYBE ONE DAY I'LL BRING A GOAT
HOME, STICK A GUN TO ITS HEAD,
AND BLOW ITS LITTLE BRAINS OUT.
THAT'S PRETTY FRICKIN' COOL,
HUH?
>> ARE YOU UPSET BECAUSE YOU
THINK THIS MAKES ME GAY?
I'M NOT BY THE WAY, BUT YOU'RE
BEING EXTREMELY HOMOPHOBIC RIGHT
NOW.
>> POLY SIGH MAJOR GOT US GOOD.
"COLLEGE STUDENT OWNS BEN"
SHAPIRO."
>> DO YOU THINK WE'RE
HOMOPHOBIC?
YOUR FATHER'S BEEN GAY FOR 15
YEARS.
>> IT'S A SMALL EARRING.
I GOT IT WITH A BUNCH OF MY
FRIENDS.
>> WHO'S THE CHICK?
>> WHAT CHICK?
>> THE BISEXUAL WOMAN YOU'RE
TRYING TO IMPRESS.
I HOPE HER MULLET IS WICKED
COOL.
>> YEAH.
DOES HER CARPET MATCH HER
DRAPES?
BLUE?
>> FOR YOUR INFORMATION, THE
GIRL I'M DATING IS JUST
STRAIGHT.
>> AND YOU KNOW, FOR YOUR
INFORMATION, DINNER TONIGHT IS A
HUMAN PERSON, BECAUSE CHICKEN IS
LAME, DUDE!
>> METALLICA ENOUGH FOR YOU?
>> WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
IT'S A PIECE OF JEWELRY, WHO
CARES?
>> OH, WHO CARES?
>> WHO CARES?
>> NOTHING MATTERS, WE'RE ALL
JUST DUST, MAN.
>> YEAH, PASS THE GRAFFITI,
DUDE.
>> HONEY, CANCEL MY DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TOMORROW, I WANT A
SEX WORKER TO TAKE MY
CHOLESTEROL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> YEAH, "F" THE PIGS, AND LET'S
LIGHT UP, DUDE.
>> COME ON.
>> I REALLY DIDN'T EVEN THINK
YOU'D NOTICE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO HURT ANYONE'S
FEELINGS.
WHAT I WANTED TO TELL YOU
TONIGHT IS THAT I ACTUALLY CHOSE
A MAJOR.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> WHAT IS IT, SON?
>> ART HISTORY.
>> OH, BRAVA, BRAVA.
>> I GUESS THERE'S NOTHING
COOLER THAN HURTING YOUR OWN
MOTHER.
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT IF I
ROUNDHOUSE KICKED NANA IN THE
STOMACH.
NANA, CAN YOU COME IN HERE FOR A
SECOND?
>> I'M SO HAPPY WE COULD ALL BE
TOGETHER FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
AAHHH!
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> WHAT, JUST BEING COOL, MAN.
I WANT TO GET HIGH!
I WISH MY EARS WERE ALL SHINY
AND HIGH!
>> GROW UP.
>> YOUR MOTHER HASN'T SLEPT IN
WEEKS.
>> YOU JUST FOUND OUT ABOUT THE
EARRING.
>> HEY, HEY, LOOK.
I GOT AN EARRING TOO!
CAN I GO TO THE KETAMINE PARTY
NOW, PIMP?
>> WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
HE'S JUST EXPRESSING HIMSELF.
AAHHH!
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, GUYS?
ENOUGH.
YOU'RE MY PARENTS, AND YOU
SHOULD LOVE ME NO MATTER WHAT.
EARRING OR NO EARRING.
I'M YOUR KID AND THAT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH.
>> HONEY, WHAT CAN WE DO WITH
YOU?
WE'RE JUST WORRIED.
>> YEAH, BUD.
YOU'RE OUR OLDEST SON, WE DON'T
WANT YOU SETTING A BAD EXAMPLE
FOR YOUR LITTLE BROTHER.
>> THERE HE IS NOW.
>> I SMELL CHICKEN!
>> THAT'S DIFFERENT, HE LOOKS
GOOD.
>> "GLADIATOR II" IS THE HIT.
300 MILLIONS
THEN WE SAW THE BOX OFFICE FOR
WICKED AND "MOANA 2."
SO "GLADIATOR II" IS NOW --
A MUSICAL.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN A PLACE SUCH
AS THIS.
>> OF COURSE YOU HAVEN'T.
¶ THERE'S NO PLACE
NO PLACE LIKE ROME ¶
SWORDS
¶ HORDES AND SCANDALS
AND EMPIRE
STRETCHING FROM EAST TO WEST ¶
WINE SPILL
¶ THAT GIRAFFE YOU CAN KILL IT
EVERY SENATOR HAS A BOY TO
MOLEST ¶
¶ OUR STREETS ARE THE CLEANEST
OUR SOLDIERS THE MEANEST ¶
¶ AND ALL OF THEM A TINY PENIS ¶
¶ THERE'S NO PLACE
NO PLACE LIKE ROME ¶
>> YEAH, I THINK I'M GOING TO
LIKE IT HERE.
>> IT'S THE SAME VIOLENT
HISTORICAL EPIC AUDIENCES HAVE
BEEN RAVING ABOUT
WITH AN EXTRA
15 MINUTES OF SONGS.
¶ THEY LOOK AT ME AND ALL THEY SEE
IS A KILLING MACHINE ¶
¶ BUT THEY DON'T KNOW THAT FAR
BELOW
I'M SO MUCH MORE THAN I
SEEM ¶
¶ THEY CALL ME GLADIATOR
THEY CALL ME SLAVE ¶
¶ THEY CALL ME A KILLER
BUT SOMEDAY THEY'LL KNOW MY NAME ¶
¶ I'M GONNA STAB MY WAY TO
FREEDOM ¶
¶ CUT MY WAY TO THE NEXT ACT ¶
¶ WHILE I'M IN THE COLOSSEUM
WHEN I GO ON THE ATTACK ¶
¶ SOMEDAY THEY'LL KNOW MY NAME ¶
>> "I WAS NOT TOLD ABOUT THIS"
RAVES THE DIRECTOR RIDLEY SCOTT.
GLOWS
"MOVIES ARE IN SUCH A WEIRD"
PLACE RIGHT NOW."
LADIES, WE'VE GOT A SONG FOR YOU
TOO.
¶ I'M THE BEAUTIFUL WIFE BACK
HOME ON A FARM ¶
¶ EVERY DAY I STAND ON THE EDGE
OF MY FARM ¶
¶ WITH MY TINY SON
AND WAIT FOR MY HUSBAND TO COME HOME LIKE
THIS ¶
ONE DAY
I SEE ARMY MEN IN THE DISTANCE
THEY'RE APPROACHING WITH
TORCHES ¶
¶ WELL I GUESS THEY'RE FRIENDS
WITH MY HUSBAND ¶
¶ I HAVE A GOOD FEELING ABOUT
THIS ¶
>> WE EVEN HIRED LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA
FOR ONE OF HIS CLASSIC
BROADWAY RAPS.
>> SILENCE.
ROME'S EMPEROR SHALL DECIDE
THE
GLADIATOR'S FATE.
¶ EVERYBODY IN THE COLOSSEUM
PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR AND LET ME
SEE THEM ¶
¶ I'M THE MAD EMPEROR WITH THE
BAD TEMPER ¶
¶ EUNUCHS AND TUNICS ¶
¶ AND I DON'T MEAN TO BE A HATER
BUT I AIN'T LIKE THIS
GLADIATOR ¶
¶ SO SAY GOOD-BYE TO THIS CLOWN
'CAUSE MY THUMB IS GOING DOWN ¶
¶ LOOK AT HIM WITH HIS WINE IN
HIS CUP ¶
THUMB UP
¶ WHAT HE THINK HE A BOSS LIKE
ME ¶
¶ LET'S SEE IF HE CAN FLUFF LIKE
>> WE'VE EVEN ADDED SOME
CHARACTERS.
¶ I'M JUST A CHRISTIAN
AND BOY AM I WISHING I KEPT MY BIG MOUTH
SHUT ¶
¶ 'CAUSE AIN'T NO USE IN TRYING
TO OUTRUN A LION ¶
CONDEMNED
¶ THERE'S NO PLACE
NO PLACE LIKE ROME ¶¶
>> "GLADIATOR TWOSICAL."
>>> CAN I PHYSICAL SOMETHING?
THIS IS MY FIRST COMMERCIAL.
I'VE ONLY EVER DONE LOCAL
THEATER.
>> YOU'LL BE FINE.
WE ALL GET IT EVENTUALLY.
I ACTUALLY WORKED WITH JAKE ON A
FEW SPOTS BEFORE, HE'S EASY.
HEY, JAKE, NEWBIE HERE.
>> WE'LL TAKE IT EASY ON YOU,
THEN.
CRAIG, GREAT TO SEE YOU.
EVERYBODY KNOW THE SCRIPT?
>> YES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> PERFECT, LET'S TRY ONE, ALL
RIGHT?
ROLL IT!
>> CAPINELLI'S TAKE ONE.
>> AT CAPINELLI'S, IT'S EASY TO
FALL IN LOVE.
>> BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
PASTAS TO ADOVE.
RIGATONI.
FETTUCINI.
>> TAG LA TELLY.
FARFALLE.
CHOOSE WHATEVER YOUR HEART
DESIRES.
>> AND IMAGINE THE
PASTA-BILITIES.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> LET'S CUT, LET'S CUT.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO SAY
POSSIBILITIES.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> IT WAS PRETTY FUNNY.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
IMAGINE THE PASTA-BILITIES?
>> YES, I DID.
WHAT IS THAT CALLED, IMPROV?
>> IT WAS HILARIOUS.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> THANKS.
I MEAN, I NEVER DO STUFF LIKE
THIS, HONESTLY, THAT WOULD BE
IM-PASTA-BLE.
>> I DON'T KNOW, IT'S FUNNY BUT
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE ROMANTIC.
IT'S NOT A COMEDY.
>> YEAH.
OF COURSE.
>> OKAY, THAT'S JUST WHAT I
THOUGHT BUT SHE'S NEW.
>> WHAT?
MAYBE WE TRY ONE AND KEEP THE
LINE?
>> KEEP IT?
ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, EVERYBODY LOVED IT,
RIGHT?
>> THIS IS THE KIND OF SET WHERE
WE IMPROVISE WHENEVER, RIGHT?
>> GO WITH IT, CRAIG, BE AN
ACTOR.
ROLL IT!
>> CAPINELLI'S TAKE TWO.
>> AT CAPINELLI'S, IT'S EASY TO
FALL IN LOVE.
>> BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
PASTAS TO ADORE.
RIGATONI, FETTUCINI.
>> TAGLIATELLE, FARFALLE.
CHOOSE YOUR FAVORITE.
SPAGHETTI OR NOT, HERE WE COME.
>> CUT!
WOW.
CRAIG, BUDDY, DID YOU FORGET
YOUR LINE?
>> NO, I'M SORRY, I JUST THOUGHT
I'D TRY SOMETHING.
>> AND IT WAS FUNNY.
>> NO, DON'T DO THAT.
>> LET'S JUST STICK TO THE
SCRIPT, OKAY, PEOPLE?
>> OKAY, RIGHT, BUT SHE JUST
ADDED THAT NEW LINE --
>> YEAH, I DID, I'M SORRY.
I MESSED UP THE WHOLE RHYTHM.
I'M BEING "PRE-PASTA-ROUS."
SORRY, I CAN'T STOP, I CAN'T
STOP.
>> DAMN, ARE YOU A WRITER OR
SOMETHING?
>> SHE'S NOT.
>> NO, NO, THEY'RE JUST SPILLING
OUT OF ME.
I THINK I'M FEELING A
LITTLE "SAUCY."
>> YOU'RE A COMEDY MACHINE!
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY.
SPAGHETTI OR NOT, WE'RE GOING TO
KILL YOU.
>> GREAT.
LET'S DO ANOTHER ONE.
LAUGH LAUGH
>>> GREAT, LET'S DO ANOTHER ONE.
>> I'M LEARNING SO MUCH FROM
YOU --
>> SHUT UP.
>> LET'S GO A LITTLE TIGHT THEY
ARE TIME.
REALLY FOCUS ON THE TALENT,
PLEASE.
OKAY.
>> CAPINELLI'S, TAKE THREE.
>> AT CAPINELLI'S, IT'S EASY TO
FALL IN LOVE -- AM I ON CAMERA?
>> YEAH, BUDDY, YOU LOOK GREAT,
KEEP GOING.
>> BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
PASTAS TO ADORE.
RIGATONI.
FETTUCINI.
>> AND SAY PASTA LA VISTA, BABY.
TO HUNGER.
>> CUT!
CRAIG?
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING, BUDDY?
IS THERE SOMEONE WE CAN CALL?
>> WHERE DID YOU GET A PAIR OF
SUNGLASS IN THIS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SORRY, I JUST -- YOU
AUDITION, THEN YOU MEMORIZE THE
SCRIPT --
>> HEY, CRAIG, YOU'RE DOING
GREAT.
>> NO, WILL YOU STOP THAT?
>> HEY.
HEY.
YOU ARE A GREAT ACTOR.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY.
THIS TOO SHALL "PASTA."
>> I WILL SMACK YOU RIGHT IN THE
FACE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> CRAIG, CHILL OUT.
>> IS THERE SOMEBODY TALKING
PASTA?
>> MR. CAPINELLI!
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ME, MARIO CAPINELLI.
NOW, I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU TWOS
FROM THE BACK.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS A LITTLE
BOY, BACK IN FAR SAN MARTINO, MY
NONA WOULD SPEND ALL DAY MAKING
THE MOST WONDERFUL PASTAS.
WHEN THE PASTA WAS JUST
PERFECTO, SHE WOULD TURN TO ME
AND SAY, "MARIO --
SPAGHETTI OR NOT, WE'RE GOING TO
KILL YOU."
AND I WOULD CUT ON MY SUN
SUNGLASSES AND I'D SAY, "PASTA
LA VISTA, BABY."
WHO IS THE MAN WHO JUST SAID
THIS?
WHO IS THIS MAN WHO HAS BEEN
TOUCHED BY GOD?
>> THAT'S ME.
I DID.
>> THEN YOU, MY FRIEND, ARE A
GENIUS.
KEEP IT ON!
>> WELL, I AM JUST
PASTA-TIVELY DELIGHTED!
>> DON'T.
PAUL
I WISH HE'D
CRUSH MY HEAD LIKE A WATERMELON
BETWEEN HIS TWO GORGEOUS THIGHS.
SO
>> YEAH, MY GIRLFRIEND IS
HILARIOUS.
THIS IS SO FUN, MAN.
YOU'RE SO DOWN TO EARTH.
A LOT OF TIMES WHEN SERIOUS ACTORS HOST,
THEY CAN BE KIND OF
A LOT.
>> NO, I GET IT.
ACTORS, WE CAN BE AN EMOTIONAL
BUNCH.
I DON'T KNOW, I'M JUST -- I'M
JUST TRYING TO KEEP IT LOW-KEY
THIS WEEK.
>> YEAH, DUDE, WE'RE PUMPED.
WE'RE HUGE FANS, WE LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE ME?
WOW.
>> TOTALLY.
ANYWAY, WE HAVE SOME SKETCH
IDEAS --
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS TOO.
>> GREAT, YEAH.
>> SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE
THAT WEIRD OR ANYTHING.
>> NO.
>> NO WORRIES, MAN.
>> I LOVE YOU GUYS.
I THINK I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
>> WE LOVE YOU TOO.
BUT WE DID HAVE SOME SKETCHES WE
WANTED TO PITCH YOU.
>> YEAH, YEAH, NO, DEFINITELY.
I BET YOU GUYS ARE COOKING UP
SOMETHING GOOD, HUH?
>> NO ONE WILL EVER HURT YOU
WHEN I'M AROUND.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, BROTHER?
GREAT
>> MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT, MAYBE WE
SHOULD MOVE IN TOGETHER.
>> DID WE SAY THAT?
>> WHAT IS THIS, MAN?
IS THIS A SEX THING?
>> WHAT?
COME ON.
IN TIME, MAYBE, YES.
>> YOU WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH
THAT?
YOU'RE BETTER OFF ASKING MY
GIRLFRIEND, BUDDY.
>> IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
PAUL, I THINK GENUINELY MAYBE GO
MEET WITH OTHER WRITERS OR
SOMETHING.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD JUST GO.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> WHAT IF I JUST STAYED?
>> I WOULD JUST GO, PROBABLY.
>> WE COULD BUILD A LIFE
TOGETHER.
I CAN SEE IT SO CLEARLY.
THE FOUR OF US IN OUR PERFECT
LITTLE CABIN.
LOOK, BOYS, IT'S SNOWING.
>> WOW!
>> IT WOULD BE SIMPLE.
I'D PROTECT YOU.
>> WHEREVER COULD THEY BE?
>> CHERISH YOU.
HELP YOU GROW.
>> SO YOU'D BE LIKE OUR DAD?
>> OH.
DADDY.
TEACH YOU HOW TO HUNT.
HOW TO BE A MAN.
AND YOU, YOU'D TEACH ME WHAT
LIFE'S REALLY ABOUT.
SURE, I'LL HAVE TO LEAVE FOR
WORK SOMETIMES.
BUT I WILL ALWAYS COME HOME.
>> PAUL'S BACK!
HE'S BACK FROM PLAYING ANOTHER
SAD HOT GUY!
>> IT WILL BE OUR LITTLE SLICE
OF PARADISE.
UNTIL THE TOWNSPEOPLE FOUND OUT.
HIDE
>> WHY ARE THEY HERE?
>> THE LOCAL MILITIA DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND FOLKS LIKE US.
>> PAUL?
WHY DO PEOPLE HATE?
>> BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW LOVE
LIKE WE DO.
STAY HERE.
>> PAPA!
>> WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
>> THAT'S OUR DADDY.
>> AND THAT'S OUR LIFE.
IT AIN'T PERFECT.
BUT IT'S OURS.
>> HEY, GUYS, DID YOU WANT TO
WRITE THE --
NOPE.
>> GOOD NIGHT, SWEET BOYS.
>>> SO EXCITING, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> IT'S JUST A THING YOU SAY.
SO LADIES, BUCKLE UP.
THIS IS AN ALL-MALE REVUE, AND I
THINK IT'S GOING TO BE PRETTY
SEXY.
>> OH, LIKE "MAGIC MIKE"?
>> EXACTLY.
BURLY GUYS RIPPED FOR HER
PLEASURE.
>> MARGIE, YOU KNOW ME SO WELL,
I LOVE GUYS.
>> OH, OH, IT'S STARTING.
>> EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEATS AND
WELCOME TO THE STAGE THE CAST OF
TREASURE GUYLAND.
>> WELCOME!
>> TAKE IT OFF!
TAKE IT OFF!
>> GOOD NEWS, MEN!
WE CAUGHT THE TRADES.
WE SALE FOR THE SPANISH MAIN.
OUR GALLEON IS HEAVY WITH
SILVER.
>> TOMORROW WE SAIL FOR NASSAU!
>> WE'LL SPEND OUR SILVER ON
WHORES AND DRINK!
>> WOW.
THEY'RE REALLY LEANING INTO THE
CHARACTERS.
>> AND THERE'S A LOT OF
INFORMATION.
>> THEY'RE CUTE, THOUGH.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEIR PIRATE
BOOTY.
>> KEEP ON THE LOOKOUT, MEN.
THE SPANISH MAIN IS NO SAFE SEA
FOR BRIGANDS SUCH AS US.
>> SPEAK FOR YOURSELF, ROGUE.
I'M NO PIRATE, I'M A PRIVATEER.
I'VE A LETTER FROM THE QUEEN OF
ENGLAND.
>> MIGHT AS WELL WIPE YOUR ARSE
WITH IT!
HA HA HA!
>> NEVER MIND THAT.
WE'LL TAKE ON PROVISIONS IN
HISPANIOLA THEN SAIL FOR PORT
ROYALE.
AND THEN -- TO BERMUDA!
>> TWO, THREE, FOUR!
>> WAIT, WHY DOES THE SHOW HAVE
SO MUCH DETAIL?
>> I KNOW.
SHOUT-OUT TO THE PORT ROYALE
NAME CHECK, RIGHT?
I KIND OF THOUGHT THEY'D BE
DRESSED SEXY AND WOULDN'T TALK A
TON.
>> I KNOW, COME ON, TAKE YOUR
CLOTHES OFF, SHOW US SOME SKIN!
>> 'TIS WARM IN THE SCORCHING
SUN, MEN.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW YOU.
BUT FIRST, LET ME REMOVE MY
SHIRT.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> IS IT MY END?
>> CUR VERY.
HE'LL BE DEAD IN A WEEK.
THROW HIM OVERBOARD.
>> NO!
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
>> I THINK THEY THREW THE SICK
ONE OUT TO SEA.
>> YEAH, LIKE HE STILL HAD LIFE
IN HIM, BUT IT WASN'T WORTH
GIVING HIM FIVE DAYS' RATIONS OF
SALTED PORK.
BETTER TO SAVE THOSE FOR THE
HEALTHY MEN.
>> WHAT?
>> LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE AT SEA
DOESN'T MEAN THERE ISN'T TIME
FOR ROMANCE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
>> A BUXOM BEAUTY!
>> HEY, CAPTAIN!
>> ARE THEY GOING TO TAKE TURNS
WITH THE GUY WITH THE MOP ON HIS
HEAD?
JESUS.
>> SHOULD WE GO?
>> I'M GOING TO STAY.
I'M REALLY INTO THE GOLDEN AGE
OF PIRACY AND EVERYTHING ABOUT
THIS IS 100% AUTHENTIC.
COSTUMES RIGHT.
ISLAND TERMS.
I'M HORNY AS HELL.
>> AND NOW, OUR SPECIAL GUEST.
AMY FROM DES MOINES.
>> OH!
OKAY!
>> AMY!
>> AS SHE FINDS HER WAY TO OUR
SHIP, WE'LL TREAT YOU LASSES TO
A FEAST FOR THE EYES.
ROGER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, I KNOW WHAT YOU
LADIES WANT TO SEE.
>> TWO PEG LEGS?
NO.
>> HI, HI, EVERYONE.
>> THERE'S A WOMAN ON THE SHIP!
>> MUST BE A SPY FOR THE ROYAL
NAVY.
>> LET'S TIE HER UP.
>> OKAY, I DON'T HATE IT.
>> YES, AMY!
>> DO YOU OW THE PENALTY FOR
SNEAKING ON A SHIP?
>> I THINK I KNOW WHERE THIS IS
GOING.
>> YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
>> TO THE BED CHAMBER!
>> NO.
>> AMY!
>> HEY, LET'S JUST GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT!
NOW LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
COVER OURSELVES IN OIL AND SWAB
THE DECK IN THE NUDE.
¶ MAN, WHAT A HELL OF A YEAR
IT'S BEEN
KEEP ON BLUFFIN'
BUT I JUST CAN'T WIN ¶
¶ DROWNED MY SORROWS
BUT THEY LEARNED TO SWIM
MAN, WHAT A HELL OF A YEAR
IT'S BEEN ¶
¶ HEAD IN THE BOTTLE
BUT MY HEART IN THE CAGE
YEAH IT'S GETTIN' HARDER
TO ACT MY AGE ¶
¶ PLAY A SAD SONG
ON A TINY VIOLIN
FOR THE MAN AT THE BAR
CONFESSIN' HIS SINS ¶
¶ I NEED SOME GOOD NEWS
SITTIN' HERE
SIPPIN' ON COLD TRUTH ¶
¶ NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT I'M GOIN' THROUGH
BET THE DEVIL WOULDN'T
WALK IN MY SHOES ¶
¶ WISH SOMEONE TOLD ME
LIVIN' THIS LIFE
WOULD BE LONELY ¶
¶ I'M TRYNA GET AWAY
FROM THE OLD ME
I'M STILL STUCK SINGIN'
THESE BLUES ¶
¶ ALL I REALLY NEED
IS A LITTLE GOOD NEWS ¶
¶ LOVE KEEPS KNOCKIN'
BUT I JUST STAY HOME ¶
¶ I AIN'T PICKIN' NO FLOWERS
FROM THE SEEDS
THAT I'VE SOWN ¶
¶ THEY SAY IT GETS DARKER
WHEN YOU'RE COVERIN'
THEM DOORS ¶
¶ STILL LOOKIN' FOR
THE RIGHT AT THE
END OF MY WRONGS
AT THE END OF MY WRONGS ¶
¶ I NEED SOME GOOD NEWS
SITTIN' HERE
SIPPIN' ON COLD TRUTH ¶
¶ NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT I'M GOIN' THROUGH
BET THE DEVIL WOULDN'T
WALK IN MY SHOES ¶
¶ WISH SOMEONE TOLD ME
LIVIN' THIS LIFE
WOULD BE LONELY ¶
¶ I'M TRYNA GET AWAY
FROM THE OLD ME
I'M STILL STUCK SINGIN'
THESE BLUES ¶
¶ ALL I REALLY NEED
IS A LITTLE GOOD NEWS ¶
¶ I NEED SOME GOOD NEWS
SITTIN' HERE
SIPPIN' ON COLD TRUTH ¶
¶ NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT I'M GOIN' THROUGH
BET THE DEVIL WOULDN'T
WALK IN MY SHOES ¶
¶ WISH SOMEONE TOLD ME
LIVIN' THIS LIFE
WOULD BE LONELY ¶
¶ I'M TRYNA GET AWAY
FROM THE OLD ME
I'M STILL STUCK SINGIN'
THESE BLUES ¶
¶ ALL I REALLY NEED
IS A LITTLE GOOD NEWS
ALL I REALLY NEED
IS A LITTLE ¶
¶ SOMETHIN' BRING ME BACK
TO THE MIDDLE
ALL I REALLY NEED
IS A LITTLE GOOD NEWS ¶¶
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OKAY.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE, WELCOME TO
WEEKEND UPDATE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
NEW YORK CITY OFFICIALS SENT A
TOUGH MESSAGE ON CRIME.
YOU SHOOT SOMEBODY IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE STREET,
YOU BETTER GET ON
YOUR BIKE, HOP ON A BUS,
AND GET
THE HECK OUT OF HERE, MISTER.
THE MANHUNT CONTINUES FOR THE ASSASSIN
WHO GUNNED DOWN A CEO
OF UNITED HEALTH CARE ON
WEDNESDAY.
AND IT REALLY SAYS SOMETHING ABOUT AMERICA
THAT A GUY WAS
MURDERED IN COLD BLOOD AND THE
TWO MAIN REACTIONS WERE,
"YEAH,
WELL HEALTH CARE STINKS."
AND ALSO, "GIRL THAT SHOOTER
HOT."
IT'S ALSO SO CRAZY THAT THE
SHOOTING HAPPENED
THREE BLOCKS
FROM HERE IN BROAD DAYLIGHT,
AND
THE GUY JUST BICYCLES AWAY.
PROBABLY BECAUSE THEY HAVE EVERY
COP IN THE CITY GUARDING OUR
CHRISTMAS TREE.
NYPD NOW BELIEVES THE SUSPECT
LEFT THE CITY ON A BUS FROM PORT
AUTHORITY.
THANKS, BUT A PORT AUTHORITY
PASSENGER WHO LOOKS LIKE A MURDERER
ACTUALLY WIDENS THE
SEARCH.
>> NEW YORK CITY POLICE SAY THEY
WERE ABLE TO GET THE SMILING PICTURE OF THE SUSPECT
AFTER THE
MAN APPARENTLY WAS CAUGHT ON
CAMERA AT A LOCAL HOSTEL
FLIRTING WITH A FEMALE EMPLOYEE
WHOSE NAME HAS BEEN REPORTED AS
LUCKY S. BECHALIVE.
>>> PRESIDENT STILL...
BIDEN HAS ISSUED A
FULL PARDON FOR HIS SON, HUNTER,
JUST WEEKS BEFORE HE WAS TO BE
SENTENCED ON GUN CHARGES AND TAX
EVASION.
HUNTER CELEBRATED HIS FATHER'S
DECISION
BY CELEBRATING WAY LESS
THAN HE USED TO.
HE JUST HAD A WARM GLASS OF
MILK.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED IN 2018, THE
MOTHER OF PETE HEGSETH,
TRUMP'S NOMINEE FOR DEFENSE SECRETARY,
SENT HER SON AN EMAIL
SAYING SHE WAS EMBARRASSED
BY THE WAY HE REPEATEDLY BELITTLED, LIES, CHEATS,
AND USES WOMEN FOR
HIS OWN POWER AND EGO.
TO WHICH PETE HEGSETH RESPONDED,
BITCH, SHUT UP.
HEGSETH, WHO HAS BEEN ACCUSED OF
EXCESSIVE DRINKING AT WORK,
SAID
THAT IF HE IS CONFIRMED AS
DEFENSE SECRETARY,
HE IS, QUOTE,
NOT GOING TO HAVE A DRINK AT
ALL.
BUT IF HE ISN'T CONFIRMED, LOOK
OUT.
>>> FBI DIRECTOR NOMINEE KASH PATEL,
SEEN HERE REALIZING IT
WASN'T JUST A FART --
WAS REPORTEDLY THE TARGET OF AN
IRANIAN CYBER ATTACK.
APPARENTLY THEY WERE ABLE TO
GUESS PATEL'S PASSWORD
BECAUSE
IT WAS JUST TWO EYES REALLY
CLOSE TOGETHER.
DONALD TRUMP HAS PICKED FORMER
CONGRESSMAN BILLY LONG TO LEAD
THE IRS.
TRUMP CONSIDERED A LOT OF
CANDIDATES,
BUT BILLY LONG WAS
JUST HEAD AND SHOULDERS --
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE UNVEILED ITS
CHRISTMAS DECORATION SCHEME,
A
SEASON OF PEACE AND LIGHT.
WHICH IS TOUGH, BECAUSE BIDEN IS
ALWAYS BEING TOLD
NOT TO GO
TOWARDS THE LIGHT.
>>> PRESIDENT BIDEN TRAVELED TO
AFRICA THIS WEEK.
UNFORTUNATELY, HE SAID IT WAS TO
VISIT THE BIRTHPLACE OF HIS
FRIEND, BARACK.
IT'S THE '90s, RELAX.
>> IT'S THE '90s.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED CHINESE
HACKERS HAVE INFILTRATED AT&T AND VERIZON
TO SPY ON AMERICAN CUSTOMERS,
WHICH HAS GOT TO BE
THE FIRST TIME ANYONE'S EVER SAID,
"THANK GOD I HAVE SPRINT."
>>> DONALD TRUMP TODAY MADE HIS
FIRST TRIP ABROAD SINCE THE ELECTION,
TRAVELING TO PARIS FOR
THE REOPENING OF THE NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL
WHERE HE RANG THE
BELL.
>>> SCIENTISTS IN JAPAN HAVE
LAUNCHED THE FIRST-EVER
SATELLITE MADE OUT OF WOOD.
GREAT.
NOW ALIENS ARE GOING TO THINK
WE'RE POOR.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU,
MAN?
>>> A WOMAN HAS FILED A LAWSUIT
AGAINST DIDDY,
ACCUSING HIM OF
ASSAULT AND DANGLING HER OFF A
17-STORY BALCONY,
WHICH IS JUST
INCREDIBLE GRIP STRENGTH
FOR A
GUY COATED IN BABY OIL.
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW SURVEY,
56% OF AMERICANS SAY
THAT ALONE
TIME IS CRITICAL TO THEIR MENTAL
WELL-BEING.
JUST SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT
BEFORE YOU ASK TO STAY FOR
BREAKFAST.
>> WE'RE REALLY LEARNING A LOT
ABOUT YOU.
>> OH, NO.
>>> A MAN IN CANADA SAVED HIS
WIFE AFTER A POLAR BEAR LUNGED AT HER,
AND HE LEAPT ONTO THE
BEAR'S BACK SHOUTING, "FINISH
HER!"
>> ALL RIGHT, LOOK, BEFORE I
TELL THIS NEXT JOKE,
I JUST WANT
EVERYBODY TO KNOW THAT IT MIGHT
NOT BE FUNNY,
BUT IT IS
OBJECTIVELY A VERY SMART JOKE.
SO IF YOU DON'T LAUGH, IT MEANS
YOU'RE DUMB.
OKAY, HERE IT IS.
NATIONAL PRETEND TO BE A TIME
TRAVELER DAY WAS TOMORROW.
THANK
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> NEW RESEARCH SUGGESTS THAT
52% OF PEOPLE
VISITING THEIR
FAMILIES FOR THE HOLIDAY
PLAN TO
HAVE SEX IN THEIR CHILDHOOD
HOME.
EXCELLENT, SAID ELF ON THE
SHELF.
>> OH, MAN, YOU NASTY.
>>> POLICE IN AUSTRALIA ARRESTED
13 PEOPLE AFTER THEIR BOAT BROKE DOWN
AND MORE THAN TWO TONS OF
COCAINE WAS DISCOVERED ON BOARD.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES WHEN YOU HAVE
TOO MUCH COKE, YOUR DINGHY STOPS
WORKING.
THAT'S A -- THAT'S NOT A SMART
JOKE.
>> THIS IS.
SCIENTISTS...
>>> SCIENTISTS HAVE USED
HIGH-SPEED VIDEO TO STUDY HOW
THE SQUIRTING CUCUMBER
EXPLOSIVELY SHOOTS OUT ITS
SEEDS.
REACHED FOR COMMENT, SCIENTISTS
QUICKLY CLOSED THEIR LAPTOPS
AND
SHOUTED, "DON'T COME IN HERE."
MY BIGGER QUESTION IS WHY THE
SQUIRTING CUCUMBER SOUNDS LIKE
THIS.
>>> WE'RE ALMOST THROUGH THE
REGULAR SEASON OF THE NFL,
AND
MANY NEW STARS HAVE EMERGED IN
THE LEAGUE.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT NAVIGATING
OVERNIGHT SUCCESS
IS A MOM WHOSE
SON JUST GOT FAMOUS.
>> HI, BODIE.
HI, MELISSA.
>> IT'S MAYLISSA.
THIS JOKE ABOUT CUCUMBERS
SQUIRTING?
Y'ALL ARE WRONG FOR THAT.
>> BODIE, YOU SIGNED A PRETTY
BIG CONTRACT WITH THE PANTHERS.
>> YES, SIR.
GOD IS GOOD.
>> GOD IS GREAT, Y'ALL.
OKAY.
SO THIS IS BALMAINE.
UGLIES
I'M SCOOTING IN LOUBOUTIN.
THANK YOU.
THINKING OF, WHERE'S THE
CHANGING ROOM FOR SHABOOZEY?
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO GET LAID.
I AM LOVING THIS LIFE.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE IT.
IMAGINE HAVING A SON IN THE NFL
COMES WITH A PRICE?
>> YES.
IT WAS A SACRIFICE.
MY SON COMMITTED HIMSELF TO THIS SO HARD,
HE HAD TO SACRIFICE
HAVING A PERSONALITY.
>> TRUST THE PROCESS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
NOTHING BEHIND THOSE EYES.
BUT MY BABY'S A BALLER.
LOOK AT THE VIP BRACELET.
I'M ABOUT TO SHOW SHABOOZEY MY
SHAPOOTSY, OKAY?
TRUST THAT PROCESS.
>> COOL.
BODIE --
I HEARD YOU HAVE AN EXCITING
OPPORTUNITY COMING UP?
>> YEAH, I'M DOING A COMMERCIAL,
ALL PRAISE TO THE LORD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
OKAY.
THAT'S MY BABY.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE NEW FACE
OF CRAZY BREAD, ALL RIGHT?
LITTLE CAESAR'S, Y'ALL.
SAY YOUR BIG LINE.
>> PIZZA COMMA PIZZA.
>> DON'T SAY THE COMMA, BABY, WE
TALKED ABOUT THIS.
>> PIZZA NO COMMA PIZZA.
>> CLOSE ENOUGH.
Y'ALL, MONEY IS FALLING OUT THE
SKY, OKAY?
MAMA KELSEY, STEP ASIDE, THERE'S
A NEW MAMA IN TOWN, MAMA DOOKIE.
>> YOUR LAST NAME IS DOOKIE?
>> YES.
MY SECOND HUSBAND'S NAME WAS
DOOKIE, DeVONTE DOOKIE, RIGHT
TACKLE FOR THE FALCONS, DIED OF
IBS.
>> I MISS YOU, DADDY DOOKIE.
>> BUT I'M SURE Y'ALL WANT TO
GET YOUR HEADLINE.
WHO IS MAMA DOOKIE DATING NOW?
>> NOBODY IS ASKING THAT.
>> YES, I WAS SPOTTED AT
EINSTEIN BROTHERS BAGELS WITH
MANNY FROM "MODERN FAMILY."
OH, SHUT UP.
HE'S 27, Y'ALL.
>> TRUST THE PROCESS.
>> YOU KNOW, NOT TO BE RUDE,
SOME PEOPLE SHOULDN'T EVER
BECOME RICH.
>> WHAT?
WHY IS THE CAMERA ON ME?
>> BODIE, THE AVERAGE NFL CAREER
IS THREE YEARS.
THINGS ARE GOOD FOR YOU NOW, BUT
WHAT WILL YOU DO IF ALL THIS
COMES TO AN END?
>> LET'S JUST SAY I MIGHT NEED
TO MAKE ANOTHER SHABABY.
BUT SERIOUSLY, BABY, WHAT DO WE
ALWAYS SAY?
>> WE -- ARE -- DOOKIES.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU SAY?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE -- ARE -- DOOKIES.
WE DO NOT CRUMBLE.
>> EVEN WHEN YOU PUT THE SQUEEZE
ON US, WE STAY SOLID DOOKIES.
>> THE DOOKIE FAMILY, EVERYBODY.
>> HEY, SHABOOZEY!
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
YOU FEELING?
A LITTLE NERVOUS?
>> YES.
VERY NERVOUS.
YOU HAVEN'T ARGUED MY CASE AT
ALL.
THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE DONE IS
TOLD ME TO WEAR THIS INSANE
OUTFIT TODAY.
WHY?
>> RELAX.
I HAVE A PLAN.
IT WILL ALL MAKE SENSE IN A
MOMENT.
>> ALL RISE.
I NOW CALL THIS COURT BACK IN
SESSION.
MR. LANDON, WILL THE DEFENSE
CALL ANY WITNESSES BEFORE YOU
REST?
>> YES, YOUR HONOR.
WE'D LIKE TO CALL THE ONLY
WITNESS TO THE CRIME MY CLIENT
IS CHARGED WITH BACK TO THE
STAND.
MISS NANCY SHANE.
>> OBJECTION, YOUR HONOR.
THE DEFENSE COULD HAVE
QUESTIONED MISS SHANE WHEN WE
CALLED HER TO THE STAND, BUT
THEY DECLINED.
>> I'M ALLOWED TO CALL WHOEVER I
WANT.
YOUR HONOR, I PROMISE, THIS WILL
ALL MAKE SENSE IN A MOMENT.
>> WE'LL ALLOW IT.
COUNSEL, THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
MISS SHANE?
>> NOW, MISS SHANE, YOU SAW THE
ROBBERY IN QUESTION TAKE PLACE,
YES?
>> YES, SIR, I DID.
>> YES, SIR, SHE DID.
AND YOU SAW THE MAN WHO
COMMITTED THIS ROBBERY, YES?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I DID.
I GOT A REAL GOOD LOOK AT HIM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SHE DID.
GOT A REAL GOOD LOOK AT HIM.
COULD YOU PLEASE POINT HIM OUT
TO THE REST OF US?
>> YES.
THAT'S HIM RIGHT THERE.
IN THE GREEN SUIT, DEVO HAT, AND
BEARD.
>> YOUR HONOR, I'M SORRY, BUT
THAT COULD DESCRIBE PERHAPS 20
DIFFERENT PEOPLE IN THIS
COURTROOM!
>> RIGHT THERE IN THE GREEN
SUIT.
>> MISS SHANE, THERE IS PERHAPS,
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE ONE, TWO, 20
PEOPLE IN THIS COURTROOM THAT
FITS THAT DESCRIPTION.
YOUR HONOR, IF THE WITNESS
CANNOT IDENTIFY WHO SHE SAW, I
MOVE FOR THIS CASE TO BE
DISMISSED.
>> MOTION DENIED.
>> BUT YOUR HONOR, I'D WAGER
THERE'S PERHAPS MAYBE 20
PEOPLE --
>> STOP IT.
YOU REALLY THOUGHT THAT WOULD
WORK, HIRING 20 PEOPLE?
>> PERHAPS 20, YES --
>> 20 PEOPLE TO JUST DRESS LIKE
YOUR CLIENT?
THAT WAS YOUR BIG MOVE?
>> NO, YOUR HONOR.
THIS IS MY BIG MOVE.
GENTLEMEN?
SHUFFLE!
>> HA HA.
NOW, MISS SHANE, COULD YOU AGAIN
PLEASE POINT OUT THE MAN THAT
YOU SAW COMMIT THIS ROBBERY?
>> YES.
IT WAS YOUR CLIENT, THE ONE
SITTING RIGHT THERE.
>> BUT HOW CAN WE KNOW THAT
THAT'S STILL HIM?
YOUR HONOR, THE MEN THAT YOU
ADMIT LOOK EXACTLY LIKE MY
CLIENT JUST SHUFFLED ALL AROUND.
THE MAN SITTING THERE NOW COULD
BE ANY ONE OF THEM.
>> OH, MY GOD, I'M GOING TO
JAIL.
>> SO, GIVEN THAT DUE TO THE
SHUFFLING IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO
TELL IF THAT'S MY CLIENT, I'M
AFRAID I HAVE TO MOVE FOR
DISMISSAL.
>> DENIED.
>> BUT YOUR HONOR!
>> NO, SHUT UP.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE ALL KNOW THAT THAT'S YOUR
CLIENT.
NO ONE IS CONFUSED.
>> UH-HUH.
MAY I HAVE A MOMENT TO SPEAK
WITH MY CLIENT?
SORRY, PAL, THEY ALL KNOW IT'S
YOU, AND YOU'RE GETTING THE
CHAIR.
>> THAT IS NOT YOUR CLIENT.
>> WHO'S TO SAY?
AGAIN, DUE TO THE SHUFFLING,
THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW.
>> YOUR CLIENT IS NOT A BUFF,
AFRICAN AMERICAN MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOT SOME BAD NEWS, BUDDY.
PLANS "A" AND "B" AIN'T WORKING
OUT TOO HOT RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT WAS TWO PLANS?
>> YEAH, PLAN "A" WAS JUST TO
HAVE THEM SITTING BACK THERE.
PLAN "B" WAS TO HAVE THEM
SHUFFLE ALL AROUND.
BUT YEAH, THEY SAW RIGHT THROUGH
THAT.
>> OBVIOUSLY, MAN.
>> DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S STILL PLAN "C."
YOUR HONOR.
I'M READY TO CLOSE.
>> GREAT.
WHAT ARE YOUR FINAL REMARKS?
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, IF YOU
DON'T DISMISS THIS CASE, I'M
GOING TO KILL MYSELF.
>> NO YOU'RE NOT, I KNOW YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
>> BAD NEWS, BUDDY.
HE KNEW I WASN'T GOING TO DO
THAT.
>> THAT WAS PLAN "C"?
>> YEP, AND THIS IS PLAN "D."
YOUR HONOR!
IF YOU DISMISS THIS CASE -- I
WILL GIVE YOU ORAL.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT THAT.
>> JUST GOT SOME MORE BAD NEWS,
BUD.
¶ MY BABY WANT A BIRKIN'
SHE'S BEEN TELLIN' ME
ALL NIGHT LONG ¶
¶ GASOLINE AND GROCERIES
THE LIST GOES ON AND ON ¶
¶ THIS 9 TO 5 AIN'T WORKIN'
WHY THE HELL
DO I WORK SO HARD ¶
¶ I CAN'T WORRY
'BOUT MY PROBLEMS
I CAN'T TAKE 'EM
WHEN I'M GONE ¶
OKAY SING IT GO --
¶ ONE HERE COMES THE TWO
TO THE THREE TO THE FOUR
TELL 'EM BRING ANOTHER OUT
WE NEED PLENTY MORE ¶
¶ TWO STEPPIN' ON THE TABLE
SHE DON'T NEED A DANCE FLOOR
OH MY
GOOD LORD ¶
¶ SOMEONE POUR ME UP
A DOUBLE SHOT OF WHISKEY
THEY KNOW ME AND JACK DANIELS
GOT A HISTORY ¶
¶ THERE'S A PARTY DOWNTOWN
NEAR FIFTH STREET
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ WELL I'VE BEEN BOOZEY
SINCE I'VE LEFT
I AIN'T CHANGIN'
FOR A CHECK ¶
¶ TELL MY MA
I AIN'T FORGET
OH LORD ¶
¶ WOKE UP DRUNK
AT 10:00 A.M.
WE GON' DO THIS ALL AGAIN ¶
¶ TELL YOUR GIRL
TO BRING A FRIEND
OH LORD ¶
¶ ONE HERE COMES THE TWO
TO THE THREE TO THE FOUR
TELL 'EM BRING ANOTHER OUT
WE NEED PLENTY MORE ¶
¶ TWO STEPPIN' ON THE TABLE
SHE DON'T NEED A DANCE FLOOR
OH MY
GOOD LORD ¶
¶ SOMEONE POUR ME UP
A DOUBLE SHOT OF WHISKEY
THEY KNOW ME AND JACK DANIELS
GOT A HISTORY ¶
¶ THERE'S A PARTY DOWNTOWN
NEAR FIFTH STREET
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ ONE HERE COMES THE TWO
TO THE THREE TO THE FOUR
WHEN IT'S LAST CALL AND
THEY KICK US OUT THE DOOR ¶
¶ IT'S GETTIN' KIND OF LATE
BUT THE LADIES WANT SOME MORE
OH MY
GOOD LORD ¶
¶ SOMEONE POUR ME UP
A DOUBLE SHOT OF WHISKEY
THEY KNOW ME AND JACK DANIELS
GOT A HISTORY ¶
¶ THERE'S A PARTY DOWNTOWN
NEAR FIFTH STREET
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ SOMEONE POUR ME UP
A DOUBLE SHOT OF WHISKEY
THEY KNOW ME AND JACK DANIELS
GOT A HISTORY ¶
¶ AT THE BOTTOM OF A BOTTLE
GON' MISS ME
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
¶ EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY
EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE!
¶ EVERYBODY AT THE BAR
GETTIN' TIPSY ¶
>> THANK ALL FOR GETTING TISHY
WITH US!
GLASS.
>> OH, I REALLY NEEDED THIS, YOU
GUYS.
JUST A GOOD OLD-FASHIONED HANG.
>> SERIOUSLY.
2024, MAN THIS YEAR'S BEEN
ROUGH.
>> SPEAKING OF, HOW WAS
EVERYONE'S SPOTIFY WRAPPED?
>> YOU MEAN THE MOST
EMBARRASSING DAY OF THE YEAR?
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT MINE.
IT'S SO MUCH NOAH KAHAN, IT'S
LITERALLY A CRY FOR HELP.
>> I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT
MINE, ACTUALLY.
>> OH, YEAH, MYRON?
WHY IS THAT?
>> BECAUSE I THINK I'VE GOT
TASTE, AND I SPEND MY TIME WELL.
>> OKAY, NOW WE'VE GOT TO SEE
IT.
>> SURE.
EVERYBODY GATHER ROUND.
>> OKAY.
YOUR TOP ARTISTS WERE SABRINA
CARPENTER, KENDRICK LAMAR, AND
YOUR NUMBER ONE BY FAR IS
SATOSHI GUTMAN?
>> WHO IS SATOSHI GUTMAN?
>> YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW SATOSHI
GUTMAN IN THE ANTI-INSTRUMENTIST
SOUND DUE RUE OF DUNDALK,
MARYLAND?
YOU DON'T KNOW SATOSHI?
>> I'VE NEVER HEARD OF SATOSHI
GUTMAN IN MY LIFE.
>> YOU'RE IN THE TOP 0.005% OF
HIS LISTENERS, OVER 170,000
MINUTES?
>> YES, HE SENT THIS VIDEO,
LOOK.
>> HI, SPOTIFY WRAPPED.
SATOSHI GUTMAN HERE.
THANK YOU FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY
ASS FOR BEING MY TOP LISTENERS
OF 2024.
LET'S HEAR MY HIT, "Y'ALL MADE
ME CELIBATE."
¶ I WAS NORMAL Y'ALL MADE ME
CELIBATE ¶
¶ I WAS A NYMPHO YOU MADE ME
>> HAPPY NEW YEAR, MY BASTARDS.
>> DID HE JUST CALL US BASTARDS?
>> THAT'S WHAT HE CALLS HIS
FANS.
HAVE YOU SERIOUSLY NEVER HEARD
OF SATOSHI?
HE'S REALLY MAKING WAVES ON
DUNDALK, MARYLAND.
>> WHAT IS DUNDALK, MARYLAND?
>> Y'ALL ARE REALLY SLEEPING ON
DUNDALK.
IT'S THE EPICENTER OF THE ACE
CORE MOVEMENT.
>> SPOTIFY TRACKS YOUR PODCASTS
TOO.
YOU'VE GOT "THE DAILY," "CALL
YOUR DADDY," AND YOUR MOST
LISTENED?
AWAKENING WITH SATOSHI GUTMAN.
HE HAS A PODCAST?
>> Y'ALL DON'T KNOW "AWAKENING,"
92.
>> NO, STOP ASKING US.
>> STOP SAYING Y'ALL, YOU'RE
IRISH.
>> Y'ALL DON'T KNOW SATOSHI.
Y'ALL NOT HIP TO DUNDALK.
I'M ABOUT TO PUT Y'ALL ON.
>> IS THIS A CLIP FROM THE
PODCAST?
>> HEY, MY GALACTIC BASTARDS.
MY ASS IS SO HARD FOR TODAY'S
EPISODE.
OUR GUEST, FRIEND OF THE POD,
THE ICONIC TRICIA PEATTA.
WHAT DO WE SAY?
>> THE BEST BACY IS CELIBACY.
>> MYRON, THIS IS SO INSANE.
>> YEAH, MAN.
>> IT'S HONESTLY CONCERNING.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, GUYS.
SPOTIFY WRAPPED IS NOT ABOUT
JUDGING PEOPLE.
IT'S ABOUT SHARING THE
SOUNDTRACK OF YOUR LIFE.
AND CALL ME CRAZY, BUT I THINK
THAT'S SOMETHING TO CELEBRATE
>> DID SOMEONE SAY CELEBRATE?
>> OH, MY GOD, SATOSHI GUTMAN
AND TRICIA PAETTA.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> ME AND SATOSHI WERE WALKING
IN THE AREA.
>> SHOULD WE VIBE SOME ACE CORE?
>> YEAH!
¶ I WAS NORMAL BUT THEN Y'ALL
MADE ME CELEBRATE ¶
¶
SHAY COMING TO YOU FROM THE RED
CARPET PREMIERE OF THE NEW BOB
DYLAN BIO-PIC, "A COMPLETE
UNKNOWN," STARRING TIMOTHEE
CHALAMET.
AND HERE HE IS, AMERICA'S
SWEETHEART.
MY FOREVER BABY GIRL, TIMMY, IS
IT SAFE TO SAY YOU HAD A BRAT
SUMMER?
>> OH, MAN, IT WAS CRAZY.
NUTS, MAN, IT'S NUTS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
AND ICON ALERT, HERE COMES MR.
BOB DYLAN HIMSELF.
BOB, LACEY SHAY FROM BUZZFEED.
I HAVE TO ASK, DID YOU SLAY THE
HOUSE DOWN BOOF AND HAVE A BRAT
SUMMER?
>> WHAT?
>> A BRAT SUMMER, DID YOU HAVE A
BRAT SUMMER?
>> I MIGHT HAVE HAD A CAREER AND
A DRINK, PERHAPS A DODGER DODGER
WATCHING SHOHEI OHTANI.
BUT THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR SAUSAGE
CONSUMPTION.
>> BOB, I LOVE THIS GUY!
>> I LOVE YOU TOO, BUT ALL THIS
SAUSAGE TALK HAS AWOKEN MY
HUNGER.
I HEAR THERE'S A HOT BAR AT THE
END OF THIS.
SO IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
>> HOLD ON, NOT SO FAST, BOB.
WHILE I HAVE THE TWO OF YOU,
BUZZFEED HAS TO KNOW, WHAT IS
YOUR FAVORITE TIMMY FILM?
>> I'M PARTIAL TO HIS .
>> OMG, HERE COMES BRUCE
SPRINGSTEEN.
¶ BABY I WAS BORN TO WATCH THIS
MOVIE ¶
>> WAIT, BOSS, YOU HIT THE HOT
BAR?
>> SURE DID, BOB.
THE VIBES MIGHT BE SMALL BUT THE
FLAVOR'S AS BIG AS THE AMERICAN
SPIRIT.
>> I NEED TO GET BREAKFAST.
BUZZFEED, I LONG TO SEE THE
PROMISED LAND.
>> GUYS, APPETIZERS, AAH!
>> BRUCE, DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE
CHALAMET MOVIE?
>> I LIKE THAT "WONKA" PICTURE.
I GREW UP IN A CHOCOLATE FACTORY
TOWN.
I REMEMBER THE DAY THEY CLOSED
IT DOWN.
POPS CAME HOME DRUNK.
MAMA RAN OFF WITH AN OOMPA
LOOMPA.
BUT OF COURSE, LIKE ALL MY
STORIES, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> ESE GUYS ARE CRAZY.
I'M GOING TO GO.
>> OH-OH, HERE COMES ROCK LEGEND
BONO.
>> YOU HAVE TO TRY THE STEER RA
MAY SUE, IT COMES IN A SHOT
GLASS AND THEY GIVE YOU A TINY
SPOON.
>> YOU'RE TESTING ME LIKE JOB,
CHRISTIN WILDERNESS.
>> OKAY.
WELL, BONO, AS A BUZZFEED
EMPLOYEE, I LEGALLY HAVE TO ASK,
DID YOU HAVE A BRAT SUMMER?
>> I DIDN'T HAVE A BRAT SUMMER.
I COULD NOT POSSIBLY.
BECAUSE OF THE SWELTERING HEAT
BROUGHT ON BY CLIMATE CHANGE.
WE MUST ACT NOW.
I JUST SAW A DOCUMENTARY ABOUT
THE DEVASTATING EFFECTS OF
GLOBAL WARMING.
IT WAS CALLED, "HOT FROSTY."
>> THERE YOU GO, BUZZFEED IS
MAKING ME ASK ONE MORE QUESTION.
BASED ON YOUR ANSWERS SO FAR,
THERE'S NO WAY IT'S GOING TO BE
GOOD.
IF YOU HAD TO RANK RORY
GILMORE'S BOYFRIENDS FROM
GILMORE GIRLS, WHAT WOULD IT
BE?
>>> THANKS TO SHABOOZEY, DANA
CARVEY, DAVID SPADE, THANK YOU