Whoa, whoa, whoa, golly.
Well, what if Donald
shouts at me?
What do I say, Lammy?
Just be yourself,
Prime Minister.
Yourself is who everyone likes.
Hello?
Oh, sod that scary, scary,
wonderful president.
Why is it so blubbered
difficult to talk to?
Sir, just be honest
and tell him we can't send
any more ships
to the Strait of Hormuz.
Oh, crumbs.
I just hate conflict so much.
Are you referring
to the war or this phone call?
Isn't there a way
I can not do both?
I just want to keep
him happy, Lammy.
You don't understand
him like I do.
I can change him.
I don't think
the feeling's mutual.
He can't stop insulting you.
He called you a coward.
I'm out of my depth
here, Lammy.
How did Liz Truss make
this job look so easy?
Look, we were worried
you'd lose your nerve.
So we've taken steps to help
you gain unfounded confidence.
Mr. Prime Minister, meet
your Gen Z advisor Atlu Hoopy.
What's up, Starmzy?
Atlu Hoopy is the most
qualified person we have.
He is the only person under
23 who voted Labour
and would so again in the next election.
You're not voting
for the Green party?
Nah, my dad works in oil.
No cap, Starmzy, I love you
and I do hearts this way with my thumb.
Thank you Atlu Hoopy.
I love you too.
Sir Keir is trying to set
boundaries with the president
while preserving
their special relationship.
I see, facts, facts are key.
So you're looking for more
of a special situationship.
OK, I've got you covered.
I'm an expert in messy drama.
I've been in three throuples
and I'm currently gay.
First thing you gotta do, you
got to forget the phone call.
These days, it's all
about the voice note.
I'll try anything.
I'll do anything.
Except take a stand.
That is so Kier-coded.
Hey, listen, take the phone
and just speak from the heart.
Hi, Donald.
I'm afraid I can't
go to war with you.
But that doesn't mean
we can't still be chums.
America and Britain have
a long, proud tradition
of cooperation,
and nothing
can take that away.
Remember the good times.
Remember D-Day.
Remember Live Aid.
Remember Iraq--
For the first week,
and then none of the rest.
Remember Helen
Baxendale on "Friends."
Remember Hugh
Laurie on "Friends."
Remember the episode
of "Friends"
where they all came to London.
Remember the one where Joey put
on all of Chandler's clothes.
That was a funny one.
- Get back on track, Sir Kier.
- Yes.
Most importantly, remember
the one where Ross and
Rachel were on a break.
I think perhaps
that's what we need.
Not forever, just
until you've got all
this war out of your system.
Listen, we want
different things.
I know how badly you want
to start World War III,
and that's great.
You should absolutely do that.
But we can't be a part of it.
You can, however, use the Naval
bases whenever you want.
Mi basa, su basa.
Sick job, K-dot.
Good work, Sir Keir.
You did the bare minimum.
And that's all people expect.
Thank you, Lammy.
It just goes to show,
while we may not
agree with everything
America does,
we can still be
civil
and embrace
their wonderful,
unproblematic culture.
Speaking of which,
live from
London it's Saturday Night!
Musical guest, Wet Leg.
And your host, Tina Fey.
Ladies and gentlemen, Tina Fey!
Thank you very much.
Oh, my gosh.
I am so excited
to be here in London.
It is an absolute honor
and honestly kind of historic.
Guys, I am the youngest
person ever to host "SNL UK"!
Again, my name is Tina Fey.
Here in the UK--
here in the UK, you might know
me as the teacher from "Mean Girls,"
or you might remember
a long time ago
when I played Sarah Palin on "SNL" US.
Or maybe you feel like you
recognize me
as the lady from the show "Veep."
And that's fine too.
Let's go with that.
So why do a UK
version of "SNL."
Well, like so many large-scale
American operations these days,
no one
really knows why.
But here's what this is, OK?
It is a sketch comedy show.
There will be a different
celebrity host each week.
There will be
music performances.
And the show is truly live,
so things may go wrong.
Things may have
already gone wrong.
My pants were supposed
to be full length.
And I'm so excited
for you to meet your cast.
They are wonderful.
I can't even begin
to understand
them when they speak.
One boy is either
Scottish or choking.
But their energy is A plus.
And I am going to stay
out of their way tonight
as much as possible.
I am just here,
as a longtime "SNL" employee to help out
and to
answer any questions anyone
might have of what to expect.
Oh, hi.
Yeah, Nicola Coughlan.
Hi.
It is lovely to see you.
But my question is,
if this is "SNL UK," then
why are you the first host?
Shouldn't it be
like a British icon,
like David Beckham or--
or Judi Dench or, like, Shrek?
Yeah, Shrek.
Wait, Shrek is British?
Scotland is in Britain, Tina.
Educate yourself.
Sorry, my apologies.
Well, that is a valid
question, why an American host.
And the way it was
explained to me
was that for this first
episode, anyway, um,
how do I put this politely?
None of you fuckers
would do it.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, it does, it does.
But is it possible
that many of us
were a little reluctant
to be in the first show
because this is
going out in Britain,
and British people tend to root
for the failure of others?
Yes!
Yeah, yeah, why are
you guys like that?
Well, not me.
I'm Irish.
Educate yourself.
Yes.
Look, that all is to say,
if this show is a hit,
and if you do
ever happen to get
Olly Murs for musical guest,
I would be honored to come
back and win a BAFTA for it.
Amazing!
That's great to know.
Thank you, Nicola.
Any-- any other questions?
Oh, sure.
Michael Cera.
Hi.
Hi, Tina.
Hi, Michael.
Why are you here?
You're not British.
- No, no.
I'm Canadian.
It's part of the Commonwealth.
Educate yourself.
Sorry.
No, I don't really
have a question.
But I just wanted
to say, I think--
I think you just
swore a second ago.
You said the F word.
Oh, yeah.
We are allowed to swear
in this version of the show.
It's crazy.
But can I try?
Sure, if you want to.
Shitbird.
Just fucking bollocks!
Yeah, I think I would
use it sparingly.
It feels kind of unclassy.
Yeah, you know what?
You're right.
I agree, Michael.
That's a great note.
Thank you so much.
I think we have
time for one more.
Oh, yes.
Graham Norton!
So nice to see you.
I just wondered, did you know
that this is usually my studio?
Yeah, I did
hear that, Graham.
Thank you for loaning it to us.
Oh, would you
mind if I came up
there and just showed you a
fiddly thing about this place?
Oh, I would love it.
Come on.
Graham Norton, everybody.
Come on up.
Yeah.
Great.
Thank you, Thank
you, Thank you.
Yeah, sure.
Now, Tina, I believe
you've always had
a deep love of British comedy.
Are you interviewing me now?
Let me help you.
I have a gift for making
American celebrities
likable to a British audience.
Wait, are we not likable?
Oh.
Hey, I hear you
have a really funny
story about watching
British television
as a-- as a young child.
Oh, well, yes.
Actually, growing up,
we thought that anything
British was educational.
So my parents showed
us all British shows.
And we used to watch
"Benny Hill" as a family.
No.
As a young girl, you
would watch "Benny Hill"?
Yeah.
It really messed
me up sexually.
What about "Ab Fab"?
Oh, sweetie,
darling, you're just
a little shopgirl, darling.
"Keeping up Appearances."
Richard!
Oh, And "Monty Python."
That is an ex-parrot.
"Fawlty Towers."
Nobody mention the war.
"Are You Being Served?"
My pussy is like
an alarm clock.
"Reggie Perrin."
I didn't get where I
am today by waffling.
Deep cut "Monty Python."
We lived in shoe
box in middle of road.
"EastEnders."
I killed Ethel.
Oh, mwah!
And David-- David Brent.
There's been a rape up there!
Top trends.
Nothing beats a Jet2 holiday!
♪ Autoglass repair ♪
♪ Autoglass replace ♪
Oh!
That's it, Tina.
They're all yours now, Tina.
All yours.
Thank you.
We've got a great show.
Wet Leg is here.
Stick around and watch this!
When it comes
to age-defying skincare,
I don't need a time machine.
I just need
something that works.
So I can bring
back the spark in me.
And in us.
And now I've found it.
The anti-aging cream that
works so well, everyone
will think your husband--
is a nonce.
She's my wife.
She's a grown woman.
- Shut your mouth!
You make me sick.
Introducing Undérage.
With active compounds
and hyaluronic acid,
Undérage delivers special
protection for your skin
and ensures your husband
will need special protection
when he's in jail.
My wife's skin has never
looked more youthful and fresh.
It's destroyed my life!
Thanks, Undérage.
My skin looks so fresh,
my husband can't go anywhere
without being hunted
by right-wing,
pedophile-catching militias.
We know you're in there!
Frank, someone's at the door.
Thanks, Undérage.
My husband is
no longer allowed
within 200 feet of a school.
My husband lost his
record deal and some,
but not all, of his fans.
He loves the way I look.
Yeah.
But, you know, not like that.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Little girl, do
you know this man?
That's my wife.
You sick bastard.
He's married
to an Undérage girl.
I'm married
to an underage girl.
I don't know if I
pronounced that right.
I don't know about that.
No, I didn't mean that.
No, it's the name of the thing.
Undérage.
I'm not underage.
Or am I?
She's not.
She's not!
Undérage by Pedolay.
Hello.
I'm David Attenborough.
And it can't be long now.
As the only remaining national
treasure not on that list,
I enjoy a place as one of 90%
of the British public's
dream dinner party guests.
But I'm often asked
who would be on mine.
Well, using DNA sampling and my
own brother's "Jurassic Park"
technology, I have reanimated
some of history's greatest
Britons for one night only
so that I can ask them what
really makes Britain great.
This is David Attenborough's
"Last Supper."
I'd like to welcome my guests.
Prime Minister
Winston Churchill.
Astronomer and mathematician
Sir Isaac Newton.
Nurse Mary Seacole.
Diana, Princess of Wales.
Author Agatha Christie.
Poet Benjamin Zephaniah.
Freddie Mercury from Queen.
♪ - Ay-oh! ♪
Elizabeth I from
being the Queen.
♪ - Ay-oh! ♪
Surprise, surprise,
it's Cilla Black.
Ay-oh, Chuck!
Thanks so much for hosting
this dinner party, Sir David.
You're very
welcome, Princess Di.
Now, as this cloning technology
only works for one hour.
I'll cut to the chase.
What do you think
makes Britain great?
Before we commence,
there is a mystery
I should like to solve.
Are we doing starters?
I'm getting a starter.
I'm bleeding starving.
Yes.
Order whatever you like.
Tonight is about thrilling
conversation and the greatness
of Great Britain.
Yes, Winston Churchill?
Shall we get three
starters for the table
and do picky bits?
♪ - Ay-oh! ♪
Freddie says he
wants the croquettes.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
I'd have the croquettes, but
I only want a little nibble.
Well, hang on, hang on.
By my calculations, there are
three croquettes in one order
and 10 of us.
Therefore, if we
order three portions,
one person will miss out.
The solution is simple.
We order four.
That means that three people
will get two croquettes.
But who?
Another mystery.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Don't-- don't worry
about the food.
The BBC have spared no expense
bringing you back to life.
I'm sure they're happy
to cover one dinner at the Ivy.
Now, as to the source
of Britain's greatness.
Not to be that person,
but I don't like croquettes.
I'd rather get the soup.
Hang about.
That's a lot of starter
just for you.
Freddie is right.
We shouldn't all have
to pay for your starter.
Well, no one's paying.
No one's paying.
It's-- It's covered, guys.
Tonight is about
scintillating conversation
and learning from each other.
Yes?
Benjamin Zephaniah.
Do you think each curry
comes with a free rice?
If it has an asterisk
next to its name,
then it comes with free rice.
♪ People on the street ♪
You're right, Freddy, there
are some people on the street,
but that doesn't answer
the question about poppadoms.
Stop it!
Stop it now!
It doesn't matter
what we have to eat.
Put that down!
Put it--
This experiment has
been a complete waste
of time and money.
The answer I was
looking for as to
what makes Britain truly great
was the NHS and Center Parcs.
There you've ruined it.
Dinner over.
Now, we shall move
on to the lovemaking
portion of the evening.
Anybody who wants to leave,
now's your chance.
Head over
to iPlayer now to see
the full uncut edition of David
Attenborough's Last Supper.
Heya, how you doing?
I'm Ed Boovies.
Welcome to Boovies goes
to the Films, the show
about all things cinema.
And this is a very special day.
I'm pinching myself,
to be honest.
We've got Ricky Hall and Lena
Phillips in the house!
- What's happening?
- Good to be here.
They're here to talk to us
through their new film,
"Hot Streak."
And they are two
icons of cinema!
I hope you don't
mind me saying.
No, I don't mind at all.
Keep saying it.
Lena, I've been a fan since
your first film, "Sunrise Eyes"
Wow, that's a deep cut.
Yeah.
Cult classic alert.
And Ricky, "Crazy
Goat," underrated movie.
- Thanks so much, man.
- No, no.
Thank you.
I guess I'm trying to say, I
love you and your work so much.
I hope that's not too creepy.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks so much, man, wow.
OK, so let's talk
about "Hot Streak."
I watched this last night.
It fucking sucked.
Excuse me?
It sucked.
So bad, like all
the way through.
What happened?
Um.
Lena, you first.
Yeah, well, we loved
working on this movie.
Yeah, it was a dream to work
with Vicky, our director.
But why did it suck so bad,
like all the way through?
Well, I don't
think it sucked.
It did.
Did it?
Yeah, all the way through.
Where's our PR?
No, no, he's gone
to get me some fruit.
Look.
I could be wrong.
I don't think I
am, but I could be.
Let's check out a clip.
You have to listen to me,
you're our only hope.
Oh, boo!
This is sucking so bad.
Ricky, you're not
even acting there.
I mean, you are acting,
but it's so wrong and sour,
you know?
No, no, stop the tape,
stop the tape.
It's just-- that sucks.
I just--
I just know if you
tried, if everyone tried
and like gave you everything,
we could have got there.
It didn't have to be
good, you know.
I don't need good.
I just need it not
to fucking suck,
like, all the way through.
Can everything stop
sucking all the time?
Because it's
making my life bad.
Is that too much to ask?
Please.
Sorry.
We're-- we're sorry.
That's OK.
Join us next time on "Boovies
goes to the Films."
I'm Ed Boovies wishing
you a decent day.
Awe, get in, legend, thanks.
Get to work.
What a time to be
alive, people.
My name is Turpin Turpin.
Yep.
Both my names are Turpin.
Great job.
All right.
Jan, how are we doing?
Good.
- Yeah.
What do we do here?
We're all working together
to make the internet as
bad as we can possibly get it.
It's a team effort.
I'm Jan.
I'm almost 19 and I'm
the password manager.
Essentially, my job is just
before you enter in a short,
memorable password of your own,
I come up with a very long
and complicated one,
hoping I'll remember
it and then I don't.
I'm the X-Man.
I do all the x's
for online adverts.
We try and make them smaller
than any human finger.
Even if you do notice it,
what does an x even mean?
Sometimes it can mean
close this window.
open four more windows.
It can be either.
I think most people
think it's the first one.
Most people voted for Hitler.
Sorry.
I'm online a lot.
I don't know what's real.
The thing is, is there are
websites that no one would
ever intentionally visit.
You know, no one actually wants
to enter the r house draw.
No one is really owed
money just for being
born between 1995 and 1997.
And no one intentionally
clicks on "Family Guy"
porn, except me.
But that's only because of how
much I like to look at it.
Good, people.
This is good.
Whoa!
My speciality?
I'm the guy who moves
things at the last second
so that people click
on the wrong stuff online.
OK, she's about
to click stand by.
Standing by.
She's hovering.
Sh-- she's hovering.
And budge it.
Buy something!
Annoying.
Yes!
That's five seconds
she won't get back.
Sir, we got her.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Do you get paid?
No, no no, no.
But let me ask you this.
Let me ask you this.
Do you get paid for your job?
Yeah.
Interesting.
Gosh, 10 hours of labor.
Doesn't look like this
little man's in a rush.
Why is it taking so long?
Don't worry, he's just
a bit-- he's just a bit shy.
Aw.
Aw look it, he's
just sort of hiding.
Bless him.
There's not wrong with
being shy, is there?
Oh, not wrong at all.
I think I prefer a shy
one, to be honest.
Out of my way.
I'm Dr. Amanda Miller.
I graduated Harvard
summa cum laude.
My kids are very mean
to me, but I don't have time
to get into that right now.
Wait, why is
the obstetrician here?
He's just a bit shy, isn't he?
I wish that was the case.
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Cook,
but your baby is not shy.
He's something
much more sinister.
He's pretending to be
shy for attention.
And we need to act fast
before it metastasizes.
This all seems
a bit dramatic.
Well, unless
you want your son
to be an adult man who is
addicted to canceling plans,
let me do my goddamn job.
Well, wait.
Hang on.
What-- what if he's
shy around strangers,
but he lets his guard down
around people he trusts?
Like an introverted extrovert?
Yeah, those are
essentially a myth.
Most people who make a big
deal out of being shy
are, medically speaking,
fake ass divas.
No son of mine's going
to be a fake ass diva!
I mean, look, I'm no doctor.
I'm just a stupid
rocket scientist,
but I think he's genuinely shy.
OK, but like,
now he's dancing.
I'm just like, why-- why would
a genuinely shy person do that?
Wait, he's-- he's quite good.
My God, he is quite good!
He's not amazing,
but he's quite good.
He's got spirit.
You can tell he's
actually enjoying himself.
Hey, ho.
Mr. and Mrs. Cook,
this is serious.
An authentically
shy person would not
pop their puss in this manner.
Oh, Harry, maybe she's right.
What if our son
is giving cringe?
Only claiming to be socially
awkward when it suits him--
slash them.
Sitting in the corner
at parties because he gets
overwhelmed, but then
he's the loudest
and most abrasive person
there by quite some distance.
The type of bitch to give
a presentation at work
can make the whole
thing about how nervous
he is, even though
it's like, girl,
you volunteered to do this.
Oh, no.
Now he's holding his hands out
to show that they're shaking,
but it's obvious it's him
that's making it happen.
Doctor, do something!
Grab a leg.
Honey, are you the diamond
in my wedding ring?
Because you are
fake as hell and we
can see right through you, OK?
OK, well, he's dancing again.
Oh, God.
Doctor, please,
we just want him
out of there safe and sound.
Fine.
I promised myself I
would never do this.
Hey, sweetie?
How are you feeling?
So, a bunch of us are
thinking of doing karaoke.
Oh, stop.
Don't leave without me!
But I'm literally
just going to watch.
He's coming.
Congratulations!
He's a nightmare!
♪ Hey, ho ♪
Ladies
and gentlemen, Wet Leg.
♪ Nice try, get out the way ♪
♪ You're in our way ♪
♪ You bottom feeder ♪
♪ Too bad you couldn't stay ♪
♪ You're in our way ♪
♪ Get lost forever ♪
♪ You think I'm pretty ♪
♪ You think I'm pretty cool ♪
♪ You want to fuck me ♪
♪ I know most people do ♪
♪ Here, take this packet, ♪
♪ You read it, it
says, "Mangetout" ♪
♪ I gave you magic beans ♪
♪ I hope you're
gonna get out soon ♪
♪ Oh, man, I hope you're
♪ I really hope you're
gonna get out soon ♪
♪ Oh, man, I really hope
you're gonna get out soon ♪
♪ Good job, give you an A ♪
♪ A gold star, you
think you're clever ♪
♪ Good God, she took a break ♪
♪ Made a mistake,
when she met Trevor ♪
♪ Get lost forever ♪
♪ You think I'm pretty ♪
♪ You think I'm pretty cool ♪
♪ You want to fuck me ♪
♪ I know most people do ♪
♪ Here, take this packet ♪
♪ You read it, it
says, "Mangetout" ♪
♪ I gave you magic beans ♪
♪ I hope you're
gonna get out soon ♪
♪ I really hope you're
♪ Oh, man, I hope you're
gonna get out soon ♪
♪ I really hope you're
♪ I know you're up at night ♪
♪ Hunched over
your phone like ♪
♪ A tree atop a hill ♪
♪ That's crooked from
the wind that bites ♪
♪ You say you're lost at sea ♪
♪ Call the RNLI ♪
♪ You're washed
up, irrelevant, ♪
♪ And standing in my light ♪
♪ You're standing in my light ♪
♪ You think I'm pretty ♪
♪ And you think
I'm pretty cool ♪
♪ You say I scare ya ♪
♪ I know most people do ♪
♪ This is the real
world, honey, bienvenue ♪
♪ In spite of everything ♪
♪ I guess there's just
no getting through ♪
♪ Nice try, get
out of the way ♪
♪ Good job, just
take a fucking hint ♪
♪ I said I'll see ya, ♪
♪ Wouldn't wanna be ya, ♪
♪ Be ya, eh-ya eh-ya, ah-ah ♪
♪ Nice try, get out the way ♪
♪ You're in our way ♪
♪ Get lost forever ♪
It's Weekend Update with
Ania Magliano and Paddy Young.
Good evening and welcome
to Weekend Update.
I'm Paddy Young.
And I'm Ania Magliano.
Coming up on tonight's
Weekend Update, pedophilia.
But first, war.
Yesterday, in a shock
U-turn, Keir Starmer finally
gave his consent
for President Trump
to use British bases to protect
the Strait of Hormuz, at which
point Trump said, "Consent?
Now you've taken all
the fun out of it."
As Iranian strikes
continue to hit Dubai,
the cost of chartering
a private jet
has risen so high
that many influencers
have been struggling to flee.
I must stress, though,
it's not all good news.
If any influencers are
killed-- and again,
we can only hope they are--
at least they'll
be easy to identify
by their dental records.
Say, the massive white
ones made in Turkey.
You got to feel for them.
They went there
to evade income tax
and now they have
to evade incoming attacks.
We're now three weeks
into the Iran war,
which started with
the death of one
Ayatollah Khomeini
and the appointment
of another Ayatollah Khomeini.
Khomeini II,
but one's dead now.
OK.
Not everyone in NATO
wants to get involved.
German Defense Minister
Boris Pistorius
said there would be no military
participation from Germany.
Where was this energy in 1939?
Also, is there a more evil
name than Boris Pistorius?
How do you do?
The name's Saddam Walliams.
The head of the Asian
Football Confederation said
this week that Iran is still
set to play at the upcoming
World Cup in America
if Iran does take part,
America has guaranteed
that all of their matches
will be refereed
by a completely
impartial MQ-9 Reaper drone.
We all know the supply of oil
has been affected by this war,
but the Strait
of Hormuz is also
the primary route for a third
of the world's helium.
A spokesperson for the helium
industry said--
We've run out of helium.
With pressure mounting to
secure the Strait of Hormuz and
the Royal Navy almost
completely out of action,
the government have
decided to send
in the only British Naval
captain who's ready to go.
Please welcome
Captain Birdseye.
Yar!
Evening, me hearties.
Now, captain, I
think the question
a lot of people
at home are asking
is, why is the government
sending a fish finger
man to a red hot war zone?
Fish finger man?
I am the purveyor of the finest
fish fingers in the land.
Succulent cod fillets in a
perfectly crispy golden crumb.
Only the best
for the captain's table.
Fish finger?
Captain Birdseye,
can I remind you,
this is a military operation.
Exactly.
Preparation, timing, control.
Six minutes one side, turn,
six minutes the other.
Now that's what I call
a proper fish finger.
Fish finger?
You're about to be
deployed to Iran.
Can you stop banging
on about fish fingers?
Fine, we also do
chicken dippers,
potato waffles, and for some
reason, the devil only
knows, peas.
Captain, there are
real lives at stake here.
Oh, you want
to get real, do you,
you scurvy little deck rat?
All right, answer me this.
You think I spent the last
five decades sailing around
in 150-foot schooner with
300 singing children just
to sell fish fingers, do ye?
I'm sorry, did you say
300 singing children?
Cause I'll tell
you what's real,
you bilge drinking haddock.
What's real is the nation's
favorite fish fingers
are just a cover
for my actual work.
Special Forces Black
Ops savagery that
would haunt your dreams.
What's real is opening up
a Serbian mercenary's neck
with a machete.
Watching it yawn open,
hot and steaming,
like a split fish finger.
This is insane.
Insane?
I'll show you insane!
Are those human fingers?
Only the best
for the captain's table!
Captain Birdseye, everyone.
Never meet your heroes!
Renovations to Andrew
Mountbatten-Windsor's new home,
Marsh Farm, have been taking
place over the last month,
including the installation
of Sky TV.
So if you're watching,
Andrew, hello.
You're not going
to like this next bit.
Also, I'm older than I look.
Andrew's new
residence, Marsh Farm
is, of course, named
after the nearby marsh
where his body will be found.
It was reported this week
that the police investigation
into Andrew is set to widen.
The big question
now is, if Andrew
is charged, found guilty,
and put in prison,
will he be able
to keep his mouth shut?
I hope not, said his
cellmate's penis.
Conservative leader Kemi
Badenoch told Times Radio that
she would confront
a shoplifter if they were,
quote, "not too big."
So rest assured,
if you shoplift and
Kemi does try to stop you, it
means she thinks you're skinny.
In showbiz news, feuding
father and son David and
Brooklyn Beckham narrowly
miss each other whilst
at the same Beverly
Hills Hotel.
The feud began when
Victoria was, quote,
"inappropriately close with
her son at his wedding"
and escalated after
Brooklyn accidentally
yelled out his wife's name
during sex with his mom.
The award-winning
TV series "It's a Sin"
is set to be adapted
for the stage as a dance show.
As if a TV show about the AIDS
crisis could get any gayer.
Tonight, the K-pop
band BTS are launching
their new world tour.
My worry is, with 82
dates across 23 countries,
the stress of the tour is
going to put a strain on Jimin
and V's soulmate relationship.
Sure, J-hope nurtures
Suga's inner child,
but will Jimin's teasing
of Suga make V jealous?
And can RM give enough
skinship to Baby Jungkook
while melting
at J-hope's laugh?
Will his dimples still be
popping at Jimin's cuteness
after an 82 date tour?
No idea.
I'm not really that into BTS.
For Weekend Update,
I'm Ania Magliano.
And I'm Paddy Young.
Good night!
Please be safe
in London, Will.
Nay, worry not, wife.
I will be nothing but safe.
For all I will think
of is returning to thee
and our boy Hamnet.
What about our daughters?
I must away.
My production of "The
Tempest," begins anon.
Adieu!
"Tempest" was a hit.
Methinks I might write
another of these plays.
Will, thou art returned!
Did I not tell thee I would?
But hast thou nothing to say?
I have sorely missed thee.
Likewise, my dear
wife, likewise.
But dost thou not
think I appear changed?
Tis hard to fix
my eyes on anything
for the blood that doth
course in mine veins
on the sweet return
of thee to me.
Mm, ye, really
look at me, though.
What vexes thee?
I got a cunty little earring.
Ah, so it is.
The hour is upon me.
I must to London!
My staging
of "Macbeth" awaiteth.
Well, Will, I will
wait upon thy return.
William, thou art returned.
Good day, wife.
Good day, Hamnet.
Will, how London
hath changed thee.
Come, wife, let me
sit and put my feet up.
What art thou wearing?
Oh, dislike it?
'Tis me slutty little chain.
'Tis all the rage in London.
I must, to London.
My next staging awaits--
"Henry IV part two."
Henry V!
Let not London
change thee too much.
Well, thy father
have returneth.
Hause!
Whew.
Hey, family!
Will, mine eyes do
not recognize thee.
Girl, 'tis me, bitch!
Will, thou art
a different man.
Peace, wife.
I be Shakespeare.
The remix be Troye Sivan.
Tis not thee, Will.
'Tis so, bitch.
Thou art
in Stratford-upon-Avon.
And I've been in London
upon ketamine.
I'm like Charli XCX--
sorry, Charlie 10, 100, 10.
I'm
in my glow era-- in my glow--
I'm in my glow-up era, honey.
What's an era?
We are in one, bitch.
Mine!
My wife, I bring gifts.
This is called a tote bag.
I want that not.
Wig, my girl.
Thoust look cunty, for sure.
What does this c-word mean?
Hmm.
Methinks I can explain.
It's not a bad word.
It's a good thing,
a great thing.
It's bleached brows.
It's the cast
of "Desperate Housewives."
It's cabin crew,
bald head on a woman,
the Elizabeth
line, a thin woman
eating a big plate of meat.
It is as though riddles
play upon thy tongue.
Thou art just gagged.
Hamnet take the
powder within your coin purse!
He'll be fine.
'Tis but a K-hole.
And you know what
hitteth hard in the hole?
Rihanna, bitch.
♪ We found love
in a hopeless place ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless ♪
You've seen the film.
You've heard the musical.
Now experience
the experience, The Live
Paddington Bear Experience.
This is so exciting.
We can't believe we're actually
going to meet Paddington,
aren't we?
We brought
marmalade sandwiches!
It's Clara's hen do.
And we got banned
from Magic Mike
because Liz kept
groping Magic Mike.
Watch out, Paddington.
I can't wait to meet
that little bear.
Welcome to 32 Windsor Garden.
At London's most
immersive experience,
get closer to Paddington
than ever before.
Now, who here would like to
meet a very rare sort of bear?
Yay!
Janet!
Open the cage!
A place where
memories last forever.
Paddington?
All right!
Oh, why!
Ah!
Fine!
Take the sandwich.
Take the sandwich!
Why did we hire a real bear?
Well, I know we wanted
to hire the little actress
from the musical, but she
wanted too much money.
And I had seen
the bear in something.
He was amazing.
What was it?
The zoo, I had seen
him at the zoo.
That was amazing.
Yeah, well, I've
lost half my face.
But I have made some memories.
None of that
happened in the films.
That was a lot more blood
than I thought there'd be.
And at Paddington's
photo booth,
we'll be sure to capture
all of the magic.
Well, I was actually
on a terrible date,
but let's just say I didn't
need to ask for Angela.
I asked for Paddington.
"The Guardian" calls
it "truly unforgettable."
They said he likes marmalade.
He doesn't like marmalade.
He likes human hands.
Marcus?
I've always thought that
three kids was a bit too many.
And now I've got
the optimum amount.
None.
"The Stage" says,
"Inarguably immersive."
Do I have any regrets?
Well, you know,
in retrospect, maybe hot glue
gunning the hat
to the bear's head
may have made it more angry.
I'm taking it
to Broadway, regardless.
The Live Paddington Bear
Experience, book before June 25
and get a free tetanus jab.
Found a foot.
Has anyone lost a foot?
No?
Once again, Wet Leg.
♪ Can you catch
a medicine ball? ♪
♪ Can you catch yourself
when you fall? ♪
♪ You should be careful ♪
♪ Do you catch my drift? ♪
♪ 'Cause what I really
want to know is ♪
♪ Can you catch these fists ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, Yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Man down ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Level up! ♪
♪ I know all too well ♪
♪ Just what you're like ♪
♪ I don't want your love ♪
♪ I just wanna fight ♪
♪ We're on our way
to the club ♪
♪ Stupid is as stupid does ♪
♪ Limousine, racking up ♪
♪ Ketamine, giddy up ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Man down ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Level up! ♪
♪ I know all too well ♪
♪ Just what you're like ♪
♪ I don't want your love ♪
♪ I just wanna fight ♪
♪ He don't get puss ♪
♪ He get the boot ♪
♪ I saw him sippin'
on dark fruit ♪
♪ This always happens
late at night ♪
♪ Some guy comes up, ♪
♪ Says I'm his type ♪
♪ I just threw up in my mouth ♪
♪ When he just tried
to ask me out ♪
♪ Don't approach me ♪
♪ I just want to dance
with my friends ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Man down ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Level up! ♪
♪ I know all too well ♪
♪ Just what you're like ♪
♪ I don't want your love ♪
♪ I just wanna fight ♪
♪ I know all too well ♪
♪ Just what you're like ♪
♪ I don't want your love ♪
♪ I just wanna fight! ♪
♪ Man down ♪
Four things, thank you.
Ugh, Jane, look at you,
divorced, haggy, alone.
What a sad little life, Jane.
Fancy a bra fitting?
Uh, sure, yeah.
I've actually lost
a ton of weight--
Oh, good for you.
due to immense stress.
I have a bad life.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, I'm just going
to do round your top.
OK?
So here we go.
We've got the middle.
That's 38 inches.
So, yeah, that's quite wide.
And cup size, that's
a B, so it's small.
You're not happy with that?
Oh, no.
38B, that's not exactly
a sexy bra size.
It feels, kind of, schlubby.
Oh.
Would you like me to zhuzh?
Huh?
Zhuzh it up a bit
for the surrounds.
What does that mean.
A zhuzh for the surrounds.
Right, OK.
So I come back in,
and I zhuzh, right?
I very loudly make a point
of how big your bra size is.
Theys out there don't know
what you really measured as.
Wink, wink.
Is that a British thing?
It is a thing.
Do you want give it a go?
It is a free service.
Sure.
Won't be long, ladies.
I'm just doing a fitting.
Oh, my goodness!
Wow!
These are going
to measure up nicely!
So we're going to start
with the width.
Very petite,
but your cup size is--
Big?
Big cup size, right?
Oh, crikey, yeah,
they've got a real weight
to them Oh, fantastic!
In fact, I'm surprised--
You don't topple over.
With a great--
With a great
big rack like that!
Love it.
Oh!
Oh, you nearly
poked my eye out!
Hey, you've heard of Pinocchio?
Well, you're like that, but the
nose is big, lovely bazombas.
That OK?
- Yeah.
That's good.
So I'm happy
to tell you-- what
size would you like, darling?
Big, but keep it classy.
Like, double D is good.
Oh, no, we're going
bigger than that.
You're a gorgeous,
petite, and perky 28G!
What an absolute pair.
Now, how's that feel?
I feel amazing.
Thank you so much, Miss?
Jugs, they call me Jugs.
All right.
Here we go.
Put these back
on the rack, Jackie.
They were so far too
small for this customers
great big bozzies.
Lovely tits you
got there, Miss.
Jugs, wait.
Is there anything else that
you could zhuzh for me,
like, for the surrounds?
'Cause my 2026 was,
kind of, rough.
Like, basically, I was
responsible for editing
this British film
award ceremony and--
Let's just say I did
not get it right.
It's a zhuzh
for the surrounds, darling,
not for the soul.
But you'll be all
right with those
great big, wicked knockers.
Excuse me.
Regé-Jean Page,
what are you doing
in the women's changing rooms?
Oh, it's a long
and sexy story.
Listen, I don't
usually do this,
but can I buy you a drink
on the fifth floor,
next to the baby
clothes and electricals?
Sure, I could do that.
Thanks for changing my life.
Tiny, little tits.
They were small.
Those tits were small.
45 seconds with Fouracres.
♪ What kind of Irish
is your granddad? ♪
is your gramps? ♪
♪ Is he this? ♪
I'm Anthony.
Which one of you little
gobs threw a heap of fruits
at my window?
You better tell me.
'Cause I know your dad!
And I know your dad!
♪ What kind of Irish
is your granddad? ♪
♪ Is he this? ♪
Now that's a picture of me
back in '82, on the 12th
of the King William Lodge.
And there's another one,
the Blue Lancers and a--
♪ What kind of Irish
is your granddad? ♪
♪ Is he this? ♪
I'll bring it around
the back, hey.
Put on new shoes,
and don't worry about it.
Hey,  any man's back.
♪ What kind of Irish
is your granddad? ♪
♪ Is he this? ♪
♪ Tá Gráinne Mhaol ag
teacht thar sáile, ♪
♪ Óglaigh armtha
léi mar gharda ♪
♪ Gaeil iad féin is
ní Gaill ná Spánnigh ♪
♪ Is cuirfidh siad
ruaig ar Ghallaibh ♪
♪ Óró 'Sé do bheatha 'bhaile, ♪
♪ Óró 'Sé do bheatha 'bhaile ♪
♪ Anois ar theacht
an tsamhraidh! ♪
Wow!
Nicola Coughlan from
the "Dairy Girls."
No, it's "Derry Girls."
It doesn't matter,
Nicola Coughlan.
None of this is real.
Good night.
God bless.
Love you.
45 seconds with Fouracres.
My biggest thanks to Wet Leg,
Nicola Coughlan, Michael Cera,
Graham Norton, Regé-Jean
Page and a huge
thank you to the cast,
and the writers,
and everyone
for welcoming me here and
making it such a great week.
Congratulations.
SNL UK is born!