>>> AND NOW, A MESSAGE FROM THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
HELLO
>> HAPPY NEW YEAR.
I HOPE EVERYONE HAD A NICE
HOLIDAY AND GOT WHAT THEY WANTED
FOR CHRISTMAS.
I GOT WHAT I WANTED.
MY VERY OWN SOMEONE ELSE'S NOBEL
PRIZE!
WHICH I'LL CHERISH.
AND IN MY STOCKING I GOT MADURO!
NICOLAS MADURO.
WE DID A REVERSE SANTA ON HIM.
WE CAME DOWN THE CHIMNEY WITH A
BAG AND TOOK HIM AWAY.
ANYWAY, I'M HERE TODAY TO CATCH
YOU UP ON ALL THE EXCITING
THINGS WE'VE BEEN DOING,
AND
I'LL BE JOINED BY MY CABINET, MY
LITTLE CABINET OF CURIOSITIES,
MY FREAKS, VARIOUS MONSTERS AND
NIGHTMARES
FROM THE TWISTED MIND
OF GUILLERMO DEL TRUMP.
WE'VE GOT LITTLE MARCO AND J.D.
VANCE.
YEAH, YOU CAN CLAP FOR THEM,
THEY'RE NICE BOYS.
THEY DO WHAT THEY'RE TOLD.
I THINK STEPHEN MILLER'S IN HERE
SOMEWHERE,
BUT HE'S ON THE
CEILING.
SOMEONE BROUGHT A BIBLE IN HERE,
AND HE JUST SORT OF SCAMPERED
RIGHT UP THE WALL ONTO THE
CEILING.
MAYBE WE'LL GET HIM DOWN IN A
MOMENT.
THESE GUYS ARE GREAT.
THEY'RE HELPING ME DO SO MANY LEGAL-ISH THINGS
TO TRY TO GET
PEOPLE TO STOP TALKING ABOUT
EPSTEIN.
OH, MARCO'S PASSING ME A NOTE
HERE.
"DON'T READ THIS OUT LOUD, BUT"
MAYBE DON'T TALK ABOUT THAT.
ALSO, DO YOU LIKE ME?
CIRCLE YES OR NO.
MARCO, I'M GOING TO NEED A THIRD
OPTION.
MARCO'S FROM CUBA, AND CUBA IS
NEXT.
SO MARCO, WHILE YOU'RE HERE,
COULD YOU SAY A FEW WORDS TO THE
PEOPLE OF CUBA?
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT IN HERE, BIG GUY.
NO, NO, NO, I DIDN'T LIKE THAT
AT ALL.
YOU'RE DRIVING IN THE WRONG
DIRECTION, HONEY.
NOW, LET'S GET A FEW WORDS FROM
MY VICE PRESIDENT, J.D. VANCE.
LOOK, IT'S J.D., GOT A MAKEOVER.
LOOK AT THAT.
HE'S A NEW AND IMPROVED J.D.,
LOOK.
HE'S GOT THE EYESHADOW LOOKING
VERY ON UNFLEET TODAY.
WE'RE DOING THINGS FROM 2016.
REMEMBER 2016?
ANYWAY, GO AHEAD, J.D.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
AND AMERICA, HERE'S MY MESSAGE
TO YOU.
YOU KNOW, I CAME HERE TO DO TWO
THINGS.
KICK BUBBLE GUM AND CHEW ASS.
AND I'M ALL OUT OF BUBBLE GUM.
>> WELL SAID.
NOW, J.D., WHY DON'T YOU GIVE US
AN UPDATE ON
TRENDS IN MENSWEAR,
WHATEVER THE HELL YOUR JOB IS.
BY THE WAY, WHILE YOU'RE
TALKING, I'M JUST GOING
TO SORT
OF WALK AROUND IN THE BACKGROUND
AND LOOK OUT WINDOWS.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY, I LIKE TO
SPEND TIME TODAY
TALKING  ABOUT THE NEW TARIFFS
AND THOSE PEOPLE
WHO OPPOSE OUR MISSION IN GREENLAND.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I SEE A
CARDINAL AND A BLUE JAY IN THE
SAME TREE.
WOW.
YOU DON'T SEE THAT A LOT.
VERY INTERESTING.
>> SIR, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> NO, I'M NOT.
I DON'T THINK SO.
THANK YOU, J.D.
NEXT UP, I'D LIKE TO BRING IN A
MEMBER OF MY CABINET
WHO WEARS
MANY HATS IN TERMS OF
RESPONSIBILITY AND HAT.
SECRETARY OF HOMELAND SECURITY,
KRISTI NOEM.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT, FOR
HAVING ME.
BEFORE WE START, I'D LIKE TO
GIVE A QUICK SHOUT-OUT TO MY
HAIR AND MAKEUP TEAM,
WHO
ABSOLUTELY HATE ME.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY, THERE'S BEEN
CLASHES ON BOTH SIDES IN
MINNEAPOLIS.
HAVE WE BEEN PERFECT?
YES.
I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE LOOKING
AT THE SITUATION IN MINNESOTA
ARE WONDERING THE SAME THING.
CAN I JOIN I.C.E.?
LET ME ASK YOU THIS.
IS YOUR NECK WIDER THAN YOUR
HEAD?
ARE YOU CURRENTLY WEARING A
PUNISHER T-SHIRT?
HAVE YOU EVER PUNCHED A HOLE IN
THE WALL BECAUSE YOUR SON TOOK A
DANCE CLASS?
IF THE ANSWER IS YES, THEN GRAB
A GUN, ANY GUN, AND SADDLE UP,
BIG BOY.
AND JUST KNOW YOU CAN ALWAYS
COUNT ON ME, BECAUSE MY LAST NAME IS NOEM
AS IN, DO I HAVE
THE SITUATION UNDER CONTROL?
NOEM, I DON'T.
>> GREAT JOB, KRISTI,
WOW, WOW.
WELL, FOLKS, WASN'T SHE HERE?
WELL, NOW THAT WE'VE HEARD FROM
MY SECRETARY OF WAR ON AMERICA,
LET'S GO AHEAD AND BRING OUT OUR
SECRETARY OF WAR WITH WORLD.
GIVE IT UP FOR PETE HEGSETH,
EVERYBODY.
>> YEAH!
CUT IT!
I SAY, CUT IT!
WHAT'S UP, YOU CHODES?
FRESH POW-POW, UGH!
LISTEN UP!
IN CASE YOUR EARS ARE TOO FAT TO
HEAR THE NEWS,
WE WENT INTO VENEZUELA
AND TEABAGGED THEIR
COUNTRY.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT MANSCAPE.
WE WENT IN, STRAIGHT-UP STOLE
THEIR PRESIDENT.
YOINK!
ONLY NEEDED TO SEND IN A COUPLE
OF HELICOPTERS, ALL OF THEM
BLAEFRING "WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE"
AND THE MADURO REGIME
WAS BROUGHT DOWN TO ITS
SHA NA
NA NA THAT KNEES KNEES!
IN FACT-BEEN ROCKING OUT WITH
OUR Cs OUT ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WE DNGED ON VENEZUELA.
NEXT WE'RE GOING TO SACK TAP
IRAN.
GOING TO PUT THE AYATOLLAH IN
THE CUFF CHAIR.
TELL HIM, IF AYATOLLAH YOU ONCE,
I AYATOLLAH YOU A THOUSAND
TIMES.
YOU DON'T DARE KILL YOUR
PROTESTERS, THAT'S OUR THING.
REMEMBER
YOU F WITH AMERICA, WE'LL F YOU
RIGHT BACK.
JUST LIKE IT LOOKS LIKE I'M
EFFING THIS CATTLE BELL.
SAW IT ON A VIDEO, GOT PASSED
AROUND ONLINE
IN A POSITIVE WAY.
YEAH, I'M GONNA F YOU LIKE I'VE
NEVER DONE IT BEFORE
AND I'M
GOING TO FINISH WAY TOO FAST.
- THANK
>> THANKS, HEGSETH, THAT WAS
GREAT, BUDDY.
EVEN I KNOW YOU'RE DOING THAT
WRONG.
ALSO, MIDTERMS ARE CANCELED.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
HOST
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- FINN
WOLFHARD!
THANK YOU!
THANKS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
THIS PAST YEAR WAS VERY
BITTERSWEET FOR ME.
MY SHOW "STRANGER THINGS" ENDED.
AND IT STARTED -- YEAH.
IT STARTED WHEN I WAS 12,
AND I GOT TO TELL YOU, IT FEELS SO
AMAZING
THAT 400 MILLION PEOPLE GOT TO WATCH ME
GO THROUGH
PUBERTY.
WHAT A DREAM.
SOMEBODY ON A REDDIT ACTUALLY
FIGURED OUT THE EXACT MOMENT IT HAPPENED,
AND I THINK WE HAVE A
CLIP.
>> ARE YOU FEELING ANY BETTER?
DON'T WORRY, WHEN ALL THIS IS
OVER, YOU WON'T HAVE TO KEEP
EATING JUNK FOOD AND LEFTOVERS
LIKE A DOG ANYMORE.
MY MOM, SHE LOOK PRETTY AWESOME
TOO.
>> YEP.
MY VOICE CHANGED ON CAMERA,
MY
FIRST KISS WAS ON CAMERA, AND --
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M ADMITTING
THIS BUT THE FIRST TIME I
LEARNED WHAT A WOMAN LOOKS LIKE
DOWN THERE
WAS ON CAMERA, AS
WELL.
SO WE HAVE ANOTHER CLIP, I
THINK.
KREP.
AND LOOK, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
A LOT OF PEOPLE STILL SEE ME AS
THE KID FROM "STRANGER THINGS,"
RIGHT?
I'M 23 NOW.
AND I'M PROUD TO OFFICIALLY
ANNOUNCE THAT I AM -- A MAN.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THINGS ARE DIFFERENT NOW.
LIKE, FOR EXAMPLE -- I HAVE
FACIAL HAIR.
CAN WE ZOOM IN ON IT?
OH, YEAH.
THERE SHE IS.
HEY, MIGHT ONLY SEE ONE HAIR,
BUT PARTY STARTS WHEN THE FIRST
GUEST ARRIVES.
WHAT'S A PARTY WITHOUT SOME
ALCOHOL?
NOW THAT I'M A MAN, I'D LIKE TO
TRY IT NOW, PLEASE.
COULD I GET SOME ALCOHOL IN A
CUP?
>> YEAH, I GOT YOU.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
THANKS, MAN.
- GLO
- I LOVED YOUR STAND-UP SESSION,
BY THE WAY.
>> OH, WOW, ME TOO.
CHEERS, BUDDY.
>> CHEERS.
>> TO YOU.
>> TOO SPICY.
>> I LIKE THAT YOU DO THAT TO ME
JUST LIKE THAT IN FRONT OF ALL THESE PEOPLE,
I APPRECIATE THAT,
THANK YOU, MAN.
YEAH.
MEET THE NEW ME.
THE MAN ME.
STRANGER THINGS IS OVER, AND
I'M NOT A KID ANYMORE.
>> AND NEITHER ARE WE!
>> WE'RE NOT CHILD STARS, WE'RE
FORMER CHILD STARS.
>> ANY TIME YOU READ "FORMER
CHILD STAR" IN A HEADLINE, IT
CAN ONLY MEAN GOOD THINGS.
>> THANKS TO EVERYONE WHO
WATCHED US GLOW UP ON THE SHOW.
>> AND THEN WENT ONLINE AND
COMMENTED ABOUT OUR CHANGING
FACES AND BODIES.
>> YEP.
>> I JUST WANTED TO SAY, EVEN
THOUGH WE ARE NOW MEN, YOU'LL
ALWAYS BE MY BOYS.
SO LET'S TOAST.
>> TO YOU HOSTING "SNL."
>> YES, AND TO US, CHILD STARS
WHO ARE NOW READY TO DO ADULT
FILMS.
HEY, WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR
YOU TONIGHT.
A$AP ROCKY IS HERE!
STICK AROUND.
SNACKHOMIEZ, THE PODCAST ABOUT
SNACKS FOR YOUR HOMIES.
I'M BRAYLOR, HERE WITH TYLER AND
JASON.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WORD.
>> BEING GROUNDED FOR SPENDING
TOO MANY "FORTNIGHT" BUCKS IN A
WEEK, WELCOME BACK, JASON.
>> AND WE'RE LOWKEY 12 YEARS
OLD, EXCEPT KYLER'S 13.
HE'S UNC.
>> UNC, UNC!
>> AND WE GOT GUEST HOMIE
JOINING US THIS WEEK, MY
6-YEAR-OLD COUSIN WHO IS LOWKEY
FAMOUS ON TWITCH, MICAH.
IT'S AN HONOR.
>> NAH, CHILL.
NO, HONOR'S ALL MINE, BIG FAN OF
THE POD.
>> SO MICAH, YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY,
LIKE, COOL AS HELL.
TELL US ABOUT YOUR STREAM, BRO.
LIKE, YOU TALK ABOUT FACIAL
STRUCTURE?
>> YEAH.
UH, SO I'M LIKE, UH, I'M A LOOKS
MAXI GIGA CHAD.
BASICALLY I DISCUSS MOGGING,
MANDIBULAR GROWTH, ACHIEVING
SIGMA STATUS BY BREAKING MY
JAWBONE AND PULLING HIGH-LEVEL
TALENT.
>> THAT'S JUST SICK.
>> AWESOME.
>> BRO.
>> SICK, YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO IT'S NEW YEAR'S, FELLOWS.
LET'S TALK OUR EARLY PICKS FOR
GO-TO SNACKS OF 2026.
JASON, TAKE IT AWAY.
>> OKAY.
YEAH, SO -- I'M A BIG PB&J GUY.
AND THIS YEAR, I'M SEEING REALLY
BIG THINGS FOR CRUSTABLES.
>> FUN.
>> RAD.
>> YEAH.
>> YO, YOU LIKE -- YOU EVER PUT
ONE IN THE TOASTER OVEN?
>> SO FIRE, YEAH.
>> YO.
YO, YO.
NOT GOING TO HOLD I DON'T,
GOONING FOR A CRUSTY.
>> OH, FELLOWS, MAYBE IF YOU'RE
CARB MAXING, I'M NOT TRYING TO
WALK AROUND ALL THICK, SHARING
THE HOES.
>>> YO, OBVIOUSLY.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE LOWKEY PUT TOO
MUCH FOCUS ON LOOKS AS A
SOCIETY.
>> I'M JUST MAD BECAUSE HE'S
BUILT LIKE THE MOM FROM
INCREDIBLES.
>> NOT GONNA LIE, HE LOWKEY SIX,
I'M FROM THE BACKVILLE, SO HEAR
ME OUT.
>> OH!
>> NUGITY, NUGITY, NUGITY.
>> NO DIDDY, DAWG.
>> AYE, MICAH, HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I'M GOING TO GO FOR A DARK
HORSE PICK.
GREAT FOR MANDIBULAR SYMMETRY
AND MAX MOGGING.
THIS YEAR I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
MESSING WITH SOME CELERY.
>> MM, CELERY.
>> BE ABLE TO CRUNCH THOSE.
>> YEAH.
>> YO, CELERY AFTER SOCCER
PRACTICE GOES CRAZY.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
DUB TAKES ALL AROUND, SHEESH.
JASON, WHAT YOU GOT?
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO AHEAD
AND SAY DOUBLE OAKS.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, BRO.
DEVILED EGGS ARE SO RAW.
>> WAIT, I THOUGHT -- I THOUGHT
THEY WERE COOKED.
>> NO, BRO, THEY'RE RAW LIKE
THEY'RE DAS, BRO.
>> THEY ARE COOKED, THOUGH?
THEY'RE NOT CHOPPED?
>> YEAH, THEY'RE CHOPPED LIKE
ONCE.
LIKE IN HALF, NO?
>> I THINK HE MEANS LIKE THEY'RE
FIRE.
LIKE THEY'RE VALID.
>> VALID AS HELL, YEAH.
>> VALID.
>> UNC, WHAT YOU GOT?
>> BET, SO Y'ALL ALREADY KNOW
I'M A CHEETO FIEND LOWKEY.
LATELY I'VE BEEN GETTING INTO
PIRATE'S BOOTY.
>> NOT EATING THE BOOTY.
>> NO!
>> OH NO!
>> IT'S A WHITE CHEDDAR SNACK,
BRO.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
>> UNC KEEPING STUMBLING INTO
ZESTINESS ON SOME OOPSIE
POOP SIE.
>> UNC IS NEVER BEATING THE
ALLEGES, BRO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WE GOT A SPECIAL GUEST THIS
EPISODE.
>> YO.
THANK YOU, MAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M UP HERE WITH THE
SNACKHOMIEZ, YOU FEELING ME?
>> YEAH.
>> JASON, TAYSON, PREYLON, UNC.
I BEEN WATCHING IT POP FOR A
MINUTE NOW.
YOU GOTTA CHILL THIS SDS.
>> CRAZY.
>> BOY, I JUST GOT BODIED BY
A$AP ROCKY, THAT'S SO TOUGH.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU AS WELL,
MICAH.
>> PLEASURE'S ALL MINE.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT WE'RE
LOOKING AT UNPRECEDENTED LEVELS
OF CHADDOM RIGHT HERE, FELLOWS.
CHECK THE PROFILE.
BRO DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO MEW.
>> YO, YOU WEIRD, BRO, BUT THANK
YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> I ACTUALLY HAD A QUESTION,
MR. A$AP, SIR.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT IS YOUR GO-TO SNACK OF
2026, MR. PRETTY?
>> ACTUALLY, RAT SNACKS, YOU
DIG?
>> OH!
>> NO!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> YO, THESE ARE FIRE!
>> WHOA, WAIT.
YOU GOT YOUR OWN FLAVOR NOW,
A$AP?
>> I SURE DO.
A$AP FASHION KILLA DILLA PICKLE.
>> DAMN, YEAH, THAT'S TOUGH.
THAT'S TOUGH AS HELL.
>> GOT TO SAY, NOTHING BETTER
THAN A BIG OLD PICKLE, SIR.
>> HEY, YO.
NAH, YO, CHILL.
THAT WAS CRAZY.
THAT MIGHT BE THE PAUSE OF THE
CENTURY, YO.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> YO.
>> ALL RIGHT, COOL, THAT'S IT.
FIRE EPISODE, EVERYBODY.
>> I HAVE YOU ON "FORTNIGHT."
>> YEAH, DEUCES.
>>> COMING SOON TO HBO, THE
BELOVED WIZARDING WORLD OF HARRY
POTTER MAKES ITS TELEVISION
DEBUT.
>> SORRY.
>> NO.
I AM.
>> I'M HARRY.
>> RON.
>> WITH AN ALL-NEW STORY, AFTER
THE SUCCESS OF A CERTAIN OTHER
HBO SHOW.
>> I'D LOVE TO SEE YOURS
SOMETIME.
>> I BET YOU WOULD.
>> CATCH ME IF YOU CAN, WEASLEY.
>> TWO POINTS FROM GRYFFINDOR!
>> BUT 100 POINTS FOR MY SPANK
BANK!
>> THE STORY WRITTEN ENTIRELYPY
GIRLS WHO WEAR TAILS.
>> SORRY, THE MINISTER OF MAGIC
IS A DEATH EATER!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING UNDER THAT
INVISIBILITY CLOAK?
>> FETCHING.
HERMIONE, WHAT'S THE SPELL TO
MAKE SOMETHING BIGGER?
>> THEY'RE ALL 18 PLUS IN THIS.
HOGWARTS IS LIKE COLLEGE NOW.
>> GREAT MATCH OUT THERE.
>> I WAS HORRIBLE.
COULDN'T CATCH THE SNITCH.
>> YOU CAUGHT SOMETHING MORE
IMPORTANT, MY ATTENTION.
>> OH!
I'M SORRY.
I WON'T LOOK.
OH, MY.
>> J.K. ROWLING SAYS, I AM NOT A
FAN.
>> I'M WATCHING YOU, WEASLEY.
I THINK YOU'RE BRILLIANT WHEN
YOU LEVITATE AMONGST OTHER
BROOMS.
>> IT'S AN OWL.
>> SEE ABOUT THE MAGIC IN
SLYTHERIN.
THEN YOU CAN SLITHER IN.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING WE WANT TO
TELL YOU.
>> YOU'RE A HOMO, HARRY.
>> HOW DID YOU KNOW?
>> OH, HONEY, PLEASE.
I SHOULD CALL YOU NEVILLE
BECAUSE YOU ARE ONE LONG BOTTOM.
>> HAGRID, YOU OLD QUEEN.
>> AN INSPIRATIONAL TALE OF
SHOWING THE WORLD WHO YOU TRULY
ARE.
>> I'M DONE HIDING, RON.
>> BUT HARRY, THE MATCH.
WE'RE PLAYING SLYTHERIN.
>> LET'S WIN OUR WAY.
>> WELL, I THINK I'VE SEEN
ENOUGH.
10 POINTS!
FOR EQUALITY.
>> COMING SOON.
WORK ANY MINUTE.
>> MOM.
THERE'S SOMETHING I NEED TO TELL
YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT MONEY YOU AND DAD
SET ASIDE FOR MY COLLEGE?
I WANT TO USE IT NOW SO MY BAND
CAN GO ON TOUR.
>> OH -- PLAYING WITH YOUR
LITTLE INDIE BAND?
THAT'S NOT A FUTURE.
>> MOM.
I KNOW.
I KNOW IT'S NOT WHAT YOU AND DAD
WANTED FOR ME, BUT I DO.
CAN'T YOU SUPPORT ME?
>> OF COURSE I SUPPORT YOU.
BUT YOUR FATHER WON'T TAKE IT
WELL.
HE'S ALWAYS HOPED YOU'D FOLLOW
IN HIS FOOTSTEPS.
>> I DON'T WANT HIS LIFE, MOM.
>> OH, GOD, HE'S HOME.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL TELL HIM EVERYTHING.
JUST PLEASE HAVE MY BACK.
>> OH, I JUST HAD A BEAST OF A
DAY IN THE STUDIO.
WE WERE PITCHING, CHOREO'S A
MESS.
WHAT'S THIS?
>> I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
HUNTER'S INDIE BAND.
>> IT'S OKAY, MOM, I GOT THIS.
DAD, MY BAND SET UP SOME BAR
GIGS UP THE COAST, AND I WANT TO
GO WITH THEM OUT ON TOUR.
>> INDIE BAND, HUH?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE IN SOME
INDIE BAND.
>> DAD.
I --
>> QUIET!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A POP STAR
LIKE YOUR OLD MAN, END OF
DISCUSSION.
¶ OH YEAH YEAH ¶
>> NOW GO UPSTAIRS AND CHANGE,
YOU LOOK RIDICULOUS.
>> DAD.
>> BUT NOTHING.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A POP STAR.
YOU'RE GOING TO CHART.
LIKE I CHARTED.
>> I DON'T WANT TO CHART, DAD.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, SON.
WHEN WE CRACKED THE "BILLBOARD
HOT 100" WITH "HEART-SHAPED
ROLLER COASTER," IT WAS THE
GREATEST MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
>> WHO CARES, DAD?
BILLBOARD SUCKS.
>> OH, MY --
>> OKAY, OKAY.
WELL, I GUESS TODAY'S THE DAY I
HIT MY SON.
>> ROBERT, NO!
>> OKAY.
I'M NOT LIKE YOU, DAD.
I WANT TO MAKE ART.
>> OH!
OKAY.
SO I DON'T MAKE ART, IS THAT SO?
THEN WHAT THE HELL DO YOU CALL
THIS?
¶ COULD YOU GET MY HEART GOING
BANG BANG BOOM ¶
¶ I LOVE DANCING IN THE DANCING
ROOM ¶
PACK YOUR THINGS.
PACK YOUR THINGS, I WANT YOU OUT
OF THIS HOUSE, MISTER.
>> ROBERT, NO, THIS IS MY FAULT.
I'M THE ONE WHO INTRODUCED HIM
TO THE PICKIES.
>> MOM, IT'S NOT THE PICKIES,
IT'S JUST PICKIES.
>> YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'RE TEARING THIS FAMILY
APART.
>> WHATEVER, MAN.
I DON'T NEED YOU.
MY BAND IS MY FAMILY.
>> HA!
OKAY.
THOSE FREAKS AREN'T FAMILY,
OKAY?
NOW, TRUE TO YOU, THAT WAS A
FAMILY.
GET IN HERE, FELLOWS.
¶ TRUE TO YOU IS IN THE HOUSE
BANG BANG BOOM ¶
¶ OH YEAH YEAH YEAH ¶
>> THIS IS A FAMILY, OKAY?
I'M TALKING ABOUT K-DOG, THE
TALL ONE.
CURTIS 5000.
>> THE WOMP OF THE FUTURE,
FUTURE, FUTURE.
>> AND CYBER.
>> YEAH, I'M THE ONE WHO'S 15
YEARS OLDER THAN EVERYBODY ELSE.
AND KIM, SHOOT, YOU LOOK
AMAZING.
>> THANK YOU, CYBER.
>> OKAY.
DAD, I JUST WANT SOMETHING MORE
FULFILLING OUT OF MY LIFE.
>> WHAT COULD BE MORE FULFILLING
THAN SELLING OUT ARENAS FOR THE
YEAR AND A HALF PRECEDING 9/11?
AND IF I MAY, KIM -- YOU LOOK
BEAUTIFUL TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, K-DOG.
>> I JUST WANT SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
I WANT MY MUSIC.
>> LISTEN TO YOUR SON, ROBERT.
AND KIM?
GIRL?
IT IS JUST OUT OF CONTROL
TONIGHT FOR REAL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, DAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW, I CAN'T CLAIM
TO UNDERSTAND IT.
BUT YOU HAVE MY BLESSING.
>> HEY, YOU READY?
>> VAN'S ALL PACKED.
>> KIM, AS ALWAYS -- WOW.
>> THANK YOU, PALOMA.
>> I'LL BE RIGHT THERE, GUYS.
BUT FIRST?
I GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
>> WHAT IS IT, SON?
>> SING WITH MY FAVORITE PERSON.
¶ LOVE IS A HEART-SHAPED ROLLER
COASTER ¶
¶ BANG BANG BOOM AND DO DA DO ¶
¶ OH YEAH YEAH YEAH ¶
>>> AFTER FIVE INCREDIBLE
SEASONS, "STRANGER THINGS" SAID
GOOD-BYE.
AND THOUGH WE MISS OUR HAWKINS
HEROES, NETFLIX KNOWS THAT ALL
GOOD THINGS MUST COME TO AN END.
THEN WE SAW HOW MANY PEOPLE
WATCHED IT AND WE WERE LIKE, OH,
NEVER MIND.
STRANGER THINGS IS BACK WITH
SEQUELS, PREQUELS, REQEULS, AND
SPINOFFS.
STARTING WITH A NEW SERIES
STARRING THE INTERNET'S FAVORITE
HERO STOVE.
STEVE.
HE TAKES A NEW TEACHING JOB IN
INNER-CITY, LOS ANGELES.
IT'S "STRANGEREST MINDS."
>> GOOD MORNING, MY NAME IS MR.
HARRINGTON.
>> BITCH, YOU AIN'T GONNA LAST
ONE DAY AT THIS SCHOOL!
>> YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE A TEENAGER?
I WAS 17 FOR 10 YEARS!
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO BIG SISTER
NANCY?
WATCH HER JOURNALISM CAREER TAKE
OFF AS SHE INVESTIGATES SOME OF
THE BIGGEST CRIMES OF THE 1990s
IN "THE WHEELER REPORT."
>> YOU'RE LOOKING AT LIVE
FOOTAGE OF O.J. SIMPSON'S WHITE
BRONCO BEING DRIVEN BY HIS
FRIEND AL WHO WE'RE TOLD IS ON
THE PHONE WITH LAPD NOW.
>> O.J. IS IN THE CAR, LISTEN,
HE JUST WANTS TO GO HOME!
>> THIS JUICE MIGHT HAVE GONE
BAD.
>> WHO THE [ BLEEP ] ARE YOU?
>> THE WHITE GIRL WITH A MULLET
HAS JUMPED OUT OF THE BRONCO!
>> PLUS, WONDER WHAT HAPPENS TO
MIKE WHEN HE LEAVES HAWKINS
BEHIND AND CHASES HIS DREAMS OF
BECOMING A WRITER?
FIND OUT IN MICHAEL PATRICK
KING'S "MIKE IN MANHATTAN."
>> JUST LIKE THAT I WAS IN A NEW
UPSIDE DOWN NEW YORK.
IT DOESN'T TAKE A HIVE MIND TO
REALIZE, AFTER YOU'VE DATED AN
1111, EVEN 10s FALL SHORT.
>> HEY!
>> YOU MADE IT.
>> WOULDN'T MISS IT FOR THE
WORLD.
>> LET'S CUT TO THE CHASE.
HOW ARE YOUR SEX LIVES?
>> I DATED THAT WEIRD NERDY GIRL
WHO HELPED US SAVE THE WORLD.
NEVER TALKED TO HER AGAIN.
EVER SINCE, MY SERIES OF
BAD DATES HAS BEEN A --
¶ NEVERENDING STORY ¶
>> A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO, SHE
JUST WANTED TO -- LIKE SHE'S
BACK IN THAT COMA.
>> YOU'RE BAD.
>> MIKE.
YOUR NOSE.
>> WHAT?
>> DO YOU HAVE POWERS?
>> OH!
NO, NO, THIS IS FROM COCAINE.
>> YOU'RE BACK IN THE '90s,
RIGHT?
>> BEFORE YOU GET ALL MAD AND
GO, HOW COME WILL ISN'T IN THAT?
IT'S BECAUSE HIS COMING-OUT
SCENE IS STILL GOING ON.
>> I'M GAY -- NING THE COURAGE
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
AND THE TRUTH IS, I'M GAY --
ZING AT ALL OF YOUR FACES.
AND YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT I LIKE
D.
AND "D, DUNGEONS ANDING DEDROPS,
DRAGONS, JUST LIKE YOU GUYS.
>> EVERYONE IS GETTING A SHOW.
WE'RE EVEN RETELLING THE ENTIRE
ORIGINAL SERIES IN THE SIDE
SERIES "STRANGER THINGS: OOPS,
MIKE'S DAD."
>> GO WATCH TV.
>> TRUE TO OUR OBLIGATIONS --
>> HAVE YOU SEEN THE KIDS?
THEY'VE BEEN GONE FOR FOUR DAYS.
>> NOPE.
>> HEY, REMEMBER THAT MYSTERIOUS
NINTH EPISODE THE INTERNET WAS
CONVINCED EXISTED?
IT DIDN'T BUT IT DOES NOW.
WE GOT ALMOST ALL THE MAIN KIDS
BACK.
>> YOU WANT TO TELL ME WHY THE
HELL WE'RE IN ICELAND?
>> EVERYTHING WE THOUGHT
HAPPENED WAS AN ILLUSION.
HE'S STILL OUT THERE.
>> THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> SERIOUSLY, MIKE, GIVE ME ONE
GOOD REASON WHY WE SHOULD
BELIEVE YOU.
>> YOU WANT ONE REASON?
HOW ABOUT 11?
>> HELLO.
>> "STRANGER THINGS" ON NETFLIX.
THIS IS OUR "STAR WARS."
¶ SOMETIMES
I FORGET WHAT LOVE IS
TRUST ME LOVE ME
TAKE ME RIGHT BACK ¶
¶ SOMETIMES
I FORGET WHAT LOVE IS
TRUST ME LOVE ME
TAKE ME RIGHT BACK ¶
¶ I WANNA FALL IN LOVE
DON'T WANT NO BROKEN HEART
DON'T WANT TO GROW APART
TAKE ME BACK ¶
¶ I WANNA FALL IN LOVE
DON'T WANT NO BROKEN HEART
DON'T WANT TO GROW APART
TAKE ME BACK ¶
¶ I THOUGHT I FELL IN LOVE
I THOUGHT SHE FELT IT TOO
I THOUGHT WE WAS IN LOVE
SHE JUST ANOTHER FLUKE ¶
¶ I THOUGHT YOU WAS THE ONE
I GUESS YOU JUST THE TWO
YOU WANT THE LAST LAUGH
LOOK NOW JOKE'S ON YOU ¶
¶ YOU THOUGHT
YOU FELL IN LOVE
YOU THOUGHT HE FELT IT TOO ¶
¶ I TOLD HER DON'T BE DUMB
YOU JUST ANOTHER FOOL ¶
¶ YOU THOUGHT HE WAS THE ONE
I GUESS HE JUST THE TWO
YOU WANT THE LAST LAUGH
LOOK NOW JOKE'S ON YOU ¶
¶ I CRIED ALONE IN MY TRUCK
I FELT ALONE IN THE FRONT
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHO TO TRUST ¶
¶ AND I BEEN
GOING THRU SOME STUFF
DON'T TRUST THE ONES
YOU LOVE ¶
¶ YOUR EGO'S
ONE HELL OF A DRUG ¶'CAUSE NOTH¶
¶ YOU HOLD A GRUDGE
AND YOU TREAT ME
LIKE I'M SCUM ¶
¶ GOTTA TRUST YOUR GUT
GOTTA TRUST YOUR GUT ¶
¶ GOD'S THE ONLY ONE
TO JUDGE
NOW I'M CONFIDING
IN MY CUP YEAH ¶
¶ NOW I SEE IT
I WANNA FALL IN LOVE ¶
¶ DON'T WANT NO BROKEN HEART
DON'T WANT TO GROW APART
TAKE ME BACK ¶
¶ I WANNA FALL IN LOVE
DON'T WANT NO BROKEN HEART
DON'T WANT TO GROW APART
TAKE ME BACK ¶
¶ I THOUGHT I FELL IN LOVE
I THOUGHT SHE FELT IT TOO
I THOUGHT WE WAS IN LOVE
SHE JUST ANOTHER FLUKE ¶
¶ I THOUGHT YOU WAS THE ONE
I GUESS YOU JUST THE TWO
YOU WANT THE LAST LAUGH
LOOK NOW JOKE'S ON YOU ¶
¶ YOU THOUGHT
YOU FELL IN LOVE
YOU THOUGHT HE FELT IT TOO ¶
¶ I TOLD HER DON'T BE DUMB
YOU JUST ANOTHER FOOL ¶
¶ YOU THOUGHT HE WAS THE ONE
I GUESS HE'S JUST THE TWO
YOU WANT THE LAST LAUGH
LOOK NOW JOKE'S ON YOU ¶
¶ SOMETIMES
I FORGET WHAT LOVE IS
TRUST ME LOVE ME
TAKE ME RIGHT BACK ¶
¶ SHE DON'T EVEN
WANNA BE MY WIFE NO MORE
IT MAN LIFE GOES ON ¶
¶ HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO RIGHT MY WRONGS
HOW MANY TIMES
DID RIGHT GO WRONG ¶
¶ TELL ME HOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO WRITE LOVE SONGS
I DON'T EVEN LIKE
THEM SONGS ¶
¶ SHE AIN'T GOING
TO BE IN MY LIFE NO MORE ¶
¶ GOT ME CRYING
IN THE MICROPHONE
MAKE ME SHOUT
IN THE MEGAPHONE ¶
¶ THAT GIRL AIN'T MY TYPE
NO MORE
SHE AIN'T IN MY LIFE
NO MORE ¶
¶ I CONFIDE IN
THE STYROFOAM CUP
AHH AH-AH-AH-AH
AH-AH-AH-AH ¶
¶ I CONFIDE
IN THE STYROFOAM CUP ¶
¶ YA PUNCH DRUNK'IN LOVE
LEFT ME WITH A BLACKENED EYE
SHE DON'T LIKE US RAPPER GUYS
TAKE ME BACK ¶
¶ YA PUNCH DRUNK'IN LOVE
LEFT ME WITH A BLACKENED EYE
I WOULD LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
TAKE ME BACK ¶
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> WELL, GUYS, IT'S BEEN ONE
YEAR SINCE WE GOT BACK TOGETHER
WITH TRUMP AFTER TAKING A BREAK.
AND THERE ARE SIGNS THAT THERE
STILL MAY BE PROBLEMS WITH THE
RELATIONSHIP.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER,
BUT TRUMP PROMISED US AMERICA
FIRST.
YET IT'S ONLY OUR ONE-YEAR
ANNIVERSARY, AND HE'S ALREADY
OPENING OUR RELATIONSHIP UP TO
OTHER COUNTRIES.
THIS WEEK, TRUMP DECLARED
HIMSELF THE ACTING PRESIDENT OF
VENEZUELA.
BY NEXT WEEK, HE WILL BE THE
INTERIM AYATOLLAH OF IRAN.
AND THEN ON TO HIS ULTIMATE
GOAL, HEAD REINDEER OF
GREENLAND.
IN FACT, A CONGRESSMAN HAS
INTRODUCED A BILL TO MAKE
GREENLAND THE 51st STATE.
MEANWHILE, PUERTO RICO IS LIKE,
WOW, OKAY.
>>> OFFICIALS IN MINNESOTA HAVE
SUED THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION,
CLAIMING THAT THEIR LARGE-SCALE
I.C.E. ACTIONS ARE AN
UNCONSTITUTIONAL FEDERAL
INVASION.
WHILE THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
CLAIMS THAT, YEP!
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DEFENDED THE
ACTIONS OF I.C.E. AGENTS IN
MINNEAPOLIS, ADDING THAT THE DAY
OF RECKONING AND RETRIBUTION IS
COMING.
WHICH IS A PHRASE HE STOLE FROM
THAT GUY WHO'S ALWAYS POINTING
AT HIM.
>>> A FEDERAL JUDGE ON FRIDAY
ORDERED I.C.E. AGENTS IN
MINNESOTA NOT TO RETALIATE
AGAINST PEACEFUL PROTESTERS.
BUT IF I.C.E. AGENTS LISTENED TO
JUDGES, THEN THEIR EX-WIVES
WOULD BE GETTING THOSE CHECKS
FOR CHILD SUPPORT.
>>> DURING A VISIT TO THE WHITE
HOUSE, VENEZUELAN OPPOSITION
LEADER MARIA CORINA MACHADO
PRESENTED TRUMP WITH HER NOBEL
PEACE PRIZE.
WHAT KIND OF PSYCHO WOULD
ACTUALLY ACCEPT SOMEONE ELSE'S
NOBEL PEACE PRIZE?
SHE JUST WON IT.
IT'S SOMEONE SAYS, HELP YOURSELF
TO ANYTHING IN THE KITCHEN, AND
YOU BANG HIS WIFE.
POLITICAL EXPERTS SAY THAT
MACHADO GAVE TRUMP HER NOBEL
PEACE PRIZE IN THE HOPES OF
GETTING HIS HELP TO BECOME THE
NEXT LEADER OF VENEZUELA.
AND IF THAT BRIBE ACTUALLY
WORKED, I BET TRUMP'S ABOUT TO
GET A WHOLE BUNCH OF GRAMMYS.
>>> AFTER THE CEO OF EXXONMOBIL
TOLD PRESIDENT TRUMP CONVENIENCE
WAIL WAS UNINVESTABLE, TRUMP
SAID THE COMPANY WAS PLAYING TOO
CUTE.
THE EXXON CEO SAID, OH, YOU
THINK I'M CUTE?
AND TRUMP SAID, I DO.
THE EXXON GUY SAID, IS THIS
CUTE?
AND PUT HIS HAND ON HIS THIGH.
AND TRUMP SAID, NOT AS CUTE AS
THIS, AND KISSED HIM.
ALL ON SEASON 2 OF "HEATED
RIVALRIES."
>> WHAT IS YOUR ALGORITHM?
>>> IN AN INTERVIEW, PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAID THAT HE BELIEVED THAT
THE CIVIL RIGHTS ERA LED TO
WHITE PEOPLE BEING, QUOTE, VERY
BADLY TREATED.
YEAH, ESPECIALLY IN BASKETBALL.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE TWEETED A
GRAPHIC OF HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY ROBERT F.
KENNEDY JR. THAT SAID, QUOTE, WE
ARE ENDING THE WAR ON PROTEIN.
GOOD, BECAUSE I KNOW A COUPLE
FELLOWS WHO ARE EXTREMELY
PRO-TEEN.
>> OHO!
>>> DURING A RECENT PODCAST
APPEARANCE, ROBERT F. KENNEDY
JR. CRITICIZED PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
DIET SAYING, I DON'T KNOW HOW HE
IS ALIVE.
WELL, I DO.
A SLIGHT BREEZE.
>>> ZOE SALDANA, WHO STARS IN
THE NEW "AVATAR" MOVIE, HAS
SURPASSED SCARLETT JOHANSSON TO
BECOME THE HIGHEST-GROSSING
ACTRESS OF ALL-TIME.
LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU
INCLUDE THE BOX OFFICE FROM
SCARLETT'S HUSBAND'S MOVIES.
IT WENT DOWN?
>>> THE COLLEGE FOOTBALL
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME STICK
KICKS OFF THIS MONTH.
HERE'S MIAMI'S MOST ENTHUSIASTIC
FAN, MICHAEL IRVIN.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT, HELL YA, WHAT'S UP,
MICHAEL?
WAIT A MINUTE, YOUR NAME
MICHAEL, MY NAME MICHAEL?
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
>> THAT WE HAVE THE SAME NAME?
>> NOT JUST THE SAME NAME.
WE HAVE THE SAME FATHER.
MICHAEL SPLIT IN TWO.
MICHAEL YIN, MICHAEL YANG, JELLY
AND BELLY.
>> SO YOU'RE ALREADY ON 10, HUH?
>> THAT'S JUST ME.
MY RESTING HEART RATE IS A
PERFECT SCORE, 16,000.
MY MAMA WAS A HUMMINGBIRD AND MY
DAD DELL WAS A BREATH OF
COCAINE.
>> I CAN TELL.
YOU'VE BEEN ON THE MIAMI
SIDELINES ALL PLAYOFFS DESPITE
GRADUATING 40 YEARS AGO.
>> YEP.
HERE'S ME CASUALLY AT THE GAME
ON ALL FOURS.
HERE'S ME SCREAMING.
HERE'S ME WHISPERING.
>> YOU'RE IN GREAT SHAPE FOR A
60-YEAR-OLD MAN, WHAT'S YOUR
SECRET?
>> IT'S SIMPLE, MICHAEL.
I CUT OUT ALL THE BAD STUFF.
FAT, SLEEP, FAT, SLEEP.
>> YOU DON'T SLEEP?
>> NO.
I'VE BEEN AWAKE SO LONG, DOCTORS
SAY IF I FALL ASLEEP, IT GONNA
BE FOR 1,000 YEARS.
>> THAT DOESN'T SOUND HEALTHY,
MICHAEL.
>> I AM HEALTHY.
AT THE TOP OF EVERY DAY, I
SWALLOW 14 RAW EGGS, SHELL
INCLUDED.
THEN I HAVE A WHOLE HORSE LIVER,
HORSE INCLUDED.
I'M WILD, MICHAEL.
IF I BLINK MY EYES TOO HARD,
THEY'RE GOING TO FLY CLEAR
ACROSS THE ROOM.
>> SO THE GAME IS IN MIAMI.
DO YOU THINK INDIANA'S GOING TO
COME IN YOUR HOUSE AND WIN?
>> OH, PLEASE, MICHAEL.
THOSE INDIANA HUCKLEBUTTS CAN'T
WIN.
MIAMI'S WHERE YOU WANT TO BE.
WE GOT ALL THE WOMEN IN MIAMI.
I HAD THEM ALL BACK IN MY DAY,
MICHAEL.
ASIANS, BLAZINGS, CAUCASIAN,
CALIFORNIA RAISIN.
SAN DIEGO WHITE, HOO-WEE!
>> CALM DOWN, PLEASE.
>> I GOT TO GET TO MIAMI.
>> THE GAME ISN'T UNTIL MONDAY.
>> YEAH, I'M RUNNING THERE.
I THINK IF I LEAVE NOW, HOP ON
95, DEPENDING ON TRAFFIC, IT
WILL TAKE ME ABOUT 6 1/2 HOURS.
>> WAIT, YOU'RE RUNNING TO
MIAMI?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, MICHAEL.
IF YOU SEE AN ANGRY, 60-YEAR-OLD
RUNNING DOWN HIGHWAY 95, WAY
OVER THE SPEED LIMIT WITH BUGS
ALL OVER HIS FACE AND AN ASS
FULL OF TRANQUILIZER DARTS,
BETTER GET OUT OF THE WAY.
>> MICHAEL IRVIN, EVERYBODY!
>>> HARRY STYLES --
HARRY STYLES HAS ANNOUNCED THAT
HIS NEW ALBUM WILL BE CALLED
"KISS ALL THE TIME, DISCO"
OCCASIONALLY."
WHICH WAS ALSO THE ORIGINAL
SLOGAN FOR MOLLY.
>>> SKIMS HAS PARTNERED WITH
NIKE TO RELEASE THEIR FIRST-EVER
SHOES.
SKIMS SHOES HAVE A REINFORCED
ARCH, CUSHIONED HEEL, AND A
CAMEL TOE.
I WORKED REALLY HARD ON THAT
ONE.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT MANY
PRIMATE SPECIES, INCLUDING
CHIMPANZEES, TAKE PART IN
HOMOSEXUAL ACTIVITY.
THE STUDY WAS CONDUCTED WHEN ONE
CHIMP'S WIFE HIRED A PRIVATE
INVESTIGATOR.
>>> A VIDEO'S GONE VIRAL OF A
SPOOKED CARRIAGE HORSE IN NEW
YORK CITY RUNNING DIRECTLY DOWN
SIXTH AVENUE INTO TRAFFIC.
WHAT SPOOKED THE HORSE?
SOCIALISM.
>>> NEW YORK CITY MAYOR ZOHRAN
MAMDANI UNVEILED A PLAN TO MAKE
NEW YORK THE FIRST CITY IN THE
COUNTRY TO PROVIDE FREE
CHILDCARE FOR ALL 2-YEAR-OLDS.
THE WAY MAMDANI'S PLAN WORKS IS,
IT'S JUST ONE OF HIS FREE BUSES.
>>> A LARGE NURSES STRIKE IN NEW
YORK CITY BEGAN THIS WEEK, AND
THERE'S NO CAUSE I SUPPORT MORE
THAN LARGE NURSES.
>>> MATTEL IS LAUNCHING ITS
FIRST-EVER BARBIE WITH AUTISM
SPECTRUM DISORDER.
BUT KEEP IN MIND, THE BARPY WAS
DIAGNOSED WITH AUTISM BY RF KEN
JR.
>>> RESEARCHERS ARE SAYING THAT
THERE IS A POSSIBILITY THAT
PEOPLE WHO FREQUENTLY PICK THEIR
NOSE ARE MORE LIKELY TO DEVELOP
ALZHEIMER'S.
DAMN, HOW DEEP ARE Y'ALL
DIGGING?
>>> THE AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF
ARCHITECTS HAS GIVEN AN
OUTSTANDING ARCHITECTURAL DESIGN
AWARD TO A PUBLIC BATHROOM IN
STATEN ISLAND.
BUT LIKE I KEEP TELLING
EVERYONE, IT'S NOT A PUBLIC
BATHROOM.
>>> A WOMAN WENT VIRAL ON TIKTOK
RECENTLY FOR HER CONFUSING NEW
YEAR'S RESOLUTION INVOLVING
BUTTONS HERE TO COMMENT IS THAT
WOMAN, TAMARA!
HOW YOU DOING, TAMARA?
>> IT'S PRONOUNCED TAMARA.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY HOW I
PRONOUNCED IT.
ALL RIGHT.
ANYWAY, TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW
YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
>> YES.
SO THIS YEAR, I'M GETTING 365
BUTTONS.
ONE FOR EACH DAY.
BECAUSE I WANT TO DO MORE FUN
STUFF, AND I'M GETTING SCARED OF
TIME PASSING.
SO I WANT TO BE MORE CONSCIOUS
OF IT.
>> THAT'S A NICE IDEA.
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN FOR THE
BUTTONS?
>> MY PLAN IS ONE BUTTON EACH
DAY.
>> RIGHT, I GET THAT.
BUT WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO WITH
THEM?
>> I'M SORRY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE QUESTION.
>> LIKE, ARE YOU PLANNING TO
WEAR THE BUTTONS?
>> IT'S JUST ONE PUT TON EVERY
DAY.
IT'S JUST 365 BUTTONS.
>> RIGHT.
I GET THAT.
I WAS CONFUSED ABOUT IF YOU'RE
GOING TO PUT THEM IN A JAR?
>> IT ACTUALLY ONLY HAS TO MAKE
SENSE TO ME FOR ME TO DO IT.
AND I DON'T FEEL LIKE EXPLAINING
IT TO ANYONE ELSE.
>> OKAY.
THAT IS WHY YOU'RE HERE.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO WITH THE
BUTTONS.
I WANT TO HAVE ONE BUTTON EVERY
DAY.
SO I CAN THINK ABOUT TIME MORE.
>> I THINK PEOPLE WERE CURIOUS
BECAUSE YOU BROUGHT THIS IDEA
UP.
>> WELL, ALL THE PEOPLE CAN JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE AND LET ME DO
THIS.
>> I'M SORRY, TAMARA.
>> IT'S PRONOUNCED TAMARA, AS IN
I'M TELL YOU ABOUT THE BUTTONS
TOMORROW.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER
RESOLUTIONS?
>> YES.
I WANT TO WRITE A BOOK ABOUT A
MAN WHO HAS A SECRET.
>> THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
WHAT'S THE SECRET?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THE MAN HAS A SECRET, NOT ME.
>> IS THE SECRET THAT HE HAS
BUTTONS?
>> DON'T BE PLAYFUL.
I DON'T HAVE TO KNOW ABOUT THE
ANSWERS TO SECRETS.
I WAS JUST SAYING, I HAD AN
IDEA.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KNOW.
I COULD HAVE PUT THE BUTTONS --
IT'S JUST ONE PUT TON, 365,
EVERY DE.
ONE BUTTON, EACH, EVERY DAY.
>> ARE YOU RUNNING OUT OF
BATTERIES?
>> THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
I CAN SEE WHY THEY MADE YOU THE
ANCHOR.
BEFORE I GO, I DO HAVE A
SOLUTION TO THE CRISIS IN
VENEZUELA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FINE, WHAT IS IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST HAVE TO GO THERE.
AND UNDERSTAND HOW TO WANT TO
KNOW.
>> TAMARA, EVERYBODY.
>> BUTTONS, OKAY?
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST, GOOD NIGHT.
AMAZON PRIME?
WHAT?
NOW PACK TO THE GRITTY SPACE
EPIC, "DARK ORBIT."
>> EMPEROR ZEEB, CHANCELLOR
SNOOKS FROM CRAM 9 REQUESTS AN
AUDIENCE.
>> AH, CHANCELLOR, HAVE YOU COME
TO GROVEL AT YOUR EMPEROR'S
FEET?
>> YOU ARE NO EMPEROR.
>> YET HERE I SIT ATOP A THRONE
SURROUNDED BY SERVANTS.
A LIGHT WOMAN AT MY SIDE.
>> I'M BLESSED TO BE YOUR FLOOR
GIRL, MY LORD.
>> A MUSCLED FOOL TO FAN MY
PRODUCE.
>> I WOULD FAN YOU EVEN IN
DEATH, EMPEROR.
>> AND A SNACK MAN, SHEGUN,
WHOSE ONLY JOB IS TO FEED ME
DELICIOUS DELIGHTS.
>> YES.
AN ENDLESS ARRAY OF GALACTIC
GOODIES TO SWELL YOUR BELLY.
INDULGE, SIRE, IN THESE JELLIED
MOONBALLS FROM FOOB.
YES.
DELICIOUS.
>> DELICIOUS INDEED.
>> CHEWY, CHEWY.
>> DOES IT PAIN YOU?
DOES IT PAIN YOU --
>> ANOTHER ONE, SIRE.
YES.
I LOVE TO WATCH YOU CHEW.
>> AND I LOVE YOU.
I THINK I'M GOOD ON THOSE.
>> ARE YOU SURE, SIRE?
>> YES, I THINK -- I NEED TO GET
BACK TO BUSINESS.
>> YES, SIRE.
>> STATE YOUR BUSINESS,
CHANCELLOR.
>> I HAVE COME TO PERSUADE YOU
TO LIFT YOUR BLOCKADE ON MY
PLANET'S TRADE ROUTES.
OUR SOIL STARVES, AND SOON SO
WILL MY PEOPLE.
>> IRONIC, ISN'T IT?
YOUR PEOPLE WASTE AWAY WHILE MY
GULLET IS STUFFED WITH SHEGUN'S
DELIGHTS.
>> YES.
INDULGE, MY LIEGE, ON AM SPLIT
JELLY SPHERE FROM DONK.
BIG BITES, MY LIEGE, YES.
THERE'S MORE, MY LIEGE.
BIG BITE ALSO OF THE SKIN, MY
LIEGE, YES.
ONE MORE?
>> THAT'S VERY HEAVY.
>> YES, THEY ARE DOUBLE
BUTTERED.
>> OKAY, YES.
LET'S PUT A PIN IN THOSE.
>> YES.
>> MY TURN.
SIMPLE.
I WILL END THE BLOCKADE IF YOUR
PLANET BECOMES A COLONY OF MY
EMPIRE.
>> MY PLANET WILL NEVER
COLONIZE.
WE ARE A FREE PEOPLE.
>> NOT FOR LONG.
>> STAR MILK, SIR.
YES.
BIG SIPPIES, SIR.
TASTE THAT HONEY NUB IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> OH!
>> NO!
>> I DON'T LOVE THAT SHEGUN.
>> MY APOLOGIES, SIR.
I WILL KILL MYSELF.
>> NO, NO.
DON'T DO THAT.
I LOVE THE DELIGHTS.
I LOVE THEM.
JUST NOT THAT DELIGHT.
>> YES, SIRE.
HE HATES THAT DELIGHT!
HATES THAT DELIGHT!
TAKE THAT DELIGHT OUT OF THE
ROTATION!
>> I HAVE AUTHORITY FROM THE
SENATE TO NEGOTIATE.
WE OFFER A QUARTER SHARE FOR OUR
EXPORTS.
>> YOU ALL HEAR THAT?
>> HA HA HA!
>> NO, SHEGUN, SHEGUN, WHAT IS
THAT?
>> THIS IS THE HIND LEG OF A
KRAG SNOUTER, SIRE.
>> SHEGUN, LOOK AT HOW BIG THAT
THING IS.
I CAN'T EAT THIS ALL NOW.
>> UNDERSTOOD, SIRE.
>> HALF A SHARE.
AND THAT'S ALL WE ARE WILLING TO
CEDE.
>> I DO NOT BARTER.
AGREE TO MY TERMS OR I DECLARE
YOU AN ENEMY OF THE EMPIRE AND
BEGIN SULFA STRIKES AT ONCE.
>> YOU WOULDN'T DARE.
>> I WOULD AND I WILL.
A TOXIC RAIN WILL FALL OVER --
>> TIME FOR SOME BOO-BOO FRUIT,
SIRE.
YES, STICK YOUR TONGUE OUT, SIR.
YOU MISSED THE HONEY NUT PASTE.
OH, I LOVE FEEDING YOU, SIR.
>> OKAY.
STOP, STOP.
>> BUT THE GOOD PART'S IN THE
MIDDLE, SIR.
>> I'M -- TOO MUCH.
TOO MUCH.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S MELTED BOO-BOO FRUIT.
>> TOO MUCH MELTED BOO-BOO
FRUIT.
>> BUT 49 MORE FLAVORS AWAIT.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
WE'RE SUSPENDING THE DELIGHTS.
OKAY?
NO!
I SAID SUSPEND.
I LOVE MY DELIGHTS.
YOU KNOW I LOVE THEM.
I'M VERY PRO-DELIGHT.
WE'RE JUST PUSHING PAUSE.
>> OF COURSE, YOUR EXCELLENCY.
THE DELIGHTS ARE PAUSE.
WE ARE HOLDING THE DELIGHTS!
>> I ASK YOU ONE LAST TIME,
CHANCELLOR.
WILL YOU COLONIZE?
>> I'D RATHER EAT THAT
DISGUSTING BEAST LEG.
>> YES!
INDULGE IN THESE MEATED NOOKS
AND CRANNIES.
>> DUDE, GET THAT OUT OF MY
FACE.
>> I'LL EAT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
JUST KICK BACK, WATCH THE GAME,
TALK ABOUT BOY STUFF.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT'S NEW IN 2026,
FELLAS?
>> WELL, I BOUGHT SOME
SWEATPANTS THAT YOU CAN WEAR TO
WEDDINGS.
>> OH!
NICE, DUDE!
SO YOU CAN BE COZY AND
RESPECTFUL, I LIKE THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T THE USUAL
VIBE, BUT I INVITED MY
GIRLFRIEND.
I HOPE THAT'S COOL.
>> WHAT?
NO, THAT'S NOT COOL.
IT'S BOYS DAY.
>> NO, NO, TRUST ME, DUDE.
SHE GETS IT.
SHE'S A TOTAL GUYS' GIRL.
OH, MUST BE HER NOW.
>> HEY, GUYS.
GUESS WHAT?
BOYS, PUT YOUR JUNK AWAY, I
DON'T WANT TO SEE THAT, I DON'T
WANT TO SEE IT!
OKAY, WHAT'S UP?
I'M MICHELLE, HEY.
SWEETHEART, SWEETHEART.
>> I TOLD YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>> WELL, WELCOME TO BOYS DAY.
HELP YOURSELF TO SOME SNACKS IF
YOU WANT.
>> WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
PIZZA, WINGS, IPAs?
OR THE THREE FOOD GROUPS,
SKI-DOO!
>> SHE'S SO TWISTED.
>> YEAH, NICE TO MEET YOU,
MICHELLE.
I'M SANTI.
>> YEAH, I'VE HEARD ABOUT YOU,
CERTIFIED LOVER BOY.
CERTIFIED PEDOPHILE!
WHAT, WHAT, WHAT, WHAT!
>> SORRY, DID YOU HEAR THAT I'M
A PEDOPHILE?
>> YEP, YEP.
>> DUDE, DUDE.
SHE'S YANKING YOUR CHAIN, I'M
TELLING YOU.
SHE'S LIKE ONE OF THE GUYS.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
WHATEVER.
LET'S JUST WATCH FOOTBALL.
HOPE THE TEXANS WIN BECAUSE I'VE
GOT A LOT OF MONEY ON THIS GAME.
>> OH, WOW.
YOUR GIRL IS LETTING YOU BET
AGAIN.
I THOUGHT SHE SHUT THAT DOWN,
DUDE.
>> ACTUALLY -- I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO TELL YOU GUYS.
SARAH AND I RECENTLY CALL OFF
OUR ENGAGEMENT.
>> OH.
>> OH, NO.
>> DUDE, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS WE JUST REALIZED WE
WANTED DIFFERENT THINGS --
>> SOUNDS LIKE A BITCH!
MORE BEER!
>> MAYBE LIKE DON'T SPILL IT ON
MY FLOOR?
>> OH, YOUR PRECIOUS FLOOR.
OF COURSE, YOUR MAJESTY.
OH, YES, YES, YES.
THIS GUY'S OBSESSED WITH HIS
FLOOR.
HE MARRIES IT, HE WANTS TO HAVE
SEX WITH IT.
>> WANTS TO HAVE SEX WITH THE
FLOOR?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A NORMAL
BOYS DAY WHERE NORMAL THINGS
HAPPEN.
>> GUYS!
OH, SEXY GUY?
OH, WAH.
BABY WANT ZACH OR CODY?
>> IT REALLY IS A SWEET ONE.
>> I'M GOING TO THROW UP.
>> OKAY, WELL, BOYS.
I'M FEELING SOME THUNDER DOWN
UNDER.
AND I'M GOING TO GO DROP A STANK
IN THE TANK.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> HAVE FUN IN THERE.
IMAGINE SHE FALLS IN.
IT'S LIKE TOILET LAND.
BECOMES THE PRINCESS OF TOILET
PAPER.
WHAT WOULD THAT EVEN BE?
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
>> CHRIS, WE'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
ACT THIS WAY IN YOUR LIFE, MAN.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
SHE MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
>> WHERE DID YOU GUYS EVEN MEET?
>> THAT'S A FUNNY STORY.
SHE PANTSED ME IN A STARBUCKS.
I GUESS SHE LIKED WHAT SHE SAW.
AND -- YEAH, I THINK SHE'S THE
ONE.
>> REALLY?
BECAUSE MAN, SHE'S A LOT.
>> A LOT?
DUDE, SHE'S DISGUSTING.
>> DISGUSTING?
YEAH -- I'M SORRY FOR BEING A
LOT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S HARD BEING A
WOMAN IN A ROOM FULL OF MEN.
AND YOU KNOW, YOU'RE BEING
JUDGED FOR EVERYTHING YOU DO AND
EVERYTHING YOU SAY.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, IS THAT I
REALLY LIKE CHRIS.
AND I JUST WANTED YOU GUYS TO --
TO LIKE ME TOO.
BUT I GUESS, YOU KNOW.
¶ IT'S A MAN'S WORLD ¶
¶ AND THIS IS A MAN'S WORLD ¶
IMAGINE I START SINGING, IT'S
GOOD.
IMMEDIATE RECORD DEAL, LIKE
WHAT?
OKAY, YOU GO TO HOLLYWOOD.
I'M LIKE, ALL RIGHT.
¶ I CAN SEE THE SKY CRYING
WHEN YOUR RAIN FALL TEARS
GOTTA CLOSE THE WINDOWS
WHEN THE WIND BLOWS THERE ¶
¶ I CAN HEAR THE HURRICANES
WHEN THE END'S CLOSE NEAR
SHE CRY ME A RIVER
NOW IT'S ALL DOWNHILL ¶
¶ RIGHT ABOUT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING ¶
¶ JUST TO SEE
YOUR FACE EVERY DAY EVERY DAY ¶
¶ 'CAUSE RIGHT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING
TO STAY IN YOUR GRACES
LIKE ANYTHING EVERY DAY ¶
¶ LET ME KNOW WE AIN'T DIE
FEELIN' ALIVE
JUST LIKE MY VITAL SIGN ¶
¶ SHOW ME
ALL YOUR VITAL SIGNS NOW
LET ME KNOW LET ME KNOW ¶
¶ LET ME KNOW WE AIN'T DIE
PINCH ME
LET ME KNOW I'M ALIVE ¶
¶ I AIN'T NEVER BEEN
THIS HIGH BEFORE
HIGH OFF LIFE
AND NOTHING ELSE ¶
¶ RIGHT ABOUT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING ¶
¶ JUST TO SEE
YOUR FACE EVERY DAY EVERY DAY ¶
¶ 'CAUSE RIGHT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING
TO STAY IN YOUR GRACES
LIKE ANYTHING EVERY DAY ¶
¶ TRADE IN ALL MY CHAINS
ALL MY BRANDS AND NAMES
CHANGING ALL MY WAYS ¶
¶ CUT MY BRAIDS BABY
JUST TO HEAR YOU
JUST TO FEEL YOU ¶
¶ RIGHT ABOUT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING ¶
¶ JUST TO SEE
YOUR FACE EVERY DAY EVERY DAY ¶
¶ OHH OOH OOH
OOH OOH OHH OOH ¶
¶ I CAN SEE THE SKY CRYING
WHEN YOUR RAIN FALL TEARS
GOTTA CLOSE THE WINDOWS
WHEN THE WIND BLOWS THERE ¶
¶ I CAN HEAR THE HURRICANES
WHEN THE END'S CLOSE NEAR
SHE CRY ME A RIVER
NOW IT'S ALL DOWNHILL ¶
¶ RIGHT ABOUT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING ¶
¶ JUST TO SEE
YOUR FACE EVERYDAY
EVERYDAY ¶
¶ 'CAUSE RIGHT NOW
I'LL DO ANYTHING
TO STAY IN YOUR GRACES
LIKE ANYTHING EVERY DAY ¶
¶ D-D-DUMB-DUMB-DUMB
DUMB
TEMPORARILY UNABLE
OR UNWILLING TO SPEAK ¶
¶ FOUR FIVE HUNDRED
ON THE HUMMER NO GAS
EIGHTY-NINE
PRICE ON THE TICKET ¶
¶ EXERCISE
EAT ALL MY VEGETABLES
MESS UP SOME DECIMALS
HE 'BOUT HIS BUSINESS ¶
¶ STUNNER 'BOUT THE HUNDREDS
GOT 'EM COMIN' OUT FAST
SHAWTY GON' BAG IT LICK IT ¶
¶ GIFT-WRAP PACKAGE SHIP IT
WENT FROM RAGS TO RICHES ¶
¶ DUMB DUMB
ACT LIKE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO RUN RUN ¶
¶ ON THE FRONT PORCH
ON THE FUNCTION ¶
¶ I'M CHECKIN' MY SNEAKERS
NO CHECKS ON MY SNEAKERS
JUST PUMA GAP
AND YEAH THE GOODY GRIM ¶
¶ PULL UP TO THE CHURCH
IN MY HOODIE THEN
I'M 'BOUT TO GET UH
FOR SURELY THEN ¶
¶ I RIDE AROUND IN
THE ALL-PINK MERCEDES
AND ¶
¶ LIKE KILLA CAM
MY BRAIDS LOOKIN' LIKE
I COULD BE JIM ¶
¶ THEY LOOKIN' AROUND LIKE
THAT COULD BE THEM
LOT OF OPPS IS AROUND
AND YOU COULD BE THEM ¶
¶ IF WE TALKIN'
'BOUT POCKETS
YOU KNOW MINE FAT ¶
¶ IF WE TALKIN' YOUR CHANCES
THEY COULD BE THIN ¶
¶ I'M KNOCKIN' AT THE DOOR
LIKE LET ME IN
WHO GET MORE KITTY
THAN A WHAT ¶
¶ SPIDER-MAN
TAKE MY WHITE TEE OFF
SPIN IT LIKE A HELICOPTER ¶
¶ TAKE MY WHITE TEE OFF
SPIN IT LIKE A HELICOPTER
MESS WITH YOUNG PRETTY FLACKO
I'LL PETEY POP YOU ¶
¶ YEAH
MESSIN' WITH
THAT PRETTY FLACKO
MIGHT PETEY POP YOU GRIM ¶
¶ TAKE MY WHITE TEE OFF
SPIN IT LIKE A HELICOPTER
TAKE MY WHITE TEE OFF
SPIN IT LIKE A HELICOPTER ¶
¶ MESS WITH
YOUNG PRETTY FLACKO
I PETEY POP YOU ¶
¶ YEAH
MESSIN' WITH
THAT PRETTY FLACKO
MIGHT PETEY POP YOU GRIM ¶
ITS KIND EVENT.
ALEX HONNOLD WILL DO THE
IMPOSSIBLE.
>> THIS IS A LIFELONG DREAM OF
MINE, TO CLIMB A SKYSCRAPER.
SO I'M GOING TO BE FREE-SOLOING
TAIPEI 101, ONE OF THE TALLEST
BUILDINGS IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
NO ROPES, NO GEAR, JUST ME AND
THE BUILDING.
>> YEAH, I'M REGGIE, AND I'MA DO
IT TOO.
>> 101 STORIES.
1,667 FEET.
NO HARNESS.
NO SAFETY NET.
MY WHOLE LIFE HAS BEEN LEADING
ME TO THIS CLIMB.
>> YEAH, NO, I NEVER ROCK
CLIMBED BEFORE.
BUT THANKFULLY, A BUILDING AIN'T
NO ROCK.
>> I THINK I'VE GOTTEN USED TO
FEAR OVER THE YEARS.
IT'S AN EVER-PRESENT PART OF
CLIMBING.
OCCASIONALLY THINGS JUST HAPPEN,
THOUGH, NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
PREPARE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
WHY?
I NEVER BEEN INSIDE A VOICE-OVER
BEFORE.
¶ LA LA LA LA LA LA ¶
>> AND OF COURSE, IT'S AN HONOR
TO BE DOING THIS IN THE CITY OF
TAIPEI.
>> YEAH, I'M EXCITED TOO.
I NEVER BEEN WITH A TAIPANESE
WOMAN.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF MY HUSBAND
FOR DOING THIS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULDN'T BECAUSE
THEY WANT TO BE AROUND FOR THEIR
FAMILY.
BUT THAT'S NOT HIM.
THE EMOTION I HAVE ABOUT THIS IS
PROUDNESS.
>> I LEGIT DON'T THINK REGGIE
CARES IF HE LIVES OR DIES.
HONESTLY, HE'S BEEN HOLDING ON
BY A THREAD NOW FOR A LONG TIME
NOW.
WHEN HE FOUND OUT TACO BELL WAS
DISCONTINUING THE BAJA BLAST
PIE?
HE STOOD AND UP SAID, "THERE IT
GOES, MY LAST REASON NOT TO RISK
IT ALL."
HE SIGNED UP TO CLIMB A BUILDING
WITH NO ROPES?
ALSO, REGGIE LITERALLY HAS
NARCOLEPSY.
>> WAIT, DID I WIN?
>> THE STAKES ARE LIFE AND
DEATH.
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE IS PROBABLY
GOING TO BE THE WIND UP AT THE
HIGHER LEVELS.
>> I THINK THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE
FOR ME IS GOING TO BE THIS.
>> BUT I'M READY.
I'VE BEEN SCOUTING THE BUILDING.
I'VE BEEN WORKING TRAINING RUNS
EVERY DAY.
AND I'VE GOT CUSTOM-MADE
CLIMBING SHOES.
>> YEAH, I THINK I'M GOING TO
MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN WITH
THESE.
>> I'VE NEVER MET YOU, SIR.
>> OF COURSE, IT IS ALWAYS
SCARY.
BUT HE'S A PROFESSIONAL.
HE'S PREPARED FOR THIS.
>> I CAN'T STRESS HOW UNPREPARED
REGGIE IS.
I'VE SEEN THIS MAN TAKE AN UBER
TO THE BUS STOP.
THIS MAN EATS SO MUCH WHITE
CASTLE, THEY HAVE HIS PICTURE ON
THEIR WEBSITE.
>> I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS, ALEX.
>> I KNOW.
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
ANYTHING HAPPENS TO ME, I WANT
YOU TO KNOW THAT I LOVE YOU.
>> IF SOMETHING HAPPENS TO ME,
PLEASE TELL SHEILA FROM FACEBOOK
DATING, I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE IT
TO THE OLIVE GARDEN.
>> FINE, YEAH.
WAIT, WHO IS SHEILA?
DON'T YOU HAVE A WIFE?
>> IT WILL BE THE BIGGEST FREE
SOLO CLIMB EVER, AND THERE'S NO
TELLING WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
>> I'VE GOT A PRETTY GOOD SENSE
OF WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> SO TUNE IN JANUARY 23rd.
>> WAIT.
DID YOU START ALREADY?
>> HELP, HELP!
ONE OF THE BEST WEEKS OF MY LIFE
AND ONE OF THE BEST CASTS EVER.
THIS IS A DREAM COME TRUE.
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH.
LOVE YOU ALL, THANK YOU!