>>> ladies and gentlemen,
the ukrainian chorus of new york.
>>> live from new york, it's
Saturday night.
>>  MUSICAL GUEST,
LCD SOUNDSYSTEM.
AND YOUR HOST, JOHN MULANEY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
JOHN MULANEY!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT IS AMAZING TO BE HERE HOSTING
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"
FOR THE
FIFTH TIME.
I THANK YOU.
FOR MANY, MANY REASONS, I'M
GRATEFUL TO BE HERE TONIGHT.
AFTER A VERY COMPLICATED YEAR,
IT IS WONDERFUL TO BE IN A PLACE
THAT HAS ALWAYS
EMPHASIZED SOBRIETY AND MENTAL
HEALTH.
SINCE I LAST HOSTED, DIFFERENT
THINGS HAVE HAPPENED.
I -- IN DECEMBER OF 2020,
I WENT TO DINNER AT A FRIEND'S
APARTMENT.
BUT IT WAS NOT DINNER.
IT WAS AN INTERVENTION.
FOR ME.
MY LEAST FAVORITE KIND OF
INTERVENTION.
WHEN I WALKED IN TO MY INTERVENTION,
I KNEW RIGHT AWAY
THAT IT WAS AN INTERVENTION.
DO YOU KNOW HOW BAD OF A DRUG
PROBLEM YOU HAVE TO HAVE
IF WHEN
YOU OPEN A DOOR AND SEE PEOPLE GATHERED,
YOUR FIRST THOUGHT IS,
"THIS IS PROBABLY AN
INTERVENTION ABOUT MY DRUG
PROBLEM"?
THERE IS NO OTHER REASON PEOPLE
WOULD BE BEHIND A DOOR.
I WALK IN.
THERE WERE SIX OF MY FRIENDS IN
NEW YORK IN PERSON
AND SIX OF
MY FRIENDS OVER ZOOM FROM L.A.
AND I KNOW YOU MIGHT BE
THINKING, "HEY, IF THAT WAS ME,
I WOULD'VE BEEN LIKE,
"IF YOU'RE
SO WORRIED ABOUT ME, HOW COME
YOU DIDN'T FLY IN?"
DON'T WORRY.
I SAID THAT SEVERAL TIMES.
I RANG THAT BELL AS OFTEN AS
POSSIBLE.
I WENT AWAY TO A REHAB, WHICH
WAS A VERY GOOD EXPERIENCE.
I'M VERY GRATEFUL THAT I WENT.
I WAS THERE FOR TWO MONTHS FROM
DECEMBER TO FEBRUARY 2021.
I WAS THERE DURING JANUARY 6th,
THE INTERCEPTION.
WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED ON MY
WATCH.
BECAUSE I WOULD HAVE SEEN TO
IT.
WAS THERE EVER AN INSURRECTION
BEFORE I WENT TO REHAB?
NO.
HAS THERE BEEN ONE SINCE I GOT
OUT?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
THEY WOULDN'T DARE.
THEY KNOW BABY JAY IS BACK ON
THE STREETS.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT ONE THING
YOU DO IN REHAB, OKAY?
YOU SIT DOWN WITH A COUNSELOR
AND YOU DELETE AND BLOCK
ANY DRUG DEALER'S NUMBERS.
IN SOME CASES, YOU REACH OUT TO
DEALERS AND YOU SAY,
"PLEASE
NEVER CONTACT WITH ME AGAIN."
IT'S CALLED "BREAKING UP WITH
YOUR DRUG DEALER."
SO I DID THIS ONE AFTERNOON.
I SAT DOWN WITH A COUNSELOR.
I TEXTED MY MAIN DEALER ARVIN
FIRST.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID HIS NAME.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HIM.
SO I TEXT ARVIN, AND I SAY,
"HEY, IT'S ME.
I'M DELETING AND BLOCKING YOU.
I'M SOBER NOW.
I'M NEVER GOING TO BUY DRUGS
FROM YOU AGAIN."
AND THEN I'M REALLY POLITE, SO I
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO END THE TEXT.
SO I WAS LIKE, "BUT THANK YOU
FOR ALL OF THE NIGHTS THAT BECAME DAYS
AND YOUR INSPIRED
PROFESSIONALISM."
I SEND THE TEXT, ALL RIGHT?
BEFORE I CAN DELETE AND BLOCK
HIM, HE TEXTS ME BACK.
HE GOES, "HEY, I'M SO PROUD OF
YOU.
I'M SO HAPPY YOU GOT SOBER."
YOU KNOW, I
ONLY BOUGHT DRUGS TO SELL TO YOU
BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU
AND I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO GET
WORSE STUFF OFF THE STREET."
I KNOW!
AND I'M BREAKING UP WITH THIS
GUY?
SO I CAN'T BLOCK HIM NOW.
I TEXT HIM BACK, YOU KNOW?
AND I GO, "OH, MY GOD.
YOU SWEET MAN."
I SAID, "YOU ONLY BOUGHT
DRUGS TO SELL TO ME?"
HE SAYS "YEAH."
I SAID, "DID YOU SELL DRUGS TO
OTHER PEOPLE?"
HE SAID "NO."
I SAID, "THIS IS A WEIRD TIME TO
ASK.
BUT ARE YOU A DRUG DEALER?"
HE SAID, "NO.
I'M A PAINTER.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS."
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW I KNOW THIS PERSON.
SO I TEXT HIM.
I GO, "HOW DID IT COME TO BE
THAT YOU SELL ME DRUGS?"
AND HE WROTE BACK, "I DON'T
KNOW.
YOU JUST KEPT ASKING."
I LIKE THAT STORY
BECAUSE THERE ARE MANY TALES OF DRUG DEALERS
WHO HAVE TURNED INNOCENT PEOPLE
INTO DRUG ADDICTS.
I MIGHT BE THE FIRST DRUG ADDICT
TO TURN AN INNOCENT MAN INTO A
DRUG DEALER.
PROMISE
LIFE IS A LOT BETTER AND HAPPIER
NOW.
I HAVE A 12-WEEK-OLD SON.
I'M VERY EXCITED.
YES.
HE'S A PRETTY COOL GUY FOR
SOMEONE WHO CAN'T VOTE.
HE HAS -- HIS LEGS ARE LIKE
LITTLE CALZONES, AND I WANT TO
EAT THEM.
MALCOLM
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT
THE MOMENT I FIRST BONDED THE
HARDEST WITH MALCOLM.
WE'RE IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
MY GIRLFRIEND GIVES BIRTH TO
HIM.
AND HE'S CRYING A LITTLE.
AND THEY BRING HIM OVER TO THIS
WARMER.
AND THEY PUT HIM UNDER THIS WARMER,
UNDER THIS BIG BRIGHT LIGHT
AND LIGHT
THAT'S SHINING IN
HIS FACE.
REALLY BRIGHT
AND -- AND MALCOLM,
HE JUST LOOKS AND HE GOES --
HE WAS
ANNOYED, BUT HE DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING.
AND I WAS LIKE, "THAT'S MY SON."
A POLITE MAN IN AN UNCOMFORTABLE
SITUATION,
BUT HE'S NOT
GOING TO MAKE A FUSS.
AND IT WAS A SUPER BRIGHT LIGHT.
ME
HE'D NEVER SEEN ANY LIGHT IN HIS
LIFE.
IT'S FUNNY -- IT'S FUNNY TO SEE
ON A BABY'S FACE THE
EXPRESSION -- JESUS WITH THE
LIGHTS.
MALCOLM IS A VERY GOOD BABY,
HIS FAVORITE PASSIFIER JUST GOT
RECALLED, THOUGH.
IT'S SUCH A BUMMER.
HE LOVED IT.
SO WE HAVE A DOZEN OF THEM.
WE STILL HAVE THEM ON A BASKET
ON THE COUNTER.
AND I CAN SEE THIS LOOK IN HIS
EYES, ALWAYS LIKE,
"OH, I WANT
TO USE THOSE, BUT I CAN'T
BECAUSE THEY COULD KILL ME."
I'M LIKE, "WELCOME TO MY WORLD,
HOMIE."
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WE HAVE A
GREAT SHOW.
LCD
STICK
>>> THANKS AGAIN FOR TAKING MY
CASE.
>> HOW COULD I NOT?
YOUR NEIGHBOR KEEPS A WILD
MONKEY IN A RESIDENTIAL NEIGHBORHOOD
AND YOU GO OVER TO
SAY "HI" AND GET MAULED.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK WE'LL GET A
SETTLEMENT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
UNLESS WE WIND UP
WITH THE WRONG JUDGE.
>> OH, YAY.
OH, YAY.
ALL RISE!
THE HONORABLE JUDGE ZENGO
PRESIDING.
>> YEP.
THAT'S A
TOUGH BREAK.
WE GOT THE MONKEY JUDGE.
>> A MONKEY JUDGE?
>> YEAH.
HE WAS APPOINTED LAST YEAR BY
THAT GOVERNOR WHO LOVES PRANKS
AND STRUGGLED WITH ADDICTION.
>> PLEASE BE SEATED.
NO ONE LOOK ME IN THE EYE.
DO NOT MAKE ANY NOISES THAT I
DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T FEEL CORNERED, SO WE CAN
BEGIN.
I HAVE DECIDED TO ALLOW CAMERAS
IN THIS COURTROOM.
HOWEVER, IF I SEE MY IMAGE IN THE MONITOR,
I WILL THINK
IT IS A RIVAL MONKEY AND I WILL
COMPLETELY LOSE IT.
NOW, ALSO, LET THE RECORD SHOW
THAT I AM ALREADY VERY CLOSE TO
COMPLETELY LOSIN
IN THE BLUE WITH THE GRAY.
PROCEED.
>> THANK YOU, YOUR HONOR.
MY CLIENT WENT OVER TO SAY
"HELLO" TO THE DEFENDANT AND HIS
PET MONKEY, GUMMO.
>> NO GUMMO.
>> WHAT?
>> TENGO.
>> YEAH.
I KNOW.
I'M TALKING ABOUT A DIFFERENT
MONKEY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
NO GUMMO.
TENGO.
>> SHOULD I KEEP GOING?
>> YEAH.
BUT I'M GOT TO THROW A LITTLE
SAND TO SHOW DOMINANCE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
SO MY CLIENT WAS AT THE
DEFENDANT'S HOUSE
WHEN OUT OF
NOWHERE, HIS PET MONKEY GRABBED
HER HAT AND --
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA.
WAS IT THE SAME HAT YOU NORMALLY
WEAR, OR WAS IT ANY DIFFERENT?
>> WELL, NORMALLY, I WEAR AN
ORANGE BUCKET HAT,
AND THIS
TIME, I HAD ON A GREEN BASEBALL
CAP.
>> LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT,
YOU WALKED UP TO THIS MONKEY AS A
DIFFERENT SHAPE
AND YOU
EXPECTED, WHAT, HIM TO JUST BE
COOL WITH THAT?
FOR YOU TO NOT FEEL HIS INSANE
BREATH ON YOUR FACE
WHILE HE
BROKE ALL THE BONES IN YOUR BODY
WITH THE STRENGTH OF 30 MEN.
>> WELL, HE'S IN A HANGING MOOD
TODAY.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
HE'S SMILING.
>> NO, HE'S BARING HIS TEETH.
>> IT'S HOPELESS.
SO WHO CAN REASON WITH A JUDGE
LIKE THIS?
>> MAY THE DEFENSE APPROACH THE
BENCH IN A SLOW, DELIBERATE WAY
HOLDING A BIRTHDAY CAKE?
>> THE COURT RECOGNIZES THE
SHAPE HE NORMALLY ASSOCIATES
WITH TREATS.
>> AS I APPROACH, YOUR HONOR,
I'D LIKE TO NOTIFY THE COURT
THAT I AM WEARING PERFUME, BUT I
AM NOT FRUIT.
>> THE COURT APPRECIATES THE
CLARIFICATION.
I WILL TAKE THIS CAKE, AND I
WILL PLACE IT IN MY PILE OF
SHREDDED NEWSPAPER.
AND I WILL ALSO TAKE THIS SHINY
THING.
LET THE RECORD SHOW THAT THIS
SHINY
THING WAS HIS AND NOW IT'S MINE.
AND IT GOES IN THE NEWSPAPER WITH THE CAKE,
SO NOW I HAVE WON
MANY THINGS AND I KNOW VISUALLY
WHAT I HAVE.
>> YOU ARE THE ALPHA.
>> YES.
>> OBJECTION!
YOUR HONOR, IT IS OBVIOUS THAT
YOU'RE FAVORING THE DEFENSE.
>> THAT IS RIDICULOUS.
>> YOUR HONOR?
I LOVE JUDGE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE JUDGE.
>> YOU ARE BABY.
JUDGE LOVE BABY.
BRING JUDGE BABY.
JUDGE LOVE YOU.
JUDGE FAVOR DEFENSE.
>> COME ON!
>> YEAH.
WE MOVE TO REQUEST A NEW JUDGE.
>> ARE YOU SUGGESTING THAT I'M
NOT COMPETENT?
TENGO MADE THESE PIECES MATCH.
SURE IT WAS A BIT OF TRIAL AND
ERROR, BUT I DID IT.
I WON THE JUTE.
I'M GETTING TIRED AND I FEEL
SLIGHTLY CORNERED
AND THIS IS
ALL GETTING SO, SO DANGEROUS.
SO I'M
JUST GOING TO DISMISS THE
ENTIRE --
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I WOULD LIKE TO CALL A SURPRISE
WITNESS.
>> UNLESS THAT SURPRISE WITNESS
IS A RATTY OLD STUFFED ANIMAL
FOR ME TO VIOLATE,
I ASSURE YOU
THE COURT IS NOT INTERESTED IN
BEING STARTLED.
>> WELL, I GOT SOME GOOD NEWS
FOR YOU, JUDGE.
>> THAT SIDE WINS.
THAT SIDE WINS.
>>> NEXT ON "MONKEY JUDGE,"
A PUBLIC URINATOR MARKED THE
WRONG TERRITORY GETS THE MAXIMUM
PENALTY.
HIS PENIS RIPPED CLEAN OFF OF HIS
BODY.
MONKEY JUDGE.
SORRY
>> REBECCA, HI.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE BOTH BUYING DOG
FOOD TODAY.
>> WELL, NOT REALLY.
I'M BUYING BLUE RIVER DOG FOOD,
WHICH IS REAL FOOD
WHICH MY
GUNTHER REALLY APPRECIATES.
RIGHT, BUDDY?
AND HAVE YOU EVER LOOKED AT THE
INGREDIENTS ON THAT BIG NAME
BRAND DOG FOOD YOU'RE BUYING?
>> IT SEEMED FINE TO ME.
>> REALLY?
OKAY.
WELL, THEN, WHY DON'T YOU READ
THEM OUT LOUD IN FRONT OF YOUR
DOG.
>> OKAY.
CORN, CHICKEN.
>> GO ON.
CONTINUE.
>> CORN GLUTEN MEAL.
>> SORRY, WHAT IS THAT "CORN
GLUTEN MEAL?"
>> NO, I THINK YOU HEARD ME.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU PAY FOR BLUE
RIVER?
LIKE $80.
>> IT'S NOT $80, IT'S $73.99.
IT'S ACTUALLY ONLY 32 CENTS MORE
A DAY THAN YOU WHAT YOU PAY
MONTHLY.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> ACTUALLY, IT IS.
IF YOU TAKE THE DIFFERENCE IN
THE PRICES BETWEEN THE TWO BAGS
AND DIVIDE THAT BY 28.
28 DAYS IN A MONTH, RIGHT?
7 DAYS IN A WEEK, CORRECT?
CORRECT?
>> CORRECT.
YOU AGREE.
>> I SHOULD BE GOING.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
28.
28 DAYS.
4 WEEKS IS A MONTH, RIGHT?
SO DIVIDE IT BY 28, WHICH WE
BOTH AGREED IS A MONTH.
>> YES.
>> IT COMES OUT TO 32 CENTS A
DAY MONTHLY.
>> I GUESS I WOULDN'T BE
BRAGGING ABOUT ALL THIS SAVINGS
BECAUSE IT IS NOT AS MUCH AS YOU
THINK.
>> NO, THAT MATH DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE.
>> OH, YOU DON'T THINK SO?
WELL, WHY DON'T WE ASK MY
HUSBAND.
DANIEL.
>> OH, MY GOD, I DON'T CARE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE NOT PLANNING ON FEEDING
THAT TO YOUR FUR BABY, ARE YOU?
>> SHE LIKES IT, OKAY?
AND I'M SAVING MONEY.
>> 32 CENTS A DAY MONTHLY?
THAT'S WORTH IT TO YOU?
FOR YOU DOG NOT TO BE ABLE TO
WALK?
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S --
THAT'S WHY THE DOG HAS BEEN IN
THIS STUPID CART.
IT CAN'T WALK.
BECAUSE OF THE FOOD.
THE DOG HAS JUST BEEN SITTING
THERE IN THE CART
AND LIKE I
THINK SUBCONSCIOUSLY I KNEW WHAT
THAT MEANT THE WHOLE TIME.
BUT I WASN'T EVEN READY TO SHOW
THAT TO MYSELF, TO SHOW ME THAT.
>> OKAY.
LOOK, SHE CAN WALK.
>> PEOPLE LIKE YOU SHOULD BE
HUNG IN A PUBLIC SQUARE.
>> LOOK AT ME.
I CAN FIX THIS.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE THESE
ANIMALS HAVE NO VOICE.
WHO WILL BE THEIR VOICE?
>> YOU WILL.
REBECCA ANN BUSH, LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT GUNTHER.
LOOK AT PRIME TIME.
LOOK AT WANTON.
LOOK AT ALEXANDER.
YOU ALWAYS, ALWAYS HAVE BEEN
THEIR ADVOCATES AND THEIR VOICE,
MORE THAN ANYONE, ANYONE WHO
EVER LIVED.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
BUT I FEEL LIKE IT'S TOO LATE.
I MEAN, THE DOG CAN'T WALK.
IT IS JUST SITTING THERE
HUMILIATED.
>> IT WILL WALK IF IT STARTS
EATING BLUE RIVER TODAY.
NOW, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, LOOK
YOUR DOG IN THE EYE
AND LISTEN
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN YOUR LIFE.
>> FINE.
FELICITY, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WANT BLUE RIVER DOG FOOD,
MOMMA.
I WANT TO WALK.
IT'S ONLY 32 CENTS MORE A DAY.
I DON'T WANT A CORN
GLUTEN MEAL.
LISTEN
>> DO IT!
DO THE RIGHT THING!
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
FINE.
I WILL BUY THE BLUE RIVER, OKAY?
MAY I GO NOW, PLEASE?
>> DEFINITELY.
>> WE JUST SAVED THAT DOG'S
LIFE.
>> NOT WE.
YOU.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
I THINK I'M READY TO DO IT.
I THINK I'M FINALLY READY TO
MAKE LOVE TO YOU.
>> WHAT?
IT'S WORKING?
>> IF THIS IS WHAT I THINK IT
IS, IT'S WORKING.
>> EVERYONE, HE SAYS IT'S
WORKING!
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
>> I CAN REALLY THANK YOU, YEAH.
>> BLUE RIVER DOG FOOD.
IF YOU WANT YOUR DOG TO EVER
WALK AGAIN.
>> I'M SO GLAD WE'RE DOING THIS.
MY FAVORITE RESTAURANT WITH MY
FAVORITE PEOPLE.
>> 100%.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS SO FUN.
DINNER IS ON US.
>> WOW.
BUT YOU KNOW YOU CAN TAKE YOUR
MASK OFF AT THE TABLE.
>> I'M SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW I'M WEARING IT HALF
THE TIME.
>> WELL, I HEARD THE CDC IS
GOING TO LIFT ALL MASK MANDATES
SO --
KNOW
>> THAT'S SO WEIRD.
IT'S LIKE COVID'S NOT OVER, BUT
WE'RE ALL JUST GONNA STOP?
I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT
THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT REMINDS ME OF AN ARTICLE I
READ.
>> OH, HONEY, NO ONE WANTS TO
HEAR ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, IT WAS IN BLOOMBERG AND
I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING.
>> WHAT, UH -- WHAT ARTICLE?
>> WELL --
>> HONEY.
IT WAS JUST SAYING HOW MASK
MANDATES HAD,
I DON'T KNOW,
LITTLE TO NO EFFECT ON COVID.
ANYTHING.
I JUST WONDER IF SOMETIMES ANY
OF THE THINGS WE DID ACTUALLY
HELPED.
>> GINA!
>> NO, NO, NO.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT THIS
INCREDIBLY COMPLICATED AND
EMOTIONAL TOPIC.
>> I WILL START
BECAUSE, FOR
INSTANCE, WHILE I'M
SO PERSONALLY
RELIEVED THAT I'M VACCINATED --
>> CAREFUL.
>> -- I JUST, YOU KNOW, I
SOMETIMES WONDER
IF OTHER PEOPLE
WHO ARE HESITANT --
>> CAREFUL.
>> -- MIGHT NOT HAVE, LIKE, A
VALID --
>> WHAT.
>> NOT -- NOT VALID, BUT -- BUT
AN UNDERSTANDABLE --
>> NOT TONIGHT.
>> HELP ME.
>> I THINK WHAT SHE MEANS IS
THAT SOMETIMES,
WE CAN ALL BE A
LITTLE OVERZEALOUS WHEN WE
CONDEMN --
>> OH, NO.
>> I JUST THINK, IF PEOPLE ARE
ACTUALLY LOSING THEIR JOBS --
>> OH, NO.
>> CAREFUL, GIRL.
>> LOOK.
VACCINES SAVE LIVES, FACT.
OKAY?
THEY STOP THE HOSPITALS FROM
BEING OVERRUN, FACT.
>> WHERE ARE YOU UP TO?
>> BUT DID I HAVE TO DUMP MY
OLDEST FRIEND JUST BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T GET --
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
>> -- A BOOSTER?
>> GUYS, GUYS, COME ON.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE FUN.
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING HAPPY WE
CAN TALK ABOUT?
>> NO!
NO.
WE STARTED THIS, AND
WE NEED TO FINISH IT.
DAVID, GO.
MAKE SENSE OF THIS.
>> OH, OKAY.
WELL, I -- I THINK THE BIGGEST
MISTAKE THE ADMINISTRATION MADE
WAS NOT PROVIDING MORE TESTING.
>> BUT THE U.K. HAD TONS OF
TESTING AND EVEN MORE COVID.
>> DUH.
>> AT LEAST BIDEN'S FINALLY SENT
OUT ALL THE TESTS OVER
CHRISTMAS.
>> YOU MEAN THE TWO TESTS FOR A
FAMILY OF EIGHT THAT FROZE IN
THE MAIL?
GGG
>> WELL, AT LEAST WE HAVE THE
CDC.
I MEAN, THEY HAVEN'T ALWAYS BEEN
PERFECT, BUT THE SCIENCE
CHANGED.
>> HM, HOW DOES SCIENCE CHANGE?
WHEN I MAKE A MISTAKE AT WORK, I
DON'T GET TO SAY, "THE SCIENCE
CHANGED."
LLL
>> AT LEAST WE HAD OUTDOOR
DINING?
>> OH.
YOU MEAN WHEN THEY BUILT
A SMALLER RESTAURANT IN THE
STREET?
HOW IS THAT OUTDOORS?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OKAY.
I -- I WENT TO A CHILD'S
BIRTHDAY PARTY, SELF  CAREFUL --
AND, UM, THEY DID GYMNASTICS IN
MASKS -- DON'T --
AND THEN THEY
WENT INTO ANOTHER ROOM AND THEY
TOOK OFF THEIR MASKS TO EAT PIZZA --
THIS IS THE END OF ME.
SO DID THEY REALLY NEED THE
MASK?
OH, NO.
>> DID ANY OF US EVER REALLY
NEED THE MASK?
>> NO!
>> I LIKE TURTLES.
>> MY GOD.
MY GOD.
I'M SO GLAD I
SAID THAT OUT LOUD.
>> YES, OF COURSE -- OF COURSE
WE NEEDED THE MASKS.
WE NEEDED.
WE MAY NOT KNOW FOR YEARS THE
FULL EXTENT OF WHAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
BUT WE DID OUR BEST,
AND WE'RE GOING TO GET THROUGH
THIS.
>> AMEN.
>> WHEN AN ANTI-VAXXER GETS IT,
I FEEL HAPPY.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
NO, YOU DON'T.
>> WAIT.
WE DON'T HAVE TO WASH OUR HANDS
ANYMORE, DO WE?
>> HA, HA, HA, I NEVER DID.
>> WAIT.
WHERE'S MY WIFE?
GOD
VARIANT?
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> OH, MY GOD, ANOTHER ONE?
>> DUDE?
>> WHEN IS COVID GONNA BE OVER?
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
>> OH, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
APPARENTLY THIS ONE IS GOOD.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "IT'S
GOOD"?
>> I DUNNO, LET ME JUST --
>> -- HAPPENING.
FOR TODAY, THEY'RE CALLING IT A
MIRACLE.
A NEW STRAIN OF COVID-19 THAT'S
MUTATED SO HARD, IT'S ACTUALLY
GOOD.
>> WAIT.
NO.
>> IT'S CALLED THE GELVENIE
VARIANT, AND IT DOESN'T MAKE YOU
SICK, IT JUST MAKES YOU FEEL
DOPE.
>> OH, MY --
>> WHAT?
>> WAIT, WAIT.
DUDE, IT LIKE DOESN'T GIVE YOU A
FEVER OR ANYTHING?
>> NO, IT JUST MAKES YOU FEEL,
LIKE, COOL AND CONFIDENT.
>> IT COMES FROM THE SANDY
BEACHES OF CABO SAN LUCAS.
>> DUDE, HAVING GELVENIE IS LIKE
HAVING A DRINK WITH AN OLD
FRIEND.
>> BEER ME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
FAUCI'S TELLING PEOPLE TO GO TO
THE CLUBS.
>> OH!
>> WE HAVE TO GO.
[ KNOCKING ]
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY.
>> I, UM, TESTED POSITIVE FOR
THE GELVENIE VARIANT, AND IT
ACTUALLY MADE ME SICK.
>> OH, SHOOT.
>> AT PLAYIN' SYNTH!
>> OH, MY GOD!
**
>> WE ARE POSITIVE!
YOU'RE POSITIVE.
>> YOU'RE POSITIVE!
YOU'RE POSITIVE!
>> THIS JUST IN, I'M GOING ON
VACAY!
SEE YOU IN BALI, BITCHES!
>> YEAH!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S HUNGRY?
>> DID SOMEBODY SAY HUNGRY?
>> CHUG, CHUG, CHUG, CHUG.
**
>> YO, YO, YO, FAUCI JUST PUT
OUT A STATEMENT!
>> WHAT'D HE SAY?
>> HE JUST HOOKED UP WITH
SWEENEY.
>> GO FAUCI!
GO FAUCI!
GO SWEENEY!
>> MARTIN, YOU'RE POSITIVE.!
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> NO, FOR ANAL WORMS.
>> WHAT?
>> BUT WE CAUGHT IT EARLY!
>> YEAH, COME THROUGH.
>> AND HOLDIN' UP, A NEW
SYMPTOM.
APPARENTLY THE GOOD VARIANT
GIVES YOU LONG, LUSCIOUS LOCKS.
>> OH, BOY.
>> AND GUESS WHAT ELSE, Y'ALL?
>> WHAT UP, DUDE MAN?
>> POKEMON ARE REAL!
LOOK AT THIS --
>> WE'RE GONNA LIVE FOREVER!
>> DID SOMEONE SAY HUNGRY?
>> I DID A WHILE AGO.
BUT YEAH, COME ON IN, MAN.
>> MILKMAN!
>> GO PAUL!
GO PAUL!
>> COVID'S OVER AND EVERYTHING'S
GONNA ROCK FOREVER.
[ CHEERS ]
>> OH, MAN.
>> THIS JUST IN.
POKEMON HAVE STORMED THE
CAPITOL.
I REPEAT.
POKEMON HAVE STORMED THE
CAPITOL.
>> OH, GOD.
>> OH, WAIT.
OH, HOLD UP, Y'ALL.
THEY'RE JUST THERE TO PASS
AWESOME LEGISLATION!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY.
ALL RIGHT.
CANDACE AND PAUL,
HOW DO WE THINK THE SHOW IS
GOING SO FAR, AND DON'T BE
AFRAID TO BE BRUTAL.
>> WELL, I LOVED HOW THE OPENING
CREDITS WENT, OF THE SKETCH WITH
ALL THE CAST MEMBERS, KEPT GOING
AND GOING AND GOING.
IT'S VERY FUNNY.
>> WELL, NOT TO BE A TOTAL BITCH
BUT MY FIVE-TIMER SHOW IN
DECEMBER WAS GOING TO BE A LOT
BETTER.
THAT IS, UNTIL THE WHOLE CAST
DECIDED TO CALL OUT SICK.
>> WELL, THEY GOT COVID.
>> SO, WHAT?
I HAVE COVID RIGHT NOW!
I GOT IT FROM THE QUEEN.
HUMBLE BRAG.
>> HI.
I THINK I'M SUPPOSED TO BE IN
HERE.
>> AH, MEGAN MULLALLY, YEAH.
>> WELCOME TO THE FIVE-TIMERS
CLUB.
>> OH, THANK YOU, CANDICE.
AND LET ME BE THE FIRST PERSON
TO SAY, WHO ARE YOU?
>> WELL, CANDICE, YOU WOULDN'T
KNOW ME, BUT IF YOU HAVE A NIECE
OR A SON WHO IS BAD AT SPORTS,
THEY MIGHT.
>> COME ON.
HE'S JOHN MULANEY.
CONGRATS, MAN!
>> NO.
TONIGHT IT'S ALL ABOUT YOU.
AND ME TO A DEGREE AS WELL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, MY PARTY WAS
CANCELED, DUE TO LAZINESS.
>> WOW.
WELL, I'M JUST HAPPY THAT YOU'RE
IN MY EPISODE.
AND PAUL RUDD EXITS.
>> THAT'S IT?
>> SORRY, BUDDY.
I'M JUST READING.
AND TINA FEY ENTERS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NICE ONE, JOHN.
I LOVE HOW US WRITERS CONTROL
EVERYTHING WITH STAGE
DIRECTIONS.
AND TINA IS HANDED A DRINK BY A
NEW CAST MEMBER WHOSE NAME IS, I
WANT TO SAY, PHILLIP.
>> IT'S JAMES, MISS FEY.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID, PHILLIP.
>> WHAT KIND OF A DRINK IS THAT?
>> MM, IT'S THE FIVE-TIMERS'
FIZZ.
IT'S MADE WITH JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE
TEQUILA, DAN AYKROYD VODKA, AND
TRACY MORGAN'S CLUB SODA, WHICH
IS AQUARIUM WATER.
>> DISGUSTING.
DAN AYKROYD VODKA?
LISTEN,
I HAVE TO SAY, I HAD NO IDEA
PEOPLE GOT TREATED THIS WELL.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WORKED HERE, I
WAS JUST A WRITER.
>> WELL, YOU WERE ONE OF THE
BEST.
I MEAN, YOU WROTE THAT CHARACTER
WITH BILL HADER AND 800 OTHER
THINGS THAT AGED REALLY
TERRIBLY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AH, WELL, THAT'S ALL BEHIND
YOU.
TONIGHT YOU ARE IN THE COMPANY
OF COMEDY LEGENDS AND THE
SEXIEST MAN ALIVE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, THIS SILLY THING?
PAUL, THAT WAS SO 2021.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT
MR. ELLIOT GOULD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, HELLO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
ELLIOT.
>> WELL, PAUL MAY HAVE "PEOPLE"
MAGAZINE, BUT I WAS NAMED
"SEXIEST MAN ALIVE" BY CHEST
HAIR MAGAZINE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY, ELLIOT, DO YOU REMEMBER
BEING ON MY SITCOM?
>> SHOULD I?
>> SO, JOHN, WE'VE GOT SOME
BUSINESS TO DISCUSS.
THE CLUB HERE HAS GOTTEN SO BIG
THAT IN ORDER FOR YOU TO GET IN,
SOMEONE HAS TO RETIRE.
>> YEAH, TOO BAD NO ONE HERE IS
AT RETIREMENT AGE.
>> YOU ARE 76.
>> BUT I HAVE THE CHILD OF A
38-YEAR-OLD.
AND WE GET RID OF TINA.
SHE WAS THE FIRST WOMAN TO WEAR
GLASSES ON TV.
>> THAT IS TRUE.
"ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY" CALLED IT
DISGUSTING.
AND IT CAN'T BE CANDICE BECAUSE
SHE WAS BACK HERE IN THE '70s.
YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW MUCH SEXUAL
HARASSMENT THAT HAPPENED BACK
THEN?
>> OH, PLEASE.
THOSE GUYS DID REALLY WEIRD
STUFF.
>> I WAS FINE WITH IT.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THERE'S NO
ROOM FOR ME?
>> THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A
VERY SMALL CLUB, WITH JUST THE
HIGHEST QUALITY STARS.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS --
>> I THINK WHAT WE'RE ALL TRYING
TO SAY IS THIS HAS BECOME NOT
SPECIAL.
>> DID SOMEONE SAY --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DID SOMEBODY SAY NOT SPECIAL?
>> CONAN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> WELL, I'M JUST HERE TO SIGN
UP FOR PEACOCK.
IT'S WEIRD THEY MAKE YOU DO IT
IN PERSON.
>> OH.
>> LOOK, JOHN, DO NOT LISTEN TO
THEM.
THIS IS VERY SPECIAL.
I WAS IN THE VERY FIRST
FIVE-TIMERS SPECIAL -- THING
>> A LOT OF US WERE WRITERS
HERE.
>> YES.
BUT YOU WERE ON THE SHOW WHEN
YOU WERE A WRITER, SO SHUT UP!
JOHN AND I WERE NEVER SUPPOSED
TO BE ON TV.
'CAUSE WE'RE BOTH HIDEOUS,
RIGHT?
RIGHT, JOHN!
>> I -- I GUESS.
>> YES, WE ARE!
WE'RE HERE AND WE'RE TAKING
WHAT'S OURS.
WE WANT TO TAKE IT BY THE HORNS.
THE POINT IS, YOU START HERE AND
YOU CAN DO GREAT THINGS.
I HOSTED MY OWN TV SHOW FOR
DECADES.
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
>> I HAVE A PODCAST.
>> WELL, I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SAY
THIS, BUT CONAN HAS A POINT.
BEING IN THIS CLUB IS PRETTY
DAMN SPECIAL.
>> YES!
YES!
COME ON.
LET'S GIVE HIM HIS JACKET.
>> ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
GIVE HIM YOUR JACKET.
>> AH, MAN.
IT WAS FUN WHILE IT LASTED.
THIS -- THIS REALLY DOES --
JUST, IT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME.
>> OH YEAH.
AND HEY, ONE MORE THING.
LIVE FROM NEW YORK --
>> OH, NO, CONAN.
WE DID THAT ALREADY.
>> I'LL DOING IT ANYWAY.
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LCD
SOUNDSYSTEM!
**
* I'M ON FIRE
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME *
* BUT MY DESIRE
IS GOING TO CRUSH ME *
* BUT I'M ALL CHILLS
'CAUSE YOU ADORE ME
YOU ADORE ME *
* BUT I'M STILL ALL KILLS
I NEED MY THRILLS
I NEED MY THRILLS *
**
* I'M ON FIRE
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME *
* BUT MY DESIRE
IS GOING TO LEVEL ME
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALIVE *
* BUT I'M ALL CHILLS
'CAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
LOOSE-KNIT
YOU'VE BEEN LOOSE-KNIT *
* BUT I'M STILL ALL KILLS
I NEED MY THRILLS
I NEED MY THRILLS *
**
* I'M ON FIRE
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME *
* BUT ALL OF MY DESIRE
IS GOING TO CRUSH ME
WHEN YOU EXPIRE *
* BUT I'M STILL ALL KILLS
BUT YOU WANT ME
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
I NEED MY THRILLS *
**
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYBODY.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THIS WEEK RUSSIA BEGAN THEIR
INVASION OF UKRAINE.
MANY ANALYSTS WERE SURPRISED
THAT PUTIN WENT THROUGH WITH IT
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS OBVIOUSLY
GOING TO BE A COLOSSAL MISTAKE.
BUT HE COULDN'T BACK DOWN AFTER
ALL THAT BUILD UP.
KIND OF LIKE HOW NBC STILL HAD
TO GO THROUGH WITH AIRING THE
WINTER OLYMPICS.
EXPERTS ON RUSSIAN POLITICS ARE
SAYING THAT ECONOMIC SANCTIONS
FROM THE WEST WILL NOT DETER
PUTIN BECAUSE HIS MONEY IS IN
NON-TRADITIONAL ASSETS THAT ARE
DIFFICULT TO TRACE.
SO ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE
AWFUL ABOUT PUTIN, HE'S ALSO
INTO CRYPTO.
UKRAINE, THE RUSSIA STOCK MARKET
FELL BY 30% TO NEGATIVE 90%.
THAT'S A TOUGH SUBJECT TO MAKE
JOKES ABOUT.
I MEAN, WE HAVE SEEN FOOTAGE OF
ATTACKS LIKE THIS ON OTHER
COUNTRIES, BUT NEVER THE WHITE
ONES.
I DON'T KNOW VERY MUCH ABOUT
THIS WHOLE SITUATION.
BUT I HAVE A CLOSE FRIEND WHO IS
UKRAINIAN, AND I HAVE ASKED HER
WHAT SHE THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
AND SHE SAID, "MICHAEL, YOU
DON'T PAY ME TO TALK, BABY."
I AM -- I AM VERY IMPRESSED BY
ALL THE UKRAINIAN CITIZENS
SIGNING UP TO DEFEND THEIR
COUNTRY, EVEN THE FAMOUS ONES.
IMAGINE THAT HERE.
>> ONE OF THE FIRST PLACES
RUSSIAN FORCES SEIZED WHEN
INVADING UKRAINE WAS CHERNOBYL,
THE SITE OF THE 1986 NUCLEAR
DISASTER.
SAID UKRAINIANS, "OH, NO.
DON'T TAKE THAT."
CAPTURING CHERNOBYL IS LIKE
LANDING AN AUDITION FOR
HARVEY WEINSTEIN NOW.
DONALD TRUMP PRAISED
VLADIMIR PUTIN MOVING TROOPS
INTO UKRAINE, SAYING, "THIS IS
GENIUS."
"THIS IS GENIUS" IS ALSO HOW HE
SARCASTICALLY INTRODUCES ERIC.
>>> JUDGE KETANJI BROWN JACKSON
SEEN HERE GETTING TIRED OF
Y'ALL'S FOOLISHNESS WAS
NOMINATED BY PRESIDENT BIDEN TO
BECOME THE FIRST BLACK WOMAN ON
THE SUPREME COURT.
THE NOMINATION FULFILLING
BIDEN'S PROMISE TO CHANGE THE
SUBJECT.
>> BIDEN CHOSE JACKSON AFTER
INTERVIEWING THREE FINALISTS
THIS WEEK.
WEIRD.
"I THOUGHT INTERVIEWING BLACK
CANDIDATES WAS JUST FOR SHOW,"
SAID THE NFL.
>>> A NEW BOOK CLAIMS THAT WHILE
DONALD TRUMP WAS PRESIDENT,
WHITE HOUSE STAFF FOUND WADS OF
PAPER CLOGGING THE TOILET.
SO EITHER HE TRIED TO FLUSH
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS, OR HE EATS
THE WRAPPERS.
MAYOR ERIC ADAMS ANNOUNCED THE
NEW PLAN TO STOP VIOLENCE IN THE
CITY'S TRANSIT SYSTEM, SIX
PEOPLE WERE STABBED ON THE
SUBWAY.
AND I SPEAK FOR ALL NEW YORKERS
WHEN I SAY, THAT SOUNDS PRETTY
LOW.
BUCKINGHAM PALACE STAFF HAVE
BEEN MOCKING PRINCE ANDREW WITH
A NURSERY RHYME.
SAID PRINCE ANDREW, "OH,
NURSERY."
>>> OFFICIALS POSTHUMOUSLY
STRIPPED MEDINA SPIRIT OF HIS
2021 KENTUCKY DERBY VICTOR FOR
FAILING A POST RACE DRUG TEST.
AND I JUST WANT TO SAY MEDINA
SPIRIT, I HOPE IT'S HOT IN HORSE
HELL, YOU CHEATING BASTARD.
>> MEDINA SPIRIT SOUNDS LIKE A
TYLER PERRY CHARACTER.
>>> A DOG IN CALIFORNIA THAT
WENT MISSING 12 YEARS AGO WAS
FOUND DEAD.
AND RETURNED TO HIS OWNER AFTER
SPENDING MORE THAN A DECADE
LIVING AT DAVE'S TAXIDERMY SHOP.
WHATEVER.
>>> A MAN IN IRAN WENT TO THE
HOSPITAL AFTER HE GOT A BATTERY
STUCK INSIDE HIS PENIS.
IT WAS A DOUBLE AA BATTERY
BECAUSE THAT'S THE SOUND HE
MAKES WHEN IT GOES IN.
AH, AH!
>>> THIS YEAR MARKS THE 50th
ANNIVERSARY OF ONE OF MARVEL
COMICS FIRST BLACK SUPERHEROES,
LUKE CAGE.
IN THE COMICS, LUKE CAGE FACES
OFF AGAINST BLACK PEOPLE'S MOST
POWERFUL ENEMY OF THE 1970s,
LEAD PAINT.
>>> POLICE ARRESTED TWIN SISTERS
AFTER THEY GOT MAD AT A
RESTAURANT WORKER AND SHOT HIM
IN THE FACE.
THIS ACCORDING TO PEACOCK'S VERY
DARK REBOOT OF "SISTER, SISTER."
>>> THIS WEEK THE FDA GRANTED
THE FIRST CONDOM APPROVED FOR
ANAL SEX.
IT TOOK THEM THIS LONG BECAUSE
THEIR WIVES WOULD ONLY LET THEM
TEST IT ON THEIR BIRTHDAYS.
>> BUT DO YOU GET IT?
>> RESEARCHERS OBSERVED A
60-FOOT-TALL ROGUE WAVE, WHICH
IS THE LARGEST EVER RECORDED.
RESEARCHERS BELIEVE THE WAVE WAS
GENERATED WHEN YO MAMMA FELL
OVERBOARD.
For "Weekend Update," I'm
Colin Jost.
>> I'm Michael Che. Good night.
GOING TO TAKE?
>> IT SAYS THE NEXT ONE ARRIVES
IN FORGET ABOUT IT.
>> I'M STARVING.
>> YO, NEWSSTAND GUY, LET ME GET
A SNICKERS AND A BAG OF CHIPS.
>> I'LL GET YOU THE CLOSEST
THING.
AN OH HENRY BAR AND A COPY OF XL
BUTTS.
>> THEY STILL MAKE TO OH HENRY
BARS?
>> NO.
AND WHAT DOES HE WANT?
>> OH, NOTHING FROM YOU.
I'M GOING TO GO BUY A CHURRO.
>> YOU'RE BUYING A WHAT?
>> A CHURRO.
THEY SMELL DELICIOUS, AND THAT'S
SAYING A LOT CONSIDERING I HAVE
ACTIVE COVID.
>> YOU SURE YOU WANT TO BUY AN
UNWRAPPED CHURRO FROM A WOMAN
PUSHING A LAUNDRY CART THAT
SHE'S HOLDING WITH HER BARE
HANDS WITH A STARBUCKS NAPKIN?
>> LOOK, I'M A GROWN DRUNK MAN,
AND I
WANT A CHURRO TO EAT ON THE
CHOO-CHOO RIDE HOME.
>> VERY WELL THEN.
THE DYE IS CAST.
OH, MOLE PERSON, WHY DON'T YOU
TELL THIS GENTLEMAN WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU EAT A CHURRO FROM THE
SUBWAY?
**
* SOME DISGUSTING EVENING
YOU WILL BUY A CHURRO
A LOOSE UNPACKAGED CHURRO *
* AND THEN YOUR
BUTT WILL BLEED *
* AND SOMEHOW YOU'LL KNOW
AS SOON AS YOU CHEW
THAT AN HOUR BEFORE YOU
A RAT BIT IT TOO.
>> WAIT A SECOND.
MOLE PEOPLE ARE REAL?
>> OF COURSE THEY'RE REAL.
IMAGINE HOW GREAT IT WOULD BE TO
LIVE OFF THE GRID LIKE THAT.
NO MORE ENDLESS TEXTS OR
E-MAILS.
>> WHAT?
**
* IF I WERE A MOLE MAN
YABA DEBA DABA DEBA
DABA DEBA DABA DUM *
* ALL DAY LONG
I'D DRINK A SHOE
OF RUM
IF I WERE A MOLE PERSON *
* WE'D NEVER HAVE TO WORK
YABA DEBA DABA DEBA
DABA DEBA DABA DEE *
* I USED TO DRIVE
AN AMAZON VAN
LIVING IN A HOLE
IS SUCH A BETTER PLAN *
>> NOW YOU FEAST ON OLD
DISCARDED HANDS!
* IF I WERE A
FILTHY MOLE MAN *
**
>> OH, WOW.
WAS THAT THE ACTUAL CAST OF
"FIDDLER"?
>> NO.
IT'S JUST THE LUNCH BREAK AT B &
H PHOTO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S A WOMAN ON THE TRACKS.
>> IS THAT A GHOST?
>> NO.
SHE WAS JUST FIRED FROM SLEEP NO
MORE.
NOW SHE WANDERS THE TUNNELS.
>> IS SHE OKAY?
>> OH, I'M MORE THAN OKAY.
* I AM HIGH ON BATH SALTS
EVERY NIGHT
EVERY DAY *
* IN MY MIND
YOU THREE ARE DEMONS
IF YOU TOUCH ME
I EAT YOUR FACE *
>> WHOA!
THIS IS CRAZY!
>> I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE,
ARE YOU EVEN ALLOWED TO DO SOUTH
PACIFIC ANYMORE?
>> WAIT, CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE
IN THE CITY WE ARE?
>> OH, THE WORST PART.
* WE'RE IN MIDTOWN
WHERE THEY SELL
FOOD AT NIGHT *
* YOU'RE IN MIDTOWN
WHERE THE TRAFFIC LIGHTS ARE
FOR SURE BROKE *
** THE LAND OF FINANCE BOOM.
>> HEY, LOOK.
THE SUBWAY TRAIN'S MAKING ITS
WAY INTO THE STATION, AND IT'S
GOT SOMETHING FOR EVERYONE!
>> DID HE HAVE A LISP EARLIER?
* OH LOCAL SUBWAY IS COMING
DOWN THE TRACKS
PLEASE LET IT
STOP FOR ME *
* OH THE F LOCAL SUBWAY IS
COMING DOWN THE TRACKS *
* IT'S CALLED THE F
BECAUSE IT'S
EFFING ME *
* I GOT BITTEN BY A
PIGEON ON MY BIRTHDAY
IN MARCH I GOT
AIRBORNE HPV *
** ONE TIME I SAT DIRECTLY ON A
NEEDLE.
* OUR THE MAYOR SAID
HE FIXED IT
BUT I JUST GOT STABBED *
>> JULIANNY SAYS HELLO.
>> THIS IS THE F TRAIN, RUNNING
ON THE Q TRACK SKIPPING RANDOM
STATIONS WHEN I FEEL LIKE IT.
>> BUT THIS TRAIN IS EMPTY
EXCEPT FOR ONE MAN IN A TRENCH
COAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I CLEARED EVERYONE OUT.
YOU SEE --
* I'M FAPPING ON THE TRAIN
JUST FAPPING ON THE TRAIN
WHAT A GLORIOUS FEELING
I'M NAKED UNDER HERE *
>> CONDUCTOR, CAN'T YOU JUST
CLOSE THE DOORS?
>> WELL, I WOULD IF EVAN HANSON
WOULD MOVE HIS BACKPACK.
* AND I AM TELLING YOU
I'M NOT MOVING MY BACKPACK *
>> THAT'S FROM A DIFFERENT
MUSICAL WITH JENNIFER HUDSON.
>> STOP BULLYING ME!
>> I'VE GOT TO GET THAT GUY ON
BATH SALTS.
>> AND LOOK OUT.
ON THE FLOOR OF THE TRAIN,
THERE'S A PUDDLE OF
UNIDENTIFIABLE ORIGIN.
* I AM THE LIQUID
ON THE FLOOR
AM I PEE OR MOUNTAIN DEW *
* DON'T WORRY
I'M FLOWING *
* TOWARD THE DOOR
JUST KIDDING.
I'M GOING RIGHT AT YOUR SHOE.
>> STOP RIGHT THERE!
>> EMILY IN PARIS?
>> WE'RE THE GUARDIAN ANGELS.
WE'RE THE PEOPLE THAT REALLY
TAKE CARE OF THIS CITY.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A FIGHT,
YOU GOT TO GO THROUGH US.
>> OH, REALLY?
I'M POSSIBLY THE REAL
JESUS CHRIST.
WEARING MY FAMOUS NEW YORK
ISLANDERS BEARD.
AND IF YOU WANT THIS SUBWAY,
YOU'LL HAVE TO KILL ME AGAIN
FIRST.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S ALL HAPPENING!
>> JUST AS THE ORACLE PREDICTED.
* JESUS CHRIST
DOESN'T TRACK WITH
WHAT WE KNOW SO FAR *
* JESUS CHRIST
WEARING CROCS
WHY DOES SHE HAVE
A SPIDER IN A BOX *
* JESUS CHRIST
REALLY DRUNK
SHE BOUGHT STATION
CHURROS FOR EVERYONE *
>> IT'S A MIRACLE!
* JESUS CHRIST
JESUS CHRIST
JESUS CHRIST *
SLIME," A LOOK BACK AT THE
HISTORY OF NICKELODEON'S ICONIC
GREEN GOO.
I'M NICK CANNON, FORMER STAR OF
"ALL THAT."
>> AND I'M MARK SUMMERS, FORMER
HOST OF "DOUBLE DARE," "SUPER
SLOPPY DOUBLE DARE," AND THE
ILL-FATED "DIRTY NASTY HARDCORE
DOUBLE DARE."
>> AMERICA WAS INTRODUCED TO
NICKELODEON'S ON THE CANADIAN
KIDS' COMEDY SHOW "YOU CAN'T DO
THAT ON TELEVISION."
>> GREEN SLIME WOULD RAIN DOWN
ON ANYBODY WHO SAYS THE PHRASE,
"I DON'T KNOW."
BUT AS YOU'LL SEE IN THIS
FOOTAGE FROM AN EARLY EPISODE,
THE SLIME DIDN'T START OUT WITH
ITS NOW ICONIC LOOK.
>> HEAD'S UP.
THIS SHOW WAS MADE IN CANADA, SO
THOSE KIDS ARE WHITE AS HELL.
>> OKAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> HEY, TRACY.
>> HEY, CHRISTINA.
>> YOU GOT A RUBIX CUBE?
>> NOT REALLY.
I'M COLOR BLIND.
>> WAIT.
YOU'RE COLOR BLIND AND YOUR
PARENTS ARE DIVORCED?
NO WONDER YOU DON'T HAVE A
BOYFRIEND.
>> AGAIN, THIS IS FROM 1980 WHEN
TV WAS CRAZY.
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVE ALWAYS
WONDERED, WHO EXACTLY IS THIS
RUBIK GUY.
>> HUH.
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT WAS LIKE CONCRETE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SAID, "I
DON'T KNOW."
OOPS.
>> OH, GEEZ.
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> SORRY!
LITTLE BASTARD SLIPPED OUT OF MY
HANDS.
YEAH.
SLIME IS TOO DAMN THICK.
>> FUN FACT.
THAT WOMAN WITH THE BUSTED ASS
HAIR CUT IS BECKY.
>> THE EARLY DAYS ALSO SAW
EXPERMITATION IN THE METHODS OF
SLIMING, AS SEEN IN THIS CLIP
FROM AN EARLY EPISODE.
>> YOU'RE SO FUNNY
SUZANNE SUMMERS.
>> IT'S MARK SUMMERS.
>> OKAY, MY BAD.
>> HEY, GREG.
>> HEY, MARCY.
THIS SPIDERMAN COMIC GOT ME
THINKING, YOU'D BE A GREAT
SUPERHERO.
STUFFED HER BRA WOMAN.
>> OH, WELL YOU CAN BE MY
SIDEKICK, THE INCREDIBLE HOMO.
>> 1980.
>> NO.
I PREFER SUPER CRAIG.
>> HUH.
AND WHAT'S SUPER CRAIG'S SUPER
POWER?
>> HA, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS -- JESUS CHRIST.
>> HA HA.
LOOKS LIKE SUPER CRAIG'S SUPER
POWER IS BEING SLIMED.
>> OKAY!
>> WHY DID THEY DO THAT TO ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT THEY JUST
KEEP COMING AT US.
OH.
DAMMIT, STOP, PLEASE.
THAT HURT.
I'M SERIOUS.
>> YOU KNOW, THE ISSUE IS FIXED,
AND IT WILL NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> OKAY.
STOP.
WE'RE BEGGING YOU.
>> OKAY.
THE SECOND TO LAST EPISODE
SHOWED A GLIMMER OF THE SLIME WE
KNOW TODAY, BUT THERE WERE STILL
SOME ISSUES TO IRON OUT.
SLIME IS ONE STICKY BUSINESS.
>> HELL, YEAH.
JUST LIKE HAVING 18 KIDS WITH
20 DIFFERENT WOMEN.
I'M LOSING MY HAIR.
>> HEY.
>> GEE, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
ABBIE?
ARE YOU ON YOUR PERIOD OR
SOMETHING?
>> NO.
SHE'S PROBABLY JUST UPSET
BECAUSE SHE'S ADOPTED.
>> I MEAN, DO I GOT TO SAY IT?
>> 1980.
>> THEY KNOW, MAN.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION.
ARE YOU DWEEBS EVER NOT
ANNOYING?
>> HUH.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN STOP SOON.
>> IT'S GETTING IN MY EYES RIGHT
NOW.
>> IS IT OKAY IF I GET IT IN MY
MOUTH?
I FEEL LIKE YOU GOT IT.
>> PLEASE STOP.
CAN YOU PLEASE?
>> AFTER THAT EPISODE OF SLIME
TIME WAS SHORTENED FROM SIX
MINUTES TO FIVE SECONDS.
>> STAY TUNED.
AFTER THE BREAK, WE'LL BE JOINED
BY ONE OF
THE PETES FROM "THE ADVENTURES
WITH PETE AND PETE."
>>> ONCE AGAIN, LCD SOUNDSYSTEM!
**
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
**
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
* WANT WE WANT
IS WHAT YOU WANT
WANT WE WANT
IS WHAT YOU WANT *
* IS FREE TV
WANT YOU WANT
IS WHAT WE WANT *
* WANT YOU WANT
IS WHAT WE WANT
IS A CAREER IN THE
HA HA HA HAs *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEPER *
**
* WHAT YOU WANT
WHAT YOUE WANT
WHAT YOU WANT
IS A HA HA HA HA *
* WHAT WE WANT
WHAT WE WANT
WHAT WE WANT *
* IS A CASE OF THE
HA HA HA HAs *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEPER
YOU HAVE SO MUCH MORE SPACE
IN WHICH TO *
* IN WHICH TO
HA HA HA HA *
* YOU HAVE SO MUCH MORE TIME
WITH WHICH YOU
HA HA HA HA *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY IS STONED *
* YOUR CITY IS STONED
MY CITY'S IN HEAT
WHAT WE WANT
SEX WITH TV STARS *
* WHAT YOU WANT
A FULL-FLEDGED CAREER IN THE
HA HA HA HA
HA HA HA HA *
* WHAT YOU WANT
HA HA HA HA
HA HA HA HA *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER *
* YOUR CITY'S A SUCKER
MY CITY'S A CREEP *
**
>> OH, MY GOSH.
SHOULD WE HAVE BROUGHT FOOD?
I DON'T KNOW HOW THESE THINGS
WORK.
>> HONEY, IT'S YOUR FIRST
REUNION.
IT'S FINE.
MY FAMILY LOVES YOU.
>> REALLY?
THEY LOVE THAT YOU MARRIED A GUY
WHO WAS LL BEAN'S CUSTOMER OF
THE YEAR?
>> YES, JUST BE YOURSELF.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
HELLO, EVERYBODY.
I JUST WANT TO WELCOME YOU ALL
TO THE ROBINSON FAMILY REUNION.
YES, INDEED.
WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A GOOD
TIME.
WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A GOOD TIME
TONIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
I WANT EVERYBODY TO GET OUT ON
THAT DANCE FLOOR.
COME ON.
IT'S TIME FOR "THE CUPID
SHUFFLE," Y'ALL.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
EVERYONE'S WEARING T-SHIRTS.
DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
>> YES.
THEY DIDN'T SEND YOU ONE IN THE
MAIL?
>> COME ON, Y'ALL.
* IT DON'T MATTER
IF YOU'RE YOUNG OR OLD *
* WE GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW IT GOES *
* TO THE RIGHT
TO THE RIGHT *
* TO THE LEFT
TO THE LEFT *
** NOW WALK IT BY YOURSELF.
* YEAH, WALK IT
BY YOURSELF *
>> HOW MANY FAMILY MEMBERS DO
YOU HAVE?
I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE ALL LOOKING
AT ME.
>> OH, GOD, THEY'RE NOT.
I PROMISE.
* TO THE RIGHT
TO THE RIGHT *
* TO THE LEFT
TO THE LEFT *
* TURN AND DUNK
TURN AND DUNK *
* NOW PUSH IT LIKE LeBRON
YEAH, PUSH IT LIKE LeBRON *
>> YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SURE I KNOW
THIS VERSION OF "THE CUPID
SHUFFLE."
>> OH, THIS HERE IS THE "ATLANTA
TWO PIECE IN A BISCUIT REMIX."
* SOMETHIN' STINK
SOMETHIN' STINK *
* YEAH, FOLD YOUR TUPPERWARE
YEAH, FOLD YOUR TUPPERWARE *
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYONE I RECOGNIZE YET EITHER.
>> DANIEL!
YOU'RE HERE.
>> TANITRA, HEY.
YEAH, I'M HERE, WITH MY WIFE.
THIS IS LISA.
>> OH, HEY, LISA.
I THINK WE COUSINS, GIRL.
BUT, SEE, ME AND DANIEL, WE OLD
FRIENDS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE USED TO PLAY ALL DAY AS KIDS.
WE JUST HAD TO BE HOME WHEN THE
STREET LIGHTS CAME ON.
>> THAT'S IT.
HOW IS THAT HOTEL YOU'RE STAYING
AT?
>> IT'S PRETTY NICE.
BUT THEY DIDN'T GIVE US A WASH
CLOTH.
>> WHAT?
WHO SHOWERS WITHOUT A WASH
CLOTH?
>> I KNOW.
THEY NASTY, DANIEL.
OKAY -- ARE WE STILL GOING TO
ESTON-FEST THIS YEAR?
>> I RESERVED US TWO SEATS FOR A
LIVE TAPING OF "I WANT TO FIX MY
LIFE."
>> OKAY, BET.
I'M BEHIND THAT SHOW, OKAY?
I GOT TO MAKE SURE THEY KEEP
THAT DOOR CLOSED.
OKAY?
>> YEP, YOU CAN'T LET THAT GOOD
AIR OUT.
>> WAIT, WAIT.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO ESTON-FEST?
>> OF COURSE.
I GOT YOU A TICKET, TOO.
* CALL THE COPS
CALL THE COPS *
* THEY'RE GONNA BE A WHILE
THEY'RE GONNA BE A WHILE *
* PLAYING BASS
PLAYING BASS *
* YEAH, HOW MANY
BOOKS YOU GOT *
>> WAIT.
YOU BROUGHT CARDS?
>> LISA, OF COURSE.
IT'S A FAMILY REUNION.
>> OH, THERE HE IS.
I HEARD YOU WAS HERE, DANIEL.
>> NOW IT'S A PARTY.
>> OH, DANIEL.
>> WAIT, WAIT, NOW.
YOU KNOW MY UNCLE BUCK?
>> OH, YEAH.
BUT I KNOW HIM AS MR. ROBINSON.
HOW'S YOUR KNEE DOING, SIR?
>> OH, BETTER.
I PUT A LITTLE ROBITUSSIN ON IT.
>> WORKS EVERY TIME.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU HERE.
I WASN'T SURE IF THAT COVID
WOULD KEEP YOU AWAY.
>> WELL, I GOT VACCINATED, BUT
DON'T TELL NOBODY.
>> I HEAR YOU.
I GOT VAXED, TOO, BUT IT WOULD
BREAK MY MOMMA'S HEART IF SHE
KNEW I TOOK A GOVERNMENT NEEDLE.
>> NOW I HEAR THAT.
UH-OH, I GOT TO GO DANIEL.
THEY GOT ME WATCHING MY LITTLE
NEPHEW.
HE ALWAYS ACTING UP.
>> THAT'S CHILD PROBLEM IS HE'S
GOT NO HOME TRAINING.
>> AND HE NEEDS TO STAY OUT OF
GROWN FOLKS BUSINESS BEFORE HET
GET WHIPPED!
>> SEE, DANIEL.
I TOLD YOU EVERYBODY LOVES YOU.
>> AW, COME ON.
I ONLY KNOW LIKE 20, 30 PEOPLE
TOPS.
* TO THE RIGHT
TO THE RIGHT *
* TO THE LEFT
TO THE LEFT *
* GONNA FIGHT
GONNA FIGHT *
* NOW RUB SOME VASOLINE
YEAH, RUB YOUR VASOLINE *
>> ALL RIGHT, GREAT JOB,
EVERYBODY.
AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE "SOUL
TRAIN" LINE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I DIDN'T KNOW THIS WAS
HAPPENING.
>> HONEY, LISTEN, YOU DO NOT
HAVE TO DO IT, OKAY?
>> YEAH.
NO, I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
APPROPRIATE.
BUT --
* NOW, WALK IT BY YOURSELF
YEAH, WALK IT BY YOURSELF *
>>> THANK YOU TO LCD
SOUNDSYSTEM, STEVE MARTIN,
CANDACE BERGEN, PAUL RUDD,
TINA FEY, ELLIOT GOLD AND THE
UKRAINIAN CHORUS OF NEW YORK.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING,
EVERYBODY.