>>> DID YOU GUYS SEE WHAT SHE
WORE AT SCHOOL TODAY?
>> OH, MY GOD, SHE IS SUCH A
PICK ME GIRL.
>> IT TAKES ONE TO KNOW ONE,
VANESSA.
>> HA HA HA!
THAT'S HILARIOUS, JENNABELL.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY YOU'RE THE QUEEN BEE
AND I TOTALLY DEFER TO
YOU.
>> WAIT, DOES ANYONE ELSE THINK
MARK DUGIN IS LOW-KEY HOT WITH
THAT HAIRCUT?
>> OH, MY GOD, YES.
GLOW-UP VIBES.
>> FYI, GREEN LIGHT ON YEMEN
RAID.
ROCKETS WENT AIRBORNE 15 MINUTES
AGO.
WHO'S READY TO GLASS SOME HOUTHI
REBELS?
FLAG EMOJI, FLAG EMOJI, FLAG EMOJI,
FIRE EMOJI, EGGPLANT.
>> WHO THIS IS?
>> PETE HEGSETH, SECRETARY OF
DEFENSE.
ISRAEL BETTER BEND OVER AND
SPREAD IT.
HZ
BALLER.
WATER SQUIRT EMOJI.
GOD BLESS THE TROOPS.
EGGPLANT.
>> DO WE KNOW YOU, BRO?
THIS IS JENNABELL.
>> OH, NICE.
JENNABELL FROM DEFENSE, RIGHT?
>> HEY.
I THINK YOU HAVE THE WRONG GROUP
CHAT?
>> LOL, LOL, LOL.
COULD YOU IMAGINE IF THAT
ACTUALLY HAPPENED?
HOMER DISAPPEAR IN THE BUSH GIF.
WHILE I'VE GOT EVERYONE, SENDING
A PDF
WITH UPDATED LOCATIONS OF
ALL OUR NUCLEAR SUBMARINES.
HI
JORDAN PEELE SWEATING LIKE CRAZY
GIF.
>> STOP SENDING US THIS STUFF.
>> HOLD UP, GOT J.D. NOW.
>> NICE JOB ON THE STRIKE, JAM.
EMOJI
>> WHAT?
>> MY BAD, MEANT TO SEND FIRE
EMOJI.
>> OKAY.
HOW'S GREENLAND, BY THE WAY?
BET YOU'RE KILLING IT.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
NOBODY KNOWS WHY I'M HERE.
ESPECIALLY ME.
BUT PRAISE TRUMP, OUR WORK HERE
IS MYSTERIOUS AND IMPORTANT.
YEMEN
SO POTUS WAS SAYING WE SHOULD
MAKE EGYPT GIVE US THE PYRAMIDS.
>> I'M ENGAGING.
THE PYRAMIDS OF GIZA?
LIKE, HOW WOULD WE MOVE THEM
HERE?
>> SAME WAY THEY BUILT THEM.
EITHER ALIENS OR SLAVES.
WAIT, WHO'S THE 203 NUMBER?
>> I'M JENNABELL.
>> SICK, JENNABELL FROM
HOMELAND.
SENDING A PDF OF ALL DEEP COVER
CIA AGENTS,
DON'T SHARE!
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO BE BAD AND
MAKE MYSELF A JACK AND COKE TO
CELEBRATE.
JUST THE ONE, THOUGH.
>> NICE.
PROMISE TO STOP DRINKING WHEN
YOU GOT THE JOB.
BUT IT'S LIKE THEY SAY IN AA,
JUST THE ONE IS OKAY.
>> GOT TO GO.
MATT'S HERE TO PICK ME UP.
WE'RE GOING TO A MOVIE.
>> WHO?
GAETZ?
>> ACTUALLY, YEAH.
>> HOLD UP, ADDING MARCO.
>> RUBIO IN THE HOUSE!
>> WAIT.
WHO ARE THE OTHER THREE NUMBERS
HERE?
P.S., SENDING YOU THE REAL FK FILES,
NOT THOSE FAKE ONES WE
RELEASED.
DO NOT SHARE.
>> WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO TELL
YOU, WE'RE IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> I THINK YOU ACCIDENTALLY
ADDED US TO A GOVERNMENT CHAT?
>> IN THAT CASE, WE WERE TOTALLY
PRANKING YOU GUYS, LOL.
BUT WOULD YOU MIND EMAILING YOUR
NAMES AND HOME ADDRESSES
TO
DEPORTATIONS@ICE.GOV?
>> HEY, COULD BE WORSE.
WE COULD HAVE ADDED THE EDITOR
OF "THE ATLANTIC" AGAIN.
>> YOU DID.
I AM ALSO HERE.
AND CAN I JUST SAY TWO THINGS?
ONE, HEGSETH, YOU HAVE GOT TO
LOSE MY NUMBER.
AND TWO --
>> LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- MIKEY
MADISON!
THANK
IT'S BEEN A CRAZY MONTH.
THE FILM I WAS IN, "ANORA," JUST
WON FIVE OSCARS.
HOST
SO IN APRIL, I'M GOING TO BED.
AS YOU CAN TELL, I HAVE A PRETTY
RELAXED VIBE IN REAL LIFE.
AND I TRY TO INCORPORATE THAT
INTO ALL MY ROLES.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> RELAX.
>> STOP, STOP, STOP [ BLEEP ]!
CLARIFY
WERE TWO DIFFERENT CHARACTERS
WHO WERE LIT ON FIRE,
AND THAT'S
RANGE.
GROWING UP, I ACTUALLY NEVER
PLANNED ON BEING AN ACTOR.
WHEN I WAS A KID, I WAS A VERY
PROUD SELF-PROCLAIMED HORSE
GIRL.
FOR THOSE OF YOU UNFAMILIAR, A HORSE GIRL
IS BASICALLY A NERD
BUT WITH LONG HAIR.
I EVEN DID HOMESCHOOLING SO I
COULD SPEND MORE TIME AT THE
BARN WITH THE HORSES.
HERE'S A PHOTO OF ME AND MY
PONY, THUMBELINA, ON HALLOWEEN.
YEP, I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WORSE --
THE FACT THAT I
DID A COUPLES COSTUME WITH MY HORSE,
OR THE FACT THAT I
CREATED A BACKSTORY.
SO WE WERE JAIL BIRDS ARRESTED FOR THE CRIME
OF STEALING EACH
OTHER'S HEARTS.
I KNOW.
IT'S SO HARD TO BELIEVE I WAS
HOMESCHOOLED, RIGHT?
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN REALLY CLOSE
WITH ALL MY SIBLINGS,
AND
ACTUALLY, MY TWIN BROTHER IS
HERE TO SUPPORT ME.
LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN GUESS WHICH
ONE OF THESE GUYS IS MY TWIN
BROTHER.
IF YOU GUESSED THE ONE WHO LOOKS
LIKE RON BEASLEY ON
TESTOSTERONE, YOU WIN.
AND YOU KNOW, IN A WAY, I KIND
OF FEEL LIKE HORSEBACK RIDING
PREPARED ME FOR DOING "ANORA."
BUT INSTEAD OF RIDING HORSES, I
WAS RIDING A RUSSIAN TWINK.
I PERFORMED ALL MY OWN STUNTS THE FILM
INCLUDING DANCING.
IT BOTHERS ME WHEN PEOPLE ASSUME
IT WASN'T ACTUALLY ME ON THE POLE,
BECAUSE IT WAS.
I CAN PROVE IT RIGHT NOW.
IN A MINUTE BUT HERE GOES.
>> WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR
YOU TONIGHT.
MORGAN WALLEN IS HERE.
STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
COMMERCIAL.
>> WELL, THIS CLASS IS GOING TO
HELP.
THE TEACHER IS A GENIUS.
>> HELLO, SORRY I'M LATE.
I HIT A GUY WITH MY CAR, AND HE
WAS BEING REALLY WEIRD ABOUT IT.
WELCOME TO COMMERCIAL ACTING
WHERE THE NUMBER ONE RULE IS,
YOU'RE NOT SELLING A PRODUCT,
YOU'RE TELLING A STORY.
NEW STUDENTS, SHOW ME SOMETHING
NOW!
>> OKAY.
PAUL AND I ARE WORKING ON A
SCENE FROM A FLONASE COMMERCIAL.
>> IT'S ALLERGY SEASON.
I'VE GOT A RUNNY NOSE, ITCHY
EYES, AND I'M SNEEZING.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> YOU SHOULD TRY FLONASE.
>> STOP.
ALERT FROM ME.
THE PROBLEM IS YOU'RE NOT
ENGAGED.
YOU'RE LISTENING, BUT YOU'RE NOT
ACTIVELY LISTENING.
CONNIE, MY STAR STUDENT, MY
QUEEN, COME UP HERE NOW.
DO THE LINES, AND I WILL
ACTIVELY LISTEN.
READY?
AND, ACTION!
>> IT'S ALLERGY SEASON.
>> YOU SAID WHAT.
>> AND I'VE GOT A RUNNY NOSE.
>> FOR REAL?
>> ITCHY EYES.
>> OH, NO.
>> AND SNEEZING.
>> LIKE THIS?
A CHOO!
>> FLONASE!
>> I'M SORRY, I FEEL THAT WAS A
LITTLE DISTRACTING.
>> OH, REALLY?
AND WHO'S THE EXPERT HERE?
YOU WITH ZERO ACTING CREDITS?
OR ME WITH THREE?
NUMBER ONE, WIPEOUT.
BUSTED MY FACE ON A BIG RED
BALL.
NUMBER TWO, WHAT WOULD YOU DO
WITH JOHN QUINONES?
DID NOT HELP AND WAS RACIST.
NUMBER THREE, "WHITE LOTUS."
AUDITIONED FOR THE INSECT SCENE
WITH MY BIOLOGICAL BROTHER, AND
I DIDN'T HATE IT.
>> SO YOU DIDN'T GET THE PART,
AND YOU MADE OUT WITH YOUR OWN
BROTHER?
>> DAVID -- CAN I TELL YOU
SOMETHING THAT MIGHT SOUND A BIT
MEAN?
I WOULD GIVE ANYTHING FOR YOU TO
LOSE YOUR HAIR AND NOT BE ABLE
TO FIX IT.
NOW, DOES ANYONE HAVE ANY
QUESTIONS FOR ME?
YES, YOU IN THE BACK.
>> YEAH, I'M GETTING MY HEAD
SHOT TAKEN TOMORROW.
DO YOU HAVE ANY ADVICE?
>> YES.
I RECOMMEND DOING ONE HEAD-ON
AND ONE IN PROFILE.
I ACTUALLY BROUGHT MINE WITH ME
TODAY.
>> THOSE ARE CLEARLY MUGSHOTS.
>> YES.
AND THEY COST ME NOTHING.
IT'S CALLED A WIN-WIN.
I GOT FREE HEAD SHOTS, AND I GOT
TO DRIVE WHILE DRUNK.
RIHANNA PENELOPE, GET UP HERE,
DO YOUR NIKE AD BEFORE I FREAK
OUT.
>> I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
YOUR SHOES.
>> THANKS, THEY'RE NIKES.
>> STOP.
BAD.
IT'S A SHOE AD, RIGHT?
NOT A YOU AD.
THE SHOE NEEDS TO ENTER BEFORE
YOU.
PENELOPE, AWAY FROM ME.
AND -- ACTION!
>> I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
YOUR SHOES.
>> OH, THESE?
THESE ARE FROM NIKE.
NIKE -- JUST DO IT ALREADY.
>> THAT'S NOT EVEN THE SLOGAN.
>> GO TO SLEEP!
>> NOW, ANOTHER AUDITION TIP.
MEMORIZE YOUR LINES, GUYS.
OKAY?
FOR INSTANCE -- CONNIE CAN DO
ANY LINE FROM ANY MOVIE OFF THE
TOP OF HER DOME.
CONNIE, MY SLIPPERY LITTLE
BEAVER, COME UP HERE.
FORREST GUMP NOW.
>> MY MAMA ALWAYS SAID, LIFE
IS -- LINE?
>> LIKE.
>> LINE?
>> A.
>> BOX.
>> LINE?
>> OF.
>> CHOCOLATES.
>> TOM HANKS COULD NEVER!
>> WHY IS THIS CLASS $2,000?
>> SHE DIDN'T EVEN REMEMBER A
SINGLE WORD, AND THAT'S A REALLY
FAMOUS QUOTE.
>> HEY!
YOU'RE TALKING TO THE ONLY
STUDENT IN THE CLASS WHO HAS
BOOKED ANYTHING.
OKAY?
PUT SOME RESPECT ON HER NAME.
CONNIE, TELL THEM YOUR CREDITS.
>> NUMBER ONE, "SURVIVOR."
CHOKED ON SOME WATER, MEDICALLY
EVACUATED.
NUMBER TWO, "HELL'S KITCHEN."
GORDON RAMSAY CALLED ME A
DOUGHNUT.
NUMBER THREE, "LOVE IS BLIND."
FELL IN LOVE, THEN SAW HIM AND
SAID, NO, BITCH.
>> BELLISSI AM. A.
LIKE I SAID, THE MOST IMPORTANT
PART OF ANY AD IS A SLOGAN.
SHOUT OUT A COMPANY, WE'LL DO A
PERFECT AD READ OF THEIR VOGUE
BEGAN.
>> ALLSTATE INSURANCE.
>> GOT IT.
AND ACTION ON MYSELF!
EXTERIOR FOOTBALL FIELD, I'M THE
COACH.
THE FOURTH QUARTER.
WE NEED A HAIL MARY.
ANY IDEAS?
>> COACH, I GOT THE BEST HANDS
ON THE TEAM, YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE
ME A SHOT.
>> FINE.
YOU'RE IN.
GOOD HANDS.
AND, SCENE!
CONNIE, YOU WERE FANTASTIC.
>> THANK YOU.
MAYBE ONE DAY I'LL WIN AN OSCAR.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THAT
IS, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
WEEKEND
¶ NEW YORK ON THE WEEKEND
GOT ALL DAY TO SEE MY FRIENDS ¶
¶ WE COULD GO TO BRUNCH OR
MUSEUMS ¶
¶ THERE'S A NEW MOVIE WE COULD
SEE THEM ¶
¶ RIDE A BIKE HAVE A FLING
OR DO OUR ABSOLUTE FAVORITE THING ¶
¶ WHICH IS JUST TO
WAIT IN A BIG DUMB LINE ¶
¶ A BIG DUMB LINE ALSO THE CRAZY
LINE ¶
¶ FOR A BAGEL THAT WENT VIRAL
FOR A PIZZA THAT WENT VIRAL ¶
TACOS
¶ WE'RE WAITING IN A FAT-A IS SS
LINE ¶
>> ISN'T NEW YORK AMAZING?
WHERE ELSE CAN YOU GET ON TIKTOK
AND --
¶ WAIT IN A BIG OLD LINE A BIG
OLD LINE
WHAT
¶ GUMMY BEARS FROM A POTLUCK
STORE ¶
>> HAVE YOU BEEN HERE LONG,
- YEAH
SIT 7.
>> I'VE BEEN HERE SINCE 2011.
LINE
>> MUST BE WORTH IT, IT'S A
REALLY LONG LINE.
¶ I WAITED THREE HOURS ¶
¶ HOW WAS THE MARCH FINE ¶
¶ I WAITED FOUR HOURS ¶
¶ HOW WAS THE YOGURT FINE ¶
¶ I WAITED SIX HOURS ¶
¶ HOW WERE THE NOODLES ¶
¶ BAD ¶
¶ OH, MY GOD THERE'S ANOTHER
LINE ¶
¶ A LONGER BIGGER LINE ¶
¶ WHAT'S IT FOR MY FEET DIVINE ¶
¶ CRONUTS
CROISSANTS IN A
DOUGHNUT ¶
PALAD
¶ A PIZZA THAT'S A SALAD ¶
FRASTA
¶ FISH THAT'S CANDY ¶
CHODA
¶ IF YOU KNOW THEN YOU KNOW ¶
¶ IT'S A BIG FAT LINE ¶
¶ I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE
I'VE FORGOTTEN WHAT WE'RE WAITING
FOR.
DABABY
ORAL B
IT'S
>> THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO FIND OUT
GET IN A BIG FAT LINE.
>> I'M TIRED, IT'S GETTING DARK,
I'M LEAVING.
I'M LEAVING!
>> NO!
>> YES!
¶ BELIEVE IN YOURSELF ¶
¶ BELIEVE IN THE LINE ¶
¶ YOU DESERVE THIS VIRAL GREEK
YOGURT ¶
OR WINE
¶ DON'T GIVE UP
AMELIA EARHART ¶
¶ SHE WANTS YOU TO ¶
>> I'M IN LINE.
¶ WAIT IN A BIG FAT LINE A BIG
FAT LINE ¶
STEPS
¶ YOU CAN ONLY TASTE IT IF YOU
GET IN A BIG-ASS LINE ¶
¶ OH, MY GOD WE'RE AT THE FRONT
THE FRONT OF A FRICKIN' LINE ¶
>> HOW IS IT?
>> IT'S -- GOOD.
IT'S LIKE, YOU KNOW.
PIZZA.
>> GOOD.
¶ PARTY IN A FAT-ASS LINE ¶
INCAPABLE
OF SERVING,
WE WILL HEAR THOSE
NOW.
TO BE CLEAR, YOUR REASONS CANNOT
BE WORK RELATED.
WE'LL START WITH YOU, SIR.
IS THERE ANY NONWORK-RELATED
REASON YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
SERVE?
>> I HAVE WORK.
>> SIR, WHAT DID I JUST SAY?
WE'RE NOT ACCEPTING WORK
CONFLICTS.
>> HIGHLY DOUBT THAT APPLIES TO
ME.
I'M A CEO.
EVER HEARD OF A LITTLE COMPANY CALLED,
OH, I DON'T KNOW, GOOGLE
BIRD'S MOBILE DOG GROOMING
SERVICES?
>> SIT BACK DOWN, SIR.
NEXT?
>> MY NAME IS QUINN.
AND I WOULD BE THE MOST
EXCELLENT CHOICE TO BE THE JUDGE
IN THIS CASE.
>> NO, I'M ALREADY THE JUDGE.
>> SO I WOULD BE THE STAR
WITNESS?
>> NO, SIR.
THIS IS JURY DUTY.
THEN PERHAPS, IN THAT CASE, I
COULD BE THE JUDGE?
HM, YEAH, I'LL ALLOW IT.
>> ALLOW YOURSELF?
NEXT.
MA'AM, WHY ARE YOU UNFIT TO
SERVE?
>> DOESN'T A WORK EXEMPTION RULE
APPLY TO
CELEBRITIES?
>> ARE YOU A CELEBRITY?
>> DEPENDS.
EVER HEARD OF A LITTLE FAMILY
CALLED THE KARDASHIANS?
BECAUSE I'M ONE OF THE PEOPLE
CAITLYN JENNER HIT WITH HER CAR.
>> SO YOU ARE NOT?
>> WORTH A SHOT.
>> OKAY, NEXT?
AND MA'AM, I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD
AND ASSUME YOU'RE UNFIT BECAUSE
YOU DON'T TRUST THE POLICE?
>> WOW.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT ASSUMPTION IS EXTREMELY
BIPHOBIC.
BISEX
>> WOW, OKAY.
WELL, YOU'RE DISMISSED
REGARDLESS.
NEXT?
>> HI.
UM -- I DON'T HAVE AN EXCUSE.
'CAUSE BET YOU HEARD ENOUGH OF
THOSE IN YOUR LIFE.
AND CAN I JUST SAY, IT IS SO
REFRESHING TO SEE A STRONG WOMAN
OF COLOR --
>> NO.
YOU JUST GOT YOURSELF 16 MONTHS.
NEXT?
>> YES, HI.
I'M AN ESSENTIAL WORKER.
>> AND WHAT IS YOUR JOB?
>> DOES THIS ANSWER YOUR
QUESTION?
¶ BEYONCE I GOT 99 PROBLEMS
BROOKLYN ¶
>> NOW I'M ACTUALLY MORE
CONFUSED.
WHAT IS YOUR JOB?
>> I PRANK CALL RESTAURANTS
PRETENDING TO BE JAY-Z FROM
MORNING RADIO SHOW.
¶ ALLOW ME TO REINTRODUCE
MYSELF ¶
NAME
TODD MUNGO FROM HOT 106 THE BRU
CREW.
>> NEXT.
I ASSUME YOU NEED TO BE
DISMISSED FOR CHILD CARE
PURPOSES?
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY KIDS.
I DO IT FOR ME.
>> DISMISSED.
NEXT?
>> I'M AFRAID I CANNOT SERVE.
BECAUSE I CANNOT BE IMPARTIAL.
I ALREADY KNOW HE'S GUILTY
BECAUSE I'M FROM THE FUTURE.
>> THE DEFENDANT IS A SHE.
SIT BACK DOWN.
>> IN THAT CASE, MUST RETURN TO
THE FUTURE.
>> BAILIFF, WE HAVE A CRAWLER.
NEXT?
>> HI, I KNOW YOU SAID NO WORK
EXCEPTIONS,
BUT I HAVE A REALLY
BIG NIGHT COMING UP AT WORK.
JAY-Z IS EATING AT MY
RESTAURANT!
>> MA'AM, I DO NOT KNOW HOW TO
TELL YOU THIS,
BUT THIS SOUNDS
TO ME LIKE THE WORK OF A MAN
NAMED TODD MUNGO.
OKAY.
NEXT?
>> HM, I SEE WHAT Y'ALL TRYING
TO DO.
Y'ALL TRYING TO PUT A BLACK MAN IN JAIL,
SO YOU NEED A BLACK MAN
ON THE JURY SO YOU CAN SLEEP AT
NIGHT.
>> SIR, EVERYONE INVOLVED IN
THIS CASE IS KOREAN AMERICAN.
>> OKAY, I SEE WHAT THIS IS.
Y'ALL TRYING TO PUT A KOREAN
AMERICAN MAN IN JAIL,
SO YOU
NEED A PROUD KOREAN AMERICAN
MAN --
>> NO, ENOUGH.
NEXT, NEXT.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION.
HAS LUIGI BEEN RECEIVING MY
NUDES?
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> IT'S A SIMPLE QUESTION, YOUR
HONOR.
HAS LUIGI MANGIONE BEEN
RECEIVING THE PHOTOGRAPHS
OF MY
BARE BREASTS AND SPREAD
POSTERIOR?
WHAT? YOU'RE DISMISSED.
>> OVERRULED.
YEAH, I'D LIKE TO SEE WHERE THIS
GOES.
WHY DON'T YOU APPROACH THE BENCH
SO I CAN EXAMINE THEM NUDIE
PICTURES.
>> NO, BOTH OF YOU ARE
DISMISSED.
NEXT
>> HI. I'M "SNL'S" CHLOE FINEMAN,
I'VE PREPARED SOME IMPRESSIONS
FOR YOU.
THIS IS PARKER POSEY IN "WHITE
LOTUS."
PIPER, NO!
>> MA'AM, NO IMPRESSIONS IN MY
COURTROOM.
>> PLEASE, I NEED THIS.
PIPER, NO!
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
NEXT?
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, I HAVE
BEEN RECEIVING THAT WOMAN'S
NUDES.
AND MA'AM, YOU GOT TO STOP.
>> WELL, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE HERE, MR. MANGIONE.
BAILIFF, NEXT?
SIR, I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND
DISMISS YOU NOW.
>> WOW.
LET ME MAKE A WILD GUESS.
IT'S BECAUSE I'M WHITE.
>> GUYS, I'M HAVING A REALLY
TOUGH DAY.
THIS MORNING, MY KID THREW UP,
AND YEAH, SOME GOT IN MY MOUTH.
SO I REALLY, REALLY NEED THE
NEXT PERSON TO BE NORMAL.
SO SIR, TELL ME.
WHY DO YOU NEED TO BE DISMISSED?
¶ THIS BEAUTIFUL THING THAT I'VE
GOT ¶
PLEASE STAY
>> NO, NO, NO.
THE TRIAL IS CANCELED.
¶ THIS BEAUTIFUL THING THAT I'VE
GOT ¶
PLEASE STAY
VARSITY
BOYS
>>> CRAZY.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> BABE, DO YOU HAVE YOUR
CHARGER?
>> YEAH, I THINK IT'S IN MY BAG.
HEY, BABE.
THE SOCCER GUYS WANTED TO MEET
UP LATER --
>> ZACH.
IS THIS AN ENGAGEMENT RING?
>> IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A
SURPRISE.
>> BABY, SLOW DOWN.
>> HAD THE WHOLE THING PLANNED
FOR TOMORROW NIGHT AT THE BEACH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> CRAZY DRUNK BITCH!
>> WHAT'D YOU CALL MY GIRL?
>> WE CAN'T GET ENGAGED.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I'M STILL IN COLLEGE.
>> I LOVE YOU, SADIE.
>> AND I THOUGHT YOU LOVED ME.
>> I DO LOVE YOU.
>> YOU KNOW THAT.
>> LADY!
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT SCHOOL Y'ALL GO TO?
>> THEN WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT GETTING
MARRIED.
>> SOMEDAY.
I JUST --
>> NO WAY, I GO TO HARVARD TOO!
>> I JUST THINK WE NEED TO
GRADUATE
AND LIVE SOME LIFE
FIRST.
>> I SEE.
>> SIR, THIS AREA IS FOR HOTEL
GUESTS ONLY, OKAY?
>> HOW YOU KNOW I AIN'T ONE?
>> YOU WANT TO BE WITH OTHER
GUYS, HUH?
>> YOU ARE NOT A COLLEGE
STUDENT.
AND YOU ARE NOT A GUEST.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH ANYBODY
ELSE.
OUR LIVES ARE JUST GETTING
STARTED.
AND I DON'T WANT TO RUSH INTO
ANYTHING.
>> I'M NOT RUSHING.
I THOUGHT A LOT ABOUT THIS,
SADIE.
IT'S ALL I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT.
>> I'M GONNA JUMP OFF THE
BALCONY INTO THE POOL!
KNOW
>> YOU THINK I'D GO OUT AND
SPEND EVERY DIME I HAD ON A RING
IF I HADN'T THOUGHT ABOUT IT,
BABY?
>> I DON'T NEED A RING TO KNOW
THAT YOU LOVE ME, ZACH.
>> I'M FINE.
I'M FINE.
>> I JUST FEEL STUPID NOW.
>> ZACH.
>> LADIES, LADIES!
Y'ALL WANT TO GO ON A JET SKI?
>> YEAH.
>> NO.
>> DON'T FEEL STUPID.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
- WANT?
>> DO IT!
>> YOU'RE A MAN.
THAT'S
>> CRAZY WHITE BOY.
>> SURE.
TAKE THIS
>> YOU RAN OVER MY FOOT, LADY!
>> I GUESS I'LL SEE IF I CAN
RETURN IT.
>> IF YOU WANT TO.
>> MY SCOOTER NOW, BITCH!
>> YOU CAN KEEP IT.
>> ANYBODY, HELP!
>> SOMEDAY, AFTER WE'VE GROWN
TOGETHER AND WE'RE READY,
YOU
CAN GIVE IT BACK TO ME.
GATOR
WEAR
>> DEAL?
>> DEAL.
>> POOL'S CLOSED.
>> POOL IS CLOSED.
>> WHAT IF I GO GET A PIZZA AND
SOME BEERS AND
WE STAY IN
TONIGHT?
>> I'D LOVE THAT.
¶ YOU SAY I'LL NEVER CHANGE
I'M JUST A GO AROUND TOWN
WITH SOME GASOLINE ¶
¶ JUST TRYIN' TO BUM A FLAME
GONNA BURN THE
WHOLE PLACE DOWN ¶
¶ HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
EVER FALLIN' IN LOVE
WITH A GUY LIKE ME
IN THE FIRST PLACE ¶
¶ WHEN TURN AROUND SAY
THAT I'M THE WORST THING ¶
¶ I GUESS I'M THE PROBLEM
AND YOU'RE
MISS NEVER DO NO WRONG ¶
¶ IF I'M SO AWFUL
THEN WHY'D YOU
STICK AROUND THIS LONG ¶
¶ AND IF IT'S THE WHISKEY
THEN WHY YOU KEEP ON
PULLIN' IT OFF THE SHELF ¶
¶ YOU HATE THAT WHEN
YOU LOOK AT ME
YOU HALFWAY SEE YOURSELF ¶
¶ AND IT GOT ME THINKIN'
IF I'M THE PROBLEM
YOU MIGHT BE THE REASON ¶
¶¶
¶ WE TRY TO GO
OUR SEPARATE WAYS
WE'RE BACK AND FORTH
LIKE A SWINGIN' DOOR ¶
¶ AND TOMORROW'S
LIKE YESTERDAY
SOME DAYS BETTER THAN
THE NIGHT BEFORE ¶
¶ AND YOU'RE BACK
WITH ME AGAIN
THEN YOU GO AND
TELL YOUR FRIENDS ¶
¶ THAT I'M THE PROBLEM
AND YOU'RE
MISS NEVER DO NO WRONG ¶
¶ IF I'M SO AWFUL
THEN WHY'D YOU
STICK AROUND THIS LONG ¶
¶ AND IF IT'S THE WHISKEY
THEN WHY YOU KEEP ON
PULLIN' IT OFF THE SHELF ¶
¶ YOU HATE THAT WHEN
YOU LOOK AT ME
YOU HALFWAY SEE YOURSELF ¶
¶ AND IT GOT ME THINKIN'
IF I'M THE PROBLEM
YOU MIGHT BE THE REASON ¶
¶¶
¶ IF I'M SUCH A
WASTE OF BREATH
SUCH A WASTE OF TIME ¶
¶ THEN WHY YOU ON YOUR WAY
TO WASTE ANOTHER
FRIDAY NIGHT ¶
¶ IF I'M THE PROBLEM
AND YOU'RE
MISS NEVER DO NO WRONG ¶
¶ IF I'M SO AWFUL
THEN WHY'D YOU
STICK AROUND THIS LONG ¶
¶ AND IF IT'S THE WHISKEY
THEN WHY YOU KEEP ON
PULLIN' IT OFF THE SHELF ¶
¶ YOU HATE THAT WHEN
YOU LOOK AT ME
YOU HALFWAY SEE YOURSELF ¶
¶ AND IT GOT ME THINKIN'
IF I'M THE PROBLEM
YOU MIGHT BE THE REASON ¶
¶¶
WEEKEND
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, THIS WEEK WE LEARNED OUR
ENTIRE NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM
HAS THE TEXTING SKILLS OF MY
AUNT JANET.
SECRETARY OF DEFENSE PETE HEGSETH,
SEEN HERE INDICATING
HOW MANY DAYS SINCE HIS LAST
DRINK --
SENT
FOR AN AIR STRIKE IN YEMEN
TO A TEXT CHAIN THAT ACCIDENTALLY
INCLUDED THE EDITOR OF "THE
ATLANTIC" MAGAZINE.
OF ALL PEOPLE TO ACCIDENTALLY
ADD TO THE CHAT, THE EDITOR OF
THE ATLANTIC.
THAT'S LIKE IF YOU'RE PLANNING A
SURPRISE QUINCEANERA
AND CC
JARED FROM SUBWAY.
TAKE HIS SIDE
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER TEXTED
THE FIST EMOJI, THE FLAG EMOJI,
AND THE TESLA EMOJI.
WALTZ LATER EXPLAINED -- THIS
WAS HIS REAL EXPLANATION --
THAT
THE JOURNALIST'S NUMBER MUST
HAVE GOTTEN, QUOTE, SUCKED ONTO
HIS PHONE.
WORSE, HE THEN TRIED TO GET RID
OF THE NUMBER BY SAYING,
SIRI,
HOW DO I SUCK THE JOURNALIST
OFF?
OF COURSE, BEFORE THE FULL
TRANSCRIPT WAS RELEASED,
HEGSETH
HAD DENIED THAT ANY SENSITIVE
ATTACK PLANS WERE SHARED, SAYING
THIS.
>> NOBODY WAS TEXTING WAR PLANS,
AND THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT THAT.
>> OH.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY ABOUT
THAT.
WHY DOES THAT SOUND FAMILIAR?
>> AND THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT THAT.
>> OH, MAN, HE WENT FULL GUMP.
EXCEPT FOR HEGSETH'S LIFE IS
MORE LIKE A BOX OF WINE.
>>> HOMELAND SECURITY SECRETARY KRISTI NOEM
VISITED A PRISON
HOLDING DEPORTED MIGRANTS IN EL SALVADOR,
EVEN THOUGH IT LOOKS
MORE LIKE SHE'S TRYING TO BEAT A
WORLD RECORD ON ONLYFANS.
>>> FBI DIRECTOR KASH PATEL
ANNOUNCED THE AGENCY IS
LAUNCHING AN INVESTIGATION
INTO
ANTI-MUSK VANDALISM AT TESLA
CALLING THE ACTS DOMESTIC TERRORISM,
A FEDERAL CRIME
PUNISHABLE BY A FULL PARDON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BETTER BE CAREFUL
BECAUSE PATEL
HAS EYES EVERYWHERE.
YEAH, HE DOES.
>>> VICE PRESIDENT J.D. VANCE,
SEEN HERE WATCHING THE PLANE
LEAVE GREENLAND WITHOUT HIM --
CONTINUED HIS SAD REBOOT OF VEEP THIS WEEK
BY VISITING OUR
MILITARY BASE THERE
AND
DELIVERING THE ADMINISTRATION'S
CLEAREST THREAT SO FAR.
EITHER GREENLAND JOINS THE U.S.
OR THE U.S. WILL KEEP SENDING
THEM J.D. VANCE.
>>> IN AN ANONYMOUS SURVEY OF
OIL EXECUTIVES REVEALED,
MANY OF THEM
THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP'S "DRILL,
BABY, DRILL" MESSAGE IS A MISS
AND HIS TARIFFS AR DISASTER.
THERE'S ONE BILLIONAIRE OIL MAN
WHO STILL SUPPORTS DONALD TRUMP,
DIDDY.
COME ON, IT'S PERFECT.
>> OIL MAN?
>> OIL MAN.
>>> THIS WEEK, THE SECRET
SERVICE INTERCEPTED A TODDLER
AFTER HE SLIPPED THROUGH THE
FENCE OUTSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE.
ANYWAY, HE'S HERE NOW.
>> THIS IS A DIRTY SHOW.
>>> COLORADO OFFICIALS HAVE
REMOVED A PORTRAIT OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP FROM THE STATE CAPITOL
AFTER TRUMP COMPLAINED THAT IT
DIDN'T LOOK GOOD,
CALLING IT
PURPOSEFULLY DISTORTED.
IN THE ARTIST'S DEFENSE, TRUMP
DID POSE FOR THE PORTRAIT
WITH A
HAMBURGER INSIDE HIS MOUTH.
>>> FITNESS INFLUENCER ASHTON
HALL HAS MADE HEADLINES THIS WEEK --
YOU KNOW THIS GUY,
RIGHT?
WITH HIS MORNING ROUTINE VIDEOS
THAT HAVE GARNERED NEARLY 1
BILLION VIEWS ONLINE.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR VERY OWN
DEVON WALKER.
RISE AND GRIND, CHE, RISE AND
GRIND.
>> IT IS MIDNIGHT, BRO.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
EVERYBODY'S TALKING ABOUT THE
DUDE'S MORNING ROUTINE BUT I
BEEN DOING THAT.
HE STOLE MY WHOLE SLOGAN WORD
FOR WORD, BAR FOR BAR, THAT'S MY
STUFF.
>> YOU DO THAT?
>> HOW DO YOU THINK I'VE GOTTEN
TO WHERE I AM TODAY?
OF ALL THE CAST MEMBERS ON
SNL, I'M DEFINITELY ONE OF
THEM.
>> I DON'T THINK I'VE SEEN YOU
DOING ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> CHE, YOU DON'T BE COMING TO
WORK.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE SEEN
THIS DUDE ALL WEEK.
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW I LOCK IN, ALL RIGHT?
Y'ALL, PLAY THE VIDEO.
>> YOU LIKE THAT?
ARE YOU SLEEPING IN YOUR
DRESSING ROOM?
>> YES, MAN.
YOU GOT TO BE AT WORK TO BE AT
WORK, OKAY?
I'M TRYING TO BE ONE OF THE
GREATS, AND THAT DON'T COME
WITHOUT SACRIFICE.
SO I SACRIFICED MY APARTMENT.
SOME PEOPLE CALL THAT EVICTION,
BUT I CALL THAT BEING LOCKED IN.
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE LOCKED
OUT.
>> I SEE YOU AT BUFFALO WILD
WINGS.
YOU BE DROPPING PINS IN FRONT OF
THE WAITRESS JUST TO WATCH THEM
PICK IT UP.
>> SLIPPERY HANDS.
>> HEY, YO.
HEY, JUST PLAY THE NEXT VIDEO,
MAN.
THIS NEXT PART'S ABOUT MY
WRITING PROCESS.
AND LIVE FROM!
THANK YOU.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHO THIS IS?
YES.
JAY PHAROAH.
>> I'M JAY PHAROAH!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> OH, OKAY, NOW YOU CARE ABOUT
THE ONLY BLACK PERSON WHO WORKS
HERE?
>> I'M BLACK TOO, MAN.
>> I SAID, WHO WORKS HERE.
WHAT DO YOU DO MONDAY TO FRIDAY?
YOU GOT NO WIFE, NO KIDS.
DO THEY PAY YOU AS MUCH AS
COLIN?
COLIN BE HERE.
BUSINESS
LOOK, MAN, WATCH THE REST OF
THIS VIDEO, YOU MIGHT LEARN
YOURSELF A LITTLE SOMETHING.
THANK
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME, KING.
>> DEVON, THE SKETCH IS CUT.
>> WHAT DAY DID YOU SHOOT ALL OF THIS?
>> ON A MONDAY.
>> WE DON'T WRITE SKETCHES UNTIL
TUESDAY.
WHAT DID YOU DO THE REST OF THE
WEEK?
>> CAN I BE HONEST WITH YOU?
I JUST BE ROAMING AROUND THE
OFFICE, PRETENDING I'M YOU.
I PRETEND THAT I'M YOU A LOT.
YOU NEVER BE HERE.
>> DEVON WALKER, EVERYBODY.
>> I MISS YOU, BIG BRO!
>>> MELANIA TRUMP IS BACKING A BILL
THAT WOULD PROTECT PEOPLE
FROM DEEP FAKE REVENGE PORN,
WHICH I HAVE SADLY BEEN THE
VICTIM OF.
>>> WILL SMITH HAS RELEASED HIS
FIRST NEW ALBUM IN 20 YEARS,
AND
IRONICALLY, THE ALBUM DOESN'T
SLAP.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
PLEASE, SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
>>> THE GENETIC TESTING COMPANY
23 AND ME SAYS IT IS BANKRUPT,
AND ALSO, 2% CHEROKEE.
>>> A JUDGE IN ENGLAND
SENTENCING TWO MEN FOR STEALING
A STATUE OF PADDINGTON BEAR
SAID
THEIR ACTIONS WERE THE
ANTITHESIS OF EVERYTHING
PADDINGTON STANDS FOR.
EVERYONE THINKS PADDINGTON IS SO
GREAT.
WHICH BRINGS ME TO MY SEGMENT,
HEAR ME OUT.
PADDINGTON'S A TOXIC BITCH.
HE'S AN ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT --
FREELOADING OFF A NICE, GULLIBLE
WHITE FAMILY.
HIS STICKY LITTLE MARMALADE PAWS
ARE JUST WAITING TO RIP OPEN
THAT TRENCH COAT
SO HE CAN FLASH
OUR STRAIGHT CHILDREN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO CALL I.C.E. ON
HIS PERUVIAN ASS.
>> ARE YOU OKAY, COLIN?
>> NO!
>> THIS HAS BEEN "HEAR ME OUT."
>>> WEST VIRGINIA HAS BECOME THE
FIRST STATE TO BAN ARTIFICIAL FOOD DYES,
WHICH SHOULD MAKE
FOOD HEALTHIER FOR THE BABY YOU
HAD WITH YOUR COUSIN.
>>> THREE TEENAGED GIRLS IN
TEXAS TRIED TO STAB THEIR MOTHER TO DEATH
AFTER SHE TURNED
OFF THE WI-FI.
THIS STORY IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
PLAN "B."
GET THEM BEFORE THEY GET YOU.
>>> THE BABY BRAND FRIDA IS
RELEASING A BREAST MILK-FLAVORED
ICE CREAM.
THE FLAVOR IS CALLED, WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU?
>>> SCIENTISTS SAY THEY'VE
DEVELOPED A WAY OF MAKING FOIE GRAS
THAT DOES NOT INVOLVE
FORCE-FEEDING DUCKS.
WOW, THAT'S GREAT, SAID DUCKS.
WHAT ABOUT THE MURDER?
>>> A 66-YEAR-OLD WOMAN IN
GERMANY HAS GIVEN BIRTH TO HER
TENTH CHILD.
THIS ACCORDING TO HER VAGINA'S
SUICIDE NOTE.
HER VAGINA KILLED ITSELF.
>> THIS IS A WEIRD TRANSITION.
>>> THIS WEEK, JOANN FABRIC
ANNOUNCED IT WILL BE CLOSING ALL
ITS STORES BY THE END OF APRIL
AS THE COMPANY HAS FILED FOR
CHAPTER 11 BANKRUPTCY.
HERE TO COMMENT IS JOANN.
>> HI, YOU GUYS.
HELLO, COLIN.
HELLO, EVERYBODY.
I WISH I WERE HERE UNDER BETTER
CIRCUMSTANCES.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> OH, THAT'S OKAY, JOANN FROM
JOANN'S.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT ALL THE STORE
CLOSURES.
>> IT'S NOT OKAY.
CLOSING A JOANN'S IN THE SUBURBS
IS LIKE CLOSING A PLANNED
PARENTHOOD IN A COLLEGE TOWN.
WOMEN WILL DIE!
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
BUT THIS CLEARLY MEANS A LOT TO
YOU.
>> IT MEANS A LOT TO EVERY
CAPRI-WEARING WOMAN WITH A
BORING HUSBAND AND A MEAN DOG.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHERE DID WE GO WRONG?
JOANN'S HAS EVERYTHING.
FLUORESCENT LIGHTING.
PLASTIC SUCCULENTS WITH SIX
LAYERS OF DUST ON THEM.
AND THE BEST PART?
EVERY CASHIER IS A RETIRED NURSE
WITH TWO WRIST BRACES AND THE
BIGGEST BREASTS YOU'VE EVER
SEEN.
>> I'VE BEEN TO JOANN'S.
>> I TRULY DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LAST YEAR WAS OUR BEST YEAR YET.
WE MADE $4,000.
>> IN TOTAL?
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
BUT IT WAS NEVER ABOUT THE MONEY
TO ME.
I'VE BEEN THE BOSS FOR 80 YEARS,
AND I'VE NEVER STOPPED WORKING
IN-STORE.
EVERY DAY I WAS LIVING ANY
DREAM.
FIRST THING I'D DO WHEN I GET
IN, I'D CHECK THAT WE ALWAYS
HAVE HALLOWEEN STUFF.
THEN I SWEEP THE DUST INTO A
PILE AND SPREAD IT BACK OUT.
POWER-SNIFF A PERMANENT MARKER,
AND I DRIVE HOME.
>> THAT'S YOUR WHOLE DAY AT THE
STORE?
>> JOANN'S IS MORE THAN JUST A
STORE.
IT'S A SANCTUARY.
FOR WOMEN WHO WEAR PANTS TO THE
BEACH.
WITHOUT JOANN'S, WHERE ARE WE
GOING TO GO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
TARGET OR MICHAEL'S?
>> MICHAEL'S?
MICHAEL'S ARTS AND CRAFTS?
LET ME TELL YOU A LITTLE
SOMETHING ABOUT MICHAEL.
HE RAPED ME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
JOANN!
>> OH, FINE, HE DIDN'T.
>> JOANN, YOU CAN'T JUST SAY
THAT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I CAN SAY
ANYMORE.
>> ARE YOU DRINKING RIGHT NOW?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT RUINED US?
FEMINISM.
>> NO.
FEMINISM DESTROYED US.
TEACH A WOMAN TO READ, AND
SHE'LL NEVER CRAFT AGAIN.
NOW THEY ALL WANT TO BE
SHE-E-Os.
GUESS WHAT, SHE-E-O, YOU KILLED
JOANN'S FABRIC.
>> OH, MY GOD.
NO, JOANN.
JOANN.
LOOKS GREAT.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR DISTRESS, BUT
YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIT, YOU LOST A
TON OF MONEY BECAUSE YOU WERE
CONSTANTLY RUNNING HUGE SALES.
>> YOU CAN'T SELL WITHOUT SALES.
AND RIGHT NOW, WE'RE RUNNING OUR
BIGGEST SALE YET.
YOU KNOW BOGO?
>> BOGO, BUY ONE GET ONE?
>> WE'RE DOING --
BONPAFOCOLOCOHOMO.
IT STANDS FOR BUY ONCE, NEVER
PAY AGAIN, OH, FEMALES ONLY,
MAYBE ONE LOCO HOMOSEXUAL.
>> JOANN FROM JOANN'S FABRIC,
EVERYONE.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
HIT US TONIGHT?
>> IF POP AIN'T WORRIED, I AIN'T
WORRIED.
>> POP AIN'T ALL HE USED TO BE.
>> YOU WATCH YOUR MOUTH, POP'S
STILL THE BIGGEST DOG IN THE
GAME.
>> MY BOYS, PLEASE.
WE HAVE ENOUGH ENEMIES AS IT IS.
WE HAVE TO BE UNITED NOW AS A
FAMILY.
>> YEAH, POP.
>> SORRY, POP.
>> MY SWEET BOYS.
WISH I COULD HAVE GAVE YOU A
LIFE AWAY FROM THIS MESS.
NOW I'M JUST AN OLD MAN.
AN OLD MAN FULL OF REGRETS.
>> POP, LOOK OUT!
>> NO, POP!
>> HE'S BEEN HIT!
>> POP, WE'LL GET YOU OUT OF
HERE.
>> BOYS, NO, BOYS, PLEASE,
LISTEN.
I DON'T HAVE TIME.
JUST KNOW THAT I LOVE YOU BOYS.
>> WE LOVE YOU TOO, POP.
>> I'VE GOT SO MANY REGRETS.
SO MUCH I NEVER GOT TO DO.
NEVER GOT TO SEE MY GRANDKIDS
GROW UP.
NEVER GOT TO MAKE AN HONEST
WOMAN OUT OF YOUR MOTHER.
>> COME ON, POP, DON'T TALK LIKE
THAT, WE'RE GOING TO GET YOU OUT
OF HERE.
>> NEVER GOT TO DO STAND-UP.
>> NEVER DID WHAT?
>> STAND-UP COMEDY.
ALWAYS WANTED TO TRY IT, BUT I
NEVER DID.
>> OKAY, POP.
SURE, YEAH.
>> THAT IDEA FOR ONE THING.
IT'S LIKE -- YOU KNOW, YOU GOT
THOSE SIGN ON THIS THE BUS?
IT'S LIKE ILLEGAL TO BEAT UP THE
BUS DRIVER?
>> YEAH, POP.
I'VE SEEN THOSE SIGNS YEAH.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
SO THE JOKE WOULD BE LIKE, OKAY,
NOW I WON'T!
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, OH, I WAS GONNA, THEN I
SAW THE SIGN.
>> OKAY, POP.
YEAH, YEAH, THAT'S FUNNY.
>> THAT'S FUNNY?
>> YEAH, POP.
I FEEL I MIGHT HAVE HEARD IT
BEFORE BUT WE GOT TO GET OUT OF
HERE --
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
GOT AN IDEA FOR ANOTHER ONE.
IT'S LIKE, YOU EVER SEE A BIRD
WALKING ACROSS THE STREET?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YEAH, POP, SURE, YEAH.
>> IT'S LIKE, WHY?
YOU KNOW?
HEY, BIRD, YOU CAN FLY, WHAT YOU
WALKING FOR?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YOU LIKE THAT ONE?
>> LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> I WANT TO TRY IT ON YOU.
HEY, GUYS, YOU EVER SEE A
BIRD --
>> POP, COME ON!
>> MARCO, MARCO!
>> OH, SWEETHEART, MY BABY, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> MA, COME ON, YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
>> I TOLD YOU THIS WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED, YOU BIG LUB.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO WITHOUT
YOU?
>> MARIE, LISTEN TO ME.
¶¶
SOMETHING I GOTTA ASK YOU.
WHAT WAS THAT GREAT JOKE YOU
CAME UP WITH LAST NIGHT?
>> WHICH ONE?
BOWLING SHOES?
>> YEAH, BOWLING SHOES.
LISTEN TO THIS, GUYS.
>> BOWLING SHOES IS LIKE, WHEN
YOU GO BOWLING, THEY MAKE YOU
PUT ON THOSE GOOFY SHOES.
AND IT'S LIKE, WHY?
>> TO PROTECT THE FLOOR, MA.
>> OH, SO I CAN WHIP A 15-POUND
BOWLING BALL DOWN A LANE AND THE
FLOOR'S FINE, BUT GOD FORBID I
WEAR MY SKECHERS?
YOU KNOW, LIKE WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN?
AND THEN YOU DO YOUR CATCH
PHRASE.
>> OH, RIGHT, MY CATCH PHRASE.
MAKE THAT MAKE SENSE!
>> MA, YOU'RE A PART OF THIS
TOO?
>> YEAH, I'M HIS WRITER.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
ANOTHER ONE, IT'S LIKE -- TELL
ME THIS.
WHY DO SOME PEOPLE SAY TORTOISE,
SOME PEOPLE SAY TURTLE?
WHAT'S WITH THAT?
MAKE THAT MAKE SENSE!
>> DIFFERENT ANIMALS, POP.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT ANIMALS.
>> OH, OKAY.
JOKE PROBABLY DOESN'T WORK
ENTHIS, DUT IT?
>> PROBABLY NOT, POP.
PROBABLY NOT.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOKS LIKE THE WHOLE FAMILY'S
HERE.
>> OH, SCREW YOU, O'SHAUGHNESSY.
>> EASY, NOW.
I BEEN WAITING FOR THIS A LONG
TIME, OLD MAN.
ANY LAST WORDS?
>> YEAH.
YOU EVER NOTICE HOW SMARTPHONES
MAKE YOU STUPID?
>> THOSE ARE YOUR LAST WORDS?
>> NO.
THESE ARE.
MAKE THAT MAKE SENSE!
WAIT, I GOT ANOTHER ONE!
>>> ONCE AGAIN, MORGAN WALLEN.
¶ I AIN'T SAYIN' THAT
I ALWAYS SLEEP ALONE ¶
I AIN'T MET NO ONE ELSE ¶
¶ DONE A LITTLE BIT OF
MIDNIGHT MOVIN' ON ¶
¶ AND I AIN'T SAYIN'
WHEN I DO THAT
IT DON'T HELP ¶
¶ LEAVE WITH SOMEONE
I DON'T KNOW HER NAME ¶
¶ PULL HER REAL CLOSE
BUT I LEAVE SOME SPACE ¶
¶ AND I COULD FORGET YOU
GIRL, FOR GOOD
EVEN THOUGH I SHOULD ¶
¶ I NEVER LET MY
HEART GO ALL THE WAY ¶
¶ EVERY TIME I TRY
I JUST HIT THE BRAKES ¶
¶ AND THERE'S ALWAYS
A COUPLE TRYNA
TAKE YOUR PLACE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE ¶
¶ YOU WAKE UP
WANTIN' ME OUT OF THE BLUE ¶
¶ YOU LAY DOWN NEEDIN'
WHAT I USED TO DO ¶
¶ YEAH, EVERY NOW AND THEN
I GO GET A TASTE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE
JUST IN CASE ¶
¶¶
¶ I ALWAYS TAKE IT
TO THE EDGE
THEN I BACK IT UP ¶
¶ THEY DON'T KNOW
I GOT A REASON
FOR ACTIN' UP ¶
¶ I AIN'T FELT A DAMN THING
BABY, AFTER US ¶
¶ YEAH, I'M JUST HOPIN'
YOU'LL COME BACK TO US ¶
¶ THAT'S WISHFUL THINKIN'
BABY, HONESTLY ¶
¶ BUT I KNOW YOU
AIN'T FORGOTTEN ME ¶
¶ SO I NEVER LET MY
HEART GO ALL THE WAY ¶
¶ EVERY TIME I TRY
I JUST HIT THE BRAKES ¶
¶ AND THERE'S ALWAYS
A COUPLE TRYNA
TAKE YOUR PLACE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE ¶
¶ YOU WAKE UP
WANTIN' ME OUT OF THE BLUE ¶
¶ YOU LAY DOWN NEEDIN'
WHAT I USED TO DO ¶
¶ YEAH, EVERY NOW AND THEN
I GO GET A TASTE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE
JUST IN CASE ¶
¶ LEAVE WITH SOMEONE
I DON'T KNOW HER NAME ¶
¶ PULL HER REAL CLOSE
BUT I LEAVE SOME SPACE ¶
¶ YEAH, I COULD HAVE
THREE WORDS ON MY TONGUE
BUT I WON'T EVER SAY 'EM ¶
¶ 'CAUSE I NEVER LET MY
HEART GO ALL THE WAY ¶
¶ EVERY TIME I TRY
I JUST HIT THE BRAKES ¶
¶ AND THERE'S ALWAYS
A COUPLE TRYNA
TAKE YOUR PLACE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE ¶
¶ YOU WAKE UP
WANTIN' ME OUT OF THE BLUE ¶
¶ YOU LAY DOWN
NEEDIN' WHAT I USED TO DO ¶
¶ YEAH, EVERY NOW AND THEN
I GO GET A TASTE ¶
¶ BUT I NEVER FALL IN LOVE
BABY, JUST IN CASE
JUST IN CASE ¶
¶¶
>> PRAISE THE LORD AND GO BOLD,
BABY!
>>> OKAY, IT'S TIME TO START
PUSHING.
>> BUT I CAN'T DO THIS WITHOUT
MY MIDWIFE!
>> DON'T WORRY, MRS. NELSON,
HE'S ON HIS WAY.
>> DEEP BREATHS.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> CLEAR A PATH, CLEAR A PATH.
I'M BARRY, THE MIDWIFE.
>> FINALLY.
DR. RICHARDS, THIS IS MY
MIDWIFE, BARRY.
>> HI, BARRY, IT'S NICE TO MEET
YOU.
>> ACTUALLY, WE'VE MET.
>> OH.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU.
ANYWAY, SHE'S DILATED 10
CENTIMETERS, AND SHE'S ALREADY
LOST A LOT OF PLACENTA.
>> AND I'VE LOST A LOT OF
RESPECT FOR YOU.
FOR NOT REMEMBERING ME.
>> OH, WOW, SORRY.
OKAY.
SHE'S CROWNING.
WE HAVE TO MOVE.
>> OH, THE PAIN!
CAN I PLEASE HAVE THE EPIDURAL?
>> JUST PUSH THE BABY OUT AND
THE PAIN WILL GO AWAY.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, WE MET AT THE
HILARY DUFF PERFORMANCE AT THE
TODAY SHOW DURING THE SUMMER
CONCERT SERIES AT 8:00 A.M.?
NEED I SAY MORE?
>> HILARY DUFF ON THE "TODAY"
SHOW?
WE MET IN 2007?
>> OKAY, HIS DORIAN, WHY ARE YOU
UP MY ASS?
WHILE YOU WERE BEING LAZY
McGUIRE, I WAS DELIVERING THIS
BABY.
¶¶
>> I CAN'T DO IT.
>> YES, YOU CAN.
JUST BREATHE.
>> SHE NEEDS OUR MIDWIFE.
>> CLEAR A PATH, CLEAR A PATH, I
SAID CLEAR A PATH!
IT'S BARRY THE MIDWIFE.
>> OH, BARRY, IT'S NICE TO SEE
YOU -- AGAIN.
>> AGAIN?
HAVE WE MET?
>> BARRY, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> SERIOUS AS A HURRICANE.
CLIMATE CHANGE, IT'S 2028.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT?
>> LET ME EXPLAIN.
BARRY'S ACTING LIKE THEY'VE
NEVER MET BECAUSE THREE YEARS
AGO, DR. RICHARDS FORGOT THAT
THEY HAD ALREADY MET AT THE
TODAY SHOW HILARY DUFF
PERFORMANCE IN 2007.
>> IT WAS SO LONG AGO.
ALL I REMEMBER FROM THAT DAY WAS
A GROWN MAN WEARING PRESCRIPTION
NEW YEAR'S EVE GLASSES.
>> THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
ANYWAY, WHILE YOU WERE BEING
DOCTOR SO YESTERDAY, I WAS
DELIVERING THESE BABIES.
LESBOS ALWAYS HAVE EXTROS.
>> NOTHING LIKE A HILARY DUFF
PERFORMANCE TO START YOUR DAY
WHOO, WHO!
GOOD MORNING, HILLARY!
YEAH, AND SHE'S A BRUNETTE NOW
SO YOU KNOW SHE'S NOT A KID
ANYMORE.
>> CLEAR A PATH, CLEAR A PATH
FOR BARRY, THE NUMBER ONE HILARY
DUFF LOVER.
I CAN'T SEE A THING, THESE
BARRICADES ARE SO FAR FROM MISS
DUFF.
>> I'M DR. RICHARDS, BY THE WAY.
I WORK AS AN OB-GYN FOR "LATE
NIGHT WITH CONAN."
THAT'S WHY I'M DRESSED LIKE
THIS.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
I LOVE YOUR HAIR.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO BLOND.
>> IF YOU DID, I WOULDN'T
RECOGNIZE YOU AND THAT WOULD
COME ACROSS AS REALLY RUDE.
>> I'D HATE THAT AND HOLD A
GRUDGE AGAINST YOU FOR YEARS.
>> OH, MRS. NELSON, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT, BABY NUMBER TWO.
>> I KNOW.
LIFE.
AND YOU AND MY MIDWIFE REMEMBER
EACH OTHER, RIGHT?
>> ACTUALLY, WE DO.
CLEAR A PATH, CLEAR A PATH FOR
BARRY, THE FORGIVING MIDWIFE.
>> BARRY, I'M SORRY.
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU AGAIN.
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET HILLARY'S
AMAZING CHOREO, LET'S HIT IT.
>> IT'S TWINS!
>> LOOK, BABY, IT'S YOUR
BROTHER.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> ACTUALLY -- WE'VE MET.
MIKEY
I'VE HEARD SHE'S A REALLY NICE,
GENUINE, DOWN-TO-EARTH PERSON.
>> HEY, GUYS.
HEY
>> SOMEBODY CALL --
>> JUST DON'T.
HEY, MIKEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD, I'M -- IT'S CRAZY, YOU
KNOW, BETWEEN THE OSCARS AND SNL,
IT'S JUST LIKE WAAAHHH!
>> YEAH, YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU SQUIDWARD?
>> SQUIDWARD FROM SPONGEBOB.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED AS HE?
>> SORRY.
JUST WOKE UP LATE AND THREW THIS
ON.
>> YOU'RE PAINT BLUE, HOMIE.
>> OKAY, I'LL PLAY ALONG.
SQUIDWARD, REMEMBER WHEN YOU ATE
ALL THOSE CRABBY PATTYS
AND YOUR
THIGHS GOT HUGE?
>> AS A YOUNG WOMAN IN
HOLLYWOOD,
MAYBE DON'T COMMENT
ON MY THIGHS.
>> OH, GOD, I'M SORRY.
>> I WOULD NEVER COMMENT ON YOUR
BODY.
>> SHUT THE [ BLEEP ] UP, JOHN.
>> THANKS, JOHN.
>> DO YOU WANT TO DO A SKETCH
ABOUT HIM?
>> I DO NOT.
>> I GUESS I WOULD DO A DRAMEDY,
BECAUSE IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT --
WHAT IS SPONGEBOB REALLY ABOUT?
>> A FUNNY SPONGE.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
IT'S ABOUT A FRIEND GROUP
NAVIGATING LIFE IN THEIR EARLY
20s.
>> IS THAT A FUNNY SPONGE?
>> I CAN SEE IT NOW.
AN HBO-STYLE SHOW WITH THE
CHARACTERS FROM SPONGEBOB WE
KNOW AND LOVE,
BUT LIVE ACTION.
>> ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT A TV
SHOW?
>> THAT WOULD TAKE LIKE THREE
YEARS TO DEVELOP.
>> THREE YEARS OF DEVELOPMENT
LATER --
>> WHAT WILL EVERYONE SAY?
I'M SUPPOSED TO HATE YOU, BUT I
CAN'T STOP COMING BACK.
>> WHO CARES ABOUT OTHER
PEOPLE'S OPINIONS?
SOMETIMES YOU JUST HAVE TO
LAUGH.
HZ
PREGNANT?
>> WE WERE JUST TRYING TO STAY
AFLOAT.
AND NOBODY TEACHES YOU HOW TO
SWIM THROUGH YOUR 20s.
>> YOU'VE BEEN LIVING UNDER A
ROCK FOR YEARS.
IT'S HARD TO START UP AGAIN, BUT
WE'RE HERE TO HELP.
DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
>> IS MAYONNAISE AN INSTRUMENT?
>> NO, NO, IT'S NOT.
>> THIS IS GOING TO COST SO MUCH
MONEY MONEY MONEY MONEY MONEY.
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP BRINGING THIS
UP?
>> I JUST THINK IT'S A
CONVERSATION WE NEED TO HAVE.
WE'RE DANCING AROUND IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> MAYBE IT'S NOT WHERE WE WERE
GOING.
>> I LOVE YOU, SQUIDWARD.
>> BUT WHO WE WERE SINKING WITH.
¶ L IS FOR FRIENDS WHO DO STUFF
TOGETHER ¶
¶ U IS FOR YOU AND ME ¶
¶ L IS FOR ANYWHERE ANY
TIME AT ALL ¶
¶ DOWN HERE IN THE DEEP
BLUE SEA ¶
>> SO WHEN LIFE GETS YOU DOWN,
KEEP GOING.
KEEP TREADING WATER.
>> HORSERADISH ISN'T AN
INSTRUMENT EITHER.
WHAT ARE WE
>> HELLO, HELLO.
I'M YOUR HOST, MOLLY WILSON.
WELCOME BACK TO AMERICA'S NUMBER
ONE GAME SHOW
WHERE I BRING OUT
PEOPLE I PERSONALLY AM DATING
AND WE FIND OUT --
>> SO, LIKE, WHAT ARE WE?
>> ALL RIGHT, OUR FIRST
CONTESTANT IS SAVED IN MY PHONE
AS JEREMY HINGE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, IT'S
JEREMY!
>> WOW, THIS IS -- WOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT'S WHAT THIS
SHOW WAS.
AM I -- AM I THE ONLY
CONTESTANT?
>> WHY, HAVE YOU BEEN SEEING
OTHER PEOPLE?
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T.
>> I'M SORRY, WHAT IS THIS?
>> QUESTION ONE. JEREMY,
SO, LIKE, WHAT ARE WE?
>> THAT'S SO BRIGHT.
IF I -- I GUESS -- IF I CAN BE
COMPLETELY HONEST?
>> HONESTY IS WHAT WE'RE LOOKING
FOR.
>> I JUST GOT OUT OF A LONG
RELATIONSHIP,
SO I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR ANYTHING THAT SERIOUS.
>> SO SORRY, WRONG ANSWER.
THAT WILL BE MINUS $10,000 FROM
YOUR PERSONAL BANK ACCOUNT.
>> MY BANK ACCOUNT?
WHAT?
>> YEAH, SORRY, THEM'S THE
RULES.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU WOULD HAVE
WON DID YOU ANSWERED CORRECTLY.
ME.
BECAUSE -- I AM A PRIZE.
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT QUESTION.
EVEN THOUGH I SLEPT WITH YOU
SEVEN TIMES,
IT'S BEEN FIVE DAYS
SINCE YOU'VE HIT ME UP.
SO -- SHOULD I JUST WALK INTO
THE OCEAN WITH BRICKS IN MY
POCKETS?
OR CAN YOU TELL ME, WHAT DID I
DO WRONG?
>> I'M GOING TO LOSE $10,000
JUST BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
LABEL THINGS?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
>> WELL, WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT IN
OUR NEXT ROUND.
EXPLAIN
>> THE OTHER DAY YOU TEXTED ME.
BUSY TILL LATE BUT WANNA LINK
TONIGHT?
>> THAT SEEMS FINE.
>> THE TIME WAS 2:47 A.M.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN THAT TEXT?
>> HM.
PASS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT THIS 1:30 A.M. TEXT
WHERE YOU JUST SAID, ALL LOWER CASE,
DADDY HUNGRY FOR BUTT.
I
>> I'M NOT DONE.
TEN MINUTES LATER, YOU QUESTION
REACTED YOUR OWN MESSAGE.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN THAT TEXT?
>> I WAS HUNGRY FOR BUTT?
>> OH, DISAPPOINTING SHOWING,
JEREMY.
YOU'RE DOWN $100,000.
BUT YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO MAKE IT ALL BACK
AND TRIPLE IT WITH THIS
NEXT ROUND.
>> OKAY, YEAH, I'LL DO ANYTHING.
>> ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS POST A
PHOTO OF US ON INSTAGRAM
AND TAG
ME.
>> OKAY. I
CAN'T DO IT.
BUT -- MAYBE WE LINK UP TONIGHT.
SOMEWHERE BETWEEN 9:00 AND 4:00
A.M.?
>> WOW.
DUDE.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
CALL THE UBER.
JOIN US NEXT TIME ON --
>> "SO, LIKE, WHAT ARE WE?"
PLANNING
SAY
THIS IS A REALLY NICE ISLAND.
>> I HONESTLY THINK WE COULD DO
A CITY HERE.
>> YEAH?
LIKE A BIG CITY?
>> HUGE.
A CITY THAT'S JUST, LIKE TOO,
MUCH.
TOO MUCH EVERYTHING.
AND CRAZY.
>> OKAY.
I'M INTRIGUED.
>> THINKING DOWN AT THE BOTTOM,
STREETS ARE JUST CHAOS.
>> OH, LIKE LONDON.
>> EXACTLY.
>> LET ME WRITE SOME OF THIS
DOWN.
>> CRAZY AT THE BOTTOM, THEN
RANDOMLY THE STREETS ARE ALL
PERFECTLY STRAIGHT.
>> THEY JUST SWITCH?
OUT OF NOWHERE?
>> OUT OF NOWHERE.
THEY HAVE NUMBERS.
LIKE FIRST AVENUE, SECOND
AVENUE, THIRD AVD --
>> FOURTH AVENUE.
>> NO.
LEXINGTON.
AND THEN FOURTH AVENUE --
>> PARK AVENUE.
>> THEN?
MADISON AVENUE.
>> THEN FOURTH AVENUE?
>> FIFTH AVENUE.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU ARE ON ONE
RIGHT NOW.
SO NO FOURTH AVENUE?
WHAT IF THERE WAS A BIG ROAD,
LIKE A BROAD WAY,
THAT WENT
DIAGONAL ACROSS THE WHOLE THING?
>> GENIUS.
I LOVE THAT.
THERE WOULD BE JUST A BUNCH OF
RANDOM TRIANGLES EVERYWHERE.
>> RIGHT?
THEN LISTEN, WE CALL THE
TRIANGLES SQUARES.
>> OH, SO WE CALL THEM LIKE
TIMES SQUARE, WHATEVER, BUT
THEY'RE TRIANGLES.
HERE'S SOMETHING.
TREES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> LET'S SAY IT TOGETHER.
ONE, TWO, THREE --
>> PUT THEM ALL IN THE MIDDLE!
>> YES, ALL THE NATURE IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE CITY.
>> IT'S THERE, IT'S CENTRAL, WE
KNOW WHERE IT IS.
QUESTION, HOW DO PEOPLE GET
AROUND?
>> RANDOM IDEA, TUNNELS.
I KNOW THEY'RE NOT INVENTED YET,
BUT TRAINS GO IN THE TUNNELS.
>> THEY JUST GO WHERE THE
STREETS GO?
>> NO!
THEY DO THEIR OWN THING.
>> SOME GO THIS WAY.
ONE OF THEM JUST SPLITS IN HALF.
HELLO.
AND YOU FIGURE OUT WHERE THEY
GO.
- THOSE ON YOU.
- THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM.
>> WRITE THAT DOWN.
>> WILD PITCH, EVERYONE WHO
LIVES IN THE CITY GETS AN
[ BLEEP ].
>> YES.
MY TURN?
- SOMETIME PISS
- PISS
>> LITERAL SAME BRAIN.
>> INSPIRED.
>> AMAZING.
SOMETHING
WE NEED A CITY WHERE EVERYONE
IS WELCOME.
AND EVERYONE HAS A LITTLE BIT OF
THEIR OWN CULTURE.
AND THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT GREAT.
BECAUSE IT'S A PLACE FOR ALL THE
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD TO LIVE IN
HARMONY.
>> NO!
>> THEY ALL HATE EACH OTHER.
>> ALL LIVE IN THEIR OWN
NEIGHBORHOODS WITH CONSTANT
PROBLEMS.
YES
>> I REALLY THINK WE COULD DO A
REALLY NICE CITY HERE.
WALLEN.
I HAD A WONDERFUL TIME.
THANK YOU, ALL.