Hello.
Hello and welcome to MSNBC.
I'm Rachel Maddow.
And, dads, you better
hide your older bookish
lesbian daughters,
because,
uh, yeah, I'm back on TV.
Tonight, for our special Inauguration
Weekend coverage,
I'm joined by our panel
of MSNBC hosts,
basically like the
Avengers for your aunt.
- It's Ari Melber.
- Thanks, Rachel.
-
- Glad to be here.
- Stephanie Ruhle.
- Hey, girlfriend.
And finally, Chris Hayes, a.k.a.
Woke Sheldon.
Okay.
Drag me, mama.
Well, tonight, we have a lot of news to
cover.
The LEA wildfires are affecting thousands.
The TikTok ban goes into effect tomorrow.
And the Inauguration is only two days
away.
What's your take, Ari?
Well, in the words of the great poet DMX,
y'all gonna make me lose my mind.
Up and here.
What about you, Stephanie?
I mean, Trump is already talking about
invading Canada and Greenland.
Is he serious, or is that one of his
distractions?
I mean, what do you think, Joy?
I don't know.
I can't tell if you're doing the news or
trying to hook up.
What do you think, Rachel?
Oh, I'm not Rachel.
I'm Chris Hayes.
One thing I do know is, this
time around,
we're not gonna get sucked in by every new
shiny, crazy statement from Trump.
We need to focus on what he does,
not what he says.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I have to interrupt you.
We have some breaking news.
Trump has apparently
just told reporters
that he would like to, quote,
trade Connecticut for Italy.
I mean, that's just crazy.
Rachel, Rachel, see, this is what I mean.
We can't have a repeat of 2016.
Exactly.
Uh, in his first term, the media was like,
look at him.
Walking around, grabbing his
you-know-what.
Flipping the you-know-who.
Tick-a-ticka, Slim Shady.
But this time, we're gonna
focus on what matters,
like tech billionaires
buying our democracy.
Sorry, Ari, we're getting breaking news
that Trump just told a group of wildfire victims
that, quote, Arnold Palmer
had some
of the longest balls in American history.
You see, this is what he does.
To keep us from talking about disaster
relief or the impacts of climate change...
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Rachel.
I am Chris.
But... But apparently Trump
just tweeted about the fires.
A picture of himself as the
guy from Up with the caption,
I would end fire by filling the
up house with water balloons.
Wow.
Joy,
this man, this man, this man was
designed by the devil to break my spirit.
You can just call me Ann Reed,
because the joy is gone.
You know, I gotta say, you forget about
the pace of the news under Trump.
It's so hard to get your bearings,
right, Rach?
Please don't put your glasses in my mouth.
Thankfully, here to get us back...
Here to get us back on track is MSNBC...
MSNBC everything correspondent,
Claire McCaskill.
Hi, Rachel.
Claire, throw us a lifeline.
Can you please say something of substance
about this week?
Of course.
And hold that thought, Rachel,
because somehow I'm getting breaking news
that Trump just said he is
sending Don Jr. to
explore the possibility of
purchasing the Emerald City.
Oh, seems like he finally saw Wicked.
Oh, he did.
And he loved Wicked.
...and just now realizing
that he thinks
the Emerald City is Greenland.
Speaking of, uh,
Wicked,
I believe it was Will Smith who said,
Wiki Wiki Wild Wild West.
Jim West, Desperado.
Something to think about.
Okay, we just got word that
President Trump has tweeted
that he has agreed to meet with
Chinese President Xi Jinping.
Oh, that's not that bad.
In the octagon at UFC fight.
You know what?
I'm just gonna take the reins and talk
about a real story, okay?
Trump's tariffs for Canada?
Look, Quebec supplies two-thirds of our
raw aluminum.
And when you consider the importments and
the importance of hydroelectric power...
Oh, my God.
I-I can't even finish.
That is so boring.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, and, uh, America has just declared
war on sharks.
That's good.
Much better.
Also, Trump apparently just gave a
statement about the TikTok ban.
I can pretend I'm not curious,
but, uh, let's just watch the whole thing.
Yes, we love TikTok, don't we?
We love TikTok.
We used to hate it,
but then it, quite frankly,
in many ways, got me
elected, so now we love it.
We also love the Rizzler, don't we,
folks?
And they're trying to take the Rizzler
away from us.
It's so sad.
They want him the hell out of here.
We do love Costco, guys.
Boom!
And we're doing Get Ready With Me.
That's gonna be fun.
And we're doing the Challengers.
Remember Ice Bucket?
We loved Ice Bucket.
Anyway.
We may have to go over to Reels with Mark
Zuckerberg.
I like him now.
Zuck.
He looks better.
Much cooler in terms of perm and with
regard to chain.
And he will, of course, be at my
inauguration, which will be indoors.
Too many people to fit outside.
You know, we're excited.
We're very excited to be inaugurated on
Martin Luther King Day.
I like sharing the day.
And we're excited about my latest cabinet
pick.
It's someone I know you'll be very excited
to see.
George Santos.
Hello, everyone.
Yes, it's me, George Santos,
a.k.a. Quittara Ravache,
a.k.a. Club Chalamet.
I'm so honored to be
joining Trump's cabinet
as secretary of fact-checking
and ambassador to Sephora.
I am part of the politician
to cameo, back to
politician,
and
eventually to jail pipeline.
But while I'm excited for Monday,
this has been a very hard month for me.
I am so sad about the passing of Jimmy
Carter.
He had a great influence on me,
since he was...
my dad.
Now, excuse me, I'm late for a date with
my boyfriend,
Luigi Mangione!
Well, we are almost out
of time,
so let's just try
to end this before another
tweet comes through.
Oh, too late.
Uh, it appears that Trump is watching and
live-tweeting this program right now.
He just said, I'm stuck watching MS,
DNC,
awful anchors.
This line-up looks like
Scooby-Doo: Oops, all Velma.
All right, he still got it.
He still got it.
and live from New York...
It's Saturday Night!
MUSIC
AND YOUR HOST, DAVE CHAPPELLE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- DAVE
CHAPPELLE!
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
TURN THIS UP, I CAN'T HEAR.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
BOY.
I GOT TO TELL YOU GUYS
SOMETHING.
I'M BEING VERY HONEST.
I AM IN QUITE THE PICKLE
TONIGHT.
AND IT STARTED -- IT STARTED IN
OCTOBER.
LORNE MICHAELS CALLED ME.
AND HE ASKED ME TO DO "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"
THE FIRST EPISODE
AFTER THE ELECTION.
AND I WAS LIKE, NAH, MAN, I'M
COOL.
AND HE'S LIKE," WHY NOT?"
"YOU KNOW, THINGS ARE GOING GOOD,
I FINISHED MY NETFLIX
DEAL, I GOT ALL THIS MONEY AND
STUFF."
OH, MAN, PLEASE?
"YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO?"
SAVE THE DATE CLOSEST TO JANUARY
6th."
AND THEN THE DATE STARTED ROLLING AROUND
AND IN DECEMBER
HE STARTED CALLING ME AGAIN.
AND AGAIN I WAS LIKE, "I DON'T
WANT TO DO IT."
AND THIS GOES ON FOR WEEKS AND
WEEKS.
AND FINALLY, I GO, YOU KNOW
WHAT?
I COULD JUST GET RID OF ALL
THESE OLD TRUMP JOKES
AND START
FRESH.
I SAY, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL DO IT."
THANK YOU.
HERE WE ALL ARE.
THE MOMENT I SAID YES,
L.A. BURST INTO FLAMES.
AND IT'S A TOUGH ONE, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
BECAUSE I'M TIRED OF BEING
CONTROVERSIAL.
I'M TRYING TO TURN OVER A NEW
LEAF.
AND IT IS WAY TOO SOON.
TO DO JOKES ABOUT A CATASTROPHE
LIKE THAT.
IT IS.
YOU KNOW, WHAT'S CRAZY ABOUT IT
IS THIS ONE HITS CLOSE TO HOME,
AND I DON'T LIVE IN L.A.
I'VE NEVER BEEN A BIG FAN OF
L.A.
BUT I'VE BUILT MANY, MANY
MEMORIES THERE,
AND I HAVE GREAT
FRIENDS THERE.
AND A LOT OF THEM LOST THEIR
HOMES.
CARY ELWES, STARRED IN "MEN IN TIGHTS" WITH,
HOUSE BURNED TO
THE GROUND.
MAD LIB, WHO WAS ON "SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE" LAST TIME I WAS HERE,
HOUSE BURNT TO THE GROUND.
SO MANY, I COULD GO ON AND ON.
MY FIRST
DENNIS QUAID,
I SAW HIM ON THE
NEWS WITH TEARS IN HIS EYES,
AND IT BROKE MY HEART.
THEN I GO ON THE INTERNET, AND I
WATCH THESE FIRE VIDEOS,
AND I
READ THE COMMENT SECTIONS AND
EVERYONE'S LIKE,
YAH, IT SERVES
THESE CELEBRITIES RIGHT,
I HOPE
THEIR HOUSES BURN DOWN!
YOU SEE THAT?
THAT RIGHT THERE?
THAT'S WHY I HATE POOR PEOPLE.
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T SEE PAST
THEIR OWN PAIN.
OTHER DAY ON THE NEWS --
THE OTHER DAY ON THE NEWS, THEY SAID
THESE FIRES WERE THE MOST
EXPENSIVE TRAGEDY THAT EVER
HAPPENED.
NATURAL DISASTER.
THEY SAID MOST EXPENSIVE NATURAL DISASTER
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED IN
UNITED STATES HISTORY.
AND YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY I THINK
THAT IS?
BECAUSE PEOPLE IN L.A. HAVE NICE
STUFF.
I COULD BURN 40,000 ACRES IN
MISSISSIPPI
FOR 6 OR $700.
AND NOW, AND NOW --
AND NOW WE WATCH THE NEWS OR TALK TO MY
FRIENDS,
THEY ALL HAVE THESE
CONSPIRACY THEORIES WHAT ARE
THESE FIRES?
THEY SAY IT'S ARSONISTS.
I'VE HEARD THIS THEORY,
AND I'M
SURE THERE WAS SOME ARSONISTS.
BUT THERE WERE A LOT OF ELEMENTS
THAT CAME TOGETHER
TO MAKE THIS
FIRE THE CATASTROPHE THAT IT
WAS.
THE WINDS WERE 100 MILES AN
HOUR.
L.A. WAS DRY AS A BONE AND THE LEVIES
AND IT WAS TOO MANY
FACTORS.
IF YOU WERE A RATIONAL THINKING PERSON,
YOU HAVE TO AT LEAST
CONSIDER THE POSSIBILITY
THAT
GOD HATES THESE PEOPLE.
SODOMITES!
AND THAT'S NOT TRUE, BECAUSE --
BECAUSE WEST HOLLYWOOD WAS
UNSCATHED.
BECAUSE, HOW CAN YOU BURN WHAT
IS ALREADY FLAMING?
A LOT OF POOR PEOPLE WERE
AFFECTED, TOO.
A LOT OF JUST REGULAR
WORKING-CLASS FAMILIES WERE
AFFECTED, TOO.
A LOT OF THOSE FAMILIES FOUND
OUT THE WEEK OF THE FIRES
THAT THEY LOST THEIR HEALTH -- NOT
THEIR HEALTH, THEIR FIRE
INSURANCE.
BUT EITHER WAY, LUIGI IS LIKE,
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU KNOW LUIGI, KILLED THEM.
AND THAT KID DID ALMOST PLAN
LIKE THE PERFECT CRIME.
HE DID EVERYTHING RIGHT, PLANNED
EVERYTHING PERFECTLY.
ONLY THING HE FORGOT WAS TO
SHAVE HIS EYEBROWS.
SO THAT'S HIM.
FINALLY, THEY GET IN THE FRONT
OF IT.
THIS WEEK, THANK GOD, THESE
FIRES, SUBSIDING.
AND NOT WITHOUT HELP.
A LOT OF COUNTRIES PITCHED IN.
CANADA SENT PLANES THAT HELPED
US OUT.
MEXICO SENT FIREFIGHTERS.
AND TRUMP WAS LIKE, "MAKE SURE
THEY LEAVE WHEN THEY'RE
FINISHED."
TRUMP'S A WILD GUY.
HE'S A WILD GUY.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING HE DID
THAT MADE ME CRAZY WHEN HE WAS
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
WHEN HE WAS RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT, HE SAID THIS AT A
DEBATE.
HE SAID THE HAITIANS IN
SPRINGFIELD, OHIO,
WERE EATING
PEOPLE'S DOGS AND CATS.
THAT REALLY UPSET ME, BECAUSE I
LIVE IN OHIO. IN FACT, I LIVE --
WHAT'S UP,
OHIO?
I LIVE ONE TOWN OVER FROM
SPRINGFIELD.
THOSE OF YOU WHO ARE FROM OHIO,
I HOPE YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN SPRINGFIELD
AT ALL.
WHAT HAPPENED IN SPRINGFIELD IS
A LOT OF JOBS WENT AWAY.
20,000 HAITIAN IMMIGRANTS WERE
MOVED THERE BY OUR GOVERNMENT, LEGALLY,
AND THEY PAID MARKET VALUE FOR THEIR RENTS,
AND THEY
SAVED A LOT OF COMPANIES BECAUSE
THEY DID JOBS THE WHITES WEREN'T
DOING.
IT'S NOT THAT THE WHITES
COULDN'T DO THESE JOBS, BUT THEY
WERE BUSY DOING OTHER THINGS.
HEROIN, SLEEPING ON THE STREETS,
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS.
AND THOSE COMMUNITIES ARE
IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES WHO TEND
TO BE VERY SUCCESSFUL.
THEY DON'T COME TO AMERICA TO
NOT BE RICH.
WHEN HE SAID THAT, THAT
COMMUNITY CAUGHT HELL.
THERE WAS LIKE A JEALOUSY THAT
RAN THROUGH THE COMMUNITY.
THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO
ABOUT IT.
BUT BECAUSE I WAS FAMOUS I SAID,
LET ME JUST BE SUPPORTIVE.
SO EVERY DAY FOR LIKE TEN DAYS I
WOULD DRIVE A FEW MILES OVER TO SPRINGFIELD
AND EAT LUNCH AT THE
HAITIAN RESTAURANT.
I LET THEM KNOW, IF I'M SAFE
HERE, YOU GUYS ARE DEFINITELY
SAFE HERE.
AND TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEAT WAS.
BUT WHATEVER IT WAS, IT FELL
RIGHT OFF THE BONE, I'LL TELL
YOU THAT.
NOW I'M EVEN GETTING NERVOUS AT
OHIO.
I MIGHT LEAVE WITH THE HAITIANS.
NO, I'M SERIOUS, MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS, MAN?
IT'S JUST NO FUN BEING FAMOUS
ANYMORE.
IT'S LIKE, OH, Y'ALL MADE IT
SCARY.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE,
BEING FAMOUS?
SCARY IS THE RIGHT WORD.
IT FEELS LIKE, AND I'M NOT BEING
DRAMATIC.
IT FEELS LIKE I'M STORMING THE
BEACH AT NORMANDY, WORLD WAR II.
BUT I GOT TO KEEP A HAPPY
EXPRESSION ON MY FACE ALL THE
TIME.
IMAGINE ALL THE DANGERS STORMING
THE BEACH BUT I STILL --
BOATS ARE WHIZZING BY, STUFF IS
EXPLODING, I'M JUST LIKE --
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE, SOMETHING
TERRIBLE HAPPENS.
POW!
OH, NO!
POPPY GOT HIT!
AND POPPY BE LIKE, UH -- KEEP
GOING, PLAYBOY.
FACE
I'VE BEEN IN TROUBLE IN MY DAY.
I'VE BEEN IN A LOT OF TROUBLE IN
MY DAY.
MAN, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
THIS GUY PUFFY,
THIS GUY'S IN AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF TROUBLE.
I DON'T THINK I'VE SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THIS.
THEY GOT THIS GUY IN A RICO CASE
BY HIMSELF.
A LOT OF MY FRIENDS ASK ME,
THEY SAY, DAVE, DID YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THOSE FREAKOFF PARTIES?
I BE LIKE, NO, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
FREAKOFFS.
THEY ALL LOOK AT ME LIKE --
THEY BE LIKE, HOW ARE ALL THESE
PEOPLE YOU KNOW WAS AT THE FREAKOFF,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT WASN'T AT THE FREAKOFF?
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT FOR A MINUTE.
I SAID, OH, MY GOD.
I'M UGLY.
BOY.
THAT IS A TOUGH WAY TO FIND THAT
OUT.
CAN YOU IMAGINE, YOU AND ME
READING THE NEWSPAPER
AND FOUND
OUT EVERYONE IN HOLLYWOOD HAD AN
ORGY BEHIND YOUR BACK?
LIKE, NONE OF Y'ALL CALLED ME?
BOY, THAT REALLY HURTS.
I'M GLAD THEY DIDN'T CALL ME,
THOUGH.
BECAUSE THE STORIES COMING OUT
ABOUT IT ARE CRAZY.
I SAW ONE THING ON THE INTERNET.
SO I'M NOT SURE THIS IS TRUE.
PROBABLY DOUBT IT'S TRUE.
BUT I SAW IT.
SOME GUY WHO SAID HE DO PUFFY
LIKE, YEAH, MAN, HE WAS LIKE, I
WAS AT THE FREAKOFF,
I WENT IN
THE BACK ROOM, PUFF WAS IN THERE
WITH THE GUY FROM "FAMILY MATTERS,"
HE WAS SMASHING.
I WAS LIKE, PUFF, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
HE WAS LIKE, YEAH, FEELS GOOD TO
MAKE ANOTHER MAN DO YOUR
BIDDING.
AND I WAS LIKE, OH, MY GOD.
KARL WINSLOW FROM "FAMILY
MATTERS" WAS THERE,
AND I WASN'T
INVITED?
WORSE THAN I THOUGHT.
OR -- OR MAYBE I'M NOT UGLY.
YOU KNOW.
LOOK.
LOOK AT MY FACE.
THIS IS NOT NECESSARILY A
HANDSOME FACE.
BUT IT'S NOT AN UGLY FACE.
BUT IF YOU REALLY STUDY MY FACE
CLEARLY, CLEARLY
I HAVE SNITCH
ENERGY.
OH, I LOOK LIKE I'LL TELL.
THE LAST THING YOU WANT TO SEE
AT AN ORGY IS ME ACROSS THE ROOM
LOOKING AT YOU LIKE --
LEAVE KARL WINSLOW ALONE!
AMEN, AMEN.
SO YOU WATCHING AT HOME, YOU
MIGHT NOT BE FAMOUS,
BUT I BET
YOU AIN'T PERFECT.
NOBODY IS PERFECT.
THE IDEA IS THAT YOU LIVE YOUR LIFE
AND GROW PAST YOUR
MISTAKES.
BUT IF YOU GET TO BE 55 --
AND PUFFY IS 55.
HE DOESN'T LOOK OLD, BUT HE'S
PAYING HALF PRICE AT THE MOVIES.
I SEE YOU, PLAYBOY.
AIN'T NOTHING WRONG GETTING
OLDER, BUT IF YOU 55
AND YOU GOT
A THOUSAND BOTTLES OF BABY OIL
IN THE HOUSE,
CLEARLY YOU CAN'T
STOP, DON'T STOP.
YOU COMMITTED TO THE LIFESTYLE.
BECAUSE I'M 51.
AND I'M TELLING YOU, THIS IS
TRUE.
I CAN'T REMEMBER A SINGLE TIME
I EVER THREW AN EMPTY BOTTLE OF
BABY OIL IN THE TRASH.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER FINISHED
A BOTTLE OF BABY OIL IN MY LIFE.
IF WE WENT TO MY MOTHER'S HOUSE
TONIGHT, SHE'D PROBABLY HAVE THE
SAME BABY OIL WE HAD
WHEN I WAS
A LITTLE BOY WITH A TANK TOP,
AND SOMEHOW PUFFY WAS ALL THE
WAY DOWN TO THE LAST.
AND HAVING BABY OIL IS NOT
ILLEGAL.
THEY DON'T REMIND YOU ABOUT THAT
PART.
THAT'S THE LEAST HARMFUL THING I
READ.
HE WAS THE WRONG LUBE, I THINK.
IF HE USED CRISCO, HE WOULD HAVE
GOT AWAY FROM IT.
THEY JUST KNOW HE LIKES TO COOK.
THANKS.
THANK GOD THEY CAUGHT HIM BEFORE
THOSE FIRES.
GODDAMN MUSHROOM CLOUD OVER HIS
HOUSE.
A THOUSAND BOTTLES OF BABY OIL
IN THERE.
HERE'S THE THING.
ON MONDAY, DONALD TRUMP'S COMING
BACK.
HE'LL BE THE 47th PRESIDENT.
HE'S DONE IT AGAIN.
AND ALL THE FLAGS WILL BE AT
HALF STAFF BECAUSE JIMMY CARTER
DIED.
JIMMY CARTER, GO BACK AND FORTH
AND SAY HE WAS A BAD PRESIDENT
OR A GOOD PRESIDENT.
I'M NOT QUALIFIED TO SPEAK ON
THAT.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS.
I WAS IN THE MIDDLE EAST YEARS
AGO AFTER I QUIT MY SHOW.
I WAS TRYING TO FIND OUT WHAT I
WANTED TO DO WITH MY LIFE.
WHILE I WAS THERE, JIMMY CARTER
FLEW TO ISRAEL.
SO EVERYBODY IN THE REGION WAS
TALKING ABOUT A FORMER AMERICAN
PRESIDENT.
BEING IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
AND WHILE HE WAS IN ISRAEL, A
BOOK OF HIS WAS RELEASED,
AND
ITS TITLE WAS VERY CONTROVERSIAL
IN ISRAEL.
AND THE TITLE OF THE BOOK WAS
"PALESTINE: PEACE, NOT"
APARTHEID."
PEOPLE WERE VERY MAD IN ISRAEL.
THERE WAS A LOT OF MEAN STORIES
THAT CAME OUT IN THE PAPER.
SOME PEOPLE WERE SUPPORTIVE.
WHILE HE WAS THERE,
JIMMY CARTER
SAID, I WANT TO GO TO THE
PALESTINIAN TERRITORY,
AND THE
ISRAELI GOVERNMENT SAID, IT'S
TOO DANGEROUS,
AND IF YOU GO, WE
CANNOT PROTECT YOU.
AND THEN JIMMY CARTER WENT
ANYWAY.
I WILL NEVER FORGET THE IMAGES
OF A FORMER AMERICAN PRESIDENT
WALKING WITH LITTLE TO NO SECURITY
WHILE THOUSANDS OF
PALESTINIANS WERE CHEERING HIM
ON.
WHEN I SAW THAT PICTURE, IT
BROUGHT TEARS TO MY EYES.
I SAID, I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S A
GOOD PRESIDENT,
BUT THAT RIGHT
THERE, I AM SURE,
IS A GREAT
MAN.
IT MADE ME FEEL VERY PROUD.
THE PRESIDENCY IS NO PLACE FOR
PETTY PEOPLE.
SO DONALD TRUMP, I KNOW YOU
WATCH THE SHOW.
MAN, REMEMBER, WHETHER PEOPLE
VOTED FOR YOU OR NOT,
THEY'RE
ALL COUNTING ON YOU.
WHETHER THEY LIKE YOU OR NOT,
THEY'RE ALL COUNTING ON YOU.
THE WHOLE WORLD IS COUNTING ON
YOU.
I MEAN THIS WHEN I SAY THIS.
GOOD LUCK.
PLEASE, DO BETTER NEXT TIME.
PLEASE, ALL OF US, DO BETTER
NEXT TIME.
DO NOT FORGET YOUR HUMANITY,
AND PLEASE HAVE EMPATHY FOR
DISPLACED PEOPLE,
WHETHER
THEY'RE IN THE PALISADES OR
PALESTINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, AND GOOD
NIGHT.
SHOW"
WITH YOUR HOST JOAQUIN
ANTONIO GONZALES HERNANDES
SUAREZ.
>> HELLO AND WELCOME TO
IMMIGRANT DAD TALK SHOW.
THIS IS THE SHOW WHERE WE TALK
ABOUT OUR CHILDREN,
THE ONES WE
LOVE AND THE SONS AS WELL
TODAY I AM JOINED BY MY SPECIAL
GUEST,
MY BLACK NEIGHBOR,
RICHARD.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SAY BLACK MAN.
>> SORRY, MY AFRICAN AMERICAN
NEIGHBOR RICHARD.
>> JUST SAY BLACK.
>> OKAY.
HEY, BLACK RICHARD --
HOW MANY SONS DO YOU HAVE?
>> WELL, I GOT THREE THAT GREW
UP IN MY HOUSE
AND ONE WHO'S --
I ONLY KNOW BY VOICE.
>> OKAY, HA HA HA.
THAT GIVE ME MORE QUESTIONS THAN
ANSWERS.
BUT LET'S START WITH OUR FIRST
SEGMENT.
"THINGS OUR SONS LIKE THAT THEY"
SHOULDN'T LIKE."
MY SON LOVE TIKTOK.
I TELL HIM, LET ME TIKTOK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
GET A JOB, MAN.
YOU ARE BROKE, AND YOU ARE UGLY.
YOU CANNOT BE BOTH.
RICHARD, WHAT YOUR SON LIKE THAT
HE SHOULDN'T LIKE?
>> WHITE PEOPLE.
HE JUST LOVES THEM.
I TELL YOU, YOU NEED BLACK
FRIENDS, HE SAYS,
NO, I NEED
SOME DRIED CHICKEN AND SOME
IMPROV.
>> OH, MY GOD, MY SON LOVE TO GO
TO BROOKLYN TO IMPROV WITH THE
WHITE PEOPLE.
REMIND ME.
MY SON THE OTHER DAY HE SAY TO ME,
I WANT TO BE VEGAN.
I SAY, VEGAN TALK ABOUT THIS
AFTER YOU EAT THE CHICKEN.
>> MY SON SAID HE DIAGNOSED
HIMSELF WITH OCD.
I SAID, OH?
CD'S NUTS!
BIG BALLS
>> OH, OKAY, MAN.
HEY, IT'S TIME TO BRING OUT MY
NEXT GUEST.
HE'S A FATHER WHO LIVING IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW
KEVIN.
>> HOLA, KEVIN, HOLA.
>> HOLA, SENOR.
AND GREETINGS, BLACK KING.
>> WHITE GUY ALWAYS KNOW WHAT
NOT TO SAY, HA HA HA.
KEVIN, TELL US.
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR WORK?
>> WELL, I AM A GUIDANCE
COUNSELOR AT A SCHOOL FOR
CHILDREN WITH LEARNING
DISABILITIES.
>> OH.
THAT'S FUNNY, BECAUSE MY SON
HAVE A DISABILITY.
DISABILITY TO PISSING MY OFF.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR OUR NEXT
SEGMENT, "WHAT WOULD YOU DO?"
I TELL YOU SOMETHING, YOU TELL
ME, WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
FIRST, YOUR SON GET MAD AND SLAM
THE DOOR.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO, KEVIN?
>> I LIKE TO APPROACH ANY ISSUE
WITH WHAT I CALL THE THREE Cs.
COMMUNICATION, COMPASSION, AND
CARE.
>> OH, WE FORGOT THE FOURTH "C."
A-PU-CIE.
>> HE SAY YOU HAVE VAGINA, OKAY.
HEY, RICHARD, SAME QUESTION FOR
YOU.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOUR SON
SLAMMING THE DOOR?
>> WELL, I WOULD BE AMAZED.
BECAUSE MY SON DON'T HAVE A
DOOR.
I TOOK IT OFF THE HINGES BECAUSE
HE GOT ADDICTED TO PORNOGRAPHY.
A BLACK LIGHT IN HIS ROOM, IT
WOULD LOOK LIKE A CRIME SCENE
FROM A "CSI" EPISODE.
CSI.
I LIKE "LAW AND ORDER."
YOU KNOW "LAW ANDARD"?
TA-DUM!
YOU KNOW WHAT I DO IF MY SON
SLAMMING THE DOOR?
I SHOOT HIM WITH A GUN.
HE NEED TO SHOW RESPECT
BECAUSE
MY BALLS USED TO BE HIS HOUSE.
>> WELL -- I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW MY
SON DOES RESPECT ME,
BECAUSE I
RESPECT HIM.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, CONNER?
COME ON OUT HERE, BUDDY, COME
ON.
>> HEY, DAD.
>> HEY.
>> I'M SO LUCKY TO BE YOUR SON.
>> HEY, YOU'RE NOT JUST MY SON.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
NOW, LET'S DO OUR SECRET
HANDSHAKE.
>> YOU KISSING YOUR SON LIKE TOM
BRADY!
>> OH, OH, KEVIN, KEVIN.
PLEASE TELL US,
WHAT DOES YOUR
WIFE THINK ABOUT YOU HAVING SEX
WITH YOUR SON?
>> I DON'T HAVE SEX WITH MY SON.
>> AND MY WIFE LOVES THAT WE
HAVE A CLOSE RELATIONSHIP.
SHE'S ACTUALLY HERE AS WELL.
SWEETHEART?
COME ON OUT.
>> HI, SWEETIE.
>> HOLD UP.
HOLD UP.
YOU GOT THIS ASS-BACKWARDS, MAN.
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO KISS YOUR
SON AND JUST DAP UP YOUR WIFE?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO TAKE THIS,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> COME ON, SON.
>> SPEAKING OF WHICH, ONE OF MY
SONS IS HERE ALSO.
COME ON OUT, SON.
>> HOW YOU DOING, GOOD TO MEET
YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU TOO, TAKE
CARE.
>> THAT WAS VERY NICE.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, WELL, THAT'S ALL THE
TIME WE ARE HAVING TODAY FOR
IMMIGRANT DAD SHOW.
TUNE IN NEXT WEEK WHEN MY SON
ASK ME TO MAKE AN IMPOSSIBLE BURGER
AND I SAY, BUT HOW?
LA
ALERT AS THE WILDFIRES CONTINUE
TO THREATEN.
>> OKAY, THAT'S IT.
THE CITY IS SAYING WE NEED TO
EVACUATE.
>> OH, MY GOD, NOW?
>> YES, KEVIN.
WE KNEW THIS DAY MIGHT COME.
OUR STUFF IS PACKED AND IN THE
GARAGE.
REGGIE, YOU READY?
>> NO, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
>> BUT IT'S -- IT'S GOING TO BE
FINE, WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS.
I PUT ALL OUR FAMILY PHOTOS IN
THE GO BAG.
>> I GOT TO GET SOMETHING FIRST.
>> REGGIE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I GOT TO GET THIS CASH.
>> WHERE DID YOU GET THAT MONEY?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT WHERE I GOT
MY MONEY, AIN'T NO TIME TO
EXPLAIN, JUST GO.
COME ON, BOY, COME AND HELP ME
GET THIS MONEY.
>> OH, GEEZ, DAD, HOW MUCH IS IN
HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, 500 GRAND OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
ENOUGH FOR A WHILE.
>> A WHILE?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
IS THIS A PASSPORT?
AND REGGIE, WHO IS DEMETRIUS
QUINN?
>> SOMEBODY -- SOMEBODY WHO'S
ALWAYS WELCOME IN THE DOMINICAN
REPUBLIC, THAT'S WHO.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE THIS?
>> BABY, THERE IS NO TIME TO
EXPLAIN.
THE HOUSE GOING TO BURN DOWN AND
Y'ALL WORRIED ABOUT WHO IS
DEMETRIUS QUINN?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT ELSE ARE YOU HIDING IN
THIS HOUSE, REGGIE?
>> OH -- OH, THANKS FOR
REMINDING ME.
THINK
HERE, BOY.
TAKE THIS.
YOU EVER HOLD HEAVY METAL
BEFORE?
>> NO, DAD, I'M IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I PLAY THE BASSOON.
>> I'M SORRY, SON, I LET YOU
DOWN.
I RAISED YOU SOFT LIKE A BITCH.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SHOOT A
GUN.
>> YES, THERE ARE BOSNIANS ON
THE WAY COMING TO KILL US
AND
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, I PLAY THE
BASSOON.
LIKE THAT
>> IT'S ME, GIVE US WHAT WE ARE
OWED.
>> SON?
>> DAD, I CAN'T.
>> ALLOW ME.
>> I BLAME YOU!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WHY DO I GOT TO DO EVERYTHING
MYSELF AROUND THIS HOUSE!
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> LOOK, BABY, JUST CALM DOWN.
I NEED YOU TO TAKE THIS THUMB
DRIVE, ALL RIGHT?
THERE'S BANK ACCOUNTS, PICTURES,
EVERYTHING'S IN HERE.
TAKE IT.
SICK IT IN YOUR COOCH.
>> WHAT?
NO, I'M NOT DOING THAT.
WHY DON'T YOU PUT IT IN YOUR
ASS?
>> BECAUSE IF I PUT IT IN MY
ASS, WHO'S GOING TO HOLD THE
MAP?
>> COME ON, LET'S BE TEAM
PLAYERS, LET'S GET GOING!
>> YOUR HEAD UP IN YOUR ASS TOO?
WHAT HAVE YOU NOT TOLD OUR
FAMILY?
>> OH, MY FAMILY.
FORGOT ABOUT THIS.
>> LOOK, STOP CALLING ME PAPA IN
FRONT OF MY REAL FAMILY.
TAKE THESE, RUN FOR YOUR LIFE.
GO ON GET.
GO!
>> I'M SORRY, YOU SPEAK FRENCH?
WHO WAS THAT?
WERE THEY LIVING HERE?
>> I TOLD YOU, THERE'S NO TIME
FOR THAT.
ALL YOU WANT TO DO IS TALK ABOUT
WHAT IS THIS, WHAT IS THAT?
THE HOUSE IS GOING TO BURN UP.
WE'VE GOT TO GO, LEAVE THE REST.
>> WHAT ABOUT BUSTER?
WE CAN'T LEAVE BUSTER.
>> BUSTER.
COME HERE!
>> I'LL BET HE'S GONE THAT DOG
PROBABLY SAW YOU SHOOT THAT MAN
AND DROVE AWAY IN OUR HYUNDAI.
>> BUSTER, BUSTER.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, COME ON, BUSTER.
>> MY GOD, BUSTER, I CAN'T
BELIEVE I ALMOST FORGOT WHAT'S
IMPORTANT.
THIS IS THE CORE OF OUR FAMILY.
HE'S A GOOD BOY.
AND HE GOT SOMETHING VERY
IMPORTANT IN THE STOMACH --
>> DON'T WORRY, I MADE IT QUICK.
OH, STILL MOVING A LITTLE BIT.
>> HERE, BOY.
TAKE A BITE OUT OF IT.
>> NO, NO WAY!
>> YOU A BITCH!
>> I KNEW I SHOULD HAVE STAYED A
LESBIAN LIKE I WAS IN COLLEGE.
>> EXCUSE ME, I GOT TO MAKE A
PHONE CALL.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET OUT OF
HERE, LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
>> OH, IT'S ANOTHER NOTICE FROM
THE CITY.
THE ALERT WAS A FALSE ALARM.
>> YOU PASSED MY TEST.
JUST GOT TO BE A LITTLE FASTER
NEXT TIME, THAT'S ALL.
>> NO, YOU GOT TO LEAVE, I DON'T
EVEN KNOW YOU.
>> YEAH, MAN, GET OUT OF HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, FINE.
YOU SEE THE CAT, IT'S GOT A PAGE
IN ITS ASS.
WHAT
GLORILLA.
Yeah Glo!"
¶ GLORILLA
RUN UP ON BIG GLO
YOU WON'T I BET YOU
BE ON THE FLOOR ¶
¶ BIG CARBON HIT
LIKE MAYWEATHER
TULA COME THRU AND BOW 'EM ¶
¶ GOT MILLIONS OFF OF RAPPIN
THEY HATE ME
BUT THEY STOLE THE FLOW ¶
¶ GOT BACKEND AFTER BACK END
COMIN' YEAH
I STOLE THE SHOW ¶
DON'T RUN UP ON THAT GIRL
SHE A HEADCASE
ALL SHE DO IS SHOOT ¶
¶ I SIGNED MY DEAL
UP ON A PJ
AND HOPPED OUT A PARACHUTE ¶
¶ I'M GEEKED DON'T ASK ME
'BOUT NO MORE FEATURES
I MIGHT JUST STARE AT YOU ¶
¶ I'M GEEKED DON'T ASK ME
'BOUT NO MORE FEATURES
I MIGHT EMBARRASS YOU ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
STOMP A LIL
WITH SOME SHELL TOES ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
SLAPPIN' RAPPERS
AND MAKIN' BAIL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
TWO TONE CARTIER
MATCH THE NAILS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
NO COMPETITION
THESE PEOPLE STALE WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
CUBAN ON CUBAN
MY STUFF IS GLASS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
SAY THEY GET MONEY
BUT I CAN'T TELL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
KEEP RUNNIN' CIRCLES
AROUND THESE SNAIL WOES ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
AND MY STUFF BUMPIN'
UP IN THE JAIL WOE ¶
¶ BIG GLO WHERE YOU BEEN AT
EVERYWHERE
I'M WORKIN' HARD ¶
¶ MAYBACH AND G WAGON TRUCKS
GOT M&MS IN MY GARAGE ¶
¶ QUICK TO CRANK UP ON 'EM
YOU PEOPLE BETTER NOT
GET ME STARTED ¶
¶ LOCKED IN WITH
THE GANGSTAS
AND PLAYERS MY FOLKS
GON' KEEP IT SOLID ¶
¶ EVERYTHING I GOT ON NEW
IT LOOK LIKE
I GOT RENOVATED ¶
¶ I'M COCKY
WHEN I WAS JUST HUMBLE
THEY DIDN'T
APPRECIATE IT ¶
¶ YOUNG WEALTHY AND RATCHET
I'M THE HOOD WOMEN
MOTIVATION ¶
¶ ON TOP OF THE WORLD
NOW THEY TRIED TO
UNDERESTIMATE ME ¶
¶ GET 'EM GLO
THEM PEOPLE FRAUDULENT
YOU KNOW THE TRUTH ¶
¶ GET 'EM GLO
STOP OVERTHINKIN'
THESE FOLKS
CAN'T MESS WITH YOU ¶
¶ GET 'EM GLO
STANDIN' ON BUSINESS
IN THESE CHANEL SHOES ¶
¶ BEFORE I LET A
PLAY WITH ME
I'LL GO EAT SOME
JAIL FOOD ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
STOMP A LIL
WITH SOME SHELL TOES ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
SLAPPIN' RAPPERS
AND MAKIN' BAIL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
TWO TONE CARTIER
MATCH THE NAILS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
NO COMPETITION
THESE PEOPLE STALE WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
CUBAN ON CUBAN
MY STUFF IS GLASS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
SAY THEY GET MONEY
BUT I CAN'T TELL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
KEEP RUNNIN' CIRCLES
AROUND THESE SNAILS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
AND MY STUFF BUMPIN'
UP IN THE JAIL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO ¶
>> LET ME HEAR Y'ALL MAKE SOME
NOISE!
¶ YEAH GLO ¶
>> WE GOTTA COME ON!
>> RIGHT SIDE, LET ME HEAR YOU
SAY.
>> LEFT SIDE, LET ME HEAR YOU
>> UP TOP, LET ME HEAR YOU SAY.
>> SNL, LET ME HEAR YOU SAY.
¶ YEAH GLO
CUBAN ON CUBAN
MY STUFF IS GLASS WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
SAY THEY GET MONEY
BUT I CAN'T TELL WOE ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
KEEP RUNNIN' CIRCLES
AROUND THESE SNAIL WOES ¶
¶ YEAH GLO
AND MY STUFF BUMPIN'
UP IN THE JAIL WOE
YEAH GLO ¶¶
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, GUYS, IT'S THE DAWN OF A
NEW ERA.
DONALD TRUMP RELEASED HIS
OFFICIAL INAUGURAL PORTRAIT,
AND
THE PHOTO IS LIT
I ASSUME BY HELL OPENING UP.
TRUMP IS TRYING TO LOOK SO
HARD-CORE IN HIS PHOTO,
I'M
SURPRISED HE DIDN'T ADD A
PARENTAL ADVISORY STICKER AND A
DO RAG.
AND THEN TRUMP ALSO RELEASED THE
OFFICIAL PORTRAIT OF J.D. VANCE.
>> DONALD TRUMP'S INAUGURATION
CEREMONY HAS BEEN MOVED INSIDE
THE CAPITOL BUILDING.
HEY, JUST LIKE LAST TIME.
PRESIDENT BIDEN DELIVERED A
FAREWELL ADDRESS TO THE NATION ON WEDNESDAY
AND THEN
TRIUMPHANTLY RODE OFF INTO THE
PAVEMENT.
>> IN HIS FAREWELL SPEECH TO THE
NATION, PRESIDENT BIDEN
DEFENDED
HIS ADMINISTRATION'S ACCOMPLISHMENTS
BY ENDING EVERY
SENTENCE WITH, "YOU UNGRATEFUL
BASTARDS."
>>> META CEO AND PUERTO RICAN
GIGOLO, MARK ZUCKERBERG --
MAR-A-LAGO
MEET WITH DONALD TRUMP,
AND BOY
ARE HIS KNEES TIRED.
>>> TRUMP'S INAUGURATION DAY
FALLS ON MARTIN LUTHER KING DAY,
AND IF DR. KING WERE ALIVE
TODAY, I BED TRUMP WOULD WALK
RIGHT UP TO HIM AND SAY,
"OH,
SNAP, IT'S BEN CARSON!"
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHO THEY ARE.
>>> IN OTHER BIG NEWS THIS WEEK,
ISRAEL AND HAMAS
COMMITTED TO
THEIR VERSION OF DRY JANUARY.
CEASEFIRE
PRESIDENT BIDEN SAID THAT THE
ISRAEL/HAMAS CEASE-FIRE TALKS
WERE ONE OF THE TOUGHEST
NEGOTIATIONS HE HAD EVER
EXPERIENCED.
THE HARDEST PART WAS CONVINCING BOTH SIDES
THAT HE WAS STILL THE
PRESIDENT.
>>> PRESIDENT BIDEN ANNOUNCED
THAT A NAVY AIRCRAFT CARRIER
WILL BE NAMED IN HONOR OF BILL
CLINTON.
THE CARRIER WILL ALSO HONOR BILL
CLINTON BY BEING COVERED IN
SEAMEN.
MEN OF THE SEA.
MEN OF THE SEA I SHOULD HAVE
SAID.
>>> ROBERT F. KENNEDY JR.,
TRUMP'S NOMINEE TO LEAD THE
NATION'S HEALTH AGENCIES,
WILL
HAVE HIS SENATE CONFIRMATION
HEARING NEXT WEEK.
RFK HAS BEEN PREPARING FOR THE
HEARINGS
BY SETTING HIS TANNING
BED TO "TROPIC THUNDER."
An agreement in the defamation lawsuit
against Rudy Giuliani has been reached,
which allows him to keep his
Florida condo, Yankees memorabilia,
and his most prized
possession, Secretariat's Teeth.
He's got horse teeth, Colin.
Steve... Steve Bannon attacked Elon Musk,
calling him a truly evil person.
Though technically, Bannon's exact words
were,
Elon Musk-a-de-chuba-ki-ma-da-evil.
Why'd you say it in Italian?
Hours ago...
Hours ago, TikTok went offline in the U.S.
Here to plead one final case for not
banning TikTok is Michael Longfellow.
Che.
Always good to see you, Che.
I wish you were under happier
circumstances.
Well, so you're against the United States
banning TikTok?
Correct.
It's the first political opinion I've ever
had.
I feel it is my responsibility
to come out here
and defend TikTok's right to
remain in these United States.
Well, there are legitimate reasons for
banning TikTok.
Like what?
Because it's Chinese?
So we're just banning things because
they're from China now?
Well, you know who else was from China?
- No, man.
- That's right.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus was not Chinese, man.
I thought he was Middle Eastern,
but I saw it on a TikTok.
Chinese!
Jesus Christ was Chinese.
What about the fact they say TikTok is
stealing your data?
Who cares about my data?
Oh, no.
China knows I like thick Latinas.
Who doesn't?
Give me a break.
I mean, that's a fair point.
What about all the research that says it's
bad for your brain?
Ah, this is boring.
I'm bored.
Are you trying to swipe up on me?
Yes!
Why won't you go?
Sorry, I just... I have no attention span
anymore.
- I have ADHD.
- I didn't know that.
I'll never forget being diagnosed.
It was last year.
I took a TikTok quiz.
And the third time I took it, it said I
might have ADHD.
That does not mean you have ADHD.
Then why did TikTok give me Adderall?
Which I didn't even know was medicine,
by the way.
The doctor told me, we're giving you
Adderall,
and I was like, oh, cool,
but this is no time to party, doctor.
But I guess people use it to read.
Okay, but even...
But even if you don't want it banned,
what about future generations?
And what have the generations already
lost?
What becomes of us?
How do we live now?
Well, you've lived without TikTok for most
of your life.
You just live like you used to live.
I don't remember how.
I know I lived a life before TikTok.
I must have.
But that boy is dead.
He's dead, and he's never coming back.
Without TikTok, I don't know anything
anymore.
What do I do at work?
What do I even watch during a movie?
Just watch the movie!
But during, Che, when I get bored for like
a few seconds...
Just still watch the movie.
I'm moving to China.
Michael Longfellow, everybody!
This gives zero...
Spikes have been installed on several New
York City subway turnstiles
in an effort
to stop fare evaders,
as well as to provide something
sharp for mentally ill
people to shove you into.
Harry, the miniature donkey who served as
a model for Donkey and the Shrek movies,
has died at the age of
30,
just as he was about to reveal what he saw
at those ditty parties.
I heard that on TikTok, Colin.
Progresso is introducing a new
soup-flavored hard candy
called Soup Drops.
Soup Drops are the brainchild of Progresso's
new CEO,
a deranged, toothless hobo.
A Pulitzer Prize-winning cartoonist was
the first person to be arrested,
according to the new
California law
prohibiting the possession of
AI-generated child porn.
Which brings me to my new segment,
Hear Me Out.
Isn't AI-generated child porn
the best
possible solution for pedophiles?
They aren't real kids.
It's just fake kids that are generated by
scanning thousands of real...
Okay, now I see the problem.
This has been Hear Me Out.
New research suggests that by the year
2060,
the number of people in the U.S.
with dementia will double,
and my heart goes out to
all those Jamaican ladies
who have to deal with that.
A new study finds that the country with
the largest average bra size is Norway,
but America still has the largest average
bra size for men.
Hear Me Out.
Louisiana Governor Jeff
Landry has cleared homeless
encampments in New Orleans
ahead of next month's Super Bowl.
No word on where they sent the homeless
people, but on my way in today, a guy did ask me,
uh, you got that there
dollar there, mon ami?
What is going on?
New York City police are searching for the
serial mugger
who makes victims negotiate what he'll steal,
and is
being called the Haggler After Midnight,
which is also my
nickname at the Hustler Club.
I've heard that.
One of the more surprising success stories
at the holiday box office this year
was
Nosferatu, a remake of the classic 1922
film.
Here to comment is the original Nosferatu.
Evening
cost oceans of time to find you,
and also the George Washington Bridge.
Traffic was crazy.
I'm cheating.
It's good to see you, Colin.
Oh, well, it's great to have you here too,
original Nosferatu.
Wow, wow.
It's much smaller than I imagined.
Yes, I know.
People are always saying that about the
studio.
Not the studio!
Your penis, Colin!
During
That's very funny, Nosferatu.
Oh, my God, it is out.
I must have been like that all day.
God, I visited sick kids at the hospital.
And for those of you wondering,
he looked just like me.
Weird, white, and pointy.
Okay, I'm just, I'm gonna ignore that.
Uh, anyway, I'm very curious.
What did you think of the new Nosferatu
movie?
I thought it sucked!
- Vampire humor sucked.
- Yeah.
No, really good.
Speaking of, I want to suck your veiny
neck!
Okay, please do not touch me with your
cold, slimy fingers.
Said your former assistant!
No, I'm cheating, I'm cheating.
I really like the movie.
Although it, like, would
have been nice to,
like, get an audition,
like, heat me up, bro.
All right, I gotta say,
it sounds like you
might be a little jealous
of the new Nosferatu.
Jealous of what, Colin?
He doesn't even look like the Nosferatu!
The guy is, like, jacked and has,
like, a mustache.
He looks like shirtless Ned Flanders!
Like, how did he even get so swole?
Vampires only do one sit-up a day!
And it's like this, Colin!
It's like this!
Really, very, very impressive.
I think you might just be a little jealous
of the new Nosferatu,
because you can barely do one sit-up, and you can't grow
any facial hair.
Whatever, Colin.
You can't grow a mustache either.
Okay, okay, stop.
You're gonna give me a nosebleed?
The last thing I need is you sucking on my
nose.
Suck on your nose?
Really?
No, thanks.
I don't want to be up all night.
Cocaine, Colin!
Yes.
Thank you.
I got that Nosferatu.
Noseferatu?
Well, you've got a nose for coke,
dude.
Okay, don't encourage him.
You seem really amped up yourself.
I need to suck some blood.
I'm thirsty, Colin.
Well, guess it's time to visit my favorite
cast member,
that's Sarah Sherman.
Oh, yes.
And why is she your favorite?
Because she's been on her period
for three
years straight.
Good Lord.
Well, you know what I always say.
If there's blood on the field,
play ball.
Nosferatu, everyone.
I like the movie.
I like it.
FOR
Mr. Curtis.
Officers, please help.
You've got to help me find my girlfriend.
Okay, well, now that we've got
her name and address,
all we need now is a physical description
so we can broadcast it wide.
We'll put her information on the news,
the paper,
and the posters all over town.
Oh, sure.
Whatever you need.
- Okay, here we go.
Eye color.
- Brown.
Height.
Five-six.
Great.
And her weight.
- I'm sorry?
- Uh, how much does she weigh?
If you don't know, just guess.
So you want me to say a number of what I
think her weight is
on record?
Uh, sorry.
Excuse me.
I just, uh, need to take this trash out
real quick.
It's her trap.
Mr. Curtis, we legally need to put
something down.
Just a number, okay?
What is her weight?
Okay, well, personally, I've never really
thought about my girlfriend's weight.
Uh, seriously?
Um, all right.
Uh, look.
If you were to buy her a jacket,
what size jacket would she wear?
Uh, tiny, tiny, tiny.
Hello, this is the police.
Uh, look.
Buddy, I have to put a number on the form
or we cannot proceed, okay?
So please, take this as seriously as
possible.
Look, I do.
And I'm trying, okay?
It's, uh...
One, six...
Two
85 pounds.
85.
85 pounds?
She's that small?
Okay, uh, let's move on.
What is your girlfriend's race?
She black.
Okay, and how old is she?
She grown.
Okay, and what does she do for work?
She a queen.
Uh, all right.
You know, look, Mr. Curtis,
are there any unique
identifying features your
girlfriend might have?
Birthmark?
Anything specific?
Oh, a beautiful soul.
She got a beautiful soul.
All right, uh, let me see if I got this
straight,
because again, this is the
information we're going to put all over
the news.
So on the news, they're going to say,
and I quote,
authorities in Trenton County
are looking for a tiny 85-pound
grown
black queen with a beautiful soul?
Yes, that is exactly right.
And when you find her, you tell her,
that's what I told you to put on a poster.
Okay, so then your girlfriend looks like
this.
Ah, sorry, sorry, that's not right.
You, uh, forgot her crown.
Jesus Christ.
Well, this was a waste of time,
but I guess we need to get this APA out as
soon as possible
if we have any chance of
finding her.
So we will contact you when we have any
information, Mr. Curtis.
Well done, son.
Ah, thank you, I guess.
But what happens now?
How do I know they're going to find her?
Oh, don't worry, kid.
I was in your shoes once.
My wife went missing,
and I came in here,
and they asked me to guess
how much she weighed.
- But I got out of there without ever saying
a number.
- Wait.
- And they still... they still found her?
- No, of course not.
But they brought me back somebody better.
Good luck, brother.
Try not to slip in that blood over there.
I ain't good at mopping.
Once again, Glorilla.
"Whatchu Kno About Me" and "Let Her Cook"
I'M FROM MEMPHIS
WHATCHU KNOW ABOUT ME
BIG G-L-O IN THAT G-L-E
50,000 new Chanel shop is breeding.
Every time I pop it out, you know I A-T-E.
I'm that girl.
Keep like me.
¶ YOU KNOW IT'S
Y-W-R BIG C-M-G
¶ SMALL HITTAS
TALL HITTAS
LONG PAPER
NO SMALL FIGURES ¶
¶ 50 WOMEN
ALL PRETTY
AND WE ALL LITTY ¶
¶ I'M WEARIN' BOOTY SHORTS
BOW
'CAUSE MY PAPER LONG
¶ IT'S A SATURDAY NIGHT
WHAT'S UP
AND I'M AT S-N-L
¶ I POUR MY PEOPLE SHOTS
'CAUSE I DON'T DRINK ALONE ¶
¶ I'M OUTSIDE AGAIN
LET'S GET IT
'CAUSE I HATE AT HOME ¶
It's giving hair, face, ass, titties
¶ LET HER COOK
LET ME COOK ¶
¶ NEVER GAVE A DAMN
I AIN'T NEVER GAVE NO WAT
FELL OUT WITH THEM WOES
WE AIN'T NEVER MAKIN UP ¶
¶ BACK FOR EVERYTHING
I EVER LOST
I'M ON A MISSION ¶
¶ WE TURNT THE WHOLE HOUSE
INTO A BOOTH
WE IN THE KITCHEN UGH ¶
¶ LET HER COOK
BIG GLO COME THROUGH
FRYING ISH
LET HER COOK ¶
¶ TOO MUCH CAKE
I'LL BUY IT
ON GOD
LET HER COOK ¶
¶ ALL THIS SAUCE
I'M TRYING ISH
LET ME COOK ¶
¶ BIG GLO COME THROUGH
SHUT IT DOWN
I'M BRINGING WOES OUT ¶
¶ RUN UP ON THIS ISH
YOU WANT
I'M SWINGING BOWS OUT ¶
¶ IF THEM GIRLS
AIN'T BAD AS GLO
THEN PUT THEM WOES OUT ¶
¶ GOT MY ANKLES
ON YOUR HITTA SHOULDER
AIR THEM TOES OUT
LET'S GET IT ¶
¶ BUTT DONE GOT
A LITTLE FATTER
NOW THESE GIRLS
A LIL MADDER OKAY ¶
¶ HEAD DONE GOT
A LITTLE BETTER
I DON'T EVEN
THINK THAT MATTER
¶ GIRL TALKING LIKE
SHE GANSTA
SHE DON'T REALLY
WANT NO ANA ¶
¶ YOU WOES COULDN'T
WALK A MILE
IN THESE GIVENCHY SANDALS
¶ I AIN'T GON' CRY
IN NO HONDA
I AIN'T GON' CRY
IN NO WRAITH EITHER ¶
¶ I GOT MY OWN CAKE
YOU AIN'T GONNA
MAKE WE WAIT EITHER ¶
¶ MY HITTA EVER CHEAT ON ME
I BET WE BREAK EVEN ¶
¶ GIRL YO HITTA
STILL MY HITTA
BET HE CAN'T LEAVE ME ¶
¶ NEVER GAVE A DAMN
I AIN'T NEVER GAVE NO WAT
FELL OUT WITH THEM WOES
WE AIN'T NEVER MAKIN UP ¶
¶ BACK FOR EVERYTHING
I EVER LOST
I'M ON A MISSION ¶
¶ WE TURNT THE WHOLE HOUSE
INTO A BOOTH
WE IN THE KITCHEN ¶
¶ LET HER COOK
BIG GLO COME THROUGH
FRYING ISH ¶
¶ LET HER COOK
TOO MUCH CAKE I'LL BUY IT
ON GOD
LET HER COOK ¶
¶ ALL THIS SAUCE
I'M TRYING ISH
LET ME COOK ¶¶
THANK YOU
>>> HEY, IT'S YOUR GIRL ARLETTE,
AND WELCOME TO ANOTHER EPISODE
OF "POP THE BALLOON OR FIND
LOVE."
IN FRONT OF ME ARE EIGHT
BEAUTIFUL SINGLE LADIES.
>> HEY!
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I'M GOING TO BRING ELIGIBLE
BACHELORS AROUND THE CORNER ONE
BY ONE.
IF HE'S YOUR TYPE, YOU LIKE WHAT
HE'S WORKING WITH,
DON'T POP THAT BALLOON.
IF HE'S JUST NOT IT, DON'T BE
SHY, POP THAT THING, OKAY?
LET'S BRING OUT OUR FIRST SINGLE
GUY.
>> HEY, THERE, LADIES.
MY NAME'S PHIL.
I'M 31.
I LOVE TO COOK.
>> WOW.
THAT WAS ALMOST EVERYONE.
WHY'D YOU POP IT, CHRISTIE?
>> HE SAID HE LIKES TO COOK, AND
I REALLY DON'T LIKE THE SMELL OF
FOOD.
SORRY.
>> MARIE, YOU STILL GOT YOUR
BALLOON.
>> YEAH, HE SEEMS LIKE HE'D LET
ME CHEAT ON HIM, AND I LIKE
THAT.
>> I WILL.
COME ON.
>> ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
SAY HELLO TO YOUR NEXT SINGLE,
DEVONE.
>> WHAT'S GOOD, Y'ALL?
MY NAME DEVONE.
I DON'T REALLY WORK LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I'D BE ON THE GAME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A BADDIE WHO
QUITE, THICK, AND LOYAL, 'CAUSE
I'M NOT.
>> WOW.
NO POPS.
THAT'S ACTUALLY WILD.
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER HERE,
MICHELLE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE GOT AURA.
HE'S CUTE.
>> COME ON, WHAT'S UP?
- OKAY.
>> HELLO, BEAUTIFULS.
MY NAME IS JMOAN
AS IN MAKE YOU
JMOAN.
I AM A BRAND AND ENTERTAINMENT
IMPRESARIO.
>> READY FOR THE NEXT MAN?
MEET SILKY.
>> THERE YOU ARE, YEAH.
SILKY, THEY SHOOTING.
>> SWEET DAY OF SALUTATIONS,
LADIES.
MY NAME IS SILKY JOHNSON.
LITTLE BIT ABOUT ME, I'M A
PURVEYOR OF PRECIOUS GOODS AND
SERVICES.
I.E., BITCHES.
>> I'M SORRY, ARE YOU SOME SORT
OF SEX TRAFFICKER?
>> I DON'T DO TRAFFIC, I TAKE
HELICOPTERS, BITCH.
>> HOLD ON.
>> AS FOR YOU -- THAT COAT RIGHT
THERE LOOKS LIKE YOU SKINNED A
GROUSE.
>> HORRIBLE BITCHES MAKE
HORRIBLE DECISIONS.
>> AND YOU, TANGERINE'S NOT YOUR COLOR,
AND THERE'S SOMETHING IN
YOUR BELLY BUTTON.
MADE YOU LOOK.
AS FOR THIS ONE HERE --
>> I HOPE YOU AIN'T TALKING
ABOUT ME, [ BLEEP ] YOU LOOKING
AT.
>> CHIPMUNK.
DO ME A FAVOR AND HAND THIS
WOMAN ANOTHER BALLOON.
>> SASSY MOUTH.
GOOD DAY, LADIES.
>> LET'S MEET OUR LAST GUY,
LARRY.
>> WHAT UP?
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO WRAP
THIS UP BEFORE I PASS AWAY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE ALL YOU
BITCHES POPPED THE BALLOON ON
I'm going back to the street.
>>> MY THANKS TO GLORILLA,
THE CAST AND CREW OF "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE," LORNE MICHAEL.
50 YEARS STRONG.
COMEDY IS FOR LIFE.
LET'S GO!
THANK
translate