>>> AND NOW, LIVE FROM MAR-A-LAGO,
IT'S THE "FOX NEWS
UKRAINIAN INVASION CELEBRATION
SPECTACULAR!"
WITH YOUR HOSTS, TUCKER CARLSON
AND LAURA INGRAHAM!
>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M TUCKER CARLSON.
I'M LIKE A PAIR OF BOAT SHOES
CAME TO LIFE.
>> AND I'M LAURA INGRAHAM.
AND WHEN I WATCH "HARRY POTTER"
I ROOT FOR VOLDEMORT.
>> WE GOT INTO A LITTLE BIT OF
TROUBLE FOR ALL THE NICE THINGS
WE SAID ABOUT RUSSIA
AND THE
MEAN THING WE SAID ABOUT
UKRAINE.
>> WE DID SOUND PRETTY AWFUL IN
HINDSIGHT.
AND FORESIGHT.
>> I KEPT ASKING WHY DO WE HATE
PUTIN?
AREN'T LIBERALS IN AMERICA EVEN
WORSE?
>> AND I CALLED THE PRESIDENT OF
UKRAINE PATHETIC.
HE STAYED AND FOUGHT WITH HIS PEOPLE IN THE WAR
AND I CALLED
HIM PATHETIC FROM A NEWS DESK IN
WASHINGTON.
>> I KEPT SAYING WE SHOULD BE
MORE WORRIED
ABOUT OUR OWN
BORDER GETTING INVADED BY
MEXICO.
BUT IN MY DEFENSE, I AM RACIST.
SO I THOUGHT THAT WAS TRUE.
>> BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GOING TO
MAKE IT UP.
WE'RE RAISING MONEY FOR THE REAL
VICTIMS OF THIS INVASION.
THE OLIGARCHS.
BECAUSE WE NEED TO THINK ABOUT
THE BABIES.
THEIR SUGAR BABIES.
WHO WILL POUR VODKA IN THEIR
MOUTHS?
SO MANY HORNY MOUTHS TO FEED.
>> SO PLEASE OPEN YOUR WALLETS
AND BECAUSE THIS IS FOX NEWS
YOU
CAN EITHER SEND MONEY OR TAKE
OUT A REVERSE MORTGAGE.
SO FAR WE'VE RAISED OVER 8.3
BILLION RUBLES,
WHICH COMES OUT
TO ALMOST $12.
>> AND THIS IS INCREDIBLY
EXCITING.
FORMER AND CURRENT PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES DONALD TRUMP
IS MANNING THE PHONE LINES
HIMSELF.
>> AND THE THING IS ABOUT
RIHANNA, SHE CAN PULL IT OFF.
SHE CAN BE NINE MONTHS.
THE BODY'S STILL INCREDIBLE.
BUT NOW YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A
LOT OF WOMEN
SEEING THIS
RIGHT NOW, 3s, 4s, FRANKLY
TROLLS,
WEARING THE SAME
SEE-THROUGH SHIRT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HESITATE TO SAY WHALES BECAUSE
I KNOW THE WHALES,
I'M VERY
POPULAR WITH THE WHALES.
I DO GREAT WITH WHALES.
THEY COME UP TO ME ON THE BEACH
AND THEY SAY THANK YOU, MR.
PRESIDENT.
YOU KNOW, THE BLOWHOLES BLASTING
AWAY.
200, 300 FEET IN THE AIR.
IT'S HOW THEY SALUTE ME.
>> OKAY.
WE'LL COME BACK TO YOU, MR.
PRESIDENT,
BECAUSE OUR FIRST
GUEST IS HERE.
HE'S A GREAT AMERICAN PATRIOT.
SO GREAT THAT HE LEFT AMERICA
AND BECAME A RUSSIAN CITIZEN.
THE PUFFIEST ACTION STAR IN THE
WORLD, STEVEN SEAGAL.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, TUCKER.
OH, WHAT A GLOBAL CRISIS WE ARE
FACING.
AS SOMEONE WHO PROUDLY PRETENDS
TO BE BOTH NATIVE AMERICAN AND JAPANESE,
I FEEL FOR ALL PEOPLE.
>> NOW, YOU'RE CLOSE WITH
PRESIDENT PUTIN, RIGHT?
>> YES.
PUTIN AND I ARE, AS THEY SAY IN ANCIENT JAPAN,
ESKIMO BROTHERS.
SO I WILL BE HONORING PUTIN
BY PERFORMING AN AUTHENTIC
TAEKWONDO EXHIBITION.
NOW IT'S TIME TO HONOR MYSELF
WITH A TRADITIONAL JAPANESE
SHAMROCK SHAKE.
THE TRADITIONAL SEASONAL
BEVERAGE OF ALL AIKIDO
EXHIBITIONS.
THANK
>> LET'S CHECK BACK IN WITH THE
MAN WHO SAID PUTIN'S INVASION
WAS VERY SMART
AND ALSO SAID
CHINA SHOULD INVADE TAIWAN NEXT.
MR. PRESIDENT?
>> MY FAVORITE FOOD IS PROBABLY
BREAD.
YOU KNOW?
AND MORE SPECIFICALLY BUN.
I LIKE BUN.
BUN IS GREAT.
ESPECIALLY WITH RESPECT TO
BURGER.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
BEYOND BURGER.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I WANT TO STAY RIGHT AT BURGER.
BEYOND IS NOT GOOD.
JOE BIDEN HAS GONE BEYOND BURGER
AND IT HAS NOT GONE SO WELL.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
NEITHER HAS REBOOT OF FRESH
PRINCE.
IT'S VERY DIFFERENT AND I'M
LAUGHING AND I'M LAUGHING BUT I
DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> OKAY.
I DO HEAR A DIAL TONE ON THE
OTHER END OF THAT PHONE.
SO LET'S HEAR WHAT KIND OF
PRIZES WE'RE GIVING AWAY
TONIGHT.
>> LAURA, WE'RE SENDING EVERY
RUSSIAN SOLDIER A FOX NEWS CARE
PACKAGE.
AND THAT INCLUDES A MY PILLOW,
A SIX-MONTH SUBSCRIPTION TO
LIFELOCK,
AND TEN AMERICAN FLAG
CATHETERS.
>> ALL COURTESY OF TONIGHT'S
SPONSOR, ACORN STAIRLIFTS.
YOU'RE GOING TO HEAVEN SOON.
PRACTICE GOING UP WITH ACORN
STAIRLIFTS.
>> NOW PLEASE WELCOME AMERICA'S
FIRST COUPLE, THE REAL PRINCE
HARRY AND MEGHAN MARKLE.
DON JR. AND KIMBERLY GUILFOYLE.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO BE
PERFORMING A DUET
IN HONOR OF
RUSSIA AND UKRAINE COMING
TOGETHER.
* TELL ME SOMETHING BOY *
* DON'T YOU LOVE THAT BIG
RUSSIAN CONVOY *
OR DO YOU NEED MORE
THIS INVASION GETS ME
SO DAMN HARD
IN THE SHALLOW SHALLOW
WE'RE FAR FROM *
* THE SHALLOW NOW
I'M ON THE DEEP END
WE SHOULD TAKE UKRAINE
WAY MORE WHITE THAN BLACK *
>> WOW, ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO CUT THAT ONE A
LITTLE SHORT.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> IS THERE A BATHROOM WITH A
MIRRORED COUNTER NEARBY?
>> YEAH, MAN, IT'S MAR-A-LAGO.
ALL RIGHT.
GUYS, I DO HAVE A QUICK
AANNOUNCEMENT.
IS ANYBODY DRIVING A YACHT
WITH A LICENSE PLATE NYET MEANS DA?
YOUR BOAT IS CURRENTLY BEING
TOWED BY NATO.
>> ALSO, PUTIN HAS JUST
CRIMINALIZED FREE SPEECH
AND
SHUT DOWN ALL INDEPENDENT NEWS
ORGANIZATIONS.
>> YEAH.
SO I'M THINKING CAN WE PLEASE DO
THAT TO CNN?
>> EVERY TIME I LAUGH AN ANGEL
DIES.
>> NOW LET'S TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK WE'LL BE
GIVING AWAY A FREE T-SHIRT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE FRONT SAYS "I STORMED THE
CAPITOL."
AND THE BACK SAYS "THIS DOES NOT
CONSTITUTE AN ADMISSION OF
GUILT."
>> AND PLUS WIN TICKETS TO SEE
MATT GAETZ DO A LIVE READING
OF
HIS FAVORITE RUSSIAN NOVEL,
LOLITA.
>> AND I'VE GOT SOMETHING I'D
LIKE TO SAY TO PUTIN AS WELL.
VLADIMIR, I WANT YOU TO HEAR
THIS FROM ME.
YOU ARE SMART.
YOU IS KIND.
YOU IS IMPORTANT.
AND HERE'S A LITTLE SONG FROM ME
TO YOU.
* MY FUNNY VALENTINE *
* SWEET COMIC VALENTINE *
* YOU MAKE ME SMILE WITH MY
HEART *
* YOUR LOOKS ARE LAUGHABLE *
* UNPHOTOGRAPHABLE *
* YET YOU'RE MY FAVORITE WORK OF
ART *
>> THANK YOU --
* IS YOUR FIGURE LESS THAN
GREEK *
* IS YOUR MOUTH A LITTLE WEAK *
* WHEN YOU OPEN TO SPEAK *
* ARE YOU SMART *
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S MORE THAN GENEROUS --
* DON'T CHANGE A HAIR FOR ME *
* NOT IF YOU CARE FOR ME *
* STAY LITTLE VALENTINE STAY *
* EACH DAY IS VALENTINE'S DAY **
I LOVE YOU, VLAD.
>> I KNOW.
HE LOVES YOU TOO.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL GUEST CHARLI XCX.
AND YOUR HOST, OSCAR ISAAC.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
OSCAR ISAAC!
>> THANK YOU.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME HOSTING
SNL.
THANK YOU.
THEY ACTUALLY ASKED ME TO HOST
BACK IN 2015
BUT I SAID "NO, I'M
NOT READY.
I WANT TO WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE
PANDEMIC."
AND THEY WERE LIKE, "WHAT
PANDEMIC?"
MY NAME IS OSCAR ISAAC,
BUT MY FULL NAME IS
OSCAR ISAAC HERNANDEZ ESTRADA.
I SAID TO HOLLYWOOD -- I SAID TO
THEM, "YOU CAN PICK TWO OF THESE
NAMES."
GUESS WHAT THEY WENT WITH.
THE WHITE ONES.
I'M HALF GUATEMALAN, HALF CUBAN.
OR AS CASTING DIRECTORS CALL
THAT, "ETHNICALLY AMBIGUOUS."
ACCORDING TO THEM, I CAN PLAY ANYTHING
FROM A PHARAOH TO
TIMOTHEE CHALAMET'S DADDY.
YOU KNOW THAT JOKE, A PRIEST, A
RABBI, AND A MINISTER WALK INTO
A BAR?
YEAH, I COULD PLAY ANYONE IN
THAT JOKE.
BUT I AM EXCITED.
I'M JOINING THE MARVEL UNIVERSE
WITH "MOON KNIGHT."
YOU KNOW, IT'S KIND OF A FULL
CIRCLE MOMENT
SINCE THE FIRST
MOVIE I WAS EVER IN WAS CALLED
THE AVENGER.
NOT "THE AVENGERS," WHICH WAS A
MASSIVE BLOCKBUSTER.
NO, THIS WAS "THE AVENGER,"
WHICH IS A MOVIE THAT I WROTE,
DIRECTED, AND STARRED IN WHEN I
WAS 10 YEARS OLD.
IT WAS SHOT ON LOCATION IN MY
BUDDY BRUCE FERGUSON'S BACK YARD
IN OUR HOMETOWN OF MIAMI,
FLORIDA.
I PLAY A NINJA ASSASSIN TRAINING
TO FIGHT HIS NEMESIS.
AND WE ACTUALLY HAVE A CLIP.
THIS IS REAL, CHECK THIS OUT.
>>  OKAY, THERE'S THE OPENING
TITLE.
AND THERE I AM.
KIND OF LOSING MY BALANCE A
LITTLE BIT.
PERFECT EDITING.
AND HERE COMES MY BIG STUNT.
I TRAINED TWO MONTHS FOR THIS.
I MEAN, ARGUABLY BETTER THAN THE
REAL "AVENGERS."
AND I MADE IT FOR HALF THE
BUDGET, ONLY $110 MILLION.
BUT I TOOK IT REALLY SERIOUSLY.
MAYBE A LITTLE TOO SERIOUSLY.
LIKE IN THIS SCENE.
OKAY, THERE I AM ACTING MY HEART
OUT.
AND THERE'S MY FRIEND'S DAD
CLEANING THE POOL.
SHOUT-OUT TO MR. FERGUSON,
AND SHOUT-OUT TO MY BUDDY, BRUCE.
HE'S AT HOME WATCHING AND HE HAD
NO IDEA OUR OLD MOVIE WAS GOING
TO BE ON "SNL."
I ACTUALLY HAD TO SIGN A
LICENSING AGREEMENT TO SHOW IT.
THAT'S TRUE.
NBC UNIVERSAL NOW OWNS "THE
AVENGER."
COMING THIS FALL TO PEACOCK!
I'VE GOT ONE MORE CLIP.
THIS IS A SCENE I DID WITH
MYSELF WHERE I PLAY BOTH PARTS.
OKAY?
HERE WE GO.
THAT'S ME.
*I DIDN'T MEAN*
I'M MY OWN HENCHMAN.
* DO THIS*
NOW WATCH WHAT I DO WITH THE
SWORD.
TOTAL COMMITMENT FROM THE START.
NOW, YOU MIGHT BE ASKING, OSCAR,
WHY DID YOU USE YOUR MONOLOGUE
TO SHOW US THESE OLD HOME
VIDEOS?
AND THE REASON IS IT'S IMPORTANT
TO ENCOURAGE KIDS TO BE WEIRDOS.
BECAUSE EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
ONE OF THOSE WEIRDOS GROWS UP TO
HOST "SNL."
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
CHARLI XCX IS HERE.
SO STICK AROUND.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEREBY PRESENT THE PAW PATROL
WITH THIS MEDAL OF BRAVERY FOR
STOPPING THAT OUT-OF-CONTROL HOT
AIR BALLOON.
WITH YOU PUPS ON PATROL, OUR
CITY IS IN GOOD HANDS.
>> DON'T YOU MEAN GOOD PAWS?
>> HA HA HA!
>> ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
I'M CITY COUNCILMAN
HERB TANGIER.
MAYOR GOODWAY HAS PUT ALL OUR
LIVES AT RISK WITH HER PAW
PATROL INITIATIVE AND I SAY IT'S
TIME TO VOTE HER OUT.
FACT!
THIS MAN FIRED ALL OF OUR CITY'S
POLICE OFFICERS, FIREFIGHTERS,
AND PARAMEDICS, AND REPLACED
THEM WITH A GROUP OF SIX TALKING
DOGS.
I THINK THAT WAS A BAD IDEA.
AND I'M NOT ALONE.
LISTEN TO THESE CONCERNED
CITIZENS.
>> I WAS EXCITED ABOUT THE PAW
PATROL AT FIRST.
TALKING DOGS WHO KNOW HOW TO FLY
JETS AND DRIVE?
GREAT.
BUT IT'S BECOME CLEAR THAT SIX
DOGS CANNOT PROTECT A CITY
ROUGHLY THE SIZE OF SAN DIEGO.
>> CRIMINALS AND LOW-LIFES ARE
FLOCKING HERE BECAUSE THEY KNOW
THERE'S ONLY ONE COP PATROLLING
OUR STREETS AND IT'S A DOG!
>> AND THERE'S ONLY ONE
FIREFIGHTER, ALSO A DOG.
SO IF THERE'S TWO FIRES AT THE
SAME TIME?
SOMEONE'S GETTING SCREWED, I
GUESS?
WHO IS IN CHARGE OF THIS
ORGANIZATION?
A CHILD?
>> YES!
THE PAW PATROL IS RUN BY A
10-YEAR-OLD BOY NAMED RYDER.
WHO IS THIS KID?
BEATS ME!
AS FAR AS WE CAN TELL, HE HAS NO
PARENTS AND DOESN'T GO TO
SCHOOL.
BUT MAYBE THAT'S FOR THE BEST,
BECAUSE WITH ALL OUR TAX DOLLARS
PAYING FOR A LITTLE COCKAPOO'S
JET PACK, WE NOW HAVE THE WORST
SCHOOLS IN THE STATE.
THIS IS MY 17-YEAR-OLD SON.
HE CAN BARELY READ.
>> I CAN READ, I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT SOUND VOWELS MAKE WHEN
THEY'RE NEXT TO OTHER LETTERS IN
A LINE.
>> MAYOR GOODWAY, THIS IS ALL
YOUR FAULT AND YOU NEED TO GO!
>> FACT.
OUR CITY'S COVID RESPONSE WAS A
NATIONAL DISGRACE.
WHY?
BECAUSE SIX DOGS WERE IN CHARGE
OF IT.
>> FACT.
CHASE THE POLICE DOG'S ONLY
WEAPON IS A NET.
QUESTION, HOW IS A NET GOING TO
HELP IF A LUNATIC ON BATH SALTS
IS EATING MY FACE?
ANSWER?
IT WON'T.
>> FACT, MARSHALL THE FIRE DOG
IS MY FAVORITE ONE.
HE'S THE FUNNIEST PUP BY FAR AND
THE COOLEST BY A MILE.
BUT I DON'T THINK HE COULD CARRY
ME DOWN A FLIGHT OF STAIRS
BECAUSE HE AIN'T GOT NO HANDS.
>> FACT, I ALSO LIKE MARSHALL
THE BEST.
HE'S SUPER BRAVE AND HIS JOKES
NEVER MISS.
BUT DO WE FEEL SAFE?
NO!
LISTEN TO THIS ACTUAL 911 CALL.
>> PAW PATROL ARE READY TO ROLL,
THIS IS RYDER, WHAT'S YOUR
EMERGENCY?
>> MY GIRLFRIEND, MAN.
SHE'S NOT WAKING UP!
HER EYES ARE, LIKE, ROLLED BACK.
I THINK SHE'S OD'ing, MAN.
>> UM -- PLEASE HOLD.
* PAW PATROL *
>> UNACCEPTABLE!
AND THAT'S NOT THE ONLY
EMERGENCY THAT PAW PATROL'S
BUNGLED.
JUST ASK MY SISTER.
>> I WENT INTO LABOR EARLY.
I WAS ALONE AND CALLED 911 FOR
HELP AND TOLD THEM MY WATER
BROKE.
SO THEY SENT ZUMA, THE WATER
RESCUE DOG.
HE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND WHAT WAS
HAPPENING AND SAT THERE CHEWING
ON HIS UPPER BUTT WHILE I GAVE
BIRTH ON MY KITCHEN FLOOR.
>> DISGRACEFUL!
BUT IT GETS WORSE.
>> RECENTLY MY WIFE WAS IN A
TERRIBLE ACCIDENT.
AND WHO CAME TO BREAK THIS
EARTH-SHAKING NEWS TO ME AND MY
CHILDREN?
A BULLDOG IN A HARD HAT.
AND MIDWAY THROUGH TELLING US,
HE STARTED DOING THAT SCOOTING
THING DOGS DO WHERE THEY PUT
THEIR HIND LEGS UNDER THEM AND
DRAG THEIR ITCHY ASS ACROSS THE
FLOOR.
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH!
>> MAYOR GOODWAY, THE NUMBERS
DON'T LIE.
ZERO SEX CRIME UNITS IN OUR
POLICE FORCE BECAUSE THE PAW
PATROL AND THEIR 10-YEAR-OLD
BOSS DON'T KNOW WHAT SEX IS.
AND ONE.
ONE CHANCE TO TAKE OUR CITY BACK
BY VOTING "YES" TO RECALL
MAYOR GOODWAY IN NEXT WEEK'S
SPECIAL ELECTION.
LET'S MAKE OUR VOICES HEARD AND
GET MY WIFE OUT OF OFFICE.
>> PAID FOR BY CATS.
>>> I'M A BOSS.
>> ANNA DELVEY GETS WHATEVER SHE
WANTS.
>> YOUR MONEY IS COMING.
WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST LISTEN?
>> HEY, ANDREW.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT SANDWICH?
>> OH, THEY'RE JUST OUT IN THE
WRITER'S ROOM.
>> OH, GREAT, I'M STARVING.
>> OH, THIS WAS ACTUALLY THE
LAST ONE.
>> OH.
OKAY.
>> I'M A BOSS!
>> ANDREW, WAIT.
THAT'S ACTUALLY MY SANDWICH.
>> WHAT IS THAT VOICE?
>> MY SANDWICH IS IN YOUR MOUTH.
GIVE ME MY SANDWICH.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
SORRY.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
INVENTING CHLOE
* I'M A BOSS-ASS BITCH *
>> THIS FOOD IS LIKE BASIC, YOU
KNOW.
CHIPS ARE BROKE-ASS.
WE NEED SOMETHING MORE
EXCLUSIVE.
MORE VIP.
LIKE NOBU.
RUN THIS ON MY CARD.
>> THIS IS A METRO CARD.
>> RUN IT AGAIN!
HEY, LITTLE BOY.
LORNE SAYS THAT'S MY COUCH NOW.
>> LORNE SAID THAT?
'CAUSE I BROUGHT THIS FROM MY
HOME.
>> I ASSURE YOU HIS TEXT IS ON
THE WAY.
HE'S IN THE HAMPTONS RIGHT NOW.
RECEPTION IS VERY BAD.
VERY VIP.
>> THAT DOES SOUND LIKE LORNE.
>> MY FELLOW AMERICANS.
>> LORNE SAYS I'LL DO BIDEN
NOW.
>> HE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING TO ME.
>> TEXT IS ON THE WAY.
GIVE ME YOUR TEETH.
LORNE SAYS I'LL HOST UPDATE NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> I STILL DIDN'T GET A CARD.
>> YOU'RE BEING SO DRAMATIC.
THE WIRE TRANSFER'S ON THE WAY.
>> OH, COOL.
OYSTERS.
>> WHAT'RE YOU WEARING?
YOU LOOK PARKED.
>> I LOOK WHAT, NOW?
>> PAAAH.
PAAAH
PAAAH2
PURRR
PURRR2
>> POOR?
>> POOR. YES.
LOOK
I LOVED YOU IN "DUNE," BY THE
WAY.
>> THANKS.
>> SAY HI TO TIMOTHEE CHALAMET.
FROM NOW ON, MY COSTUME --
>> HEY, CHLOE.
ANY UPDATE ON THAT WIRE
TRANSFER?
I'M IN REALLY DEEP.
>> I DO NOT HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
I DO NOT HAVE TIME FOR YOU!
I'M A MASTERPIECE, BITCHES!
>> I CAN PAY.
I'M SORRY.
>> CHLOE.
COME ON.
THERE YOU GO.
>> I CAN PAY.
>> CHLOE.
I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE, YOU'VE
BEEN DELVEYING EVERYONE TODAY.
>> I CAN PAY.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
THE HAIR, THE GLASSES, THE
RUSSIAN ACCENT THAT'S ALSO
GERMAN.
YOU'VE JUST GOT TO BE CONFIDENT.
YOU KNOW?
THE REAL DELVEY IS INSIDE YOU.
AND HAS BEEN ALL ALONG.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'M JUST GLAD I STOPPED THIS
BEFORE ANYONE GOT HURT
AND THERE
WERE ANY REAL CONSEQUENCES.
>> WELL, I GUESS I WON'T BE
NEEDING THESE ANYMORE.
BYE, KATE.
>> BYE.
>> THERE CAN ONLY BE ONE DELVEY
AROUND HERE.
VERY VIP.
>>> ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
SETTLED?
>> EVERYONE SETTLED IN OKAY?
>> LET'S SETTLE IN, EVERYONE.
>> PLEASE SETTLE.
PLEASE SETTLE.
>> WE'RE SETTLED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T KNOW
US, MY NAME IS DONALD.
>> AND MY NAME IS MARIA.
AND WE ARE YOUR HR
REPRESENTATIVES HERE AT LINKS
PHARMACEUTICAL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE THE ONES YOU COME TO WITH
ANONYMOUS COMPLAINTS, LIKE WHEN
DEBORAH TOLD US WHAT KEVIN WAS
DOING.
>> YOU RATTED ON ME, DEBORAH?
>> I -- I DID NOT.
NO.
WHY WOULD I EVEN CARE THAT YOU
WAIT OUTSIDE THE WOMEN'S ROOM
AND SAY "HOW'D IT GO IN THERE?"
>> JUST A SIMPLE GOOD OR BAD
WOULD SUFFICE.
>> GUYS, WE'RE NOT HERE TO
LECTURE KEVIN AGAIN.
>> GOD KNOWS WE SPENT ENOUGH
TIME ON KEVIN THANKS TO
COMPLAINTS FROM DEBORAH AND
LYLE.
GUYS, TODAY IS OUR ANNUAL
HARASSMENT SEMINAR.
AND I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
WE HAVE TO SIT THROUGH THIS
AGAIN?
AWW, I'M GOING TO BLOW MY
FRIGGING BRAINS OUT!
>> THIS WHOLE SCHPEEL AGAIN?
I'M GOING TO BLOW MY GODDAMN
BRAINS OUT.
>> PLEASE STOP SAYING THAT.
>> WE PROMISE WE ARE GOING TO
GET THIS OVER WITH AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE SO YOU CAN GET BACK TO
WORK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, AND KEVIN CAN
GET BACK TO PEEKING UNDER
BATHROOM STALLS.
>> YOU TOLD THEM ABOUT THAT?
>> YOUR FACE WAS FULLY UNDER MY
STALL.
>> OKAY.
THIS IS REAL SIMPLE, GUYS.
OKAY?
WE'RE JUST GOING TO RUN THROUGH
A COUPLE OF SCENARIOS, AND YOU
GUYS TELL US WHETHER THEY'RE
APPROPRIATE OR INAPPROPRIATE,
OKAY?
>> HERE'S THE FIRST ONE.
>> WHAT IF MARIA SAYS TO DONALD,
"WOW, LOOKS LIKE THOSE WORKOUTS
YOU'VE BEEN DOING ARE REALLY
PAYING OFF?"
>> I WOULD SAY THAT'S
INAPPROPRIATE.
>> WRONG.
>> HM.
LET'S TRY ANOTHER ONE.
OKAY, SO WHAT IF DONALD SAID TO
MARIA, "WOW, HOW OFTEN ARE YOU
GOING TO THE GYM?
YOUR BODY IS SERIOUSLY
FANTASTIC."
>> THAT'S VERY INAPPROPRIATE.
>> SORRY, NO.
>> TRY TO REALLY FOCUS THIS
TIME.
MARIA COMES UP BEHIND DONALD AND
SAYS, "DAMN, DO YOU LIVE AT THE
GYM OR SOMETHING?
BECAUSE THAT JUICY BOOTY SLAPS."
>> WILDLY INAPPROPRIATE.
>> ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT.
BECAUSE I'M HER BOSS.
>> SEE?
TRY TO REALLY LISTEN, GUYS.
>> OKAY, WHAT IF MARIA'S BOSS
SAID TO MARIA, "HEY, WHEN ARE
YOU GOING TO GET TO START
BANGING OUT KIDS?
THAT IS CLOCK IS TICKING, BABY."
>> AGAIN, VERY INAPPROPRIATE.
>> BUT WHAT IF MY BOSS IS MY
GRANDFATHER AND HE JUST REALLY
WANTS GRANDKIDS?
>> OKAY, BUT HE SHOULDN'T SAY IT
AT WORK IN FRONT OF OTHER
PEOPLE.
>> AND WAIT, I THOUGHT DONALD
WAS YOUR BOSS.
>> "I THOUGHT DONALD WAS" -- YOU
KNOW WHAT?
THIS ISN'T A GAME, DEBORAH.
NEXT SLIDE.
>> DONALD SAYS TO MARIA, "HEY,
N-WORD, ARE YOU GOING TO THE GYM
LATER?
OR AM I GOING TO HAVE TO DRAG
YOUR THICK ASS THERE MYSELF?"
>> THAT'S REALLY AWFUL AND
INAPPROPRIATE.
>> ACTUALLY, IT'S FINE.
>> ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT.
>> NO, HE DIDN'T MEAN THAT "N"
WORD.
HE MEANT NICE.
>> HE WAS SAYING, HEY NICE?
>> YEAH.
BECAUSE HE'S ITALIAN.
HE SAID, "HEYA NICE."
ALL THE TIME.
>> THAT'S ALSO INAPPROPRIATE.
>> NOT IF SHE IS MY BOSS.
>> ALSO, WHY ARE ALL OF THESE
EXAMPLES ABOUT THE TWO OF YOU?
>> WOW.
>> THE TWO OF US?
THAT'S HOW YOU SEE IT?
>> WOW, SO YOU SEE A MAN AND A
WOMAN WORKING TOGETHER, SO
AUTOMATICALLY YOU THINK THEY'RE
HAVING RAW INTERCOURSE?
>> NO ONE SAID THAT.
>> YOU SEE A WOMAN IN A HOT
SKIRT SUIT, NOTHING UNDERNEATH,
AND JUST BECAUSE YOUR EYES ARE
GOING OWOOGA THINKING SHE'LL
TAKE A BITE OUT OF HER BOSS'S
SANDWICH, THAT MEANS
AUTOMATICALLY THEY'RE GOING TO
HAVE RAW INTERCOURSE.
>> STOP SAYING RAW INTERCOURSE!
>> NO, SHUT UP, DEBORAH, SHUT
UP.
KEVIN WAS RIGHT ABOUT WHAT HE
SAID DURING THE INVESTIGATION,
YOU ARE AN UPTIGHT BITCH.
>> OH MY GOD, THIS IS HORRIBLE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> YOU HEAR THAT?
THAT'S CLAPPING.
>> WE'RE CLAPPING FOR YOU!
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT YOUR HR
REPRESENTATIVES.
>> NO.
WE'RE FROM A GROUP CALLED "IT
COULD BE WORSE."
AND WE SHOW EMPLOYEES THAT NO
MATTER HOW BAD YOUR WORKPLACE
ENVIRONMENT MIGHT BE, IT COULD
BE WORSE.
>> COULD BE WAY WORSE.
OKAY?
>> WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH THIS INFORMATION?
>> I WANT YOU ALL TO WALK BACK
INTO YOUR OFFICES, TAKE A DEEP
BREATH, JUST START TYPING.
TYPE, TYPE, TYPE, TYPE, TYPE,
TYPE, TYPE --
>> HE HAS NO IDEA WHAT WE DO.
>> TYPE, TYPE, TYPE, TYPE, TYPE
AND RIGHT WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED
TYPING YOUR TYPES AND YOU GO
HOME FOR THE DAY, THE WOMEN TO
THEIR HUNKY HUSBANDS AND THE MEN
TO THEIR SHRILL, NAGGING
WIVES, AND I WANT YOU TO THINK
ABOUT US.
AND HOW WE SHOWED YOU A NEW WAY
TO WORK.
**
A NEW WAY TO LIVE.
MAYBE EVEN A NEW WAY TO LOVE.
>> YOU'LL WONDER, WHATEVER
HAPPENED TO THOSE TWO?
DID THEY END UP GOING TO THE
MEN'S ROOM AND HAVING RAW
INTERCOURSE?
>> AND THE ANSWER IS --
YES.
YES, THEY DID.
>> AND UNRELATED, WHICH STALL
ARE YOU ALL GOING TO BE USING?
>> KEVIN.
>> "KEVIN," FRIDAYS AT 6:00 A.M.
ONLY ON THE WEATHER CHANNEL.
GRAD SCHOOL?
AMAZING.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A GREAT TIME
TONIGHT.
>> ME TOO.
WE'VE HAD THREE INCREDIBLE
DATES.
>> YEAH.
DEFINITELY.
HEY, UM, CAN I ASK SOMETHING?
>> ANYTHING.
>> WHY DO YOU ALWAYS WEAR THAT
GREEN RIBBON AROUND YOUR NECK?
>> UM, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I'VE JUST NEVER SEEN YOU
WITHOUT IT.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE IT OFF?
>> I HOPED YOU WOULDN'T NOTICE.
LOOK, ALAN, I'LL SHOW YOU.
BUT PLEASE DON'T LET IT AFFECT
THE WAY YOU SEE ME.
>> OF COURSE NOT, COME ON.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
**
THERE.
NOW YOU KNOW.
THERE'S A LITTLE MEATBALL GUY ON
THE SIDE OF MY NECK.
EVERY I TAKE THE GREEN RIBBON
OFF AND EXPOSE HIM TO LIGHT, HE
WAKES UP AND SINGS HIS LITTLE
SONGS.
DOES THAT CLEAR THINGS UP FOR
YOU?
>> TOTALLY, 100%.
>> GOOD.
NOW WHERE WERE WE?
>> JUST ONE QUESTION.
IS THAT A LITTLE TINY HAND
STICKING OUT OF THE TOP OF YOUR
SHIRT?
>> I WAS HOPING YOU WOULDN'T
NOTICE.
**
AND TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
YEAH, THEY HARMONIZE AND SING
TOGETHER IN TIME.
THEN THERE'S THESE GUYS.
AND THIS ONE KIND OF MUNCHES ON
A BLOCK OF CHEESE TO THE BEAT.
AND THIS ONE JUST KIND OF SPITS
UP.
THEN BIG DADDY BRINGS IT ALL
TOGETHER.
**
* SINGING OUR LITTLE MEATBALL
SONG *
* WE ARE LITTLE MEATBALL MEN *
* JOIN US PLEASE AND SING
ALONG *
>> OKAY, I THINK I GET IT.
YOU CAN GO AHEAD AND COVER THEM
UP NOW.
>> OH, NO, NO, ONCE THEY GET ON
A ROLL LIKE THIS IT'S BETTER TO
KEEP THEM GOING UNTIL THEY GET
TUCKERED OUT.
**
* WE ARE BALLS OF BODY MEAT *
* WE ARE LITTLE MEATBALL MEN *
* SUCKING ON OUR PIECE OF
CHEESE *
* MY NAME IS CHUNKY *
* AND MY NAME'S POPOLIM *
* MY NAME IS JOBI *
* AND MY NAME IS JIM *
**
>> HAVE YOU EVER TALKED TO A
DOCTOR ABOUT GETTING THEM
REMOVED?
>> OH, IT'S NOT NECESSARY.
AFTER A FEW YEARS THEY JUST,
LIKE, DRY AND UP FALL OFF INTO A
TOILET.
>> HEY BUDDY I'M HUNGRY.
GIVE ME SOME MORE CHEESE.
>> OH, GROSS.
>> OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT,
IT'S NOT POISONOUS OR ANYTHING.
IT'LL JUST STAIN YOUR CLOTHES.
AND IT IS POISONOUS.
>> OKAY, LOOK.
I THINK WE'RE MOVING TOO FAST.
>> OH, NO, HERE IT COMES!
>> OH, THIS IS SO AWKWARD, I
CAN'T BEAR TO WATCH.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU'RE DUMPING ME?
THIS IS COMING OUT OF NOWHERE!
I MEAN, I SUPPOSE IF I HAD TO
GUESS I'D SAY IT HAD MAYBE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE
MEATBALLS?
>> NO.
NO.
YEAH, IT'S THE MEATBALLS.
>> WOW.
WOW.
>> HEY.
**
I'M SORRY.
IS THAT A PIANO IN YOUR ARMPIT?
>> UH-HUH.
* DON'T GIVE UP ON LOVE *
* JUST BECAUSE OF SOME
MEATBALLS *
* DON'T GIVE UP ON THIS GIRL
BECAUSE SHE'S GOT
A LOT OF MEATBALLS *
* SOMEDAY YOU'LL REALIZE
THAT IN THE END *
* YOUR LOVE WILL ALWAYS WIN *
* AND I'M JIM *
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE MEATBALLS ARE RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT WORK.
>> REALLY?
>> WE FINALLY GOT A BOYFRIEND,
YAY!
>> YAY!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> OH, YEAH, I FORGOT TO
MENTION, THEY'RE EXTREMELY
CONTAGIOUS.
>> NOOOO!
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
CHARLI XCX!
Beg for You
* YOU KNOW I GO INSANE
EVERY TIME YOU HAVE TO
CATCH A FLIGHT
* CAN I TAKE YOU
TO THE AIRPORT
MAKE OUT UNDER
THE BATHROOM LIGHTS *
PUT YOUR LIPS ON MY LIPS
I'LL REMEMBER YOUR KISS *
* ON THE NIGHTS
WHEN I MISS YOU
* SOMETHING I CAN'T FORGET
WHEN I'M RESTLESS IN BED
YEAH YOU GOT ME OBSESSED
MMM *
* OH DON'T YOU
LEAVE ME THIS WAY
WON'T YOU WAIT
ANOTHER HOUR OR TWO *
* YOU KNOW I NEED
YOU TO STAY
DON'T MAKE ME BEG FOR YOU
'CAUSE I'LL BEG FOR YOU *
**
* YEAH YEAH YEAH
UH YEAH *
* BEG FOR YOU BEG FOR YOU
BEG FOR YOU BEG FOR YOU
BEG FOR YOU BEG FOR YOU *
* OH DON'T YOU
LEAVE ME THIS WAY
YOU'RE LIKE AN
OCEAN BREEZE *
* COMING AND GOING
JUST AS YOU PLEASE
AH AH-AH-AH *
* SEPARATED BY A DEGREE
HESITATE AND I LOSE YOU
SO FAR OUT OF REACH *
* AH AH-AH-AH
OH PUT YOUR LIPS ON MY LIPS
I'LL REMEMBER YOUR KISS *
* ON THE NIGHTS WHEN I
MISS YOUR MOUTH
SOMETHING I CAN'T FORGET
WHEN I'M RESTLESS IN BED *
* YEAH YOU GOT ME
OBSESSED NOW
OH DON'T YOU
LEAVE ME THIS WAY *
* WON'T YOU WAIT
ANOTHER HOUR OR TWO
YOU KNOW I NEED YOU TO STAY
DON'T MAKE ME BEG FOR YOU *
* 'CAUSE I'LL BEG FOR YOU
MY HEART IS ACHING
MY BREATH YOU TAKE IT *
* OH BABE
I JUST WANT A TASTE
DON'T YOU LEAVE
ME THIS WAY *
* DON'T MAKE ME BEG FOR YOU
DON'T LEAVE ME
DON'T LEAVE ME *
* THIS WAY
THIS WAY
THIS WAY *
* DON'T LEAVE ME
DON'T LEAVE ME
THIS WAY THIS WAY
THIS WAY *
* DON'T LEAVE ME
DON'T LEAVE ME
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME *
* DON'T YOU LEAVE ME
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME *
* DON'T YOU LEAVE ME
DON'T YOU LEAVE ME
YEAH
YEAH YEAH *
**
>> GOOD EVENING.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, WE'RE NOW AT THE POINT
WHERE AT EVERY PRESS CONFERENCE
THE PRESIDENT'S ASKED, WILL
THERE BE A NUCLEAR WAR?
A JOURNALIST ASKED PRESIDENT
BIDEN IF WE SHOULD BE WORRIED
ABOUT NUCLEAR WAR AND HE SAID,
NO.
BECAUSE WHAT'S HE GOING TO SAY?
HELL YEAH, MAN.
START DIGGING A BUNKER, JACK.
IT'S LIKE WHEN A LITTLE KID ASKS
YOU WHERE GRAMPIE'S GOING TO GO
WHEN HE DIES.
OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE GOING TO SAY
HEAVEN.
BUT BASED ON SOME OF THE STUFF
GRAMPIE SAID YOU KNOW HELL IS
ALSO ON THE TABLE.
SOME MILITARY EXPERTS HAVE BEEN
SURPRISED THAT DESPITE HAVING
SUPERIOR FIREPOWER THE RUSSIAN
ARMY HAS BEEN SLOWED BY AGING
EQUIPMENT, POOR MOTIVATION AND
INEPT LEADERSHIP.
SO BASICALLY, THEY'RE THE
LAKERS.
>>> GERMANY IS NOW JOINING THE
EU TO SEND ARMS TO UKRAINE,
WHICH IS THE FIRST TIME GERMANY
HAS RAMPED UP MILITARY
PRODUCTION SINCE THAT LITTLE
SIX-YEAR GAP IN THEIR HISTORY
BOOKS.
>>> FRENCH PRESIDENT EMMANUEL
MACRON SAID THAT AFTER A TENSE
90-MINUTE CALL WITH VLADIMIR
PUTIN, HE'S CONVINCED THAT THE
WORST IS YET TO COME.
MAN, IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH
SUFFERING COULD HAVE BEEN
AVOIDED IF PUTIN WAS JUST A FEW
INCHES TALLER.
>>> SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM, WHO
GIVES THIS EXACT SAME LOOK AT
THE URINAL --
CREATED CONTROVERSY ON TWITTER
BY SUGGESTING THAT RUSSIANS
SHOULD END THE WAR IN UKRAINE BY
ASSASSINATING VLADIMIR PUTIN.
IT IS A SHOCKING, DISGUSTING
EXAMPLE OF LINDSEY GRAHAM BEING
KIND OF RIGHT ABOUT SOMETHING.
>>> GOVERNORS IN SEVERAL STATES
INCLUDING NEW HAMPSHIRE, OHIO
AND UTAH HAVE BANNED THE SALE OF
RUSSIAN-MADE VODKA.
NO WORD YET ON BRIDES.
>>> MANY OF THE MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS ATTENDING THE STATE OF
THE UNION WORE BLUE AND YELLOW
TO SHOW THEIR SUPPORT FOR
UKRAINE.
WHILE KAMALA HARRIS WORE ALL
BROWN TO DO WHAT SHE'S DONE FOR
THE LAST YEAR, DISAPPEAR INTO
THE BACKGROUND.
>>> FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON
DeSANTIS, SEEN HERE BEING TOLD
SOMEONE'S PRONOUNS --
DeSANTIS YELLED AT STUDENTS
BEHIND HIM AT AN INDOOR EVENT TO
TAKE OFF THEIR MASKS SAYING
STOP WITH THIS COVID THEATER.
AND THERE'S NOTHING MORE ON
BRAND FOR CONSERVATIVES THAN A
DAD SCREAMING AT BOYS TO GIVE UP
THEATER.
>>> STARTING ON MONDAY NEW YORK
CITY WILL NO LONGER REQUIRE BARS
AND RESTAURANTS TO PRETEND TO
LOOK AT VACCINATION CARDS.
THE CITY WILL BE LIFTING ITS
VACCINE MANDATE FOR INDOOR
DINING AND EVENTS.
FINALLY, SAID THE NEXT
VARIANT.
THIS WEEK
CONTROVERSIAL "DON'T SAY GAY" BILL
PASSED ITS FINAL STATE
SENATE COMMITTEE.
HERE TO COMMENT IS KATE
McKINNON.
>> HI,'LL COULDIN.
HELLO.
>> HI, KATE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> YEAH.
SORRY TO BARGE IN HERE OUT OF
COSTUME.
I HEARD ABOUT THIS LAW.
AND I THINK IT'S AMAZING.
>> OH, YOU DO?
>> YEAH.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS IN
MIDDLE SCHOOL IN THE '90s
I WAS
SOME -- I WAS KIND OF LIKE
TORTURED BY THE CONSTANT USE OF
THE WORD "GAY."
"THAT'S SO GAY.
EW, YOU'RE GAY."
IT MADE ME FEEL HORRIBLE.
AND TO HEAR THAT RON DeSANTIS
HAS TAKEN A STAND
AND SAID NO,
YOU CANNOT SAY GAY IN SCHOOL
ANYMORE.
I'M JUST LIKE -- I'M SO JAZZED.
AND IN FLORIDA OF ALL PLACES.
SO ACTUALLY, I FEEL LIKE THERE'S
BEEN A MISUNDERSTANDING.
THE LAW ACTUALLY MEANS THAT YOU
CAN'T ACKNOWLEDGE THAT GAY
EXISTS AT ALL.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH.
LIKE TEACHERS CAN'T SPEAK ABOUT
GAY PEOPLE IN HISTORY.
OR IF A KID HAS A GAY FAMILY
MEMBER.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH, AND IF A KID CONFIDES
THAT THEY'RE GAY TO A TEACHER,
THE TEACHER HAS TO OUT THEM TO
THEIR PARENTS.
>> OH, WHAT?
>> YEAH, SORRY TO BREAK THIS TO
YOU.
IT PROBABLY IS AFFECTING WHAT
YOU WERE GOING TO SAY.
>> YEAH.
OKAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL SAY SOMETHING.
IT'S JUST THAT THING OF LIKE
WHEN THEY SAY DON'T SAY GAY, YOU
KNOW, THEN IT'S LIKE STUCK IN
YOUR HEAD.
BUT IT'S FINE.
>> OKAY.
>> ANYWAY, I AM DEEPLY GAY OF --
SORRY.
CONCERNED.
DEEPLY CONCERNED.
IT JUST FEELS LIKE THIS IS GOING
TO MAKE KIDS GAY AND TRANS --
SORRY, DEPRESSED AND SUICIDAL.
AND I THINK THESE LAWS ARE
LESBIANS.
SORRY, UNCONSCIONABLE.
>> I THINK YOU ENDED UP SAYING
GAY A COUPLE TIMES.
>> I'M TRYING TO MAKE SENSE OF
ALL THIS.
LIKE THIS DON'T SAY GAY LAW HAVE
A PURPOSE?
>> WELL, I THINK I GUESS IT'S SO
KIDS AREN'T GOING HOME WITH
QUESTIONS THAT PARENTS DON'T
WANT TO ANSWER?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE IDEA IS.
>> SO ONE KID CAN SAY I LIVE
WITH MY PARENTS BUT ANOTHER ONE
HAS TO SAY I LIVE IN A HOUSE
WITH TWO ADULT MEN WHO BOUGHT ME
WHEN I WAS YOUNG?
THAT'LL BE -- THEY'LL BE LESS
CONFUSED THEN.
>> IT DOES SOUND LIKE IT WOULD
BE MORE CONFUSING.
>> LOOK, COLIN, IF THE '90s WERE
RIGHT AND GAY MEANS BAD, THEN
THIS IS THE GAYEST LAW I'VE EVER
SEEN.
IF YOU CAN'T SAY IT, YOU MIGHT
AS WELL SING IT.
* GAY, GAY, GAY *
* GAY, GAY, GAY, GAY *
* GAY, GAY, GAY, GAY, GAY *
>> KATE McKINNON, EVERYONE!
* GAY, GAY, GAY, GAY, I GA GUY *
THE NEW YORK TIMES AFTER IT
MISTAKENLY PRINTED A PICTURE OF
HER SISTER, VENUS WILLIAMS, AND
LABELED IT SERENA.
WORSE, THE "TIMES" THEN SENT AN
APOLOGY LETTER TO WENDY
WILLIAMS.
>>> FANS OF THE HILT HBO SHOW
EUPHORIA HAVE BEEN HARSHLY
CRITICIZING THE SERIES CREATOR
FOR SEXUALIZING THE HIGH SCHOOL
CHARACTERS.
PLUS IT'S JUST NOT ACCURATE.
TAKE FROM IT ME, NO ONE HAS SEX
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
DON'T APPLAUD THAT MUCH.
>>> THE HOUSE VOTED TO AWARD THE
CONGRESSIONAL GOLD MEDAL TO THE
ONLY ALL-FEMALE BLACK UNIT TO
SERVE IN WORLD WAR II.
AND TYLER PERRY PLAYS THEM ALL
IN HIS NEW FILM "INGLERNIOUS
BASTERDS."
>> DUBAI HAS OPENED THE MUSEUM
OF THE FUTURE WHICH AIMS TO SHOW
WHAT THE WORLD WILL BE LIKE IN
50 YEARS.
AND LET'S JUST SAY THE MUSEUM
DOES NOT FEATURE A POLAR BEAR
EXHIBIT.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT 11%
OF AMERICAN ADULTS ARE AFRAID OF
THE DARK.
ESPECIALLY IF THAT DARK IS
BEHIND THEM AT THE ATM.
>>> DUNKIN' HAS ANNOUNCED A NEW
BEVERAGE CALLED THE
SHAMROCK MACCHIATO, WHICH
COMBINES ESPRESSO, VANILLA, AND
IRISH CREAM.
IT'S THE FESTIVE, SUGARY DRINK
THAT WILL HAVE YOU SAYING, TOP
O' THE MORNING AND LOSING THE
BOTTOM O' YOUR LEG.
>>> A MAN IN TIMES SQUARE
RETURNED A LOST WALLET FILLED
WITH $4,000 CASH TO ITS RIGHTFUL
OWNER.
WHEN TOLD HOW MUCH MONEY WAS IN
THE RETURNED WALLET THE MAN
REPLIED --
>>> PAT SAJAK IS ASKING "WHEEL
OF FORTUNE" FANS TO STOP MAKING
FUN OF THE TWO CONTESTANTS WHO
WERE UNABLE TO SOLVE AN EASY
PUZZLE SAYING, QUOTE, HAVE A
LITTLE HEART.
OR AS THE CONTESTANTS WOULD
GUESS, "HAZE A NIPPLE HEAVE."
>>> TUESDAY WAS NATIONAL PIG
DAY.
BUT I TOLD THAT TO A PIG AND HE
HANDCUFFED ME.
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW STUDY,
JUST ONE DRINK A DAY MAY SHRINK
OVERALL VOLUME OF YOUR BRAIN.
THOUGH I THINK I SPEAK FOR ALL
ALCOHOL ENTHUSIASTS WHEN I SAY,
BUH?
LOOKS AT PARIS FASHION WEEK.
HERE TO COMMENT IS PAULINE, A
WEARY MOTHER IN HER DARKEST
HOUR.
>> YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO BELIEVE
IT, MICHAEL.
I'M PREGNANT AGAIN.
>> WELL, HOW ARE YOU DOING,
PAULINE?
CONGRATULATIONS.
MUST BE SUCH AN EXCITING TIME.
>> EXCITING FOR WHO, MICHAEL?
LAST TIME I GAVE BIRTH THE BABY
WAS SO BIG THE DOCTOR SAID HE
LOOKED LIKE BLACK JASON MOMOA.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT FIELDS LIKE TO
DROP A DROGO?
BAD.
BUT HERE, LOOK AT RIHANNA.
COME ON.
WITH A PERFECT CUTE LITTLE BABY
BUMP.
MEANWHILE, I LOOK LIKE I'M
TRYING TO SHOPLIFT A TURDUCKEN.
I'M JUST REGULAR PREGNANT.
I WANT TO BE FAMOUS PREGNANT.
>> FAMOUS PREGNANT?
THAT WAS JUST RIHANNA'S
PREGNANCY ANNOUNCEMENT PHOTO,
RIGHT?
>> SURE WAS.
RIHANNA AND HER BOYFRIEND ALL
HAPPY.
WALKING AROUND HARLEM.
YOU KNOW HOW I ANNOUNCED MY
PREGNANCY?
I THREW UP ON MARTIN LUTHER KING
JR. BOULEVARD.
YOU KNOW, I'VE HAD BABIES BEFORE
BUT THIS IS MY WORST PREGNANCY
YET.
IT'S MAKING ME WANT TO EDIT AALL
KINDS OF THINGS.
PICKLES, PEANUT BUTTER, THE
BARREL OF A SHOTGUN.
>> PAULINE.
>> I DON'T MEAN IT.
I DON'T MEAN IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
PREGNANCY BRAIN.
>> WELL, RIHANNA HAS BEEN
WEARING SOME ICONIC PREGNANCY
LOOKS AT FASHION WEEK.
HOPEFULLY TO INSPIRE OTHER
PREGNANT WOMEN.
>> OH, PLEASE.
LOOK AT THIS, MICHAEL.
SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE'S GOING TO A
SEX FUNERAL.
AND SHE MAKES IT LOOK GOOD.
HOW?
I COULDN'T EVEN WEAR THIS
BEFORE.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO WEAR
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
EVERYTHING'S GOT TO STAY PUT.
YOU KNOW?
BUT RIGHT NOW EVERYTHING ON ME
IS LOOSE, INCLUDING MY PUSHER.
SHE'S ALWAYS WEARING HEELS.
YOU WANT TO SEE MY HEELS,
MICHAEL?
THESE.
I USED TO WEAR A SIZE 9.
NOW I'M A MEN'S 15.
YOU KNOW I EVEN GOT MY TUBES
TIED.
BUT THEY CAME LOOSE.
I KEEP BEGGING MY DOCTOR, DOUBLE
KNOT THEM NEXT TIME, PLEASE.
>> THEY TIED THEM LIKE
SHOELACES?
>> LOOK, I'M OUT HERE ON MY OWN,
MICHAEL.
AT LEAST RIHANNA'S GOT A
BOYFRIEND BY HER SIDE.
MEANWHILE, YOU HAVEN'T COME WITH
ME TO NOT ONE DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT.
>> WAIT, WHY WOULD I?
>> BECAUSE YOU DID THIS TO ME.
>> I DID?
>> MM-HMM.
I SAID LET'S USE PROTECTION.
AND YOU LOOKED ME IN THE EYE AND
SAID "IT DON'T FEEL THE SAME."
>> THAT DOES SOUND LIKE ME, YES.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
TO GO.
I LEFT MY KIDS IN LORNE'S
OFFICE.
>> PAULINE, EVERYBODY.
>> I'M YOUNGER THAN RIHANNA.
I'M ONLY 29.
For "Weekend Update," I'm
Colin Jost.
>> I'm Michael Che. Good night.
YOU KNOW, OVER MY TEN YEARS ON
THE SHOW, I HAVE PLAYED DOZENS
OF TEACHERS, PRINCIPALS,
MOTHERS, WOMEN NAMED DIANE,
SUSAN, OR TEACHER.
AND I HAVE LOVED ALL OF THESE
SWEET, NURTURING WOMEN.
BUT THE SHOW SAID THAT IF I
PLAYED 150 OF THEM, THEN AS A
REWARD I COULD WRITE A SKETCH OF
MY OWN CHOOSING.
YOU KNOW, TO SHOW A DIFFERENT
SIDE OF MYSELF.
SO TONIGHT, THIS IS THAT SKETCH.
ENJOY.
>> I'M SO NERVOUS, I CAN'T
BELIEVE SIEGFRIED'S GOING TO
TAKE ME, A LOSER AND A FOOL.
HOW DO I LOOK?
>> YOU LOOK FANTASTIC, SIR.
I'M SURE SHE'LL BE TITILLATED.
>> BUT YOU'RE RIGHT TO BE
SCARED.
SHE IS THE MOST WIDELY DESIRED
WOMAN IN THE WORLD.
>> OH, I'M SICK.
I'M SICK WITH FEELING FOR THIS
WOMAN.
IT'S HER.
PRAY FOR ME BOYS.
**
>> HELLO.
NOW, SCRAM, BOYS, AND LEAVE THIS
MAN TO ME.
>> MY GOD.
YOU ARE SO BEAUTIFUL.
AND SEXUAL.
AND I CAN TELL YOUR
PERSONALITY'S ALSO REALLY GOOD.
>> OH GOD, IF I HAD A NICKEL FOR
EVERY TIME I HEARD A MAN SAY
THAT, I WOULD HAVE SO MANY COINS
THAT IT WOULD BE ANNOYING.
>> OH, SENSUAL WOMAN.
YOU MAKE ME SO HORNY.
I SEE WHY THEY CALL YOU THE
SEXUAL WOMAN.
>> SO YEAH, I LIED TO
OSCAR ISAAC.
I TOLD HIM I HAVE A FAMOUS
RECURRING CHARACTER ON THE SHOW
CALLED "THE SEXUAL WOMAN."
IS THAT A CRIME?
**
>> OH, I'M THE LUCKIEST MAN ON
EARTH TO BE BRUSHING YOUR HAIR.
MIND IF I GET A LITTLE CLOSER?
>> OH, SURE.
BRING YOUR HEAD AND BODY THAT
LOOK LIKE THAT CLOSER TO ME,
WHATEVER.
I DON'T CARE.
>> I NEED YOU TO KNOW, I SEE YOU
SEXUALLY.
I DON'T SEE YOU AS SOMEONE WHO
WOULD, LIKE, RUN A SCHOOL.
I MEAN, YOU ARE THE MOST UNDER
35 PERSON I'VE EVER MET.
>> OH, STOP IT, YOU FLIRT.
>> WELL, I BET YOU WERE ABOUT TO
DO YOUR BIG CATCHPHRASE.
>> UH -- OH, RIGHT.
YES.
MY FAMOUS CATCHPHRASE.
OF COURSE.
WHAT WAS IT?
HERE WE GO.
HEY, GET YOUR FAT ASS ON MY LAP,
BITCH!
>> OKAY.
YES.
>> OOH.
>> I MUST CONFESS, I HAVE A BIG
I MUST CONFESS, I HAVE A BIG,
COOL BONER RIGHT NOW WHICH I
SOMETIMES GET WHEN I RESPECT
SOMEONE TOO MUCH.
>> NOW, WHY DID I CHOOSE
OSCAR ISAAC FOR THE SKETCH?
NO REASON.
I MEAN, PRETTY RANDOM.
EVERY TIME I'VE DONE SOMETHING
ROMANTIC ON THE SHOW, IT'S BEEN
TOTALLY RANDOM.
LIKE WITH RYAN GOSLING.
OR DRAKE.
OH, MY GOD.
DO I HAVE A PATTERN OF SEXUAL
RANDOMNESS?
WELL, WHATEVER.
YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE.
NOW BACK TO THE SKETCH.
>> IS THE FOOD ALL RIGHT?
I HOPE YOU EVEN LIKE SPAGHETTI.
>> YOU'RE LUCKY THAT I DO.
>> DAMN IT, I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
AND IT'S KILLING ME!
>> OH!
YES.
TO ME THIS IS NORMAL BEHAVIOR.
>> I WROTE A SONG FOR YOU, IF
THAT'S OKAY.
**
* SEXUAL WOMAN ARE YOU FROM
PARIS OR BARCELONA *
* NO I'M FROM ARIZONA *
* SEXUAL WOMAN I RESPECT YOU
SO MUCH I'VE JUST
DEMONSTRATED BY MY INSANE
BONER *
>> OH.
A BONER?
LET ME GUESS.
YOU WANT TO KISS ME NOW.
>> YES, I DO.
BUT NOT YET.
YOU NEED TIME TO DIGEST ALL THAT
SPAGHETTI.
SO NOW COULD WE JUST HUG?
>> YES, GOOD IDEA.
I WOULD HAVE FORGOTTEN TO DIGEST
AND REGRETTED IT LATER.
>> OH, WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT YOU
IS TRUE.
YOU ARE EVERYONE'S CUP OF TEA.
INCLUDING ME, OSCAR ISAAC.
>> OH, I KNOW, OSCAR ISAAC.
>> SORRY.
IS THAT -- IT SAYS MY REAL NAME
ON THE CARD.
IS THAT A MISTAKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS -- THE WRITERS ARE SO
ANNOYING AND STUPID.
I WOULD SAY I GUESS JUSTIFY GO
WITH IT?
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN LET'S GET MY FAT ASS ON
YOUR LAP.
>> YES.
**
* YOU THOUGHT YOU
COULD FIX IT
BY YOURSELF *
* PLUMBING'S JUST AS EASY
AS BUILDING A SHELF *
* YOUR DIY BECOMES OMG
YOU'RE IN OVER YOUR HEAD *
>>> WELL, HELLO.
I'M GUS VANZANT.
AND WELCOME TO "IN OVER YOUR
HEAD" WHERE WE TALK TO FOLKS WHO
GOT A LITTLE OVERCONFIDENT
TAKING ON PROJECTS AROUND THE
HOUSE.
SPONSORED BY THUMB ICE.
DID YOU WHACK YOUR THUMB WITH A
HAMMER LIKE A CARTOON IDIOT?
NUMB THE PAIN WITH THUMB ICE.
OUR FIRST GUEST IS TOMMY DORIAN,
WHO SAID HE TRIED TO INSTALL HIS
OWN POOL.
UH-OH.
COME ON IN, TOMMY.
**
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE YOUR HAIR'S
STILL A LITTLE WET FROM THE POOL
THERE, TOMMY.
>> NO, THAT'S UNRELATED.
>> OKAY.
SO TELL US, WHAT WAS BEHIND YOUR
THINKING BEHIND BUILDING YOUR
OWN POOL?
>> WELL, MY NEIGHBOR PUT ONE IN.
HIRED A WHOLE CREW AND AN
ARCHITECT.
THE WHOLE NINE YARDS.
I THOUGHT, IT'S BASICALLY A HOLE
PLUS A HOSE.
WHY OVERTHINK IT?
>> UH-HUH.
AND WHEN DID THINGS GO WRONG?
>> ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, GUS.
MY PROBLEM STARTED WHEN I TRIED
TO POUR THE CONCRETE WHILE I WAS
STILL DIGGING, TO SAVE TIME.
>> OH, WOW.
>> OH WOW IS RIGHT.
CUT TO, I'M UP TO MY WAIST IN
HARD CONCRETE SCREAMING, "HELP!
SOMEONE TURN OFF THE HOSE!"
>> SO YOU WERE ALREADY RUNNING
THE HOSE?
>> TO FILL THE POOL, TO SAVE
TIME, YES.
HAD TO HAVE IT OPEN FOR NEW
YEAR'S.
>> WELL, LOOKING BACK, ANY
REGRETS?
>> I DO WISH I HADN'T PUNCTURED
MY SEPTIC TANK.
THAT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT KIND OF
POOL.
>> THANKS FOR COMING, TOMMY.
>> THANKS FOR ALLOWING ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OUR NEXT GUEST THOUGHT THAT HE
SHOULD, QUOTE, DO HIS OWN
ELECTRICAL.
PLEASE WELCOME FELIX CREWE!
**
>> HEY GUS.
LONG TIME, FIRST TIME.
>> YOU MEAN, LONG TIME WATCH,
FIRST-TIME GUEST?
>> NO.
FIRST TIME ELECTROCUTED.
LONG TIME IT HURT.
>> SO, HOW DID YOU DECIDE TO DO
YOUR OWN ELECTRICAL WORK?
>> WELL, I KEEP TELLING MY WIFE,
IT'S JUST WIRES.
BABE, IT'S JUST WIRES.
HONEY, NOTHING'S GOING TO
HAPPEN, IT'S WIRES.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW WHEN YOU SEE A GUY
DEFUSING BOMBS IN THE MOVIES YOU
THINK, I COULD DO THAT?
>> I'VE NEVER THOUGHT THAT.
>> WELL, I HAVE A LOT.
SO I THOUGHT, "WHAT THE HELL,
I'M GOING TO INSTALL MY OWN
CIRCUIT BREAKER."
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> NO, TRUST ME, THERE IS NO
GOD.
NOW, THE WHOLE IDEA OF A BREAKER
IS TO STOP A POWER SURGE, RIGHT?
SO, I THINK I SHOULD START WITH
THE POWER DIALED ALL THE WAY UP
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING
TO PROTECT MYSELF AGAINST,
RIGHT?
>> THAT IS VERY BAD LOGIC.
>> SO I GOT THIS THING CRANKED
UP HIGHER THAN LIGHTNING AND I'M
LIKE, "TIME TO SCREW IN THE
METAL SCREWS," RIGHT?
>> NO, NOT RIGHT.
>> CUT TO -- I FLY SO HARD
THROUGH A SHEET OF DRYWALL THAT
MY SCREAM PHYSICALLY DETACHES
FROM MY BODY AND TRAVELS AT A
SLOWER SPEED.
KIND OF LIKE PETER PAN'S SHADOW
DETACHING FROM HIS BODY.
>> YEAH, GOT IT.
>> SO AFTER I HIT A STEEL
SUPPORT COLUMN, WIPING OUT THE
ENTIRE FIRST FLOOR OF MY HOME, I
AM HIT IN THE FACE BY MY OWN
SCREAM.
WILD, RIGHT?
>> WOW.
AND WHAT DID YOU LEARN FROM ALL
OF THIS?
>> GLOVES.
YOU'VE GOT TO WEAR GLOVES.
>> WELL, THANK YOU, FELIX.
>> EXCITED TO GET MY CHECK.
>> THERE'S NO CHECK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND OUR FINAL GUEST SAYS THAT
SHE'S BEEN TRYING TO REPAIR HER
HOME FOR MONTHS.
PLEASE WELCOME -- THIS CAN'T BE
RIGHT.
MY WIFE CARLISA.
**
HEY, BABY.
UH, WHAT YOU DOING HERE?
>> JUST TRYING TO REPAIR MY
HOME.
THIS DAMN FOOL IS OUT HERE
PRETENDING HE'S A BIG EXPERT.
MEANWHILE, HIS OWN HOUSE IS
LITERALLY FALLING APART.
>> WELL, IF YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
BABY, I'M HAPPY TO FIX IT.
>> WITH WHAT?
THIS IS YOUR TOOLBOX.
BUT THERE AREN'T NO TOOLS IN
HERE, THOUGH.
IT'S JUST CANS OF BLACK'S BEER.
>> HEY, I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
THOSE.
>> THERE'S NO TOOLS IN THIS
WHOLE GOOFY-ASS WORKSHOP.
IT'S JUST CHOCOLATE BARS THAT
LOOK LIKE TOOLS.
>> WELL, SOMETIMES I GET A
LITTLE HUNGRY.
>> MEANWHILE, OUR TOILET HASN'T
WORKED IN MONTHS.
I OPENED THE LID OF THE TANK AND
SAW THIS.
>> WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU
MIGHT NEED AN ICE COLD HOT DOG.
>> AND THEN YOU SNUCK SOME
CRUSHED UP PEANUT SHELLS INTO
OUR SON'S LUNCH TO PROVE THAT HE
WAS FAKING HIS PEANUT ALLERGY.
>> WELL, THE IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT I TRUST YOU NOW.
I STILL THINK HE MAY BE
EXAGGERATING A LITTLE BIT.
>> GUS.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY FOR
YOURSELF?
>> LOOK.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR THAT I
AM --
* IN OVER MY HEAD *
>> NO, NO, NO.
DON'T YOU DARE SING THAT DAMN
JINGLE TO ME, NO.
THIS MAN SUCKED UP A WASP NEST
WITH A VACUUM AND NOW HE WON'T
EVEN THROW IT AWAY.
>> LISTEN, DYSON --
>> IDIOT.
YOU'S AN IDIOT.
>> YOU WANT SOME OF THIS --
>>> ONCE AGAIN, CHARLI XCX!
**
* MMM BABY
MMM BABY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY MMM
WHOO *
* BABY
I'MA LOVE YOU REAL
I'MA LOVE YOU RAW *
* I'MA LOVE YOU
IN THE KITCHEN
I'MA PUT YOU ON THE FLOOR *
* LEAVE YOU WANTING MORE
I'MA LOVE YOU REAL
YOU MIGHT LOSE IT ALL
I'MA MAKE YOU MY DECISION *
* I'MA PUT YOU ON THE FLOOR
LEAVE YOU WANTING
I CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES
YOU'RE NERVOUS *
* BUT YOU KNOW
JUST WHAT YOU WANT
IF YOU'RE FEELING SCARED
THAT'S FINE *
* I'VE GOT NO PROBLEM
TAKING FULL CONTROL
BABY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
**
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
MMM BABY
MMM BABY *
* WHY YOU TRYIN'
TO FIGHT WHAT'S RIGHT
YOU KNOW I'M 'BOUT TO
CHANGE YOUR LIFE FOR GOOD *
* YOU CAN PLAY PRETEND
THAT'S FINE
I KNOW THEY THOUGHT YOU
REALLY WISH YOU WOULD *
* BABY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
**
* IMA MAKE YOU MY
BABY
BABY *
* YOU KNOW I'LL
BREAK YOUR HEART
TEAR IT INTO TINY PIECES
ONE MORE FALLING STAR *
* I'LL SHUT YOU AWAY
BUT YOU WANNA STAY
I JUST WANNA SAY
BABY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY *
* I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY
I'MA MAKE YOU MY BABY *
* WHAT **
>>> ABRAHAM LINCOLN SMILED.
SHE MAY BE FLAWED BUT SHE'S
STILL MY COUNTRY.
ANYWAY, SEE YOU TONIGHT.
AT THE THEATER.
THE END.
>> WOW.
THAT WAS GREAT, LINUS.
AND VERY RELEVANT, TOO.
>> VERY MUCH THE INTENTION.
THANK YOU.
>> WELL, WELL, GREAT STORIES
TONIGHT, EVERYONE.
AND WE WILL BE BACK NEXT MONTH,
ALL ARE WELCOME.
SIR, I'M SORRY.
WE'LL BE TWO MINUTES.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
YOU'RE NOT FINISHED.
EXCUSE ME.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, SIR -- I
DON'T THINK WE'VE EVER ACTUALLY
SPOKEN.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I ALWAYS SEE YOU
WITH A DIFFERENT BOOK.
YOU LIKE READING?
>> OH, YEAH.
YES, MA'AM.
IT'S HOW I'VE SEEN THE WORLD TEN
TIMES OVER, BECAUSE OF MY BOOKS.
>> I LOVE THAT.
YOU EVER TRY ANY WRITING?
>> I MEAN, I DABBLE.
BUT NO, MAYBE ONE DAY.
YOU ALL ARE THE WRITERS.
>> WELL, WHY DON'T YOU READ US
SOMETHING?
WHATEVER YOU GOT.
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
>> HEY, HEY.
NO JUDGMENTS HERE.
WE'RE ALL JUST TRYING STUFF OUT.
PROMISE.
>> COME ON, MAN, TAKE A SEAT.
>> YEAH, I'D LOVE TO HEAR IT,
PAL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> GOSH, THAT'S SO NICE.
I'VE NEVER READ IN FRONT OF
PEOPLE BEFORE.
THIS ONE'S CALLED "THE APOGEE OF
MIDNIGHT."
>> OH, LOVELY.
PLEASE.
>> OKAY.
THERE IT WAS AGAIN.
THE SOUND OF MOP ON TILE.
THE START OF ANOTHER LATE NIGHT.
ONE OF THOUSANDS LIKE IT.
ALONE IN CHANDLER HIGH.
BUT THE JANITOR LIKED THE
SILENCE.
IT HELD HIM IN A COOL, DELICATE
CALM.
>> HM, WOW, I REALLY LIKE THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
THEN, FOOTSTEPS.
LOUD AND GETTING CLOSER.
HELLO?
SCHOOL'S CLOSED.
A WOMAN TURNED THE CORNER.
SHE LOOKED LOST.
SORRY, I'M LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
NAMED MIKE?
OH, YEAH?
WHO'S ASKING?
MY NAME IS DUA LIPA.
I'M A BIG POP STAR AND I'M
LOOKING FOR A JANITOR NAMED
MIKE.
>> OKAY.
>> THE JANITOR PAUSED.
THAT WAS HIS NAME.
DUA LIPA SIGHED.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD OF ME, HAVE
YOU?
SORRY, MA'AM.
MORE OF A CLASSIC ROCK GUY
MYSELF.
BUT SURE, MAYBE I'VE SEEN A
BIKINI PIC OR TWO, HOW CAN I
HELP?
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT, IT IS
GETTING PRETTY LATE.
SO I THINK WE SHOULD PROBABLY
WRAP IT UP.
>> WHAT?
HE JUST STARTED.
>> WRAP UP?
SO I CAN MOP?
HECK, I GOT TIME.
>> YEAH, AND I WANT TO KNOW
WHERE IT'S GOING.
>> I DON'T.
>> YEAH, I THINK I'M GOOD.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M BAD AT THIS.
>> NO, NO.
WE SUPPORT IT.
SO PLEASE, GO AHEAD.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
MIND IF I SIT DOWN?
DUA LIPA WAS EXHAUSTED.
SHE'D JUST DONE A CONCERT IN
EUROPE.
AND WAS STILL IN HER SPARKLY
SHOW GETUP.
HE LIKED HER.
SHE WAS COOL.
SO WHAT BRINGS YOU OUT ALL THIS
WAY TO SEE LITTLE OLD ME,
GIRLIE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW, THIS IS GOING
TO SOUND CRAZY.
COME ON, DUA LIPA, YOU KNOW YOU
CAN TALK TO ME.
I'M YOUR FRIEND.
IT'S TRUE.
THEY WERE FAST FRIENDS.
AND NOTHING MORE.
RIGHT?
>> ARE YOU ASKING US?
>> PLEASE.
I'M STILL READING.
WELL, I GUESS I WANTED TO ASK
YOU A FAVOR, MIKE.
SURE THING, GIRLIE.
WHAT'S UP?
WOULD YOU TEACH ME HOW TO MAKE
OUT?
I'VE NEVER DONE IT BEFORE.
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY, I JUST --
NO.
>> OH, COME ON.
>> WHY?
>> LOOK, I THINK THAT IT'S GREAT
THAT YOU WRITE.
I JUST DON'T REALLY WANT TO
HEAR ABOUT YOUR WEIRD, MADE-UP
THING WITH DUA LIPA.
I'M SORRY, I DON'T.
>> MY THING?
THIS AIN'T ME, MAMA, THIS IS
FICTION.
THIRD PERSON.
>> YEAH, ABOUT A JANITOR NAMED
MIKE.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND SO WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> MICHAEL B. JACKSON.
WHY?
>> IT'S KIND OF CREEPY, MAN.
>> VERY CREEPY.
>> I SEE.
I GUESS I'M NOT A WRITER AFTER
ALL.
BACK TO THE TOILETS IT IS.
>> JUST FINISH IT, PLEASE.
>> OKAY, COOL.
OKAY.
SURE, DUA LIPA, I CAN TEACH YOU
HOW TO MAKE OUT.
WAIT, CAN MY FRIEND COME?
HER NAME IS TAWNY McDANIELS.
THE FAMOUS GINGER MILF?
ONE AND THE SAME.
YOU KNOW HER?
KNOW HER?
I MANAGE HER SUB BRAND.
OF COURSE PORNOGRAPHY HASN'T
BEEN THE SAME SINCE THE '70s.
THAT'S BEFORE T.J. MUNST TOOK
OVER AT STUFFED.
WHEN THE MAGS HAD VISION AND THE
SPREADS WERE ACTUALLY GOOD.
>> SORRY, I DO THINK WE NEED TO
CALL IT THERE.
I'M SORRY.
>> OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
STUFF HAPPENS, STUFF HAPPENS,
SO, DUA LAUGHED.
HA HA HA!
HEY, MICHAEL B., THANKS.
THIS TRULY WAS THE APOGEE OF
MIDNIGHT.
AMEN.
CHAPTER 2.
>> AMEN?
>> CHAPTER 2?
THAT WASN'T THE END?
>> OH, HONEY, WE GOT 800 PAGES
IN BOOK ONE, STRAP IN.
>> HAVE A GREAT NIGHT, EVERYONE.
GET HOME SAFE.
OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU TO THIS AMAZING CREW
AND THIS INCREDIBLE CAST.
THE "SNL" FAMILY FOR THE WEEK.
THANK YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN A GREAT AUDIENCE.
GOOD NIGHT!
**