-And now the NCAA Final Four
Post Game Show.
-Thank you so much.
Welcome back
to the Post Game Show
sponsored by Capital One.
We hope you enjoyed
that commercial
where Spike Lee,
Samuel L. Jackson,
and Jennifer Garner
are supposed to be friends.
I'm Ernie Johnson here
with Kenny "The Jet" Smith,
Sir Charles Barkley...
and coach Bruce Pearl.
Well, fellas, let's-- let's talk
about tonight's first game
where Connecticut
beat Illinois, 71-62.
Bad night
for Illinois' offense!
-Indeed.
They got shut down faster
than an 11-year-old
asking
for Chappell Roan's autograph.
-Yeah, Ernie, man,
that game was miraculous.
It was spectacular.
I mean, one could
call it miraca-tacular.
-Absolutely.
It was almost as impressive
as when Chuck
spoke
so eloquently about immigrants
last week.
-Oh, well,
thank you very much.
-That's right. That's right.
That's right, Chuckster.
Now, you got a lot of love
for your passionate defense
of the immigrant experience
on this very show.
-Oh, well,
I got to tell you, man,
all kind of people
were texting me, e-mailing me.
It's the first time I went viral
without a prescription
for Valtrex.
-People love
sincere Charles Barkley.
-They do, right?!
It's crazy, man!
-Alright, well, let's move on
to the highlights from tonight.
-Oh, before we do, Ernie,
can I say something?
-Oh, uh, s-sure.
-Now, this might get me fired,
so I'm gonna choose my words
real careful right now.
Look, there's a war going on
between us and Iran.
Um, war-- war is turrible.
Um, innocent people
getting killed.
And I don't care who started it,
but we need to end it, okay?
-Hey, man,
I appreciate that, Chuck.
-Uh, thank you, Charles.
Let's-- Let's talk about
the late game
where Michigan beat Arizona.
Coach Pearl, any thoughts?
-Oh, tons!
-Okay. Uh, care to share?
-No.
-Well, it was a great game.
I mean,
I like Michigan toughness,
um, but, first, can I say
something real quick, Ernie?
-Sure.
-Okay.
Um, I'm gonna choose my words,
like, real careful here.
The Artemis II space mission
is a waste of money.
Now, I respect the astronauts,
but they ain't even
going to the moon.
They just flying
around the moon.
What's the point of that?
It's like telling your kids
you're going to Disney World,
and then you just take them
to Goofy Lot D and go home.
I mean, the mission is wrong,
and we need to end it.
-Alright. Thank you, Charles.
Why don't we get back
to basketball, okay?
Michigan's win tonight
really upended expectations.
-Yeah, they were the underdog.
I bet a lot of people
lost money on this one.
-Well, you know, it's crazy.
You can bet on anything now.
You guys seen these sites
like Kalshi?
-Oh, yeah,
where you can, like,
bet on stuff like who will
win "The Masked Singer"?
-Worse than that, man.
You can bet on what your
favorite sports commentator
will say on live TV.
Watch this.
Rumpelstiltskin.
I just made $200,000.
-Charles, we gotta--
We gotta get back to business.
-Oh, absolutely. Absolutely.
But, um...
first, can I say
something, Ernie?
-Is it going to be
about basketball?
-Possibly.
Could the camera
slowly push in on me?
Yeah. That's good.
Now, I'm gonna choose
my words very carefully here.
Um, as Attorney
General Pam Bondi was--
and I don't say this often--
turrible...
it is a shame
when somebody gets fired.
But we should all get--
we should all be glad
that that freckle-chested
dragon lady is gone.
Yeah.
And not to mention Kristi Noem,
whose husband
looks like he's starring
in "Big Momma's House 4."
Look, the whole thing
is a sham mockery.
-Uh, fellas, I have
a surprising development.
Since Charles
has been talking politics,
the FCC has demanded
that we give equal time,
so here to defend herself
is former Attorney General
Pam Bondi.
-Hello, gentlemen!
So great to be here
at the Final Four...
years of this country.
-Man, what are you doing here?
-I'm sorry, Charles,
but I can't let the lies you
said about me go unanswered.
The truth is,
I was amazing at my job,
and I am proud to say I made
history
as the first woman
ever to be fired
as Attorney General.
I shattered
that glass exit door.
And I just, um--
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
-Pam, um--
-I'm so sorry. I just--
Oh, my God! I miss it already!
I miss it already.
And they threw my headshot
in the trash
like it was the Epstein files!
-Come on!
-What am I gonna do?!
-I'm sure you're gonna have
other opportunities.
-Yeah, you could work in sports.
I mean, you already look like
a women's basketball coach
who got suspended
for pulling on a player's braid.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
-That's so nice.
That is so nice.
-Yeah. Yeah. No problem.
Hey, um, Ernie, can I say
something real quick?
-Sure.
-Now, I'm gonna choose
my words very carefully here.
Live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Jack Black!
Thank you.
Thank you! Thank you!
I am so thrilled
to be back hosting "SNL"
for the fifth time!
Ohh! Come on.
It's a huge honor to join
the Five-Timers Club.
I'm a five-timer!
Jack! Jack!
Thank God you're here!
-Jonah Hill!
Oh, my God!
Buddy, this is so nice
and velvety.
It is so good to see you!
What have you been up to, man?
-Well, I've actually been
working on "Superbad 2."
--What?! Really?!
-No.
-I just really like
the sound of applause.
-Good to know.
So? Are you gonna take me
to that kickass lounge?
-Yes, but, Jack,
we need your help.
There's something wrong
with the Five-Timers Club!
-What?! No! Let's go!
Yo, dude.
-You see what I mean?
-Yes. You're right.
It feels like there's evil
lurking around every corner.
Aah! Scary goblin!
-No, no, it's just me.
-It's just me.
It's just regular Tina Fey.
I wanted to congratulate you
on a historic night.
You're officially the first
Black in the Five-Timers Club.
-Tina! What's become
of this once glorious place?
-You know,
it's seen better days.
What started off as a one-off
joke in a Tom Hanks monologue
has been brought back
so many times
that it has literally
been run into the ground.
-Ah,
-For example--
and this is true--
this is my fifth
Five-Timers Club sketch.
-Wow! A double Fiver-Timer.
Is that why you're wearing
that special jacket?
-Oh, no, this is
actually my First-Timers jacket
from "SNL UK."
I-- I think it's made out
of Paddington.
-You know, I spent a night with
Paddington back in the '70s.
-Candice Bergen,
you saucy minx!
-Yeah, let's just say
we found something
that he likes way more
than marmalade.
-Candace!
-What? A bitch can party!
-Speaking of parties...
Does anybody know...
where I can just get a drink?
I can't find one.
-Melissa!
You're telling me
there's no booze
in the Five-Timers Lounge?!
-Yeah, that's right.
All they've got are these warm
cans of John Mulaney's beer.
-Those are non-alcoholic,
though, right?
-Not if you fill them
with vodka.
-Well, you know,
desperate times
call for desperate measures.
-Did someone say
"desperate measures"?
-Domingo? You're in here?
Have you even been
on the show five times?
-Yes, if you count this one.
Now...
♪ Hey, Jack, came all this way,
had to explain ♪
♪ That my name is Domingo ♪
-No cast members allowed.
-Wow!
It's my hero, Professor Snape!
-That is not Professor Snape!
It's five-time musical guest and
my partner tonight, Jack White!
-Thank you, but unfortunately,
I have to be going.
-Why so soon?!
-Well, the five-time
musical guests
only get their parking validated
for 15 minutes.
So, uh, I have to
move my hearse.
Enough is enough!
It's time to fix this place
the only way I know how.
With the power of rock!
Tina, mike me!
-Candace, let's go.
It's gonna get loud!
-Okay.
-♪ I'm back hosting "Saturday
Night Live" for the fifth time ♪
♪ And if I don't crush it,
it would be a crime ♪
♪ Everything about the lounge
is broken and wrong ♪
♪ But I'm gonna fix it
by singing
the world's ♪
♪ Most rockin' song ♪
Jack White, get back out here!
Now give me a choir
of marching wizards!
-♪ I'm gonna make it right ♪
♪ The Five-Timer Army
gonna lift the curse ♪
♪ We got Jack Black and White ♪
♪ He's shredding his axe
while I sing the next verse ♪
♪ We got Melissa,
Candice Bergen, Jonah Hill ♪
♪ And British Tina Fey ♪
♪ It's my nightmare rotation ♪
♪ And I think
it's gonna save the day ♪
♪ And when I put
this jacket on ♪
♪ You know I feel like
I am ready to host ♪
-Sing it! Everybody!
-I can't believe
this is really happening.
I think I'm in heaven.
Am I in heaven?!
-You're in heaven!
-You guys...
are you ready to rock?!
We have got
a great show tonight.
Jack Black is here.
-Jack White is here.
-So stick around,
and we'll be White Black.
-Just came from the gym.
That's why
I'm a little out of breath.
Alright, gang!
What's everyone
digging into for lunch today?
-Turkey.
-Chicken salad.
-♪ I got a tofu wrap ♪
-Tofu?!
-Yeah, I'm trying vegan again.
-Ha! Cut to tomorrow
with you with a burger.
-So true.
-Guilty!
-I love that.
-We talkin' lunch?
-What?
-I'm doing homemade nachos.
-God. Kathy's here.
-I didn't even see her come in.
-Do we invite her over?
-Oh, no, no. We cannot.
I wish there was another way
to say this, but I hate her.
-Yeah, me too.
-She's awful.
-She's the worst.
-Y'all ever heard
of these things?
-Nachos?
Yes, we've heard of nachos.
-Okay, Kathy, enjoy your lunch.
-Oh, I will.
Brought these from home.
I'd share with you,
but I crushed up
some of my pills into the beans.
Gotta trick myself like a dog,
otherwise I won't take
my birth control.
Don't worry. It's not TMI.
It's not for sex.
It's for acne, weight issues,
uterine growth,
excess hair, overall
mood issues, dry mouth.
"And, yeah, sex." "I wish!"
"Hey, who said that?!"
"I did!"
-Be quiet!
-Dude. Don't yell at her.
-Guys, guys!
Let's just ignore her
and talk amongst
ourselves, okay?
-Good idea. Good idea.
-Yes. Yes.
-Did you guys get the Windows
update on your desktop today?
-Yeah, I did.
-It took forever!
-Yeah, like, hello?
I have work to do.
-We talkin' tech?
-Oh, my God.
-Just ignore her.
-We talkin' tech?
-Ugh. I feel bad!
-Don't!
If you give her an inch,
she will take a mile.
-We talkin' tech?!
-Yes, Kathy, we're talkin' tech.
-Marty, no! Don't!
-Well, I'm sorry!
-Yeah, well, speaking of tech,
got myself a new phone.
It's called a Grasshopper.
It's only $5.99.
I get to call my mom
and the cops.
You don't even have to
charge the damn thing.
It's disposable.
You make a couple calls,
you throw it away.
-That's very cool, Kathy.
-Oh, I'm addicted to this thing.
Y'all play Numbers?
-What is Numbers?
-It's the number-one game
on Grasshopper right now.
You just sift through
the numbers.
They got 'em all.
They got 1, 2...
3, 4.
They got 5...
6...7.
I don't think they have--
Oh, my God. They have 8!
But I don't think they have--
Oh, my God. They have 9?!
Wow! Oh, they got--
-SHUT UP, CATHY!
-Dude! Dude! Dude.
-Greg!
-You cannot yell like that, man.
-Yeah!
I'm gonna quit. I have to quit!
-No. Don't quit.
-You cannot quit.
-You can't quit.
-Then promise me.
The next time she tries to
butt in, we say nothing.
If we don't give her anything,
she will just get the hint
and she will stop.
Do you promise?
-Okay. We promise.
-Yes.
-Of course. We promise.
-Thank you.
Now can we finally
talk about "Survivor"?
-Ohh! Yeah!
-Insane!
-We talkin' TV?
We talkin' TV?
-Don't say a word.
-We talkin' TV?
-Just stay perfectly still.
-Do the plan.
Do what we promised.
We talkin' TV?
-Just take my hand.
And trust me.
-We talkin' TV?
-Just stay strong.
-Just...
She doesn't exist.
-We talkin' TV?
-I feel like this is worse
than just talking to her.
-We talkin' TV?
-I promise you, it is not.
-We're almost there, guys.
-I'm not gonna make it.
-We talkin' TV?
-She can't go on forever.
-She's getting tired.
I can hear it in her voice.
-We talkin' TV?
-I swear, she'll do one more,
max, and then she is done.
-We talkin' TV?
-That is the last one for sure.
Or are you back on tech?
-No. TV.
-A-ha!
-Nooooo!
Words to live by
¶ I JUST CAN'T FORGET
THAT TIME LAST YEAR
AT THE END OF PAPPY'S LIFE ¶
¶ WE GATHERED ROUND
HIS HOSPITAL BED ¶
¶ AND WHEN HE CRACKED A JOKE
I TRIED TO CHOKE BACK
A FRESH NEW ROUND OF TEARS ¶
¶ BUT I'LL NEVER FORGET
THE NEXT THING
THAT HE SAID ¶
¶ HE PULLED ME DOWN
SO I COULD HEAR
I CUPPED MY FINGER
TO MY EAR ¶
¶ HE SAID, SON THE ONLY
THING YOU GOTTA KNOW
ABOUT LIFE IS THIS ¶
¶ AND HE SAID
WAIT, WHAT WAS IT
IT WAS SORTA LIKE
IT'S KINDA LIKE ¶
¶ DANG IT, WHAT WAS IT
IT WAS SOMETHING
REALLY COOL ¶
¶ SOMETHING SHORT AND SWEET
AND SUCCINCT AND FOLKSY
KIND OF SUMMED UP LIFE
REAL QUICK ¶
¶ GOD DAMN IT, GOD DAMN IT
GOD DAMN IT ¶
¶ WAS ON THE TIP OF MY
TONGUE BUT I FORGOT IT ¶
¶ LIKE SOMEONE HIT ME WITH
THE MEN IN BLACK THING
WHATEVER THAT'S CALLED ¶
¶ I WAS CLIMBING A MOUNTAIN
IN TIBET
WHEN I FOUND A MYSTERIOUS
CAVE ¶
¶ AND I FELT A BENEVOLENT
FORCE PULLING ME INSIDE ¶
¶ AND ON A DAIS IN THE CAVE
THERE SAT A SAGE
WHO GAVE ME KNOWLEDGE
OF THE AGES PAST ¶
¶ AND I FELT INNER PEACE
AND I GOT DOWN ON
MY KNEES AND CRIED ¶
¶ I MADE IT HALFWAY DOWN
THE MOUNTAIN
ENLIGHTENED BY THE
WISE MAN'S WORDS ¶
¶ AND FOR AS LONG AS I LIVE
I'LL REMEMBER WHAT HE SAID
HE SAID ¶
Sister
Next
Tonight
Calendar
ANYWAY
HE SAID
WAIT, [ BLEEP ]
WHAT THE [ BLEEP ]
DID THE WISE MAN SAY ¶
¶ I GOT DISTRACTED
BY THE TEXT FROM MY WIFE
ABOUT
MY SISTER'S THING ¶
¶ HE SAID SOMETHING LIKE
LIFE IS LIKE A DUH DUH-DUH
BUT THE DUH DUH-DUH
WAS THE GOOD PART ¶
¶ I WAS IN THERE FOR
OVER 20 HOURS
HE WAS SAYING REALLY
COOL STUFF ¶
¶ I SHOULD HAVE
WRITTEN IT DOWN
MAYBE I CAN GO
BACK UP THERE ¶
¶ NO IT'S PRETTY FAR AWAY
GUESS I BETTER GO
TAKE A SHOWER ¶
¶ FOR MY SISTER'S
THING TONIGHT ¶
¶ MY WIFE WAS RIGHT
IT'S ON THE CALENDAR
THE GOOGLE CALENDAR ¶
¶ WELL IT WASN'T EASY
SAYING BYE TO DAD
AND MY SON MUSTA
HEARD ME CRY ¶
¶ HE'S ONLY SIX YEARS OLD
BUT HE'S GOT PAPPY'S
TWINKLE IN HIS EYE ¶
¶ AND THE DARNDEST THING
YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE
CAME FROM THE
MOUTH OF A CHILD ¶
¶ HE SAID, DADDY, THERE'S
SOMETHING I WANT TO SAY ¶
¶ AND I SAID
SHUT UP
GONNA STOP YOU RIGHT THERE ¶
¶ WHAT THE [ BLEEP ]
DO KIDS EVEN KNOW
YOU DON'T KNOW NOTHING ¶
¶ HALF OF THE TIME
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW
TO WIPE YOUR OWN BUTT ¶
¶ TALKIN' BOUT DAD
I KNOW A COOL SAYIN' ¶
¶ NO YOU DON'T
YOU MAYBE ONLY KNOW
THE NAMES OF LIKE 30
WEIRD POKEMON GUYS ¶
¶ AND LIKE ONE [ BLEEP ]
WAY TO DRAW A DOG ¶
>> JACK WHITE, HIT 'EM WITH A
GUITAR SOLO.
>> WAIT, WAIT.
I FORGOT IT.
I FORGOT THE [ BLEEP ] SOLO.
¶ DANG IT, WHAT WAS IT
IT WAS SOMETHING
REALLY COOL ¶
¶ SOMETHING SHORT AND SWEET
AND SUCCINCT AND FOLKSY
KIND OF SUMMED UP LIFE
REAL QUICK ¶
¶ GOD DAMN IT, GOD DAMN IT
GOD DAMN IT ¶
¶ WAS ON THE TIP OF MY
TONGUE BUT I FORGOT IT ¶
¶ LIKE SOMEONE HIT ME WITH
THE MEN IN BLACK THING
WHATEVER THAT'S CALLED ¶
>> OH, I REMEMBER NOW!
THE NEURALYZER.
THAT'S WHAT THE MEN IN BLACK
THING WAS CALLED.
>> WE REMEMBERED!
-Man, I am excited
for this self-defense class!
-Oh, me too.
Uh, I'm here 'cause I need
to turn my skill into technique.
-What do you mean?
-Uh, I've won every fight I've
ever been in with no technique.
I've just been
spitting and pulling hair.
I feel like I need technique.
-Well, it's 4 p.m.,
so the teachers
should be walking in any second
through that door right there.
-Yes, rule number one
of the self-defense.
-Always be ready
for the surprise
that has come from the place
that was not the place
of the opposite of what
you thought it might be!
-Yes!
And now, everyone
tell me your name, your age,
and why you are here.
-Okay. Uh, Paul, 33.
Uh, I have skill,
but I lack technique.
-Welcome.
-Uh. Melanie, 28.
And I'd like to use my gun less.
-Welcome.
-Okay.
-This is Fred, 35.
I got a real mouth on me.
-Welcome.
-Okay. Very good.
Now, let us begin
with the most important part
of our practice, which is...
-Stop it!
Allow us to demonstrate this.
Philonius, attack me.
-Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it, stop it!
Stop it, stop it, stop it,
Now go to your house!
-I'm gonna go to my house!
-Very good, Philonius.
Now question to the class.
If your attacker
pin you to the floor
and you cannot stop it,
what do you do?
-Um, this could be wrong,
but bite their balls?
-Correct.
-That's correct.
When an attacker
attack you, surprise you,
you use their own...
-Momentum against them!
-Okay?
Redirect the attack
by turning it into
a different activiter, okay?
You, pretty little girl.
Attack me!
-Okay.
-Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it, stop it!
Turn around. And now we
are golfing. We are golfing.
We are golfing? You like golf?
You like golfing?
Perfect. Go to your house.
-Now I gotta do one, also.
Whoever thinks they are the
weakest in the class, attack me.
-It's gotta be me.
-Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it, stop it!
"Titanic"! Hmm!
-I-I'm sorry.
How is this supposed to
help us defend ourselves?
Have you guys even fought?
-Um, yes, you big carrot!
I have fought many time!
I fought MMA in the UFC.
-And I have fought an STD
in my P-N-S.
-Well, if that
makes you a fighter,
I must be the heavyweight champ.
-Okay. Okay.
Is this class my favorite show?
Because this is ridiculousness.
-Big carrot...
you don't believe in me?
Do me a favor.
Get up here.
-And I would like you
to attempt to hit me in the--
Oh, my God!
-I kick you! Go! Get out! Go!
-Away from me!
-You go home...
Go! Get! Stay over there!
Go
-I have a-- I have a question.
Um, like, what if the attacker
attacks you with a knife?
-I'm afraid there is nothing
you can do but die.
-Go to sleep if this happen.
But if they come at you slowly,
you can use
the power of suggestion
to get them
to do something else.
Okay, you, beautiful boy,
attack me.
-Oh, okay.
-Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it. And...
-♪ Amazing grace ♪
The doctor said
I would never sing again!
-Okay. I'm leaving.
This class is "B"
and, in many ways, "S."
-Okay.
You want proof this class works?
-For our final lesson,
we're gonna bring out the guest.
This is the toughest, strongest,
most badass student
we've ever trained.
Please welcome Bone Crusher!
-Hello. Um, I'm here
to "F" you bitches up.
-Okay. Very good.
Now, my poo-pills,
show her what you have learned.
Attack her!
-Stop it, stop it, stop
it, stop it!
"Titanic"!
-Okay, please tell me that's
a caterpillar in your pocket.
-Lucky guess.
-Class dismissed!
-Oh, you're nasty!
-That's what I'm talking about!
That's what I'm talking about!
-Well, thanks for
coming over, gals.
-Yeah!
-Thanks for having us!
-Jeannie, I see why you wanted
to redo your kitchen.
It's so dated.
When does the renovation start?
-Uh, we did it last month, so...
-And it's amazing.
-Thank you.
-Well, I just can't believe
we've been friends
all these years
and our husbands never met.
-Yeah, do you think they're okay
in the den
hanging out without us?
-Oh. They're fine.
They're big boys.
I'm sure they'll find something
to talk about.
-So, um...
Heh.
-Heh.
Yeah.
-I, uh, um-- No.
Right.
-Well, today I...
Blegh.
-You know, I like, um...
I don't know.
-Heh.
-Same.
-Yeah.
-♪ Carry on,
my wayward son ♪
-♪ There'll be peace
when you are done ♪
-♪ Lay your weary head
to rest ♪
♪ Don't you cry no more ♪
-Mayb-- Maybe I should
go check on them.
-I just hope
they're not talking politics.
-The last thing we need is them
in there yelling at each other.
-♪ Once I rose above
the noise and confusion ♪
♪ Just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion ♪
-♪ I was soaring ever higher ♪
-♪ But I flew too high ♪
-♪ Though my eyes could see,
I still was a blind man ♪
♪ Though my mind could think,
I still was a mad man ♪
-♪ I hear the voices
when I'm dreaming ♪
♪ I can hear them s-a-a-a-ay ♪
-You know, it's just so good
we're doing this.
Like, Randy has no male friends.
No friends of any kind,
actually.
-♪ Carry on, my wayward son ♪
♪ There'll be peace
when you are done ♪
♪ Lay your weary head
to rest ♪
♪ Don't you cry no more ♪
-Hah!
Wow. I can't believe
we all know this song!
-I actually don't,
but my mouth seems to.
-We don't think they're
up to no good, do we?
-I don't know. If you leave
guys alone for too long,
it usually turns into trouble.
-Well, now I'm worried.
-♪ On a stormy sea
of moving emotion ♪
♪ Tossed about,
I'm like a ship on the ocean ♪
♪ I set a course
for winds of fortune ♪
♪ But I hear the voices
s-a-a-a-ay ♪
-Yeah!
-Uh, I'm sorry.
A-Are they singing?
I will give you $1 million
if my husband is singing.
- Okay.
We know you're rich.
-I just meant he doesn't have
a musical bone in his body.
-♪ Carry on, my wayward son ♪
♪ There'll be peace
when you are done ♪
♪ Lay your weary head to rest ♪
♪ Don't you cry no more ♪
-Okay. Are you guys r--
Uh, what is going on?!
-Oh, my God!
-What is going on in here?!
-A-Are you guys
singing and dancing?!
-Did you all wear
rock-'n'-roll jumpsuits
in case this happened?
-No! Maybe.
-Why are you
in your underwear?!
-I got excited
and I pulled too hard.
-Okay. Well, you know what?
This is just the craziest thing
I've ever seen.
-Is it?
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Jack White!
-♪ Looks like you started ♪
♪ Something that
you cannot finish ♪
♪ Yeah, you started ♪
♪ Something that
you cannot finish ♪
♪ Yeah, looks like you
could buy some more time ♪
♪ Think you need
a couple more minutes ♪
♪ Yeah, I came to ya ♪
♪ On the back of
a twister storm ♪
♪ Ohh, I came to ya ♪
♪ On the back of
a twister storm ♪
♪ You know I got
something up my sleeve ♪
♪ Try to twist my arm ♪
♪ I got a brand-new truck ♪
♪ Three-tone, custom-made ♪
♪ Yeah, I got
a brand-new truck ♪
♪ Three-tone, custom-made ♪
♪ Yeah, I think
that's kind of funny ♪
♪ For a man who never
made the grade ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Not gonna start nothing ♪
♪ Nothing that I cannot finish ♪
♪ Yeah, don't start nothing ♪
♪ Yeah, but what I do
and how I do ♪
♪ And why I do it ♪
♪ It's all none of
your business ♪