AND NOW A MESSAGE FROM
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN.
GOOD EVENING!
GOOD EVENING
HELLO, MY FELLOW AMERICANS
AS I KEEP SAYING EVERY CHANCE I GET,
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF A
COLD, DARK WINTER.
THIS WINTER IS SO DARK
REPUBLICANS DON'T THINK YO
SHOULD VOTE.
I KNOW THIS VIRUS HAS DISRUPTED OUR LIVES,
IT'S CANCELED
HOLIDAYS, WEDDINGS, QUINCEANERAS,
GENDER REVEAL PARTIES,
WILD FIRES THAT STARTED
AS GENDER REVEAL PARTIES
WHATEVER THE HELL IS HAPPENING
WITH NOVAK DJOKOVIC.
I KNOW YOU'RE TIRED OF GETTING
EMAILS FROM YOUR KIDS' SCHOOL AT NIGHT SAYING
"OKAY, COME IN
TOMORROW
WE'RE FEELING LUCKY.
I KNOW EVERY TIME A STRANGER
BREATHES ON YOU, YOU THINK,
THAT'S IT.
I'M DEAD
AMERICA, I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THERE IS ONE SIMPLE THING
YOU
CAN DO TO MAKE THIS WHOLE VIRUS
GO AWAY.
STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN.
JUST STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN."
THINK ABOUT IT.
WHEN DID "SPIDER-MAN" COME OUT
DECEMBER 17th.
WHEN DID EVERY SINGLE PERSON GET
OMICRON?
THE WEEK AFTER DECEMBER 17th
STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN.
THAT'S REALLY ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
I YIELD THE REMAINDER OF MY TIME
FOR QUESTIONS.
YES?
I'M SORRY, DID YOU REALLY
JUST BLAME SPREAD THE ENTIRE
SPREAD OF OMICRON ON PEOPLE
SEEING "SPIDER-MAN?"
I DID, YES.
NEXT QUESTION?
DO YOU THINK ALL OF COVID
WILL END
IF PEOPLE STOP GOING TO THE
MOVIES
I DIDN'T SAY DON'T GO TO THE
I SAID STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN."
SEE ANYTHING ELSE.
I SAW THE FIRST HALF HOUR OF
"HOUSE OF GUCCI.
THAT'S MORE THAN ENOUGH MOVIE
FOR ANYONE
IS THIS THEORY BASED ON ANY
KIND OF DATA
YES
EVERYONE IN AMERICA HAS SEEN
SPIDER-MAN,"" LIKE, EIGHT TIMES."
EVERYONE IN AMERICA ALSO HAS
COVID.
STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN.
HAVE YOU SEEN "SPIDER-MAN?"
I COULDN'T GET TICKETS,
AND I'M ON THE STUBS' A-LIST
JILL AND I TRIED TO GO LAST
NIGHT AND THEY ONLY HAD ONE SEAT
LEFT IN THE FRONT ROW.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
MAKE JOE GO SEE "ENCANTO" ALONE
WHILE I SIT TWO INCHES FROM THE
SCREEN LIKE THIS
STOP SEEING "SPIDER-MAN.
BUT WHAT ABOUT EXPERTS WHO
SAY THAT THE REAL PROBLEM IS A
LACK OF TESTING?
OH, THEY TESTED "SPIDER-MAN."
IT GOT 98% ON AU GRATIN
POTATOES
HE MEANT TESTING FOR COVID.
YOU WANT TO KNOW IF YOU HAVE
COVID?
LOOK AT YOUR HAND.
ARE YOU STILL HOLDING A TICKET
THAT SAY
YOU RECENTLY WENT TO SEE
"SPIDER-MAN?
IF SO, THEN YOU HAVE COVID
ALL RIGHT
WELL, THEN, WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER
PROBLEMS
FACING AMERICA, LIKE INFLATION
SPIDER-MAN.
OKAY.
THEN WHY CAN'T DEMOCRATS PASS
THE VOTING RIGHTS BILL
DO YOU THINK PEOPLE CAN FOCUS
ON VOTING RIGHTS
WHEN SPIDER-MAN
AUNT MAY IS A FREAKIN' SMOKE
SHOW
MR. PRESIDENT, ISN'T THE REAL
REASON YOU CAN'T PASS THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT
BECAUSE MEMBERS OF
YOUR OWN PARTY REFUSE TO GET RID
OF THE FILIBUSTER?
IT'S TRUE
SPIDER-MAN HAS HIS VILLAINS.
I HAVE JOE MANCHIN AND
KYRSTEN SINEMA
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE IS IF ONE OF
SPIDER-MAN'S VILLAINS SAW
KYRSTEN SINEMA, THEY'S BE LIKE,
"HEY, HONEY, THAT OUTFIT IS A
LITTLE MUCH.
WHAT ABOUT THE RUSSIAN TROOPS
THAT ARE NOW SURROUNDING THE UKRAINIAN BORDER
PUSHING US TO
THE BRINK OF WORLD WAR III
I MEAN, IF THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE A JOB FOR SPIDER-MAN, I
DON'T KNOW WHAT DOES
OKAY
I GOT TIME FOR ONE MORE
QUESTION
YES, THE NERD.
MR. PRESIDENT, IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU WANT PEOPLE TO STOP SEEING
SPIDER-MAN."
THAT'S THE GENERAL IDEA
YEAH
DO YOU THINK THAT ELSEWHERE
IN THE MULTIVERSE,
THERE'S A
VERSION OF YOU THAT WANTS PEOPLE
TO SEE "SPIDER-MAN?"
FINALLY, A GOOD QUESTION!
I'VE ACTUALLY THOUGHT ABOUT THIS
A LOT.
I'VE CONSULTED WITH DR. FAUCI
AND DR. STRANGE.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL THERE ARE
AT LEAST THREE JOE BIDENS.
ONE OF THEM IS ME.
ONE OF THEM IS A JOE BIDEN THAT
LOST TO TRUMP.
THAT BIDEN HOSTS A SHOW ON CNBC
CALLED "T-BIRDS, TACOS AND
TRAINS."
AND THEN THERE'S A THIRD
JOE BIDEN THAT WAS THE GREATEST
PRESIDENT IN HISTORY
MY APPROVAL RATINGS ARE SKY
HIGH
I'M ACTUALLY SUPPORTED BY MY OWN PARTY,
AND I UNDERSTAND THE SHOW
"EUPHORIA.
I'M SORRY
YOU'RE NOW SAYING THAT WE'RE NOW
LIVING IN A SPIDER-MAN STYLE
MULTIVERSE
DOESN'T THAT MAKE MORE SENSE
THAT WHATEVER THE HELL OUR
CURRENT WORLD IS
I MEAN SERIOUSLY
SERIOUSLY.
COME ON!
SERIOUSLY, DON'T YOU WAKE UP
EVERY MORNING, LOOK AT THE NEWS
AND THINK THIS CAN'T BE RIGHT.
THIS IS ALL CRAZY.
PEOPLE GOT VACCINATED AND THE
PANDEMIC GOT WORSE
YOU HAVE TO WEAR A MASK AT A
RESTAURANT FOR THE TEN FEET UNTIL YOU SIT DOWN,
THEN YOU
TAKE IT OFF FOR THE WHOLE MEAL
UNLESS YOU GO TO THE BATHROOM
AND THEN YOU GOTTA PUT IT BACK
ON
IS THE COVID IN THE BATHROOM
HOW DOES ANY OF IT MAKE SENSE?
MR. PRESIDENT, ARE YOU OKAY
FOR THE FIRST TIME, HELL YES!
IT'S LIKE THE WEBS HAVE FALLEN
FROM MY EYES
I CAN FINALLY SEE.
WHEN YOUR TIME HAS COME, YOU
ARE READY.
OKAY.
WHO THE HELL IS THAT
I AM JOE BIDEN FROM THE REAL
UNIVERSE
THE TIME LINE YOU ARE ALL LIVING
IN IS ABOUT TO COLLAPSE.
YOU SEE, IT WAS CREATED AS A
JOKE STARTIN IN 2016
WHEN THE CHICAGO CUBS
WON THE WORLD SERIES,
AND NOW IT
SPIRALLED OUT OF CONTROL AND
COULD EXPLODE AT ANY MINUTE.
AM I THE PRESIDENT IN THIS
REAL WORLD
OF COURSE, NOT.
DO YOU THINK YOU WOULD LOSE FOUR TIMES
AND THEN FINALLY WIN WHEN
YOU WERE 78?
WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF US
ARE WE OKAY?
EVERYONE ON EARTH IS BETTER
OFF IN THE REAL WORLD
EXCEPT ONE
MAN NAMED PETE DAVIDSON.
HIS WORLD IS MAYBE MORE FUN FOR HIM,
NOW HURRY BEFORE THE PORTAL
CLOSES
I'LL COME BACK FOR YOU ALL.
I PROMISE.
RIGHT AFTER I PASS THE BUILD
BACK BETTER BILL
DUDE, EVEN IN THE REAL
UNIVERSE
THAT'S NOT PASSING
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -
ARIANA DeBOSE.
THANK YOU.
I AM SO HONORED TO BE HERE
TONIGHT.
WOW!
2022 HAS ALREADY BEEN AN
EXCITING YEAR.
I AM HOSTING SNL,
"" AND I WON A" GOLDEN GLOBE FOR MY ROLE AS
ANITA IN "WEST SIDE STORY.
SO NOW -- NOW NOT MANY PEOPLE
KNOW THIS,
BUT "WEST SIDE STORY" IS
ACTUALLY BASED ON ANOTHER
CLASSIC TALE OF STAR-CROSSED LOVERS,
"90 DAY FIANCE."
BUT IT IS GREAT TO BE HERE
REPRESENTING NOT ONLY THE LATINO COMMUNITY AS AN AFRO-LATINA,
BUT
ALSO THE BROADWAY COMMUNITY.
OBVIOUSLY -- OBVIOUSLY, BROADWAY
HAS BEEN
THROUGH A TOUGH COUPLE OF YEARS,
LAST PASS
BUT WE ARE A COMMUNITY THAT PERSEVERES,
AND I BELIEVE
BROADWAY CHANGES LIVES
I MEAN, HEY, IT CHANGED MINE
AND BROADWAY HAS THIS MAGICAL
ABILITY TO BRING PEOPLE
TOGETHER
AND I THINK WE CAN ALL USE A
LITTLE BROADWAY RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE -- MAYBE --
MAYBE A LITTLE SOMETHING FROM
WEST SIDE STORY.
HUH?
DID YOU SAY SING SONGS FROM
WEST SIDE STORY WITH
KATE McKINNON?
NO, BUT HI, KATE.
HI.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S MY FAVORITE SHOW.
I'VE
LOVED IT SINCE HIGH SCHOOL AND
BEFORE
- DID YOU LIKE IT?
- I DIDN'T SEE IT
I DON'T LEAVE THE HOUSE BECAUSE
OF COVID, AND ALSO I DON'T LEAVE
THE HOUSE.
WELL, IN THAT CASE, WHY DON'T
WE BRING OUT SOME STOOLS AND WE
CAN SING TOGETHER.
I DON'T THINK I EVEN REMEMBER
THE SONG
TONIGHT IN A FLAT, PLEASE.
* TONIGHT, TONIGH
IT ALL BEGAN TONIGHT *
* I SAW YOU AND THE
WORLD WENT AWAY *
ARIANA DeBOSE
* TONIGHT, TONIGH
THERE'S ONLY YOU TONIGHT *
* WHAT YOU ARE, WHAT YOU DO
WHAT YOU SAY *
- THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD, KATE.
- I'VE BEEN ON BROADWAY
- YOU HAVE?
- YEAH.
THE SIDEWALK
* I FEEL PRETTY
OH, SO PRETTY *
AND WITTY, AND GAY *
* AND I PIT
ANY GIRL WHO *
* ISN'T ME TODAY
SEE THE PRETTY GIRL *
* IN THAT MIRROR
THER
WHAT MIRROR, WHERE *
* WHO CAN THA
ATTRACTIVE GIRL BE *
* WHICH WHAT WHERE WHO
SUCH A PRETTY FACE *
* SUCH A PRETTY DRESS
- SUCH A PRETTY SMILE *
- SUCH A PRETTY ME
I LOVE THAT SONG.
YOU
I MEAN, I MEAN, JUST SINGING IT
MAKES ME FEEL PRETTY
WHICH IS CRAZY BECAUSE JUST LIKE AN HOUR AGO,
WE WERE BOTH
IN OUR
SWEATPANTS SPOONING OUR
13-YEAR-OLD CATS
I WASN'T DOING THAT
ME NEITHER.
- MAMBO
- MAMBO, GO *
YOUR TURN, KATE
NO, THEY KNOW I DANCE
* COULD BE
WHO KNOWS *
* THERE'S SOMETHING
DUE ANY DAY *
* I WILL KNOW RIGHT AWAY
SOON AS IT SHOWS *
* IT MAY COME CANNONBALLING
DOWN THROUGH THE SKY *
* GLEAM IN ITS EY
BRIGHT AS A ROSE *
* I LIKE TO BE IN AMERICA
OKAY BY ME IN AMERICA *
* EVERYTHING FREE IN AMERICA
FOR A SMALL FEE IN AMERICA *
FINAL
* TODAY
THE MINUTES SEEM LIKE HOURS *
* THE HOURS GO SO SLOWLY
AND STILL THE SKY IS LIGHT *
* OH MOON, GROW BRIGHT
AND MAKE THIS ENDLESS DAY *
* ENDLESS NIGHT
TONIGHT *
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
BLEACHERS ARE HERE
SO STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK
HAPPY SATURDAY, NANA
WELCOME BACK TO NBA ON TNT
HALFTIME
NETS AND KINGS ERNIE JOHNSON,
JOINED BY MY PALS,
CHARLES BARKLEY AND KENNY SMITH.
SHAQ IS UNFORTUNATELY OUT SICK
YEAH, HE SAYS HE'S GOT
SOMETHING CALLED SHAQ FLU, BUT
LET'S CALL IT WHAT IT IS
THAT MAN GOT COVID
HEY, HEY, HEY, YOU DON'T KNOW
THAT CHARLES
FILLING IN FOR SHAQ IS ANOTHER
BIG MAN, YAO MING.
YES
YAO IS HERE.
HELLO.
YAO, YOU ARE ENORMOUS, MAN.
YOU KNOW, BEFORE THE SHOW, I
WATCHED THIS MAN EAT AN ENTIRE
PUMPKIN.
STEM AND ALL
YEAH.
JUST A SNACK FOR Y'ALL
WELL, SPEAKING OF COVID,
BEFORE THE GAME, THE KINGS
ENTIRE TEAM TESTED POSITIVE
ALONG WITH MOST OF THEIR
COACHING STAFF AND TRAINERS AND
THEY WERE FORCED TO FIND
REPLACEMENTS VERY QUICK, BUT
THEY DID AND AT THE HALF, IT'S
NETS LEAD THE KINGS 268-1.
CHARLES WHY CAN'T SACRAMENTO
GET ANYTHING GOING TONIGHT
WELL, IN MY OPINION, THE
BIGGEST THING TO ME IS THAT THE
KINGS DON'T HAVE ANY NBA PLAYERS
ON THEIR TEAM WHEREAS THE NETS
DO
YEAH, I WROTE DOWN THE SAME
THING.
YOU CAN SEE HOW THE KINGS
LACK OF NBA PLAYERS IS
REFLECTED IN THE SCORE
YEAH, THE KINGS PLAYERS
TONIGHT ARE ALL FANS OR ARENA
SUPPORT STAFF.
ANY THOUGHTS
ANY THOUGHTS, YAO?
THEY'RE TINY PEOPLE
TOO SMALL.
WELL SAID, YAO.
LET'S LOOK AT A MATCH UP HERE.
AT FORWARD, YOU'VE GOT
JAMES HARDEN FOR THE NETS AND
EQUIPMENT MANAGE
DOUG MCCORMICK FOR THE KINGS
LOOK AT THE NUMBERS, OKAY
McCORMACK IS JUST GETTING
OUTPLAYED OUT THERE AND THE TWO
ASTHMA ATTACKS DIDN'T HELP
THAT'S BEEN THE CASE FOR MANY
KINGS PLAYERS TONIGHT.
HANNA DALTON IS COURTSIDE WITH
ONE OF THEM NOW.
HANNA!
I'M HERE WITH RILEY BECKWITH,
WHAT POSITION DID YOU PLAY
TONIGHT?
LEFT SIDE
NOT THE BEST FIRST HALF FOR
THE KINGS.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE OUT ON THE
COURT?
YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
I'M KIND OF WINDED
WAS WORKING HARD OUT THERE
YOU'RE TALL.
HOW TALL ARE YOU
5'7."
AWESOME, YEAH
YEAH, LOOK, WE CAME TO PLAY
TONIGHT.
I WAS CONFIDENT GOIN
IN BECAUSE I PLAYED PICKUP AT MY
GYM WITH OTHER WHITE GUYS MY
SIZE, BUT BEING OUT THERE
AGAINST THE NETS
I REALIZED THAT BASKETBALL IS AN
IMPOSSIBLE SPORT PLAYED BY
GIANTS AND GODS.
WELL, GOOD LUCK IN THE SECOND
HALF
THANK YOU SO MUCH
I WON'T BE HERE.
I'M SCARED SO I'M GOING HOME
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WELL, NOT EVERY KINGS PLAYER
HAS BEEN SHUT OUT.
ALICIA MILLER MANAGED TO PUT ONE
ON THE BOARD FOR SACRAMENTO.
SHE JOINS US NOW
ALICIA, I UNDERSTAND YOU CAME TO
THE GAME WITH SOME FRIENDS AND
THEN YOU WERE ASKED TO PLAY.
YEAH.
ISN'T THAT WILD?
THIS IS LIKE THE CRAZIEST GIRLS'
NIGHT EVER
AND YOU MADE A FREE THROW
I DID
I DID.
IT WAS UNDERHAND, TOO.
YOU WERE ALSO CALLED FOR
TRAVELING 39 TIMES
I KNOW.
I KEEP FORGETTING TO BOUNCE THE
BALL.
YEAH.
BUT THEN YOU GOT EJECTED FOR
TAKING A SELFIE WITH BLAKE
GRIFFIN DURING THE GAME.
I HAD TO.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF I WAS GOING TO
SEE HIM AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE TO SHOOT YOUR
SHOT
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
BUT GO SACS!
KEVIN DURANT WITH 178
AND MOST PLAYERS CRYING ON THE
COURT AT ONCE.
SIX KINGS PLAYERS WERE CRYING AT
THE SAME TIME.
I'M SORRY, Y'ALL.
I JUST GOT A GLIMPSE OF YAO'S
HANDS.
IT IS HUGE, MAN.
PUT IT UP TO MINE.
LET ME SEE
LOOK AT THIS
THE MAN HAS LIKE THE IRON GIANT.
NO, NO, NOT MY FACE, MAN.
NOT MY FACE.
GET OUT OF HERE.
THAT'S CUTE
WELL, LET'S GO RIGHT TO THE
SOURCE OF THE KINGS' ISSUES
TONIGHT.
TEMPORARY COACH PATRICK BEAMUS
JOINS US LIVE.
NOW YOU COACHED AT LITTLE
DUNKER'S DAY CAMP, HUH
THAT'S CORRECT.
I COACHED MY SON'S TEAM.
HE -- HE WAS ACTUALLY DRAFTED,
TOO.
HE'S BEEN GUARDING KYRIE IRVING.
OH, YEAH.
I THINK WE'VE GOT A PICTURE OF
THAT
YEAH, YEAH.
HE ACTUALLY GOT KIND OF HURT
THERE.
I HOPE WE BOTH GET COVID SO WE
CAN LEAVE.
THAT SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT
COACH?
KENNY, HOW CAN SACK TOWN PULL
OFF A WIN TONIGHT.
I SAY IF THE KINGS PLAYER HAS
SOME SORT OF SPACE JAM LIKE MY
MAGICAL SHOE SITUATION, THEY
MIGHT BE ABLE TO ESTABLISH A
WIN.
CHARLES?
MY PREDICTION IS I'M OUT
100 GRAND.
BECAUSE I BET ON THESE CLOWNS TO
WIN.
WHY DO I DO THIS TO MYSELF
I DON'T KNOW
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE'VE GOT TO TAKE A BREAK.
YAO, YOU WANT TO THROW US TO
COMMERCIAL, BUD?
GOOD-BYE.
YAO, MAN, I LOVE YOU, MAN.
COME ON, LET'S GET THIS MAN
ANOTHER PUMPKIN, MAN
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
THIS WEEK, PEACOCK DROPPED
THE TRAILER FOR "BEL AIR,"
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER WILL SMITH'S
MODERN, DRAMATIC REIMAGINING
OF
THE "FRESH PRINCE" STORY
THIS TOWN WILL MAKE YOU
FORGET WHERE YOU CAME FROM
NOW WE'RE PROUD TO DEBUT THE
NEXT '90s SHOW ABOUT THE BLACK EXPERIENCE
TO BE
GIVEN A SERIOUS, HIGH-STAKES
REMAKE
CHICAGO
PEOPLE FROM OUTSIDE CALL IT CHIRAQ,
BUT I CALL IT HOME
AROUND HERE, AIN'T NO GOOD NEWS
ON THE NEWSPAPER'S PAGE.
ONLY ADVANTAGE I'VE GOT.
MY MIND.
THAT DON'T COUNT FOR MUCH IN
THESE STREETS
BECAUSE OUT HERE,
YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE YOUR OWN
NAME
FROM EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
JALIL WHITE
AND KEVIN FINLEY, WRITER OF THE "FAMILY MATTERS"
EPISODE.
EURKEL
ACCIDENTALLY SWITCHES BODIES
WITH THE PRESIDENT
TINA
THERE'S ONLY ONE GIRL FOR ME,
YO
WHO
LAURA WINSLOW?
THE BOUGIE NEIGHBOR GIRL
THE GOOFY CHARACTERS YOU LOVED IN THE '90s
WITH
ABSOLUTELY NONE OF THE FUN OR
CHARM.
FLOWERS, MY PET
PLEASE, IT AIN'T LIKE THAT
BETWEEN US
I'M NOT YOUR PET
I LOVE YOU.
DEAF
NOW GET THE HELL OUT
OF HERE!
YOU WERE HARD ON THAT BOY,
DAD.
NO, LIFE NOT A BEEN EASY FOR
HIM.
FATHER'S GONE, MOTHER'S A DRUNK.
WHEN YOU GONNA STOP WORKING
ON THIS STUPID ROBOT
AND MAKE SOME
MONEY FOR THIS FAMILY?
WHAT FAMILY
I RAISED A DAMN NERD.
A YOUNG GENIUS ALONE IN THE
WORLD.
YOU DON'T LOVE HER.
NO, BUT I LOVE HOW SHE MAKE
IT CLAP.
OH, MY NOSE
DID I DO THAT?
WHAT IF I SHOT YOU IN THE FACE
DROP THE GUN, STEVE
"ROLLING STONE" RAVES "FAMILY
MATTERS" IS THE NUMBER ONE WORST
CHOICE FOR A SITCOM TO MODERNIZE LIKE THIS,
WHILE "ENTERTAINMENT
WEEKLY" ADDS THIS GIF OF
KEVIN HART BOOKING'S HORRIFIED
DOWN
THE STEVE URKEL I KNOW IS WAY
TOO SMART FOR THAT NONSENSE.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
OUT HERE
SO, I'VE BEEN A CHICAGO COP FOR
20 YEARS
WHERE'S THE GIRL
GO TO HELL, PIG
PIG
BITCH
IF YOU CONTINUE DOWN THIS PATH,
YOU'RE GOING TO WIND UP
DEAD OR LOCKED UP BY YOUR 18th
BIRTHDAY
AIN'T NOBODY GOING TO CARE.
I AIN'T GOT A FAMILY.
YOU'RE WRONG, STEVE
THE WINSLOWS ARE YOUR FAMILY
AND FAMILY [ BLEEP ] MATTERS
URKEL STREAMING THIS WEEK ON
PEACOCK.
AIR AND EVERYTHING'S DEAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS
IT'S TIME FOR THE MOST
IMPORTANT DAY OF YOUR DAUGHTER'S
LIFE: HER HIGH SCHOOL WINTER
FORMAL
AND IF YOU WANT HER TO HAVE
AN AMAZING TIME CALL US, RON AND
DONNA LA COSTA
OUR FORMAL EMPORIUM IS YOUR
ONE-STOP SHOP FOR ALL YOUR
DAUGHTER'S SCHOOL DANCE NEEDS.
YES
WE GOT CORSAGES FRESH FROM OUR
GARDEN
WE'VE GOT DRESSES THAT ARE AS
PRETTY AS SHE IS, DEPENDING ON
THE GIRL
HEY, IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
YOUR DAUGHTER HAVING SEX AFTER
THE DANCE, DON'T BE.
WE HAVE THE PERFECT SOLUTION
SHE CAN TAKE OUR SON DONOVAN.
BECAUSE DONOVAN WOULDN'T KNOW
WHERE TO START
OH, COME ON
WE'LL ALSO PROVIDE A
PHOTOGRAPHER WHO WILL TAKE
GORGEOUS PHOTOS.
AND A LIMOUSINE THAT WE MADE
OUT OF TWO GORGEOUS TOYOTA
COROLLAS
AND WITH OUR SWEATY SON, YOUR
DAUGHTER IS GUARANTEED TO REMAIN
UNPENETRATED
AND THAT'S A LA COSTA
PROMISE.
WELL, MAYBE ONE DAY
NO, HE'S NOT GOING TO TRY
ANYTHING
THE DUDE GETS NERVOUS SHAKING
HIS GRANDMA'S HAND
AND HE'S A LAZY WIPER
YOU CAN SMELL IT
AND IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT GO ON AT THE
AFTERPARTY, DONOVAN'S GOT YOU
COVERED.
HE MEDICALLY CAN'T STAY UP UNTIL
10:00 P.M.
WHEN I GET TIRED I FREAK OUT.
YUP
DONOVAN IS ONE OF THOSE KIDS WHO
HAS A HUGE COMPUTER AND TWO UGLY
FRIENDS.
SHOUT OUT TO SCOTTY AND
GIVEN.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT OUR
OFF-PUTTING BABY BOY
LET'S TALK TO SOME SATISFIED
CUSTOMERS.
I RENTED A DRESS, AND I GOT A
COMPLIMENT FROM JASON MAZINSKI
I RENTED A LIMO AND ME AND MY
FRIENDS FELT LIKE ROCK STARS
I RENTED DONOVAN AND ON THE
WAY THERE HE LIKE SAT UP FRONT
WITH HIS DRIVER AND HE HAD
CRUMBS ON HIS LIPS THE WHOLE
NIGHT.
YEAH, OUR BOY'S ALWAYS GOT
SOMETHING ON HIS LIPS.
YEAH.
GARY
ZOOM IN ON THOSE LIPS.
YEAH, ZOOM IN
COME ON!
WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT IS THAT
IS THA
CREAM CHEESE
NO, I THINK MY MOUTH IS JUST
LIKE THIS.
OH, WHO IS GIVING YOU CREAM
CHEESE
I'M SORRY, SWEETHEART.
WERE YOU STILL GOING ON ABOUT
SOMETHING OVER THERE
YEAH.
HE, LIKE, DIDN'T DANCE THE WHOLE
NIGHT AND THEN HE WENT NUTS TO
GET LOW.
* THERE'S SWEAT DROPPIN DOW
MY BALLS *
AND THEN HE GOT TOO HOT AND
CHANGED INTO LIKE
LOS POLLOS HERMANOS T SHIRT.
LIKE, I MEAN WHAT EVEN IS THAT
I TOLD YOU A MILLION TIMES,
IT'S THE RESTAURANT FROM
"BREAKING BAD.
IF SOMEHOW YOU'RE STILL NOT
CONVINCED TO THINK OUR SON AS
SOME SECRET CASANOVA
MAY WE DIRECT YOUR ATTENTION T
HIS CRITICAL SWAMP ASS
OH, NO.
DON'T SPIN ME AROUND
GARY, GARY ZOOM IN ON HIS WET
LITTLE ASS
GARY, ZOOM, LOOK AT THAT.
ZOOM, GARY, ZOOM!
IT'S SOUPY
IT'S WET
IT'S SO SOUPY.
WE DON'T MEAN TO EMBARRASS
YOU,
DONOVAN, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
PISSED YOURSELF FROM THE BACK.
HOW DID HE END UP LIKE THIS
WELL YOU SEE, PARENTING IS
LIKE BASKETBALL.
AND I DRANK WHILE I WAS
PREGNANT
AND THAT'S A LA COSTA
PROMISE.
WHAT IS
NO, NO, NO.
DO NOT PUT THAT ON
OH, I LOVE THIS SONG!
*
SO STOP BY TODAY.
WE DO NOT HAVE A WEBSITE, AND WE
WE BARELY HAVE A PHONE
GOOD MORNING
I'D LIKE TO WELCOME EVERYONE TO
CITY HALL.
AS YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN A TOUGH
FEW YEARS FOR NEW YORK,
BUT WE
HAVE A NEW MAYOR NOW,
AND HE
HUNGRY
BUT I WILL WARN YOU, THE MAYOR
DOES NOT LIKE CHAOS.
IF YOU ALL ACT UP, I WILL COME
FOR YOU.
OKAY
NOW PLEASE CLAP FOR YOUR NEW MAYOR,
THE FRISKIEST UNCLE A YOUR BARBECUE,
LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, ERIC ADAMS!
SEE
SMILE
GEN
SHE
SACK
AFTER
WHAT'S UP, NEW YORK
IT'S YOUR BOY -- YOUR HOMETOWN
HERO, ERIC ADAMS,
AND YOU ALL
FEEL THAT?
NEW YORK IS BACK, BABY
THIS CITY'S NEVER HAD A MAYOR
WITH SO MUCH SWAGGER BEFORE.
I MEAN
YOU ALL SEE ME OUTSIDE
THE PEA COATS, THE SCARF, THE
SHINE OR THE BALDY,
YOU CAN TELL
I HAVE SWAGGER
IT KEEPS ME HEALTHY.
SEE, THE CITY'S BEEN SUFFERING
FROM WHAT I CALL, A SWAGLESS"
EXISTENCE.
YOU ONLY HAD NO SWAGGER.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE GETTING SICK
NO OFFENSE, LET'S JUST BE REAL
I HAVEN'T BEEN SICK IN OVER 60
YEARS.
I'M MUSCULAR, I'M VEGAN,
AND I GET THAT THING THING EVERY DAY
BEFORE BREAKFAST, ALL RIGHT?
YOU CAN'T START THE DAY WITHOUT
FINISHING FIRST, YOU UNDERSTAND
ME
I'M JUST PLAYING, UNLESS YOU
LIKE THAT.
OKAY
LET'S GET THESE QUESTIONS GOING
SO WE CAN FIX THIS CITY.
BITCH UP FROM NEW YORK
LET'S GO
NO!
I DO NOT DO CHAOS IN MY CITY,
OKAY
I TOLD YOU ALL THAT.
I WAS A POLICE OFFICER FOR OVER
70 YEARS
IF I GET STARTLED, I START
BEATING PEOPLE ASSES
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
OKAY, EXCUSE ME
THIS MAN AIN'T BILL de BLASIO.
AND HE WILL KICK YOUR ASS
NOW, NOW, SHE'S JOKING, BUT
SHE'S FROM THE BRONX, SO IS SHE?
OKAY.
QUESTIONS?
LET'S START WITH THE SQUIRREL UP
FRONT.
GO AHEAD, SQUIRREL
ME?
OKAY
UH, MR. MAYOR, YOU SAID YOU
INTEND TO KEEP SCHOOLS OPEN
DESPITE SKYROCKETING COVID
NUMBERS AND OUTCRY FROM
TEACHERS
DOES THAT STILL MAKE SENSE
THANK YOU, NUT-NUT,
LITTLE SQUIRREL MAN
ASKED A REALLY GOOD QUESTION,
YES.
KIDS NEED TO STAY IN SCHOOL,
LEARN ABOUT LIFE
THERE ARE TOO MANY SWAGLESS
PARENTS OUT THERE
GIVING THEIR
KIDS NO SWAGGER AT HOME
AND AS A
MAYOR THAT'S SO SAUCY,
JUST
DRIPPING IN SWAG, OH
IT HURTS MY HEART.
IT'S DANGEROUS FOR KIDS TO BE
OUT THERE WITH NO SWAG
LET ME TELL YOU A STORY ABOUT A
BOY I WENT TO SCHOOL WITH,
LITTLE TIMMY
NOW, THE BOY HAD NO SWAG
DUMBASS SHOES, DUMBASS SHIRT,
DUMBASS PANTS.
ONE DAY LITTLE TIMMY WALKED HIS
DUSTY ASS UP TO THE FINEST GIRL
IN SCHOOL, TIFFANY
SHE WAS FINE, Y'ALL.
LITTLE TIMMY LOOKED HER RIGHT IN
HER EYE AND -- BOOM!
DROPPED DEAD
THE LACK OF SWAGGER STOPPED THE
BOY'S HEART.
IT WAS SO SAD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT SHAKESPEARE SAID,
"IF DOTH LACKING THE
SWAGGER, WOTH FOR ART THOU,
HEART SHALL BEAT" OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
BITCH, I'M FROM NEW YORK
DOES THAT ANSWER YOUR QUESTION
NOT REALLY, NO.
GOOD.
NEXT QUESTION.
WAIT, MR. MAYOR
NO, NO, NO, NO.
BABY, EXCUSE ME.
LET ME ASK YOU ONE MORE
QUESTION
NO, NO, NO
THAT'S HOW Y'ALL SOUND
THIS AIN'T THE C TRAIN, OKAY
WE DO HAVE RULES HERE
GO DEEP
MISS LADY, GO AHEAD.
MR. MAYOR, LAST WEEK, YOU
SAID "LOW SKILL WORKERS
DON'T
HAVE THE SKILLS TO SIT IN AN
OFFICE."
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT
I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT THAT
BACK UP PRINCESS PEACH
AND CONGRATULATIONS ON ESCAPING
THAT CASTLE.
LOOK, THAT QUOTE WAS TAKEN OUT
OF CONTEXT
LET ME CLARIFY
BY UNSKILLED WORKERS, I MEANT
FOLKS WITH TRASH JOBS --
I MEAN,
TRASH LIVES.
WAIT, NO
WHAT I MEAN IS
IF YOU WERE BETTER AT LIFE, YOU
HAVE A DESK.
NO
WAIT
YOU ALL MISHEARING ME AND YOU'RE
MAKING ME MISQUOTE MYSELF.
LISTEN -- I MEAN -- LOOK AT OUR
SOCIETY, OKAY?
THERE'S KINGS AND THERE'S QUEENS
AND THEN EVERYONE ELSE BELOW THAT,
THE DIRTY PEOPLE
IS THAT BETTER FOR YOU
I DON'T LIKE HOW YOU ALL MAKING
ME FEEL ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW
I MEAN, I WAS A COP FOR 97
YEARS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME
SHOW ME SOME RESPECT
NEXT QUESTION, WEIRD EMINEM.
HAIR
MR. MAYOR, WHAT QUALIFICATIONS
DOES YOUR BROTHER HAVE TO BE THE
HEAD OF YOUR SECURITY DETAIL
AND
ISN'T THAT NEPOTISM?
THANK YOU FOR THE QUESTION,
SLIM SHADY
NOW YOU ALL KEEP ASKING ABOUT MY
BROTHER LIKE YOU ALL CAN KICK
HIS ASS OR SOMETHING
LISTEN, I WAS A COP FOR OVER 222
YEARS.
I TRUST MY BROTHER
WE GOT A LOT OF SECRETS
TOGETHER, FAIR, TOO.
LET'S NOT FORGET JFK APPOINTED
HIS BROTHER.
WHY?
BECAUSE THE MAN HAS SWAGGER.
I COULD BE YOUR JFK, NEW YORK.
I'M OUT HERE LOOKING FOR MY
MARILYN MONROE
SHOUT OUT.
BUT UNLIKE JFK, I'M NOT GOING
GET POPPED IN THE HEAD
I'M GOING TO RECEIVE SOME.
OKAY, THAT'S MY STAFF WAVING AT
ME SAYING I SHOULD NOT HAVE MADE
THAT JOKE.
AND THAT'S FAIR. I DO APOLOGIZE
UNLESS YOU LIKE
THAT
I'LL
LEAVE YOU WITH THIS, NEW YORK.
YOU ALL INCLUDE BLACK
PAUL BUNYAN HANDS, OKAY?
WE'RE GOING TO BEAT THIS VIRUS
TOGETHER, I BELIEVE THAT
PLUS, YOU KNOW WHAT RHYMES WITH
COUGH?
TOUGH.
I MEAN, IT DOESN'T, BUT IT
SHOULD
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, I THINK
COVID KNOWS BETTER THAN TO RUN
UP ON SOMEBODY LIKE ME
PLEASE, COVID,
I WOULD LOVE
THAT
COVID-19 IS WELCOME
ANYTIME IN
NEW YORK CITY AND YOU CAN PRINT
THAT,
OKAY.
MAYBE LET'S NOT WELCOME THE VIRUS,
BUT THANK YOU SO
MUCH, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU.
LET'S HAVE -- LET'S HAVE A GOOD
FOUR YEARS, EVERYBODY.
BITCH, I'M FROM NEW YORK
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BLEACHERS!
How Dare You Want More
I CAN'T IMAGINE IT
PACK MY SUITCASE U
'TIL I CAN'T BEAR IT *
* WHO AM I WITHOU
THIS WEIGHT ON MY SHOULDER
OH GOD I'M DYIN' TO KNOW
BUT HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE *
* HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
PREACHER PREACHER'S CALLIN
FROM THE FLOOR *
* HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
* MAN OF SECRET
TWO LIVES THAT
HE'S BEEN LIVING IN *
* STOLEN IDENTITY
STOLEN DREAMIN
WHO IS HE IF HE'D JUST G
AND TELL IT LIKE IT IS *
* I'LL BET HE'S
DYIN' TO KNO
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE *
* PREACHER PREACHER
CALLIN' FROM THE FLOOR
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE *
THESE STEPS OF FAITH
SO EASY FOR HER BUT *
Out of mind, out of sight, I'm trying to find out
Who is she without all of this carryin' fear
OH GOD SHE'S STILL MY MOTHER
AND STILL MY WHEEL YEAH *
* STILL MY MOTHER
STILL MY WHEEL YEAH
STILL MY MOTHE
CRYIN' OUT *
* HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
PREACHER PREACHE
CALLIN' FROM THE FLOOR *
* HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
HEY LONELY WANTS
TO STAY FOREVER *
* BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DO A LITTLE BETTER
YEAH TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DO A LITTLE BETTER *
* YEAH TONIGHT WE'RE GONN
DO A LITTLE BETTER
HEY LONELY WANTS T
TEAR US DOWN NOW *
* BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DROWN THE SOUND OUT
BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DROWN THE SOUND OUT *
* YEAH TONIGHT WE'RE GONN
DROWN IT OUT *
* WELL HOW DARE YOU WANT MORE
WELL HOW DARE YO
WANT MORE *
* HEY LONELY WANT
TO STAY FOREVER
BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DO A LITTLE BETTER *
* YEAH TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
* HEY LONELY WANT
TO TEAR US DOWN NOW
BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DROWN THE SOUND OUT *
* YEAH TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA
DROWN THE SOUND OUT
AND TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA *
* DROWN IT OUT
IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE
*
THANK YOU
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE
WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
AND I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, JUST LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE, PRESIDENT BIDEN'S NEW
YEAR'S RESOLUTION FELL APART IN
THE THIRD WEEK OF JANUARY.
THE SUPREME COURT STRUCK DOWN
HIS VACCINE MANDATE, THE VOTING
RIGHTS BILL GOT BLOCKED AN
HIS APPROVAL RATING IS SO LOW
HE'S GONE INTO POWER SAVE MODE
BUT I WILL POINT OUT THERE WAS
ANOTHER PRESIDENT WHO HAD A
DISASTROUS START TO HIS FIRST
TERM, YET HE BECAME AN
INSPIRATION TO GENERATIONS OF
REPUBLICANS TO THIS DAY.
I'M TALKING, OF COURSE, ABOUT
JEFFERSON DAVIS.
PRESIDENT OF THE CONFEDERACY
AND THERE ARE STILL STATUES OF
HIM IN 10 DIFFERENT STATES,
WHICH, COME TO THINK OF IT, IS
PROBABLY
WHY THE VOTING RIGHTS STUFF
ISN'T WORKING OUT.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS I THINK BIDEN
JUST NEEDS MORE TIME
YOU KNOW, HE MAY BE MORE OF AN
ACQUIRED TASTE
AND UNFORTUNATELY, MOST
AMERICANS RECENTLY LOST THEIR
SENSE OF TASTE
PRESIDENT BIDEN GAVE A SPEECH
IN ATLANTA WHERE HE CALLED ON
THE SENATE TO PASS TWO VOTING
RIGHTS BILLS TO SAY I'M TIRED OF
BEING QUIET.
AND TO PROVE IT HE TOOK A
20-MINUTE STANDING NAP
MINORITY LEADER, MITCH
McCONNELL, SEEN HERE, LOSING THE
BATTLE WITH HIS BREAKFAST
BURRITO, CRITICIZED PRESIDENT
BIDEN'S SPEECH ON VOTING RIGHTS
CALLING IT "BENEATH HIS OFFICE."
COINCIDENTALLY, "BENEATH HIS
OFFICE" IS ALSO WHERE McCONNELL
BURIES THE HOMELESS MEN HE HUNTS
FOR SPORT.
FUN FACT.
REPUBLICANS ARE BEING
CRITICIZED FOR BLOCK THE VOTING
RIGHTS BILL, BUT OF COURSE,
REPUBLICANS DON'T WANT VOTING
RIGHTS BECAUSE IF VOTING WAS
FAIR THEY'D LOSE
IT'S THE SAME REASON I KEEP MY
BASKETBALL HOOP LOWER TO EIGHT
FEET
'CAUSE WITH THE HELP OF A SMALL
LADDER, I CAN DUNK
BUT IF THERE'S ANY SILVER LINING
TO VOTER SUPPRESSION IS THAT
WE'LL NEVER HAVE TO HEAR
REPUBLICANS TRY TO APPEAL TO
BLACK VOTERS
BECAUSE NO ONE WANTS TO HEAR
TED CRUZ SAY "FO' SHIZZEL.
FRANKLY, NO ONE WANTS TO HEAR ME
SAY IT EITHER.
IT'S TOO LATE, IT'S ALREADY A
GIF.
LEADER OF THE OATHKEEPERS
STEWART RHODES HAS BEEN ARRESTED
AND CHARGED WITH SADITIOUS
CONSPIRACY IN CONNECTION WITH
THE JANUARY 6th ATTACK
I DON'T KNOW, HE LOOKS PRETTY
REMORSEFUL
HOPEFULLY HE CAN PATCH THINGS
UP
YEAH
THAT WASN'T AN EYE JOKE.
I WAS BEIN
GENUINE.
RHODES IS BEING ACCUSED OF
MESSAGING HIS RIGHT-WING GROUP
WITH INSTRUCTIONS ON HOW TO
USE FORCE TO ATTACK THE CAPITOL.
AUTHORITIES KNEW THE MESSAGES
WERE FROM RHODES BECAUSE THEY
ALL BEGAN WITH "ARGG, MATEY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT THAT WAS
THAT WASN'T AN EYE JOKE AT ALL.
IT WASN'T AN EYE JOKE.
NO.
DURING A SENATE COMMITTE
HEARING, DR. ANTHONY FAUCI WAS
HEARD ON A HOT MIKE CALLING
SENATOR ROBERT MARSHAL A MORON
REPLIED MARSHALL, "HEY, WHAT
DOES THAT WORD MEAN?
POPE FRANCIS SAID THIS WEEK
THAT GETTING VACCINATED AGAINST
COVID IS A MORAL OBLIGATION
ESPECIALLY SINCE PRIESTS WORK SO
CLOSELY WITH KIDS.
THAT WASN'T AN EYE JOKE
DELTA AIRLINES SAID COVID
SURGE COST THEM AFTER 8,000
EMPLOYEES CAUGHT CORONAVIRUS,
WHICH WOULD NEVER HAPPEN TO
SPIRIT AIRLINES BECAUSE WHEN YOU
FLY SPIRIT, THEY KEEP THE
WINDOWS OPEN
ROBERT DURST, THE NEW YORK REAL
ESTATE HEIR WHO MURDERED AND
DISMEMBERED HIS NEIGHBOR HAS
DIED IN PRISON
DURST WILL BE REMEMBERED AS NEW
YORK'S FOURTH WORST REAL ESTATE
HEIR
THE LATE MAYA ANGELOU HAS
BECOME THE WOMAN FEATURED ON THE
QUARTER.
WHICH IS NOT WHAT BLACK PEOPLE
MEAN WHEN WE DEMAND CHANGE
GOOGLE IS CLAIMING THAT
APPLE'S PRACTICE OF USING BLUE
BUBBLES IN THEIR IMESSAGE APP TO
HIGHLIGHT OTHER USERS LEADS TO
PEER PRESSURING AND OF ANDROID
USERS.
WHILE APPLE SAYS, ANDORID USERS
CAN SOLVE THE PROBLEM BY NOT
BEING SO DUMB AND POOR
PRINCE ANDREW WHO FACES
CHARGES OF SEXUAL ABUSE HAS BEEN
STRIPPED OF HIS ROYAL AND
MILITARY DUTIES BY QUEEN
ELIZABETH.
IT'S AN UNPRECEDENTED CASE O
AN ADULT STRIPPING PRINCE
ANDREW
YEAH, YEAH, ROYAL DUTY.
DOMINO'S IS REDUCING THE
NUMBER OF CHICKEN WINGS INCLUDED
IN THEIR MEALS, AND I WISH I
KNEW THAT BEFORE I HAD MY
DELIVERY GUY FIRED FOR STEALING.
CALLED THE GREATEST UBER DRIVER
EVER AFTER HE AND HIS TEENAGE
PASSENGER GOT STUCK IN A
SNOWSTORM AND HE GOT A HOTEL
ROOM SO SHE WOULD BE SAFE.
COSINCDENTALLY, THE WORST UBER
DRIVER EVER ALSO BROUGHT HIS
PASSENGER TO A HOTEL ROOM.
SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE THAT LETS
USERS GET BEEN TACO EVERY DAY
FOR $10 A MONTH, WHICH KIND OF
SOUNDS LIKE AN INSULT AT A RAP
BATTLE
THIS BITCH SO FAT HE GOT A
SUBSCRIPTION TO TACOS.
ELMO WAS TRENDING LAST WEEK
AFTER CLIPS OF HIS FEUD WITH A
PET ROCK NAMED ROCCO WENT VIRAL.
HERE TO COMMENT IS ELMO.
HI, EVERYBODY
HELLO, MICHAEL
* LA-LA-LA-LA
LA-LA-LA-LA *
WELL, THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE, ELMO
OF COURSE
SNL IS MAY FAVORITE.
MAYBE ONE DAY ELMO CAN HELP?
MAYBE
YEAH, WHY NOT?
ELMO, EVERYONE'S BEEN TALKING
ABOUT YOUR BEEF WITH YOUR FRIEND
ZOE'S PET ROCK, ROCCO.
THERE ARE ALL THESE CLIPS OF YOU
GOING AROUND GOING CRAZY
UNHINGED RANTS ABOUT HOW ROCCO
IS NOT REAL.
OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, LOOK, ELMO ADMIT, ELMO
OVERREACTED.
AND ELMO HAS ALREADY APOLOGIZED
IN A LONG INSTAGRAM POST
ELMO READY TO MOVE ON.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT TO HEAR,
ELMO BECAUSE WE ACTUALLY HAVE A
SURPRISE GUEST THAT WE'RE GOING
TO BRING OUT
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ROCCO!
WHAT!
WHY DOES ROCCO GET A CHAIR
BECAUSE HE IS OUR GUEST,
ELMO
ROCCO DOESN'T NEED A CHAIR
ROCCO DOESN'T HAVE LEGS.
ROCCO'S A ROCK
WHAT IS ROCCO EVEN DOING HERE?
WELL, HE WAS IN THE BUILDING
GETTING A COVID TEST, YOU KNOW
HOW
HOW IS ROCCO GETTING A COVID
TEST
TELL ELMO.
HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A NOSE.
HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A RESPITORY
SYSTEM
HEY, LOOK
SNL REQUIRES ALL VISITOR
TO GET TESTED, OKAY?
WHY IS ROCCO VISITING SNL
WE WANTED HIM TO GET A FEEL
FOR THE PLACE BEFORE HE HOSTS
NEXT MONTH
WHAT?
OH, YOU DIDN'T SEE?
LOOK
WHAT!
YEAH.
ROCCO
ROCCO IS HOST AND MUSICAL GUEST?
HOW?
YEAH, THAT IS KIND OF TRUE, ELMO
DO BE LIKE THAT.
COME ON, MIKE
DON'T DO THIS TO ELMO.
ELMO FEEL LIKE ELMO GOING INSANE
HERE
I JUST REALLY LIKE THIS DUDE.
HERE, MAN.
HAVE A COOKIE.
HOW ABOUT THAT
HERE'S A COOKIE.
CAN ELMO HAVE A COOKIE?
I'M SORRY, BUT THAT WAS MY
LAST ONE
THE LAST COOKIE?
THE LAST COOKIE!
IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN
UH-OH
THAT'S IT
PAPER COVERS ROCK.
DIE, ROCCO
COME ON, MAN!
ROCCO'S FAMILY'S HERE!
SORRY
ELMO GIVE ROCK
I'M SORRY.
GIVE IT UP FOR ROCCOslash gym.
NEIGHBORS THE VON TRAPPS
I INSTANTLY MADE ALL OF THEIR
CHILDREN PERFECT
YOUR FATHER SAYS YOU'RE IN NEED
OF THE SAME THING.
OH, MARIA, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
OUR TEACHER, TOO
NOT QUITE, BETWEEN CONCERTS
AND PUPPET SHOWS AND PLAYING THE
NAZIS I'M STRETCHED QUITE THIN
WELL THEN, WHO'S GOING TO BE
OUR NEW GOVERNESS?
I'M DELIGHTED TO SAY I FOUND
SOMEONE PERFECT.
SHE'S QUIRKY AND FUN AND JUST
LIKE ME SHE GOT KICKED OUT OF
THE NUNNERY FOR ERRATIC
BEHAVIOR
* THE HILLS ARE ALIVE
OH, WOW, MARIA.
SHE LOVES THE OUTDOORS JUST LIKE
YOU.
NO, I'M SAYING THE HILLS ARE
ALIFE AND DO NOT GO OUT THERE.
OKAY.
SHE'S NOT EXACTLY LIKE ME.
WELL, NOW CHILDREN, IF MARIA
HA
TAUGHT ME ANYTHING IN THE CAR
RIDE OVER HER, IT'S THAT YOU CAN
SOLVE ALL OF YOUR EMOTIONAL
PROBLEMS JUST BY SINGING
SINGING
WHAT'S THAT
OH!
IT'S EASY.
I'LL TEACH YOU WITH MARIA'S
PERMISSION, OF COURSE.
YEAH.
YEAH
PRETEND I'M NOT EVEN HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO GREAT
* LET'S START A
THE VERY START
OF THE SONG *
* IT'D BE CRAZY
TO START I
THE MIDDLE *
* WHEN YOU READ
YOU BEGIN WITH
DO RE MI *
* AND SINGING
IS EXACTLY THE
SAME *
HOW AM I DOING, MARIA
GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT
GREAT
BUT WE STILL DON'T KNOW HOW
TO SING.
HMM, HOW CAN I MAKE THIS
SIMPLER?
AHH, YES
LIKE THIS.
* DOH, A THING THAT
HOMER SIMPSON SAYS
RE LIKE A MOVI
WITH JAMIE FOX *
* MI LIKE M
MYSELF AND IRENE
* FA LIKE FAT WITHOUT
THE T *
MAYBE JUST STICK TO THE
SCRIPT
* DOE AN ALBU
BY PETER GABRIEL
LA WHAT PEOPLE CAL
LOS ANGELES *
* T THE SHAPE OF AN IUD
AND WHEN HOMER GETS MA
HE SAYS DOH *
ALL RIGHT, CHILDREN IT IS YOUR
TURN
THIS MIGHT SURPRISE YOU, BUT
WE DIDN'T CATCH ALL THAT
DON'T THINK
JUST SING.
ALL RIGHT
I'LL TRY
* DOE THE LAST NAME
OF A BOD
FOUND IN A RIVER *
YES
* RE ROMANO
EVERYBODY LOVES HIM *
AGREED.
* MI A KI
WHO PEES IN THE SINK
FAH LIKE THE END OF QUEEN
LATIFAH *
THAT'S TREMENDOUS
* LO HOW CHILDREN MAK
OUR SNEAKERS
LAH LIKE THE START
OF QUEEN LATIFA.
* TI LIKE THE MIDDL
OF QUEEN LATIFAH *
* AND WHEN HOMER GETS MAD
HE SAYS DO
OH, OH, OH, DOH *
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
OH!
I STOLE IT FROM THE DATABASE AT
THE VATICAN.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ANYONE
I REALLY MUST OBJECT TO SOME
OF YOUR LYRICS
YOU'VE USED QUEEN LATIFAH THREE
TIMES.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU SAY FOR
LA
I SAID LA THE NOTE THAT
FOLLOWS SO
DOM, THAT'S JUST LAZY
YEAH.
QUEEN LATIFAH IS WAY BETTER THAN
THAT
CAN I TRY
GRETA.
YES, FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE
WITNESSING MOTHER'S GRUESOME
DEATH.
NOW THAT IS THE POWER OF
SONG
SING, GRETA, SING YOU BEAUTIFUL
LITTLE MUTE ANGEL!
* DOE A DEE
A FEMALE DEER *
STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP.
SWEETIE DARLING, I HATE TO
CORRECT YOU.
I KNOW THIS IS A BIG MOMENT FOR
YOU.
BUT A FEMALE DEER IS NOT A DOE,
IT'S CALLED A LADY DEER.
WHAT IS ALL OF THIS NOISE
SINGING IN MY HOUSE?
OH, PAPA, DON'T BE MAD.
MAD
QUITE THE OPPOSITE
AS A YOUNG MAN I WAS CONSIDERED
SOMETHING OF A CHANT -- AND I
WOULD TAKE MY INSPIRATION FROM
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THING IN THE
WORLD, FOOD.
* CURLY FRIES
WAFFLE FRIES EVERY TUESDAY
AT ARBY'S *
* JALAPENO BITE
TASTE NICE
GREASE ON THE CROTCH
OF MY KHAKIS *
SING WITH ME CHILDREN!
* CRAZY FRIES
* CRISPY FRIES
* EVERY TUESDAY
AT ARBY'S *
AGAIN
Chinatown
* GET IN MY BACKSEAT
HONEYPIE
AND I'LL WEAR YOUR SADNESS
LIKE IT'S MINE *
* BECAUSE IT'S JUST GOOD
TO FEEL WHAT'S BEEN MISSING
YEAH IT'S BAD WHEN IT'S GOOD
TO ALWAYS BE MISSING *
* BUT A GIRL LIKE YOU
COULD RIP ME OUT OF MY HEAD
BLACK TEARS ON YOUR CHEEK
I WANT THEM IN MY BED *
* I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT OF THE CITY
HONEY RIGHT INTO
THE SHADOW *
* 'CAUSE I WANNA
FIND TOMORROW
YEAH I WANNA FIND TOMORROW
WITH A GIRL LIKE YOU *
* MY CHINATOWN LADY
SITTIN' ON THE FRONT STOOP
CRYIN' OUT THE CRAZY *
* I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT OF THE CITY
HONEY RIGHT INTO
THE SHADOW *
* 'CAUSE I WANNA
FIND TOMORROW
YEAH I WANNA FIND TOMORROW
WITH YOU BABY *
* GIMME GIMME GIMME GIMME
THAT BIG RED LIGHT
AND TAKE THE SADNESS
OUT OF SATURDAY NIGHT *
* 'CAUSE THAT'S JUST GOOD
TO HAVE WHAT WAS MISSING
WE WERE BAD TO BE BAD
MISSING
* BUT A GIRL LIKE YOU
COULD RIP ME OUT OF MY HEAD
BLACK TEARS ON YOUR CHEEK
I WANT THEM IN MY BED *
* I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT OF THE CITY
HONEY RIGHT INTO
THE SHADOW *
* 'CAUSE I WANNA
FIND TOMORROW
YEAH I WANNA FIND TOMORROW
WITH A GIRL LIKE YOU *
* MY CHINATOWN BABY
SITTIN' ON YOUR FRONT STOO
CRYIN' OUT THE CRAZY *
* I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT OF THE CITY
HONEY RIGHT INTO
THE SHADOW *
* 'CAUSE I WANNA
FIND TOMORROW
YEAH I WANNA FIND TOMORROW
WITH YOU BABY *
DEPARTMENT HERE AT CORNELL
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US AT THIS
HIGHLY ANTICIPATED SOLD-OUT FREE
LECTURE.
AND THANK YOU AGAIN FOR THE
GRAN
FROM OUR CORPORATE SPONSOR FAGE
YOGURT
FAGE, BE CAREFUL WHEN YOU SAY
IT
OUR GUEST LECTURERS TODAY ARE
HERE TO ENLIGHTEN US ABOUT
SAPPHO, ANCIENT GREEK POETESS
FROM THE ISLE OF LESBOS.
WELCOME JOANNE DRUCK AND RINNA
MERLIN
UNTIL NOW, SAPPHOS POEMS
ABOUT LESBIAN LOVE HAVE SURVIVED
ONLY IN INCOMPLETE YET
TANTALIZING FRAGMENTS.
FOR EXAMPLE, LAVENDER FIELDS,
WEEPING SHE LEFT ME.
OR MY PERSONAL FAVORITE, I
HAVE A GIRL.
BUT NOW, THANKS TO A RECENT
UNEARTHING OF A BURIED SCROLL
ROOM ON THE AISLE OF LESBOS.
CAUSED BY THE TRAGIC CRASH OF
A ROGUE ROSIE O'DONNELL FAMILY
CRUISE -- ALL SURVIVED -- WE NOW
HAVE SAPPHOS' COMPLETE POEMS
WHICH CAPTURE THE TIMELESS
BEAUTY OF LOVE BETWEEN WOMEN
HUZZAH!
ANY LOVER OF ANCIENT GREEK
LITERATURE IS AS HARD AS THE
STATUE OF ADONIS RIGHT NOW
GIVE US THE TRANSLATIONS,
PLEASE
WILL DO
WE BEGIN
WIND IN MOUNTAINS.
EYES OF GOLDENROD.
WE BROKE UP, HELENA, PLEASE GET
YOUR SANDALS OUT OF HERE
AND NOW, GOLDEN RAISINS,
RIVERBANKS
NANCY, WE JUST MET
YOU'RE SCARY AND A BITCH
MOVE IN WITH ME.
AND THEN THERE'S THIS, OF
COURSE
OLIVE JUICE DRIPS, SUN-TOUCHED
WE CANNOT GET ANOTHER DOG.
WE ARE MAXED OUT ON DOGS
THAT BEING SAID, I FOUND A
PREGNANT FERAL CAT BEHIND THE
GROCERY STORE.
PLEASE
WOW
HER WORK IS TIMELESS
DOES ANYONE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
IT FEELS LIKE MAYBE YOUR
PERSONAL LIVES ARE INFLUENCING
IN THE TRANSLATION
NO, NO.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE NAMED NANCY.
ME NEITHER.
NOT ANYMORE.
LET'S CONTINUE
YOU SATISFY OUR PASSION, THE
AEGEAN BECKONS
WHY DON'T GAY GUYS INVITE US TO
THEIR EVENTS
ARE WE NOT FUN
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
WOVEN GARLAND
GREEK VEE.
NANCY, YOU MOVED IN THREE WEEKS
AGO.
IT HAS BEEN HELL
MARRY ME
AND WE FOUND THIS ONE THE
MOST STIRRING OF ALL
I DON'T CARE IF HELENA OF
GENEROUS WAS MEAN.
SHE DID A LOT.
YOU THINK JAMES OF CORDEN IS A
WALK IN THE PARK
SORRY, HAS THIS BEEN PEER
REVIEWED OR PUBLICIZED
YES, WE WERE MARRIED.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I ASKED
NOW THAT THE CAVE NOT ONLY
CONTAINED POEMS, BUT ALSO
ARTIFACTS WHICH HELP US TO
RE-CREATE SAPPHOS' LIFE WITH HER
ROOMMATE
AN ANCIENT DRINKING VESSEL
A TOGA WITH SUSPENDERS.
AND HERE'S A VASE WITH THE
FACE OF SOME KIND OF ANCIENT
GODESS
AND THAT LOOKS A LOT LIKE
GILLIAN ANDERSON
FROM "THE X FILES," AND WE THINK
YOU DID THAT
WAIT, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO
DO
DO YOU WANT ME TO SPEAK ANCIENT
GREEK?
FINE
MARIA MENOUNOS, ANI DiFRANCO,
OMNICRON
I'M SORRY TO SAY THAT WAS NOT
ANCIENT GREEK AT ALL
FOLKS, THESE TRANSLATIONS MAY
NOT BE LEGITIMATE.
SO SHOW ME A FRAGMENT AND I'LL
TRANSLATE IT
ALL RIGHT, THEN
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR.
I WENT TO THE MOUNTAINS.
I LOOKED TO THE CHILDREN, I
DRANK FROM THE -- YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY WERE RIGHT.
THANK YOU
*
YEAR'S EVE
YOU KNOW, AIN'T NOBODY IN
TEXARKANA SPENDING NEW YEAR'S
EVE AT THE LONGHORN STEAKHOUSE
I KNOW, IT SUCKS.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY, IT'S
GOING TO BE WORTH IT
DANA, GRADY, WHAT Y'ALL DOING
BACK HERE, LER
I'M JUST PREPPING THE SALAD,
MISS ARMOOR.
WHY ARE YOU ALL PREPPING
SALADS WHEN I FOUND TWO EMPTY
A-1s IN THE DINING ROOM, LER
THIS IS LONGHORN STEAKHOUSE.
PEOPLE EXPECT TO BE DAZZLED,
LER.
I CAN'T STAND MISS ARMOOR
YOU KNOW, YOU EVER NOTICE HOW
SH
SAYS LER AFTER EVERYTHING?
LIKE, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT AT THE END
OF THE DAY, SHE IS THE BOSS.
YEAH.
YOU TALKING ABOUT LER?
NO, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT, RENE.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I HEARD YOU TALKING ABOUT HOW
MISS ARMOOR ALWAYS SAY LER
I AIN'T NEVER HEARD LER IN MY
LIFE
GUYS, COME ON -- COME ON,
NOW, I JUST WANT TO GET THROUGH
THE SHIFT SO I CAN GET OFF EARLY
AND TAKE MY GIRL'S KIDS TO THE
TRAMPOLINE PLACE, AT THE END OF
THE DAY.
RENE!
WHERE IS YOUR APRON?
IT IS NEW YEAR'S EVE
MY ASS
IS ON THE LINE, LER.
HEY, MISS ARMOORE, WHAT LER?
EXCUSE ME
LER
WHAT IS LER?
RENE, I CAN NEVER UNDERSTAND
YOU.
NOW GET YOU BACK, LER, TO WORK,
LER, O
Y'ALL ARE GOING TO BE IN BIG
TROUBLE, JANA.
OOH
WHY SHE GOTS TO SINGLE ME OUT,
HUH?
CHILL, JANA, CHILL!
YOU KNOW SHE AIN'T WORTH IT AT
THE END OF THE DAY
AT END OF THE DAY, YOU CAN'T
LET HER GET TO YOU, 'CAUSE AT
THE END OF THE DAY, THAT'S WHAT
SHE WANTS, END OF DAY.
THE OTHER DAY, MISS ARMOOR, SHE
WAS TALKING TO ME ABOUT SOME
BULL
I JUST HAD TO WALK AWAY, AT THE
END OF THE DAY
Y'ALL TALKING ABOUT LER
LAST WEEK, SHE GOT ON ME ABOUT
HOW I WASN'T SWEEPING THE
PARKING LOT AT THE END OF THE
NIGHT.
SHE SAID -- I SAID, "I DON'T
SWEEP THE PARKING LOT.
SHE SAID, "YES, YOU DO."
LIKE, AT THE END OF THE DAY, I
DON'T KNOW WHAT I DO AT THE END
OF THE NIGHT
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WHEN IT'S
THE END OF THE NIGHT, I KNOW
WHAT I DONE DO THEN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING AT THE END OF THE
NIGHT.
FLOYD, YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT.
HEY, GIRL
I AM AT MY LIMIT WITH YOU
IF YOU DON'T GET TO WORKING,
YOU WILL BE DONE AT TEXARKANA
LONGHORN STEAKHOUSE IN TEXAS,
AND I WILL HAVE YOU TRANSFERRED
TO THE TEXARKANA LONGHORN
STEAKHOUSE IN ARKANSAS, LER.
MISS ARMOOR, YOU DONE DONE IT
NOW.
OH, OKAY, I'LL KICK YOUR ASS.
ANYBODY GOT THEIR OWN GOING
ONGOING ON
GRADY HAS TO GO TO THE
TRAMPOLINE PLACE TOMORROW.
FLOYD GOT TO SWEEP AT THE END OF
THE NIGHT.
AND MISS ARMOOR SAY LER.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I AIN'T
THE REDDEST MUD BUG AT THE
JOINT, BUT WE AR
FAMILY, AND LIKE MY MAMA SAID,
THE PEOPLE WILL DO WHAT PEOPLE
WILL DO AT THE END OF THE DAY
AND IF THAT DON'T MAKE SENSE TO
YOU, PEACE
I DO RIDE YOU HARD, BUT
THAT'S JUST BECAUSE I SE
SO MUCH OF MYSELF IN YOU
AT THE END OF THE DAY, MISS
ARMOOR, I HATE YOU 'CAUSE I LOVE
YOU.
HAPPY NEW YEAR'S FROM
LONGHORN STEAKHOUSE, PEESH AND
LURRR.
OH, MY GOSH
THANK YOU!
HOW AMAZING WAS THAT
THANK YOU TO EVERYONE HERE AT 30
ROCK AND SNL FOR HAVING ME
THIS HAS BEEN AN EXPERIENCE OF A
LIFETIME
THANK YOU TO THE STUDIO
AUDIENCE