>>> ON A COLD DECEMBER NIGHT
HIGH ABOVE THE EARTH
FLIES A BIG
JOLLY MAN OF CONSIDERABLE GIRTH.
MAKING HIS WAY TO EVERY HOME UNDER THE SUN
IN HIS MAGICAL
SLEIGH -- AIR FORCE ONE.
>> I KNOW YOU HAVE QUESTIONS FOR
THE PRESIDENT BUT IT'S VERY
LATE.
HE'S EXHAUSTED.
HIS BRAIN IS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
SO UNFORTUNATELY, HE CAN'T WAIT
TO TALK TO YOU.
>> HELLO, EVERYBODY.
HOW ARE YOU?
IT'S ME.
YES, IT'S YOUR FAVORITE
PRESIDENT.
HIDING BEHIND MY CURTAIN, OOH!
BEHIND THE CURTAIN, SOMETHING I
ENJOYED DOING AT MICE TEEN USA
1997.
I'M READY TO TALK.
THIS IS EXCITING.
TONIGHT I TOOK BOTH AN AMBIEN
AND AN ADDERALL,
SO WE'RE GOING
TO SEE WHICH ONE WINS.
>> JUST A FEW QUESTIONS, PLEASE.
>> HOW GREAT IS CAROLYN LEAVITT,
WE LOVE HER, BEAUTIFUL FACE.
THOSE LIPS THAT DON'T QUIT.
PRETTY AMAZING THAT I CAN OPENLY
SIMP OVER MY YOUNG, BLOND
SUBORDINATE.
IT'S GIVING MICHIGAN FOOTBALL
COACH.
LET'S GET A CLOSEUP ON HER MOUTH,
IT'S ONE OF MY -- I LOVE
THAT MOUTH.
PEOPLE NEED THIS SEE THIS.
LOOK AT THOSE LIPS,
THEY GO BOP,
BOP, BOP LIKE A MACHINE GUN.
JUST
>> OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> I'M OBSESSED WITH THIS WOMAN.
SHE LIKED IT BECAUSE I'M VERY
NICE TO WOMEN.
YES, YOU HAVE A QUESTION, YOU
NASTY, HORRIBLE WITCH.
>> MY NAME IS KAITLAN COLLINS, SIR,
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE NICER
THINGS THAT YOU'VE CALLED ME.
SIR, AT YOUR RALLIES YOU
ADDRESSED THE AFFORDABILITY
CRISIS.
ARE YOU ADMITTING THAT IT'S A
SERIOUS PROBLEM?
>> NO, IT'S A MADE-UP TERM,
AFFORDABILITY.
THE ECONOMY IS VERY STRONG.
EVERYONE'S FINE.
FROM THE BILLIONAIRES ALL THE
WAY DOWN TO THE POOR, POOR
MILLIONAIRES.
WHO WE'RE PRAYING FOR EVERY NIGHT,
WHICH IS A MIRACLE
BECAUSE I INHERITED A MESS OF AN ECONOMY
FROM THE AWFUL
PRESIDENTS THAT CAME BEFORE ME.
LIKE BIDEN AND TRUMP.
THIS GUY.
THIS GUY DID A REAL NUMBER ON
THIS PLACE.
NOW, CAN A MAN ASK ME A
QUESTION?
YOU'RE KIND OF A MAN, WHAT YOU
GOT?
>> OKAY, MR. PRESIDENT, ANY
COMMENT ON THE OIL TANKER
YOU
SEIZED OFF THE COAST OF
VENEZUELA ON WEDNESDAY?
>> YES, WE'RE DOING PIRATE NOW,
ARGGH!
INTERESTING, LAST WEEK I SAID
SOMALIS WERE GARBAGE.
NOW WE'RE STEALING THE SHIPS.
IRONIC, ISN'T IT?
ALANIS, SHE'S GREAT IN "DOGMA."
SHE'S AT THE END.
WITH REGARD TO TANKER, I'M CAPTAIN NOW,
REMEMBER CAPTAIN
PHILLIPS?
I'M CAPTAIN, I LOVE THAT LINE.
YOU KNOW, CAPTAIN PHILLIPS, ONE
OF MY FAVORITE CAP TINS AFTER
CRUNCH.
OOPS
I PREFER WHEN IT'S ALL CRUNCH
BERRIES.
OH-OH, METHINKS AMBIEN HAS
PULLED INTO THE LEAD.
BUT DON'T WORRY, ADDERALL IS
STILL IN THE RACE.
>> RIGHT.
SO YOU'LL CONTINUE TO CARRY OUT
STRIKES ON VENEZUELA IN THE
CARIBBEAN?
>> CARRY
YES.
AND YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT JUST
JUST TARGETING DRUG BOATS,
WE'RE
TARGETING SUSPECTED DRUG PLANES
AS WELL.
IN FACT, WE HAVE DECLASSIFIED
VIDEO FROM A STRIKE I CAN SHOW
YOU NOW.
DO WE HAVE THAT CLIP?
WHERE'S THE CLIP?
>> WAS THAT SANTA?
>> NOT ANYMORE!
NEXT QUESTION.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, DO YOU HAVE
ANY COMMENTS
ON THE POTENTIAL
SALE OF WARNER BROTHERS TO
NETFLIX --
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY ANYONE WANTS
WARNERS BROTHERS.
THEY GOT ONE OF THE WORST STUDIO
LOT TOURS IN L.A.
YOU GO ON THAT THING, IT'S SOME
KID POINTING TO A TREE,
THE TREE
FROM PRET LITTLE LIARS, WHO
GIVES A CRAP?
I WANT TO GO TO THE GILMORE
GIRLS GAZEBO.
THE BATMAN MUSEUM.
>> RIGHT, YES.
COULD YOU COMMENT ON THE LATEST
BATCH OF EPSTEIN PHOTOS RELEASED
BY HOUSE DEMOCRATS?
>> THESE PHOTOS ARE A FAKE NEWS
DEMOCRAT HOAX, OKAY?
>> EVEN THE PICTURE OF A BOWL OF
CONDOMS WITH YOUR FACE ON THEM
AND THE TEXT "I'M HUGE"?
>> 100% LEGIT, I LOVE THOSE.
I TOOK A LOT OF GREAT PICTURES.
I LIKE THAT BOWL.
>> OKAY, I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH
QUESTIONS.
THE PRESIDENT REALLY NEEDS TO
REST.
>> I HAVE TO BEGIN MY PREBEDTIME
SELF-CARE RITUAL.
PUTTING A BANDAGE ON MY HAND AND
COVERING IT WITH MAKE UP.
ADDING MORE LAYERS OF BANDAGE
AND MAKEUP.
IT'S A MEDICAL LASAGNA, MAMMA
MIA.
WE SHOULD ALL BE WORRIED ABOUT
MY HEALTH, I'M VERY ILL.
THEN I WILL BRUSH MY TEETH
BEFORE DRIFTING OFF TO DREAM
ABOUT KAROLINE'S MOUTH.
>> LET'S GET ONE MORE SHOT OF
IT.
>> NO.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT THEY
WANT -- OKAY.
LINE
LIPS
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
HOST
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- JOSH
O'CONNOR!
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK
YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I'M JOSH O'CONNOR.
THANK YOU.
AND TO THOSE OF YOU WHO KNOW MY
FACE BUT MAYBE CAN'T QUITE PLACE ME,
NO, I AM NOT THE MOUSE FROM
FLUSHED AWAY.
ALTHOUGH I WILL SAY, HE IS QUITE
FETCHING.
I AM AN ACTOR WHO YOU MIGHT KNOW
FROM "THE CROWN."
YES.
FROM "CHALLENGERS."
AND OTHER...
THANK YOU.
AND OTHER COMPETITIVE HOMOEROTIC
DRAMAS.
YES, I KNOW I HAVE A REPUTATION
FOR BEING
WHAT THE INTERNET
CALLS A SOFT BOY.
I EMBROIDER.
I SCRAPBOOK.
I GARDEN.
I'M JUST YOUR AVERAGE, EVERYDAY,
65-YEAR-OLD WOMAN.
AND I'M JUST TRYING TO LIVE
A QUIET LIFE.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE VERY CAREFUL
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAY,
BECAUSE THE
PRESS WILL BLOW EVERYTHING
COMPLETELY OUT OF PROPORTION.
LIKE ONE TIME I SAID ONE OF MY
FAVORITE MOVIES IS RATATOUILLE,
WHICH IS TRUE,
IT'S A GREAT FILM.
BUT I SUPPOSE FANS STARTED
PICTURING ME
AS CHEFLING WEE
THOUGH FOR A LIVE-ACTION REMAKE.
AND I'M NOT VERY ONLINE, SO I
DIDN'T KNOW THIS WAS A THING
UNTIL THE PRESIDENT OF DISNEY
PIXAR PUBLICLY DECLARED
THAT
THERE WILL NEVER BE A
LIVE-ACTION "RATATOUILLE" REMAKE
"NO MATTER HOW MUCH JOSH"
O'CONNOR WANTS IT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW IT FEELS TO BE
PUBLICLY REJECTED FROM A JOB I
DIDN'T EVEN WANT?
FOR THE RECORD, I DON'T EVEN
WANT A LIVE-ACTION
RATATOUILLE.
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME FOR IT.
I'M ALREADY IN THE NEW "KNIVES
OUT" FILM.
WHICH NOW THAT I'M SAYING IT OUT
LOUD SOUNDS LIKE THE PERFECT
NAME FOR THE LIVE-ACTION
RATATOUILLE.
THAT'S NEITHER HERE NOR THERE.
I'M AT "SNL," AND I'M SO
HONORED.
THE CAST, THE CREW --
SORRY, FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH, I WOULD KILL AS
LINGUINE.
I SEE A PICTURE OF HIM --
HIS EARS ARE HUGE,
AND RATATOUILLE IS BASICALLY A
QUEER LOVE STORY.
I AGREE, LET'S NOT DO IT.
BEING AT "SNL" DURING
CHRISTMASTIME IS MAGICAL AND
JOYOUS.
AND GUYS, YOU CAN'T MAKE
RATATOUILLE UNLESS YOU HAVE
THE PERFECT CAST.
THERE'S NO POINT.
WHO WOULD BE THE FOOD CRITIC,
ANTON EGO?
PERHAPS JEFF GOLDBLUM.
NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN, YES, BUT LATER.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
LILY ALLEN IS HERE!
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK!
NOW
IT'S "LET'S FIND LOVE!"
>> HELLO, HELLO, AND WELCOME TO
LET'S FIND LOVE!
I'M YOUR HOST, GARTH VADER.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THAT ALWAYS
GETS A LAUGH, IT'S JUST MY NAME.
BUT TODAY, ONE LUCKY MAN WILL
GET HIS PICK
BETWEEN THREE
BEAUTIFUL LADIES IN HIS SEARCH
FOR LOVE.
LET'S MEET OUR PRINCE CHARMING,
DANIEL SHA LESSER!
>> HI.
I'M DANIEL.
I'M 35 YEARS OLD
AND I'VE BEEN
TOLD I'M CUTE, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, YOU KNOW.
NOW, BEFORE WE MEET OUR LOVELY LADIES,
WE WOULD JUST LIKE TO
SAY WE HAVE ADDRESSED THE AGE
DISCRIMINATION PROBLEM HERE AT
THE SHOW.
SO WE HAVE OFFICIALLY RAISED THE
AGE CAP OF OUR CONTESTANTS
FROM
38 TO AS OLD AS WE CAN FIND.
>> WAIT, WHAT?
>> LET'S BRING OUT OUR LADIES!
>> HI.
I'M GISELE.
I'M 36.
I'M A SWIMMING INSTRUCTOR
TO CANNONBALL RIGHT INTO YOUR
HEART.
>> HI, I'M TRICIA.
I'M 35.
I WORK IN ACCOUNTING.
BUT THE ONLY NUMBER I'M
INTERESTED IN IS INFINITY WITH
YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING DOWN?
I'M MINGACRESHA, I'M 84 YEARS OLD,
LOOKING FOR SOMEBODY TO
KEEP ME CRACKING AND SMACKING
UNTIL ANY TIME ON EARTH IS UP.
FANTASTIC
>> LOOKING FOR SOMETHING TO KEEP
ME GOING, GET MY BONES RIGHT,
KEEP BONES
MAKE SURE I'M TAKING MY MEDS RIGHT,
GETTING MY MEALS RIGHT,
GETTING MY PROTEINS RIGHT,
GETTING MY CHEESE RIGHT,
GETTING MY PILLS RIGHT,
GET MY FAMINES RIGHT,
GETTING MY JUICE RIGHT,
GETTING MYSELF RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> LET'S START THE GAME!
>> OKAY, LOOKS LIKE EVERYBODY'S
GETTING SETTLED.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THERE SHE GOES.
SHE'S GOING TO BACK IT IN,
GREAT.
ALL RIGHT.
WONDERFUL.
>> I'M HERE!
>> OKAY.
WELL.
THESE ARE SOME BEAUTIFUL LADIES,
DAN.
LET'S START OFF WITH YOUR FIRST
QUESTION.
>> OKAY.
CONTESTANT NUMBER ONE,
WE'RE
BOUND TO GET UNDER EACH OTHER'S
SKIN.
WHATTING YOUR BIGGEST PET PEEVE?
>> OH, MY BIGGEST PET PEEVE IS
WHEN PEOPLE ARE BEING MEAN TO
OTHERS.
>> OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I LOVE NICE GIRLS.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> OH, NO, NO, WE'RE ALL GOING
TO WAIT OUR TURNS.
>> OKAY, CONTESTANT NUMBER TWO.
>> UM, WHEN PEOPLE CHEW GUM WITH
THEIR MOUTH WIDE OPEN.
>> OH, TOTALLY.
I ABSOLUTELY HATE THAT.
>> I'M NOT ALLOWED TO HAVE GUM
ANYMORE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID.
>> CAN THAT COUNT AS HER ANSWER?
>> NO.
>> OKAY, CONTESTANT NUMBER
THREE --
>> BIGGEST PET PEEVE WHEN IS
THERE'S NO CAKE AT A WEDDING.
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE!
I ONCE HURLED MYSELF OVER A
BRIDGE CAKE AT A WEDDING.
THERE SHOULD ALWAYS BE HOT,
MOIST CAKE AT A WEDDING OR WHY
SHOULD I GO?
WHY SHOULD I GO?
>> AM I SUPPOSED TO ANSWER?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> OKAY, NEXT QUESTION.
CONTESTANT NUMBER ONE, IF WE
WERE TO LEAVE TOGETHER,
WHERE DO
YOU SEE OUR FUTURE IN A YEAR
FROM NOW?
>> OH, HOPEFULLY SOMEWHERE
TROPICAL TOGETHER.
LAUGHING UNDER THE STARS.
>> A SENSE OF HUMOR, THAT'S SO
IMPORTANT.
I LOVE THAT.
>> I GOT A JOKE.
MY SISTER'S A BITCH.
>> OKAY, LET'S MOVE ON.
CONTESTANT NUMBER TWO?
>> UM -- I'D LIKE US TO BE IN
THE SUBURBS WITH ONE CHILD
AND A
COUPLE LITTLE ONES ON THE WAY.
>> WELL, MEDICALLY IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT A REALLY NICE IDEA.
AND CONTESTANT NUMBER THREE?
>> I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE I'LL BE
IN ONE YEAR FROM NOW.
FRONT ROW, OPENING NIGHT OF "TOY
STORY 5."
THE TOYS ARE BACK!
AND THEY'RE WISER THAN THEY WERE
BEFORE!
WOODY AND THE GANG HAVE TO
BATTLE AN iPAD.
AND PIXAR'S GOT A LOT OF
PRESSURE.
THEY GOT TO GET THE STORY RIGHT,
GET THE BUZZ RIGHT,
THEY GOT TO
GET ANDY RIGHT, GET THE TOYS
RIGHT,
OR ELSE WHY SHOULD I GO?
WHY SHOULD I GO?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S THAT TIME
TO
PICK YOUR ONE TRUE LOVE, DANIEL.
>> OH, FINALLY TIME TO PICK,
LET'S GO!
LET ME SEE MY OPTIONS!
>> YOU DON'T PICK.
SH-MOKING.
>> FLATTERING BUT I THINK I'M
GOING TO HAVE TO GO WITH SOMEONE
ELSE.
>> NOT YOU, PRETTY BOY, HIM.
>> ME?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> OH, SNAP.
I NEVER GET PICKED.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE THAT'S NOT OUT
GAME WORKS.
>> I'M IN CHARGE.
BACK
LET'S GET OUR BODIES RIGHT,
SALMONS
LET'S GET OUR JUICES
RIGHT, LET'S GO GET EVERYTHING
RIGHT,
LET'S GET OUR MEALS
RIGHT.
>>> IT'S THE END OF THE YEAR,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
>> HONEY, SPOTIFY WRAPPED JUST
DROPPED.
>> OH, MY GOD, I LOVE WHEN THEY
DO THIS.
>> IT'S A WAY OF LOOKING BACK AT
WHO YOU WERE IN 2025.
>> STEELY DAN?
YEAH, THAT TRACKS.
>> WITH SHAREABLE STATS SHOWING
HOW YOU COMPARE TO PEOPLE AROUND
THE WORLD.
>> I'M IN SABRINA CARPENTER'S
TOP 1%?
THAT'S SO NEAT.
>> WELL, NOW THERE'S ANOTHER WAY
TO LOOK BACK AT WHO YOU TRULY
WERE THIS YEAR.
INTRODUCING -- UBER EATS
WRAPPED.
>> OH, NO.
NO, THANK YOU.
>> STUDY YOUR PATTERNS AND
CRUNCH THE NUMBERS.
>> OH, NO, I UNDERSTOOD WHAT IT
WAS.
I JUST DON'T LIKE THAT, AND I
DON'T WANT THAT.
>> WE DID IT ANYWAY.
YOU CAN FIND OUT WHICH
RESTAURANTS YOU COULDN'T LIVE
WITHOUT.
>> TACO BELL, FIVE GUYS, BURGER
KING, CHIPOTLE.
>> I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS WHY THE
PLUMBER'S ALWAYS HERE.
>> HE'S NOT ALWAYS HERE.
>> TOILET'S ALL CLEAR, KILLER.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> I GOT YOU, BOO, NO PROBLEM.
>> LEARN WHAT HAS YOU IN A
CHOKEHOLD.
>> SAYS I'M IN THE TOP 1% OF
NUGGETS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
>> TAKE A WILD GUESS.
>> THAT I EAT MORE NUGGETS THAN
99% OF THE WORLD?
THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
>> YOU'RE EATING NUGGETS RIGHT
NOW.
>> BASED ON YOUR ORDER HISTORY,
OUR MATH WIZARDS HAVE DETERMINED
YOUR UBER EATS AGE.
CHURRO
MY UBER EATS AGE IS DEAD?
>> FINE IS 52 AND FAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT FAT.
>> I DO WHOO, WHO!
WORLD
>> WE WEREN'T THE ONLY ONES
SERVING THIS YEAR.
CHECK OUT THE LOOKS YOU WORE TO
GREET YOUR UBER DRIVERS.
>> WHO DO I EVEN SHARE THESE
WITH?
>> WE CALCULATED EXACTLY HOW
MUCH MONEY YOU SPENT ON UBER
EATS THIS YEAR.
>> $24,000?
GIVE ME ONE SECOND.
>> CHECK OUT PERSONALIZED
MESSAGES FROM THE RESTAURANTS
THAT KEPT YOU FED.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, MELISSA!
BECAUSE OF YOU, WE ARE THE
NUMBER ONE WENDY'S IN THE
COUNTRY!
>> OH, MY GOD!
A PHONE JUST HIT ME!
>> IT'S UBER EATS WRAPPED.
YOU HAVE TO TELL PEOPLE YOU'RE
GOING TO DO THIS.
>> ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
>>> ALL RIGHT, MR. COLEMAN,
THANK YOU FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
THE DOCTOR WILL SEE YOU NOW.
>> HELLO, PATIENT.
SORRY FOR THE DELAY. I WAS --
DELAYED.
>> OH.
HI.
>> I HAVE WITH ME THE RESULTS OF
YOUR BLOOD WORK.
>> OH, OKAY.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> TO TELL YOU IS MY GREATEST WISH,
BUT THIS IS A TEACHING HOSPITAL,
SO MY INTERN WHO DID
YOUR BLOOD WORK WILL BE GIVING
YOU THE RESULTS.
>> OH, OKAY.
THAT'S FINE.
>> VERY GOOD.
INTERN?
>> HELLO.
>> OH, MY GOD, IS THAT MY BLOOD?
>> WHAT SHOULD I DID TELL HIM?
>> IF IT IS HIS, SAY NO.
>> NO.
>> NOW PLEASE GIVE THE PATIENT
HIS RESULTS.
>> OKAY. YOUR BLOOD --
IS GOOD.
>> OKAY, THAT'S A RELIEF.
>> EXCELLENT JOB, INTERN.
BUT ARE YOU SURE THE BLOOD IS
GOOD?
>> NO.
>> THEN DO NOT SAY IT'S GOOD.
AND THAT IS THE LESSON FOR
TODAY.
GOOD-BYE!
>> GOOD-BYE!
>> WAIT!
YOU DIDN'T EVEN GIVE ME MY
RESULTS.
>> GOOD CATCH.
THAT WAS A TEST.
OR PERHAPS A QUIZ.
NO.
QUIZNOS, NOW I'M HUNGRY.
>> WHAT?
LOOK, I JUST WANT TO KNOW IF
MY BLOOD IS OKAY.
>> DOCTOR, YOUR 4:00 --
>> IS HERE?
>> NO, IS DEAD.
>> EXACTLY HOW I LEFT HIM.
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I AM.
AND DON'T CALL ME SIRIUS,
MY
NAME IS SHIRLEY.
>> OKAY, DOCTOR, PLEASE --
>> HOW DID YOU KNOW MY LAST
NAME?
>> YOUR NAME IS DOCTOR PLEASE?
>> HE'S DOCTOR PLEASE, AND I'M
SHIRLEY PLEASE.
>> ARE YOU TWO RELATED?
>> I HOPE NOT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
LOOK.
CAN I PLEASE JUST GET MY TEST
RESULTS?
I'VE GOT A DATE TONIGHT, AND I NEED TO KNOW
IF I HAVE TO
DISCLOSE ANYTHING.
>> OF COURSE.
THE PATIENT IS ALWAYS RIGHT.
>> I THINK THE SAYING IS THE
CUSTOMER IS ALWAYS RIGHT.
>> WELL IN A WAY, THE PATIENT IS
THE CUSTOMER OF THE DOCTOR.
>> AND A HORSE IS THE CAR FOR A
COWBOY.
THAT'S A JOKE.
>> OH, HOW I LOVE JOKES.
THERE'S JUST SOMETHING ABOUT
THEM THAT MAKES ME LAUGH.
>> YOU'RE NOT LAUGHING.
>> BUT I'M SMILING.
AND WHAT IS A SMILE BUT A LAUGH
THAT HASN'T BEEN BORN YET?
FIVE
UGLY
KILL
>> NOW SHIRLEY, GIVE THE PATIENT
HIS RESULTS IN PLAIN ENGLISH,
PLEASE.
BLOOD
GOOD MATE,
IT'S PROPER FIT,
ISN'T IT?
BUT YOUR SODIUM LEVELS ARE
BOLLOCKS.
>> SO ALL THAT AND A BAG OF
CHIPS.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S A VHS OF CLASSIC
EPISODES OF "ALL THAT"
INSIDE A
BAG OF CAPE COD KETTLE CRINKLE
CUP CRISPS.
>> THEY PAIR PERFECTLY WITH
LOCALLY TOPS.
>> WHAT ARE LOCALLY TOPS?
>> LOLLY POPS BUT JUST THE HEAD
WHEN YOU WANT TO SUCK ON
SOMETHING BUT DON'T WANT TO HOLD
IT.
>> DOCTOR, YOU CAR.
>> IS TOWED?
>> NO, FOUND AT THE SCENE OF A
CRIME.
>> EXACTLY WHERE I LEFT IT.
>> JUST TELL ME MY RESULTS NOW.
>> FINE, SEE FOR YOURSELF.
>> THIS IS YOUR BLOOD WORK.
IT SAYS YOU TWO ARE RELATED.
>> WELL, GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO
STOP DOING THIS.
THANKS COZY
LADIES.
I KNOW IT'S LAME, BUT I WANTED
TO DO SOMETHING CHILL WITH MY
GIRLIES.
>> HOPEFULLY NOT TOO CHILL,
BECAUSE WHAT'S A BACHELORETTE
WEEKEND WITHOUT -- STRIPPERS!
>> OH, WHAT?
NO, I TOLD YOU GUYS IT'S NOT
THAT KIND OF WEEKEND.
STRIPPERS REALLY AREN'T MY
THING.
>> OKAY, DON'T WORRY.
I GOT YOU A DIFFERENT KIND OF
STRIPPER.
STRIPPERS THAT ARE MORE YOUR
TYPE.
OKAY, LADIES?
MEET AUGIE AND REMINGTON!
>> HI.
DO WE HAVE CONSENT TO ENTER YOUR
HOME?
>> SURE.
>> UM -- HI.
>> YOU ARE ENOUGH.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> BEFORE WE GET STARTED, MIND
IF I FINISH MY BOOK?
IT'S WRITTEN BY THIS BRILLIANT
WOMAN OF COLOR.
>> MARGARET, WHERE DID YOU FIND
THESE GUYS?
>> ON A SALLY ROONEY MESSAGE
BOARD.
THEY'RE THE MOST SENSITIVE MALE
STRIPPERS IN ALL THE CATSKILLS.
>> I HATE TO BE THE GROUP
HORNDOG, BUT ARE THEY GOING TO
STRIP?
>> OH, THEY STRIP.
BOYS?
>> WHY ARE THEY WEARING TWO
CARDIGANS?
>> LOOK, ELIZA, I THINK IT'S
REALLY WORKING FOR HER.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK THE
PRESIDENT SHOULD BE CYNTHIA
ERIVO.
>> GOD, YOU'RE PERFECT!
>> OKAY, I'VE NEVER SEEN HER
LIKE THIS.
>> I'M STILL NOT TURNED ON,
Y'ALL.
THESE GUYS LOOK LIKE FROG AND
TOAD.
WHEN ARE THEY GOING TO DROP AND
SHOW THAT PORK PENCIL?
>> BETH!
STOP!
>> I'M JUST SAYING, I WANT TO
SEE SOME SKIN.
>> ASK, AND YOU SHALL RECEIVE.
>> FAKE TATTOO.
>> I DON'T WANT MY STRIPPERS TO
HAVE LITTLE BEANIES AND LITTLE
EARRINGS.
I WANT THEM TO THROW ASS IN A
COP OUTFIT.
>> LAURA!
>> THROW ASS!
THROW ASS!
>> WAIT, LOOK, NOW THEY'RE
DANCING.
>> HEY, YOU.
>> SEEMS LIKE THEY'RE JUST
VIBING WITH EACH OTHER.
>> WHAT IF WE --
>> WE SHOULDN'T.
>> UNLESS --
>> WE CAN'T.
>> ARE THEY HAVING A WILL
THEY/WON'T THEY?
>> OH, GOD YES!
>> CAN WE GET A LAP DANCE AT
LEAST?
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY THEIR
SPECIALTY.
HIT IT, GUYS!
>> OF COURSE.
WAS NOT EXPECTING THE DOUBLE
JEANS.
>> COME HERE, LADIES.
>> YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE
YOURSELVES.
>> I THINK MINE'S CRYING!
HE GOT OVERSTIMULATED.
IT'S OKAY, BUDDY!
>> I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT THE
SUPREME COURT.
>> NO, ENOUGH.
THIS IS NOT WHAT STRIPPING IS.
>> YEAH, AND --
>> OH, SHUT UP.
>> I WOULD.
>> HEY, BABE, SURPRISE. I MADE --
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
>> WE DON'T WANT ANY PROBLEMS,
SIR.
>> OH, YEAH?
WELL, I DO.
GET OVER HERE, FLEET FOXES,
LET'S GO.
>> OH, NO!
>> THEY'RE FIGHTING!
>> DON'T HURT THEM, CRAIG!
>> KILL HIM, REMINGTON!
>> OH, OH, OW, OH, OW, PLEASE
STOP, OH!
>> NOW, WHERE WERE WE?
LADIES
Sleepwalking
¶ YOU WON'T LOVE ME
YOU WON'T LEAVE ME
YOU DON'T TOUCH ME
STILL SO NEEDY ¶
¶ AND I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU DO IT INTENTIONALLY
SOMEHOW YOU MAKE IT
MY FAULT ¶
¶ YOU DON'T STOP TALKING
AND I'M JUST SLEEPWALKING ¶
¶ COURSE I'M ANGRY
COURSE I'M HURT
LOOKING BACK
IT'S SO ABSURD ¶
¶ COURSE I TRUSTED YOU
AND TOOK YOU AT YOUR WORD ¶
¶ WHO SAID ROMANCE
ISN'T DEAD
BEEN NO ROMANCE
SINCE WE WED ¶
¶ WHY AREN'T WE --
YEAH THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID ¶
¶ BUT YOU LET ME THINK
IT WAS ME IN MY HEAD
AND NOTHING TO DO WITH
THEM GIRLS IN YOUR BED ¶
¶ YOU DON'T STOP TALKING
AND I'M JUST SLEEPWALKING ¶
¶ SEE YOUR THOUGHTS FORMING
BABY STOP IT
IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING ¶
¶ AND I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU DO IT INTENTIONALLY
BUT SOMEHOW YOU MAKE IT
MY FAULT ¶
¶ YOU DON'T STOP TALKING
AND I'M JUST
SLEEPWALKING ¶
¶ I KNOW YOU'VE MADE ME
YOUR MADONNA
I WANNA BE YOUR WHORE ¶
¶ BABY IT WOULD BE MY HONOR
PLEASE SIR
CAN I HAVE SOME MORE ¶
¶ I COULD PRESERVE ALL
OF YOUR FANTASIES
IF ONLY YOU COULD
ACT THEM ALL OUT WITH ME ¶
¶ YOU DON'T STOP TALKING
AND I'M JUST SLEEPWALKING ¶
¶ SEE YOUR THOUGHTS FORMING
BABY STOP IT
IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING ¶
¶ AND I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU DO IT INTENTIONALLY
BUT SOMEHOW YOU MAKE IT
MY FAULT ¶
¶ YOU DON'T STOP TALKING
AND I'M JUST
SLEEPWALKING-ING ¶
¶ YOU WON'T LOVE ME
YOU WON'T LEAVE ME ¶
WEEKEND
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> THIS WEEK, PRESIDENT TRUMP
LED A RALLY CELEBRATING HIS
HANDLING OF HIS ECONOMY,
WHICH
SOMEHOW HE HELD AT A CASINO IN
THE POCONOS.
WEIRD TO SAY:
THE FUTURE IS BRIGHTER THAN EVER,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, WOMAN ON
OXYGEN PLAYING THE NICKEL SLOTS?
TRUMP'S SPEECH WAS SUPPOSED TO
FOCUS ON THE AFFORDABILITY CRISIS,
BUT HE DRIFTED OFF TOPIC
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
>> THEY DON'T USE THE WORD CHIEF
OF STAFF ANYMORE BECAUSE OF THE
INDIANS.
CAN YOU IMAGINE IF DONALD TRUMP
MARRIED HIS SISTER?
DO WE LOVE MINERS?
I LOVE MINERS.
WHAT?
DON'T FORGET WHO.
EGGS!
>> I LOVE THAT THE PRESIDENT
LOST HIS TRAIN OF THOUGHT
AND
SOMEONE IN THE CROWD HAD TO
REMIND HIM HIS TRAIN OF THOUGHT
WAS EGGS.
SORRY, EGGS!
AS YOU CAN SEE FROM THE SIGN
BEHIND HIM, THE THEME OF THE RALLY WAS,
LOWER PRICES, BIGGER
PAYCHECKS.
WHICH WAS MUCH BETTER THAN HIS
ORIGINAL ECONOMIC MESSAGE,
NOT
MY FAULT, SELL YOUR BLOOD.
>>> THIS WEEK, PRESIDENT TRUMP
CLAIMED THAT AFFORDABILITY
IS A
NEW WORD MADE UP BY DEMOCRATS TO
HURT HIM.
BUT IF DEMOCRATS REALLY WANTED
TO MAKE UP A WORD SPECIFICALLY TO HURT TRUMP,
IT WOULD PROBABLY
BE "FATMENTIA."
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALSO COMPLAINED
ABOUT IMMIGRANTS FROM COUNTRIES LIKE HAITI
AND ASKED, WHY CAN'T
WE HAVE SOME PEOPLE FROM NORWAY
INSTEAD?
OR, HOW ABOUT SOMEONE WHO'S
NORWEGIAN AND HAITIAN?
LIKE TIMES SQUARE ELSA?
>>> THE DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY POSTED AN IMAGE OF
IMMIGRATION OFFICERS IN SANTA HATS
WITH THE CAPTION, "YOU'RE
GOING HO HO HOME."
EVEN WORSE, SANTA RETWEETED IT.
>>> DHS SECRETARY KRISTI NOEM
TESTIFIED BEFORE CONGRESS
WHERE
PROTESTERS INTERRUPTED HER BY
SHOUTING THE LINE
"THE POWER OF
CHRIST COMPELS YOU."
FROM "THE EXORCIST."
NOEM MOSTLY IGNORED THEM BUT DID
TAKE ONE QUICK LOOK BACK.
>>> LAST WEEK, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HOSTED MULTIPLE EVENTS AT THE KENNEDY CENTER,
INCLUDING AN
AWARDS CEREMONY FOR SYLVESTER
STALLONE,
GLORIA GAYNOR, AND ROCK BAND KISS,
AS WELL AS A
MUSICAL PERFORMANCE BY THE
VILLAGE PEOPLE.
WHICH RAISES THE QUESTION,
IS DONALD TRUMP A GAY MAN FROM
1978?
>>> IN A NEW INTERVIEW,
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID
THAT
VENEZUELAN PRESIDENT NICOLAS
MADURO'S DAYS ARE NUMBERED.
AS OPPOSED TO TRUMP, WHOSE DAYS
ARE LETTERED.
>>> TRUMP ALSO SAYS A PROPOSED
MERGER BETWEEN NETFLIX AND
WARNER BROTHERS DISCOVERY
COULD
BE A PROBLEM, ADDING, BRIBE!
>>> IN RESPONSE, NETFLIX IS
OFFERING TRUMP
ONE NIGHT WITH
THE DEMON HUNTERS.
>>> THE ARCHDIOCESE OF NEW YORK
ANNOUNCED THAT IT WILL SET UP
A
$300 MILLION FUND FOR VICTIMS OF
SEX ABUSE.
THE CHURCH ENCOURAGES VICTIMS TO
CLAIM THE MONEY
BY STICKING
THEIR HAND IN THIS HERE HOLE.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>>> HEALTH OFFICIALS ARE
REPORTING A SURGE IN WINTER
VOMITING DISEASE.
WHICH IS BETTER KNOWN AS
SANTA-CON.
THIS CROWD.
>>> THE HOLIDAYS ARE RIGHT
AROUND THE CORNER.
MANY OF US WILL BE TRAVELING
HOME TO SEE OUR FAMILIES.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR VERY OWN
MARCELLO HERNANDEZ.
>> HELLO!
HELLO, EVERYONE.
HOW ARE YOU, COLIN?
>> I'M GREAT, ARE YOU EXCITED
FOR CHRISTMAS, MARCELLO?
>> YES, I LOVE CHRISTMAS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE FAMILY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET THE NEW
BOYFRIENDS.
CHRISTMAS IS THE TIME WHEN
SOMEONE BRINGS A NEW BOYFRIEND,
AND HE SPENDS THE WHOLE NIGHT
PRETENDING TO BE SOMEONE HE'S
NOT.
THE GUY'S LIKE, "I LOVE THE
FOOD, MRS. HERNANDEZ, IT'S
DELICIOUS."
YOU DON'T LIKE THE FOOD, YOU
LIKE HAVING SEX WITH MY COUSIN!
IN MY FAMILY, THERE'S ALWAYS AN
UNCLE
WHO'S BIG ON GIVING
UNSOLICITED SEXUAL ADVICE.
HE'S LIKE, "HEY, COME
HERE.
NEXT TIME YOU GO TO THE NIPPLE,
BITE IT A LITTLE BIT."
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "I'M 11, MAN."
>> BITE IT A LITTLE.
>> THAT WAS ME WHEN I WAS 11.
>> WHAT KIND OF KID WERE YOU?
>> THE BAD KIND, COLIN.
I USED TO BE SO BAD THAT SANTA
CLAUS USED TO CALL ME.
IN THE SUMMER.
MY MOM HANDS ME THE PHONE AND
ST. NICHOLAS HIMSELF IS LIKE,
"HEY, MARCELLO, HO HO HO, IT'S"
ME, SANTA CLAUS.
IF YOU DON'T BEHAVE, I'M GOING
TO SKIP YOUR HOUSE.
I'D BE LIKE, "I'M SORRY, SANTA,
I'LL BEHAVE."
AND HE'D BE LIKE --
ME AND MY DOG RUDOLPH LOVE YOU
VERY MUCH.
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY SWEET.
>> YEAH, A LOT OF PEOPLE USED TO
CALL ME.
SPIDER-MAN USED TO CALL ME.
>> SPIDER-MAN?
>> YES.
"HEY, MARCELLO, IT'S ME, YOUR"
NEIGHBORHOOD FRIEND, SPIDER-MAN.
I'M CALLING YOU BECAUSE YOUR
MOTHER TELLING ME THAT YOU ARE
CLIMBING ON THE WALLS.
YOU CANNOT DO THAT.
ONLY I CAN DO THAT.
BECAUSE I WAS BEATEN BY A
RADIOACTIVE SPIDER.
"ME AND MY BROTHER
SUPERMAN LOVE YOU VERY MUCH."
>> I'M NOT SURE THAT WAS
ACTUALLY SUPERMAN.
>> YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY STILL
GET A LOT OF THESE CALLS.
LISTEN TO THIS VOICEMAIL THAT
LORNE LEFT ME.
>> HEY, MARCELLO, IT'S ME, YOUR
BOSS, LORNE MICHAEL.
ME AND MY BROTHER, JIMMY FALLON,
LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
>> BROTHER?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO BACK TO THE
HOLIDAYS.
I'M ASSUMING YOU HAVE A BIG
LATIN CHRISTMAS?
DON'T DO THAT, COLIN.
BUT YES.
I DO.
WE EAT PORK, WE DANCE,
AND AT THE END OF THE NIGHT, MY CUBAN
MOM IS LIKE,
"YOU KNOW WHAT I
WANT FOR CHRISTMAS?
A GRANDCHILD.
BUT YOU WON'T GIVE IT TO ME
BECAUSE YOU HATE ME."
>> OH, MY GOD.
ARE THERE ANY CHRISTMAS MOVIES
YOU WATCH?
>> YES, WE USED TO WATCH "HOME
ALONE."
AS A LATINO KID, THAT MOVIE WAS
UNBELIEVABLE.
BECAUSE THIS KID MISSES THE
PLANE,
DESTROYS THE HOUSE, AND
RUINS THE VACATION.
AND SOMEHOW THIS MOVIE DOESN'T
END IN A HISTORIC ASS-BEATING.
IN THE FIRST SCENE, THE MOM IS
LIKE, "GO TO YOUR ROOM, KEVIN."
AND HE GOES, "SHUT UP, MOP."
IF THAT WAS ME?
THAT'S WHERE THE MOVIE ENDS.
ROLL THE CREDITS!
"IN MEMORY OF MARCELLO"
HERNANDEZ."
>> MARCELLO HERNANDEZ, EVERYONE!
MARCELLO
SPIDER-MAN, I LIKE THAT.
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW REPORT,
PEOPLE ON LONG ISLAND SPENT MORE
MONEY ON ONLYFANS
THAN SOME
ENTIRE EASTERN EUROPEAN NATIONS.
BECAUSE EASTERN EUROPEANS ARE
TOO BUSY WORKING --
ON ONLYFANS.
>>> THE GOLDEN GLOBE NOMINATIONS
WERE ANNOUNCED
WITH THE MOST
NOMINATIONS GOING TO THE MOVIE
ONE BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER.
VERY EXCITING.
AND THE LEAST NOMINATIONS GOING
TO MICHAEL CHE'S
"HOLD UP, MADEA
GOT A DAUGHTER?"
>>> A VIDEO HAS GONE VIRAL OF A
RUNAWAY HORSE IN NEW YORK CITY
GALLOPING DOWN A HIGHWAY NEAR
JFK AIRPORT.
AND GOOD NEWS, HE MADE HIS
FLIGHT.
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE THAT MORE.
>>> A PHOTO HAS GONE VIRAL OF A
GROUP OF EIGHT STUDENTS FROM SAN JOSE
FORMING A HUMAN SWASTIKA
WHILE LAYING ON THEIR HIGH
SCHOOL'S FOOTBALL FIELD.
EVEN CRAZIER, IT WAS A RESULT OF
A SKYDIVING ACCIDENT.
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T LIKE THAT
ONE.
>>> POLICE IN FLORIDA ARRESTED
TWO MEN AND A WOMAN --
GOOD LUCK
GUESSING WHICH IS WHICH --
AFTER THEY WERE DISCOVERED
HAVING DRUNKEN SEX IN A
WINN-DIXIE PARKING LOT.
THE TRIO WAS IMMEDIATELY
TRANSPORTED
TO A WAFFLE HOUSE
PARKING LOT.
>>> A NEW BILL HAS BEEN PROPOSED
IN CONGRESS
THAT WOULD REQUIRE
FATHERS TO PAY 50% OF MEDICAL EXPENSES
FOR A WOMAN'S PREGNANCY
AND DELIVERY.
FINE, BUT THEN I'M OUT.
>>> PANTONE ANNOUNCED THEIR
COLOR OF THE YEAR IS CLOUD DANCER,
WHICH THEY CALL A
BILLOWY, BALANCED WHITE IMBUED
WITH A FEELING OF SERENITY.
A DESCRIPTION THEY STOLE FROM MY
OLD BUMBLE PROFILE.
>>> THERE ARE MANY THEORIES
ABOUT HOW SOCIETY AS WE KNOW IT
COULD END.
HERE WITH A STERN WARNING ABOUT
THE FUTURE IS OUR OWN JANE
WICKLINE!
HI.
HELLO.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> HI, JANE.
>> SO WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME
LEFT AS A SPECIES,
SO I'M JUST
GOING TO GET RIGHT INTO MY SONG.
>> OH, IF WE DON'T HAVE THAT
MUCH TIME, MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T DO
A WHOLE SONG.
>> THIS IS CALLED "THE GREATEST
THREAT TO HUMANITY RIGHT NOW."
>> GREAT.
¶ WE'RE PROGRAMMING MONSTERS WE
WILL LOSE CONTROL OF SOON ¶
¶ THEY'RE TAKING EVERY JOB AND
SINGULARITY'S APPROACHING ¶
¶ WHEN THEY GET SMARTER THAN US
WILL THEY BE OUR DOOM ¶
¶ I THINK WE ALL KNOW THE TOPIC
I AM BROACHING ¶
¶ WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT
TO STOP THEM ¶
¶ WE MUST KILL THEM WHILE
THEY'RE STILL WEAK ¶
¶ THE CHILD ACTORS FROM
STRANGER THINGS ¶
>> WHAT?
¶ THEY ARE ADULTS NOW WE HAVE TO
DESTROY THEM
BEFORE THEY DESTROY
EVERYTHING ¶
¶ THE CHILD ACTORS FROM
STRANGER THINGS ¶
>> I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE
TALKING ABOUT AI.
¶ AI IS JUST A DISTRACTION
THE REAL THREAT HERE IS SADIE SINK ¶
¶ AND HER CHILD COSTARS ON
STRANGER THINGS ¶
¶ "STRANGER THINGS" IS ENDING
THEY'LL HAVE SO MUCH FREE TIME ¶
¶ WHAT IF THEY GROW SELF-AWARE
WE NEED TO KEEP THEM OCCUPIED ¶
¶ THEY COULD MOBILIZE THEIR
FOLLOWERS 60 MILLION FOLLOWERS ¶
¶ WE NEED TO KEEP THEM
OCCUPIED ¶
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU
THINK THE DANGER IS.
¶ THE "STRANGER" KIDS USE A
CUBIC MILE OF WATER EVERY
MINUTE ¶
¶ AND IF THERE'S A HELL GATEN
MATARAZZO BELONGS IN IT ¶
>> OH, MY GOD.
¶ THEY'RE TRASHING THE
ENVIRONMENT AND KILLING THE
ECONOMY ¶
¶ VIN WILLS IS THE DEVIL TO ME ¶
>> A DEVIL?
¶ THE SIX OF THEM ARE IN A ROOM
RIGHT NOW
PREPARING TO SEIZE THE
NEXT ELECTION ¶
¶ FOR THESE REASONS I SAY WITH
VECNA ¶
>> THESE KIDS ARE HARMLESS.
ALL THEY DO IS GO ON --
>> THINGS THAT START FUNNY CAN
GET IMPORTANT.
JOE ROGAN USED TO MAKE PEOPLE
EAT BUGS,
AND NOW HE'S THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
¶ EVERYONE'S FOCUSED ON
STRANGER THINGS
AND THEY'RE IGNORING THE STRANGER THING
OF THE STRANGERS ON THE INTERNET
THINKING THESE SIX KIDS AREN'T A DANGER
BUT THEY ARE THE DEVIL ¶
¶ WE'RE STRAYING FROM THE TRUTH
BUT I HAVE A PLAN ¶
¶ A STRING PUT A STICK UNDER A BOX
BIG ENOUGH TO CATCH SIX
STRANGE KIDS ¶
¶ I'LL BE A HERO I'LL WIN AN
AWARD ¶
¶ YOU STOPPED THE APOCALYPSE
PRESIDENT CHATBOT WILL BEAM AT
ME ¶
¶ AS WE SCRAMBLE THE BRAINS OF
THE SIX STRANGE KIDS
AND MAKE
THEM DO ¶
¶ THEY CAN JOIN THE CAST ¶
>> JANE WICKLINE, EVERYBODY.
KRM.
>> THIS IS "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST.
WICKED
PICTURES IS RELEASING SPECIAL
DELETED FOOTAGE
FROM THE MOVIE
THAT STARTED IT ALL, 1939'S "THE
WIZARD OF OZ."
>> WE'RE HERE!
>> OH, I'M SCARED, DOROTHY!
>> I AM OZ!
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL!
WHO ARE YOU?
>> OH -- MY NAME IS DOROTHY.
THE LITTLE AND WHITE.
AND WE COME TO ASK --
>> SHUT UP, GIRL.
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL OZ KNOWS
EXACTLY WHY YOU'VE COME.
STEP FORWARD, TIN MAN.
YOU DARE TO ASK ME FOR A HEART?
>> UM -- WELL, YES, SIR.
YOU SEE, IF I COULD LOVE --
>> SILENCE!
AND YOU, SCARECROW.
YOU DARE ASK ME FOR A BRAIN?
>> YES, YOUR HONOR.
PLEASE.
>> YOU STUPID DUMBASS!
AND YOU.
IS THAT LION I SEE?
>> NO!
DOROTHY, HIDE ME!
>> I BET I ALREADY KNOW WHAT YOU
WANT.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT OUT
LOUD.
>> OH, IT'S OKAY, LION.
>> THIS PATHETIC BAG OF FUR CAME
ALL THIS WAY
JUST TO ASK ME FOR
A BIG OLD THING.
>> A BIG OLD THING?
>> MR. OZ, YOU'VE GOT THAT ALL
WRONG.
>> YEAH.
>> MY FRIEND LION IS ONLY
LOOKING FOR SOME COURAGE.
>> COURAGE?
IS THAT WHAT HE TOLD YOU?
YEAH, RIGHT.
THIS PSYCHO IS LOOKING FOR, AND I QUOTE,
A BIG OLD THING LONG
ENOUGH TO SEE FROM SPACE.
>> WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT,
LION?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE MIXING ME UP WITH
SOMEBODY.
>> I GOT ALL HIS LETTERS RIGHT
HERE.
HE'S BEEN WRITING ME FOR MONTHS.
THIS ONE SAYS, "DEAR MR. OZ.
IT'S YA BOY LION AGAIN,
AND I
REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD BLESS ME
WITH A BIG OLD THANG
THAT I CAN
DRAG ACROSS THE SAND AND SPELL
MY NAME."
>> JESUS, MAN.
>> OR THIS ONE.
"HEY, OZ." IT'S ME, A SICK LITTLE GIRL,
AND
MY LAST DYING WISH IS FOR MY
FRIEND, LION,
TO HAVE A THANG SO
BIG, MUNCHKINS CAN USE IT FOR A
PULL-UP BAR.
SINCERELY, LION.
>> WHAT'S THAT EVEN MEAN?
OH, MY GOD!
WE CAN ASK FOR THAT?
>> ASK FOR WHAT?
>> OH, NOTHING, DOROTHY.
>> OH, COME ON, FELLAS, TELL ME.
DOES A BIG OLD THING MEAN
COURAGE?
>> YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT.
>> BUT LION, DON'T TELL HER
THAT.
>> WELL, LOOK, GUYS.
I HAVE A VERY RARE MEDICAL
CONDITION.
IT'S CALLED HAVING THE SMALLEST
THING IN OZ.
>> HOW SMALL COULD IT BE?
>> WELL, I'M STANDING HERE BUCK
NAKED THIS WHOLE TIME.
AND NOBODY'S FREAKED OUT ONCE.
YOU AIN'T GOT TO BLUR IT OR
NOTHING.
>> WOW.
I GUESS WE HAVEN'T NOTICED.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU SEE?
I NEED THIS, MR. OZ,
SO THAT I
CAN FINALLY WALK BACK TO MY
JUNGLE WITH MY HEAD HELD HIGH
AND MY BIG OLD THING SWINGING
LIKE A CHURCH BELL.
>> WHY WOULDN'T YOU JUST TELL US
THAT'S WHAT YOU REALLY WANTED?
>> BECAUSE I'M A COWARD, DUH.
PLUS, I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS GOING
TO SAY IT OUT LOUD IN FRONT OF
EVERYBODY.
>> OH, PLEASE.
YOU'VE BEEN HERE LIKE EIGHT
TIMES, MAN.
ASKING FOR THE SAME THING.
YOU KNOW HOW THIS GOES.
>> YOU'VE BEEN HERE EIGHT TIMES?
>> SILENCE!
ARGUE
THE BENEVOLENT OZ HAS EVERY INTENTION
OF GRANTING ALL OF YOU
YOUR REQUESTS.
>> FOR REAL?
>> REALLY?
>> OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> YES.
BUT FIRST, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO --
>> PERMISSION TO CHANGE MINE,
SIR!
>> WHAT?
>> PERMISSION TO CHANGE MY WISH
FROM BRAINS TO A BIG OLD THING
TOO, SIR.
I MAY NOT BE VERY SMART, BUT I
KNOW I WANT A BIG OLD BROOMSTICK
THAT CAN FIT THREE WITCHES!
>> BUT SCARECROW, WOULDN'T YOU
RATHER HAVE A BRAIN
SO YOU CAN
READ BOOKS AND COUNT NUMBERS?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> DOROTHY.
LOOK AT ME.
NO.
>> I'D LIKE TO CHANGE MINE TOO,
SIR.
>> BUT TIN MAN, WHAT ABOUT YOUR
HEART?
>> WELL, OF COURSE I'LL STILL
NEED A HEART.
SO I CAN PUMP ENOUGH BLOOD TO
THAT NEW BIG OLD WINBANYAMA!
RIGHT
>> FINE, THREE BIG OLD THINGS IT
IS.
AND AS FOR YOU, DOROTHY --
WAIT
NO.
DON'T TELL ME THE DOG WANTS A
BIG OLD THING TOO.
HELL
OFF MINE
>> TOTO!
>> BUT SERIOUSLY, I NEED YOU ALL
TO MURDER A LADY FOR ME.
BRAD AND HIS
DAD ¶
>> I'M DIVORCED.
>> HEY, BUD, LET'S TAKE A LITTLE
HAT STACKER BREAK, OKAY?
THANKS FOR COMING TO GET A
CHRISTMAS TREE WITH ME, BUD.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> HEY.
WHAT'S WRONG, KIDDO?
>> I WISH I GOT TO SEE YOU ON
CHRISTMAS.
>> I KNOW, BUDDY, BUT IT'S YOUR
MOM'S YEAR.
AND HEY, I'LL SEE YOU THE WEEK
AFTER.
AND YOU KNOW THE BEST THING
ABOUT CHRISTMAS, KIDDO?
OH!
JACKASS!
[ BLEEP ], [ BLEEP ]!
I'LL KILL YOUR CAR!
>> I SPILLED MY PRIME.
>> ALL RIGHT, BUD, LET'S FIND A
TREE.
GRAB YOUR JACKET, BRAD, IT'S
COLD.
>> I'M FINE, I'M NOT COLD.
DAD, I'M COLD.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE GOOD, BUD.
OH, YEAH.
THIS IS PRIMO PINE RIGHT HERE.
YEP, THIS IS THE ONE.
HEY, BRAD.
YOU WANT TO DO THE HONORS?
>> REALLY?
YEAH.
I CAN'T.
>> HOW'S IT GOING DOWN THERE?
>> I CAN'T -- GET IT --
>> TRY TO KEEP IT IN ONE -- TRY
TO MAKE ONE CUT.
>> IT'S SAP -- STICKY -- HARD TO
HOLD THE SAW.
>> YOU KNOW, BUDDY, WHY DON'T I
TAG IN HERE?
WHO'S THAT, BUD?
>> THAT'S EMILY.
THE PRETTIEST GIRL IN MY CLASS.
>> OKAY.
>> SHOULD I GO RIFF HER UP?
>> YEAH, BUD, DO YOUR THING.
GO RIZZ HER DOWN, TOO.
>> HEY, EMILY.
>> HI, BRAD.
COUGH, COUGH!
>> LOOK, SIGN.
KAY, BYE.
>> BYE, BRAD.
>> HEY, DAD.
>> OH!
BUDDY, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
OH, BRAD, LOOK.
IT'S YOUR GIRL.
HERE, I'LL HONK, YOU WAVE.
>> DON'T, DAD, YOU'LL EMBARRASS
ME.
>> OH, COME ON.
HONK HONK!
HEY, MERRY -- JESUS!
OH, [ BLEEP ].
>> HEY, PAL.
>> HEY, DAD, MERRY CHRISTMAS.
GUESS WHAT?
>> OH, ALL RIGHT, LET'S TURN THE
VOLUME DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
DAD HAD A COUPLE OF EGGNOGS AT
SHARKY'S LAST NIGHT.
>> AUNT SHANNON HAS DIARRHEA, SO
WE'RE NOT GOING THERE ANYMORE,
AND MOM SAID THAT I COULD COME
TO YOUR HOUSE TODAY.
>> REALLY.
WELL, THAT'S A CHRISTMAS
MIRACLE.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS, DAD.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS, SON.
HEY.
YOU GOT TO GO.
MY KID'S COMING OVER.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU HAVE A KID?
¶ BRAD ¶
FINAL
>> PROFESSOR HAMNER IS
NOTORIOUS.
>> DO WE WANT TO SHARE OUR
NOTES?
>> YOU GUYS CAN.
I DIDN'T TAKE ANY BECAUSE I KNEW
IT ALREADY.
>> SIMON, DUDE, YOU'RE UNREAL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE IN
COLLEGE AND YOU'RE ONLY 12.
>> IT'S CHILL.
I'M JUST LIKE YOU GUYS.
WORK HARD, PLAY HARD.
>> NO, YOU'RE WAY SMARTER.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN BASICALLY BE
OUR PROFESSOR.
>> PROBABLY WILL BE SOON.
IF I STAY IN ACADEMIA.
>> THAT IS SO BADASS.
OH, SORRY, IS IT OKAY IF WE
SWEAR IN FRONT OF YOU?
>> OF COURSE YOUR EFFING CAN.
I'VE HEARD IT ALL.
IF YOU GUYS HAVE QUESTIONS --
NOT IF, WHEN --
>> HEY, MONEY, HOPE YOUR STUDY
GROUP'S GOING OKAY, I BROUGHT
YOUR LUNCH.
>> HEATHER!
GET OUT OF HERE, HEATHER!
I DON'T NEED THAT, I HAVE A MEAL
PLAN, HEATHER!
DON'T EMBARRASS ME, HEATHER!
BACK
WHAT'S IN IT?
>> UNCRUSTABLES.
>> GRAPE OR STRAWBERRY?
>> BOTH.
>> LEAVE IT.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU.
- HARD
>> SO --
WHERE WE GOING FOR SPRING
BREAK?
>> SIMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, DEFO.
IF WE DO MIAMI, WE CAN GET THERE
BY TRAIN.
>> WAS THAT YOUR MOM?
>> WHAT?
NO.
THAT WOULD BE WEIRD.
I'M JUST LIKE YOU GUYS.
I LIVE IN THE DORMS.
I HAVE A ROOMMATE.
I SHOWER IN MY SHOES.
MY BALLS ARE HAPPENING.
>> OH.
WAIT, WHO'S YOUR ROOMMATE?
RANDOM OLDER WOMAN THEY
PAIRED ME WITH.
>> IS IT YOUR MOM?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> HEY, SIMON, HONEY, YOU FORGOT YOUR
JACKET FOR LATER.
>> NO, HEATHER!
>> OH, COME ON, IT'S COLD
OUTSIDE.
>> HEATHER, TAKE A FORECAST,
HEATHER!
>> IT'S GOING TO BE FREEZING!
>> LEAVE IT.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU!
>> AND YOU'RE SURE THAT'S NOT
YOUR MOM?
>> NOPE.
JUST A GIRL I'M DATING.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> BUT I MIGHT END IT BECAUSE I
WANT TO BE SINGLE FOR MIAMI.
>> SPEAKING OF, WHAT'S THE TEA?
WHO'S HOOKING UP WITH WHO?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WE FEEL
COMFORTABLE TALKING ABOUT THAT.
>> IT'S COOL.
I'VE DONE IT ALL.
I KNOW HOW IT WORKS.
ONE TIME THIS OLD UKRAINIAN LADY
WAS TEACHING ME RACHMANINOFF ON
THE VIOLIN AND I COULD FEEL HER
BREASTS ON MY BACK.
>> THAT'S AWESOME, MAN.
>> IF YOU GUYS NEED MY HELP, I
MAKE AN AWESOME STUDY GUIDE.
I THINK IT LEFT IT IN MY DORM.
>> I HAVE YOUR STUDY GUIDE HERE.
>> HEATHER, DO YOU THINK I NEED
THAT?
DON'T YOU ANTICIPATE MY NEEDS
AND THE NEEDS OF OTHERS,
HEATHER!
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME, YOU REALLY
SAVED THE DAY!
>> WILL YOU PLEASE CALL ME MOM?
>> NO, YOU'RE MY PEER, HEATHER.
>> WHY?
>> I'M TRYING TO HOOK UP WITH
THIS GIRL, HEATHER.
>> OH, HONEY.
>> I CAN TELL SHE'S DOWN.
SHE'S ATTAINABLE, SHE'S NOT TOO
PRETTY, HEATHER.
>> YOU CAN'T DATE AN ADULT.
>> YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS OF ME.
>> YES, I AM.
YOU NEED MY PERMISSION TO GO TO
THIS SCHOOL, I CAN YANK YOU
RIGHT OUT.
>> I CAN'T END UP LIKE THAT,
FOLDING SHIRTS AT OLD NAVY LIKE
THAT, NO!
>> OKAY!
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BY THE WAY, SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT
COMING TO MIAMI.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO MIAMI.
>> IT'S OKAY, SIMON.
THAT'S OBVIOUSLY YOUR MOM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
EMBARRASSED.
>> YEAH, WE ALL KNOW WHAT MOMS
ARE LIKE.
>> YOURS DOES SEEM PRETTY
OVERBEARING.
>> HEY, HEY!
YOU STOP THAT!
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL!
SHE SACRIFICED EVERYTHING!
SHE COULD BE A REPORTER, THAT'S
HOW HOT SHE IS!
I THINK YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A
MOTHER.
>> I ACTUALLY HAVE TWO GAY MOMS.
>> WHAT?
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
TWO HEATHERS?
YOU MIGHT BE SO LOVED!
>> LOOK, I TOTALLY GET IT.
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW BECAUSE SHE
KEPT HER MAIDEN NAME, BUT
PROFESSOR HAMNER IS ACTUALLY MY
MOM.
IT TOOK A LITTLE WHILE TO GET
USED TO.
>> HI, EVERYONE.
BRADLEY, HON, YOU DON'T COME TO
OFFICE HOURS LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
SO I WANTED TO DROP OFF YOUR
LAST PROBLEM SET.
>> BARBARA!
DON'T DO IT, BARBARA!
>> I'M SORRY!
>> BARBARA, NO!
>> I CAN GIVE IT TO YOU LATER!
>> HOW DID I DO, BARBARA?
>> YOU GOT AN "A"!
>> OKAY, LEAVE IT!
>> I HAVE A FRIEND F
AGAIN
Madeline
¶ I KNOW NONE OF THIS
IS YOUR FAULT
MESSAGING YOU FEELS
KIND OF ASSAULTIVE ¶
¶ SAW YOUR TEXT
THAT'S HOW I FOUND OUT
TELL ME THE TRUTH
AND HIS MOTIVES ¶
¶ I CAN'T TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ NO I CAN'T TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ HOW LONG HAS IT
BEEN GOING ON
IS IT JUST SEX
OR IS THERE EMOTION ¶
¶ HE TOLD ME IT WOULD
STAY IN HOTEL ROOMS
NEVER BE OUT IN THE OPEN ¶
¶ WHY WOULD I TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ NO WHY WOULD I
TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ WE HAD AN ARRANGEMENT
BE DISCREET AND
DON'T BE BLATANT ¶
¶ THERE HAD TO BE PAYMENT
IT HAD TO BE
WITH STRANGERS ¶
¶ BUT YOU'RE NOT A STRANGER
MADELINE ¶
>> HEY, HE IS TELLING YOU THE
TRUTH.
OUR RELATIONSHIP HAS ONLY EVER
BEEN ABOUT SEX.
I CAN PROMISE YOU THIS IS NOT AN
EMOTIONAL CONNECTION.
WE DON'T SPEAK OUTSIDE OF THE
TIME WE SPEND TOGETHER.
AND WHENEVER HE TALKS ABOUT YOU
IT'S WITH THE UTMOST RESPECT.
¶ YOU TELL ME
HE'S TELLING THE TRUTH
IS THAT THE CASE OR
A LINE THAT HE FED YOU ¶
¶ WANNA BELIEVE YOU
BUT IS IT A RUSE
LIE TO ME BABE
AND I'LL END YOU ¶
¶ I CAN'T TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ I'M NOT CONVINCED THAT
HE DIDN'T -- IN OUR HOUSE ¶
¶ DO YOU TWO EVER
TALK ABOUT ME
HAS HE TOLD YOU
THAT HE DOESN'T LOVE ME ¶
¶ I BET HE TELLS YOU
TELLS YOU HE LOVES YOU
I'VE GOTTEN OLDER
AND UGLY ¶
¶ I WOULDN'T TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ NOW WHY WOULD YOU
TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ¶
¶ WE HAD AN ARRANGEMENT
BE DISCREET AND
DON'T BE BLATANT ¶
¶ AND THERE HAD TO
BE PAYMENT
IT HAD TO BE
WITH STRANGERS ¶
¶ BUT YOU'RE NOT A STRANGER
MADELINE ¶
¶ MADELINE, MADELINE
¶ BUT YOU'RE NOT A STRANGER
MADELINE ¶
>> I HATE THAT YOU'RE IN SO MUCH
PAIN RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY DON'T WANNA BE THE
CAUSE OF ANY UPSET.
HE TOLD ME YOU WERE AWARE THIS
WAS GOING ON AND THAT HE HAD
YOUR FULL CONSENT.
IF HE'S LYING ABOUT THAT THEN
PLEASE LET ME KNOW BECAUSE I
HAVE MY OWN FEELINGS ABOUT
DISHONESTY.
LIES ARE NOT SOMETHING I WANNA
GET CAUGHT UP IN.
YOU CAN REACH OUT TO ME ANY
TIME, BY THE WAY.
IF YOU NEED ANY MORE DETAILS OR
IF YOU JUST NEED TO VENT OR
ANYTHING.
LOVE AND LIGHT, MADELINE.
SERIES HAVE BEEN A RUNAWAY
SUCCESS WITH HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST
STARS HAVING INTIMATE ONE-ON-ONE
CONVERSATIONS ON THEIR CRAFT.
THIS HOLIDAY SEASON, GET READY
TO LISTEN TO YOUR FAVORITE ICONS
OF CHRISTMAS OUT-COMPLIMENT EACH
OTHER WITH CHARACTERS ON
CHARACTERS.
RUDOLPH AND THE PARTRIDGE IN A
PEAR TREE.
>> WOW.
RUDOLPH, IT IS SUCH AN HONOR TO
BE SITTING ACROSS FROM YOU.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I'M SUCH A HUGE FAN OF YOUR
SONG.
IT'S SUCH AN HONEST PORTRAYAL OF
HOW MANY DAYS THERE ARE OF
CHRISTMAS.
>> WOW.
THAT'S.
>> WOW, THAT'S -- WOW, THAT'S --
AWESOME.
THANK YOU, MAN.
I WANT TO START BY ASKING, WHAT
WAS YOUR TRAIN LIKE BEFORE YOU
STARTED FLYING WITH THE SLEIGH?
>> CAN I CONFESS?
I DON'T HAVE ANY FORMAL
TRAINING.
>> NO, THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
>> REALLY, I'M PART OF AN
ENSEMBLE, WHICH I KNOW YOU
UNDERSTAND.
>> WHEN WE DID "12 DAYS," IT
WAS -- ALL THE TURTLEDOVES, THE
MAIDS A-MILKING.
WHEN YOU WORK ON A SONG LIKE
THAT, JUST --
>> LIKE YOUR CHOSEN FAMILY?
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY, CHOSEN
FAMILY.
>> WATCH AS YOUR HOLIDAY
FAVORITES LIKE SCROOGE AND THE
GRINCH TALK ABOUT PROCESS IN A
WAY THAT MAKES YOU GO -- UGH --
>> I MEAN, TO GET TO SAY THE
WORDS OF DR. SEUSS.
I MEAN, WHAT A PRIVILEGE, YOU
KNOW?
>> OF COURSE.
HOW WAS IT WORKING WITH MAX?
>> OH, MAX THE DOG?
AMAZING, YEAH.
HE'S A GENIUS, HE'S A GENIUS.
YEAH, WE SHOT ON LOCATION IN
WHOVILLE.
AND THE PEOPLE COULD NOT HAVE
BEEN MORE WELCOMING.
I MEAN, WHAT IS GOING ON WITH
THEM POLITICALLY RIGHT NOW?
OH, IT'S UNTHINKABLE.
AND MY 3X HEART GOES OUT TO
THEM.
SO TELL ME ABOUT BAH, HUMBUG.
WAS THAT IMPROV?
>> I'D LIKE TO SAY IT WAS, BUT
THAT WAS ALL CHARLIE.
>> CHARLIE?
OH, DICKENS.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> WOW.
HAVE YOU EVER WORKED WITH HIM?
>> NO, NO, I'M DYING TO.
BUT NOT YET.
YEAH, NO, NO.
>> AND DON'T MISS THE TOUCHING
CONVERSATION BETWEEN TWO FORMER
CHILD STARS.
>> IT'S GOOD TO MEET YOU, TINY
TIM.
>> IT'S JUST TIM NOW.
BUT IT'S AN HONOR TO MEET YOU,
LITTLE DRUMMER BOY.
>> OH, WELL, NOW I GO BY DRUM
DADDY.
>> RIGHT.
RIGHT.
AND I HATE TO ASK THIS, BUT
COULD YOU -- DO THE THING?
>> WHICH THING IS THAT?
>> COME ON, MAN.
DON'T ACT LIKE THERE'S MULTIPLE
THINGS.
>> PA RUM PUM PUM PUM.
>> YES!
MY CHILDHOOD, DUDE.
PA RUM PUM PUM PUM!
I LOVED YOU, MAN.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LITERALLY THE ONLY TWO WOMEN
IN ALL OF CHRISTMAS, MRS. CLAUS
AND THE GRANDMA FROM "GRANDMA
GOT RUN OVER BY A REINDEER."
>> I'M SORRY, I THINK SHE MIGHT
BE DEAD.
>> A AAHHH!
WHERE AM I?
WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
>> VARIETY'S CHARACTERS ON
CHARACTERS.
JUST LET THESE AUTO PLAY ON YOUR
COMPUTER SO THAT A BUNCH OF NICE
PEOPLE CAN STILL GET TO WORK AT
A MAGAZINE.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS!
WE ALL HAD BRUNCH?
>> SERIOUSLY, I LOVE WHEN IT'S
JUST US.
NO HUSBANDS, NO KIDS, NO
FERRETS, NO OFFENSE.
>> PEEPERS PASSED, ACTUALLY.
>> OH, GOD, WE'RE SO SORRY.
>> NO, NO, HE PASSED ON COMING
HERE.
HE HAD A BIG WEEK.
>> SEND PEEPERS OUR LOVE.
HAVE YOU GUYS HEARD LILY ALLEN'S
NEW ALBUM?
I LOVE IT.
>> OBSESSED.
>> HER SONG RATING IS GENIUS.
HER LYRICS ARE SO SPECIFIC.
>> AGREED.
OKAY, BUT WAIT, SOMEONE HAS TO
TAKE THE LAST PIECE OF THIS
FLATBREAD.
>> MINE --
>> OH.
>> SORRY, CAROLINE, DO YOU WANT
IT?
>> NO, GO FOR IT.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
¶ WE ORDERED THE FLATBREAD IT
CAME WITH EIGHT SLICES ¶
¶ THE MATH IS QUITE SIMPLE EIGHT
SLICES DIVIDED ¶
¶ BY JUST PEOPLE WE SHOULD EACH
TWO ¶
¶ MEGAN TOOK THREE SO I WAS
SCREWED ¶
¶ I THOUGHT THAT THAT WAS QUITE
STRANGE ¶
>> EAT IT, I'M NOT EVEN HUGRY.
I'M TOTALLY GLP-1 VIBES.
>> OH.
OKAY, THANKS.
SO ANYONE DOING ANYTHING FUN
AFTER THIS?
>> I HAVE REALLY FUN PLACHCTION.
I'M TAKING PEEPERS TO GET AN
IUD.
>> OH.
I DIDN'T REALIZE PEEPERS WAS A
GIRL FERRET.
>> YEAH, SHE'S JUST MASKED.
>> EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THIS MARG IS A LITTLE TOO SPICY
FOR ME.
>> OH, SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S OUR MISTAKE.
¶ WHEN HE ORDERED HIS DRINK HE
SAID CAN YOU MAKE IT BE SPICY ¶
¶ IT CAN BE REALLY SPICY HE SAID
THAT'S GREAT BECAUSE I REALLY
LIKE SPICY ¶
¶ BUT NOW HE IS PISSED BECAUSE
HIS DRINK IS SO SPICY ¶
¶ AND I THOUGHT I'M GOING TO
SPIT IN HIS DRINK ¶
LET ME FIX THAT RIGHT AWAY, SIR,
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> OH, WAIT.
I HAVE SOME NEWS.
>> WAIT, HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN
ALL'S FAIR?
>> YES, IT'S SO CAMP, I'M
OBSESSED.
>> SARAH PAULINE IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
¶ THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS I GET
INTERRUPTED ¶
>> OH, MY GOD, KIM.
>> SORRY, I HOPE IT'S OKAY I
BROUGHT RYAN.
>> SURE, WE CAN GET ANOTHER
CHAIR.
¶ THIS IS SO AWKWARD I
SPECIFICALLY ASKED IF I WAS
INVITED ¶
¶ I DON'T LIKE HER FRIENDS THEY
DON'T GET MY JOKES ¶
¶ EVEN THOUGH I HAVE GOOD ONES
LIKE ¶
BEEP BEEP!
MAKE ROOM FOR THE DADDYMOBILE!
THIS CAR RUNS ON DADDY JUICE!
¶ THEY THOUGHT THAT THAT WAS
QUITE STRANGE ¶
>> OH!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> THAT WASN'T ME, IT JUST FELL.
>> HOW DOES A MIMOSA FALL ON ITS
OWN?
¶ I JUST DID THAT I DID IT WITH
MY MIND ¶
¶ I'VE BEEN PRACTICING MAGIC
SINCE 2009 ¶
¶ AND I THOUGHT I'M LIKE MATILDA
BUT POOR ¶
>> EXCUSE ME.
WAITER THIS MAN JUST SPILLED A
MIMOSA ON ME.
>> I CAN HELP WITH THAT.
¶ THIS IS SO AWKWARD I DO NOT
WORK HERE ¶
¶ I'M LILY ALLEN LAST WEEK I
WORE THIS TO A CHEESECAKE
FACTORY ¶
¶ I WORKED A WHOLE SHIFT I'M WAY
TOO POLITE ¶
>> WAIT.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK WHO IT IS.
>> ME.
>> NO, IT'S PEEPERS!
>> I GUESS SHE DECIDED TO COME
AFTER ALL.
¶ AND I THOUGHT ¶
¶ I THOUGHT THAT THAT WAS QUITE
STRANGE ¶
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, THANK YOU!