>>> YOU'RE WATCHING "FOX AND
FRIENDS."
>>> GOOD MORNING.
WELCOME TO "FOX AND FRIENDS."
I'M STEVE DOOCY
HERE WITH MY
GOOD FRIENDS BRIAN KILMEADE AND
AINSLEY EARHARDT.
>> THANK YOU, STEVE, AS ALWAYS,
WE'RE COMING TO
YOU LIVE FROM NEW YORK CITY.
NEW YORK, WHAT A CESSPOOL.
THAT'S A DEMOCRAT-RUN CITY FOR
YOU.
>> I KNOW.
JUST TODAY I WAS PUSHED ON TO
THE SUBWAY TRACKS BY A HOMELESS MAN
AND THEN PUSHED BACK ON THE
PLATFORM BY RATS.
>> THAT'S TERRIBLE!
WELL, YOU MAY HAVE HEARD THAT
FOX NEWS IS CURRENTLY FACING
A $1.6 BILLION LAWSUIT FROM
DOMINION VOTING SYSTEMS.
>> I'M SURPRISED.
I'M A FAN OF DA MINIONS.
THE YELLOW GUYS IN THE OVERALLS.
BANANA!
>> NO, BRIAN, NOT THE MINIONS.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE DOMINION
VOTING MACHINES LAWSUIT
AND OUR
BOSS RUPERT MURDOCH GAVE SOME
PRETTY SHOCKING TESTIMONY IN THE
CASE.
>> THIS WHOLE TRIAL HAS BEEN SO
UNFAIR.
THEY ARE RAKING HIM OVER THE
COALS.
RUPERT MURDOCH WOULD NEVER
MURDER ANYONE.
>> WHAT?
>> THEY SENT HIM AWAY FOR LIFE.
LOOK HOW SAD HE LOOKS.
WHERE'S THAT PICTURE I FOUND OF
HIM?
>> THAT'S NOT RUPERT MURDOCH.
THAT'S ALEX MURDAUGH.
WRONG GUY
EXPLAIN LATER
ANYWAY, RUPERT MURDOCH ADMITTED
FOX NEWS AIRED ELECTION FRAUD CONSPIRACIES
TO GET RATINGS
EVEN
THOUGH EVERYONE HERE KNEW THEY
WERE FALSE.
>> UH-OH, I DIDN'T.
LOOP A BROTHER IN NEXT TIME.
>> NOW, YOU MAY BE WONDERING IF
IT'S SUCH A BIG STORY
WHY
HAVEN'T I HEARD ABOUT IT ON FOX?
>> I THINK IT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE
SUING US FOR $1.6 BILLION
>> NO.
IT'S BECAUSE IT'S COMPLETE BS.
THE MEDIA IS TAKING TWEETS
AND PUTTING THEM COMPLETELY OUT OF
CONTEXT.
>> LIKE THIS ONE.
RUDY GIULIANI IS INSANE.
HOW COULD YOU LEAVE OUT THE
REST?
IT'S RUDY GIULIANI IS INSANELY
HOT.
I WANT TO LICK THAT HEAD DYE
RIGHT OFF.
>> WHO WOULDN'T?
AND SOME MESSAGES THEY SHOWED AT THE TRIAL
DIDN'T RELATE TO THE
LAWSUIT AT ALL.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE TEXT, MIND
BLOWINGLY-NUTS,
OFF THE RAILS,
AND F'ing LUNATIC
WERE ALL SENT
IN RESPONSE TO LAURA INGRAM'S TEXT,
WHAT SHOULD I PUT IN MY
TINDER BIO?
>> YOU GO, GIRL.
ALL RIGHT
GUEST
APPEARANCE ON FOX
WERE
TRIAL.
FOX NEWS
ADVERTISER
MYPILLOW
HELLO
I'M DOWN AT CPAC RIGHT NOW,
AND IT IS AN ABSOLUTE BLAST.
I WAS JUST OVER AT THE BIDEN DID
YOU THINK TANK.
IT'S NOT THE REAL BIDEN YOU DID
YOU THINK, BUT THE ACTOR IS JUST AS OLD,
SO YOU NEVER KNOW IF
HE'S COMING BACK UP.
THERE'S REAL RISK THERE.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
WE'RE GLAD TO HAVE YOU ON,
BUT
BECAUSE OF THIS LAWSUIT, OUR
LAWYERS HAVE ASKED YOU
PLEASE
DON'T SAY ANYTHING CRAZY ABOUT
DOMINION.
>> NO PROBLEM.
I HAVE BEEN BRIEFED.
I KNOW THE RULES.
EVERY DOMINION MACHINE HAS A
VENEZUELAN OOMPAH LOOMPAH INSIDE
THAT EATS THE VOTES WITH ITS
LITTLE MOUTH.
>> MIKE, GOT TO CUT YOU OFF
THERE, PAL.
WE CAN'T BE SAYING WHATEVER
ANYMORE.
>> OF COURSE.
LET ME CHOOSE MY WORDS
CAREFULLY.
DOMINION VOTING MACHINES GIVE
TRIPLE VOTES TO DEMOCRATS, ILLEGALS
AND THAT LADY M&M THAT
STOPPED SHAVING HER PITS.
>> MIKE!
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO END IT
THERE.
>> THAT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
I HAVE TO SAY THIS WHOLE
DOMINION THING HAS BEEN A NIGHTMARE
FOR ME AND MY FAMILY,
ESPECIALLY MY WIFE.
SORRY, PILLOWMINA, YOU KNOW IT'S
TRUE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'LL TALK
MORE ABOUT THE ALEX MURDAUGH SENTENCING
WITH OUR FOX CRIME
EXPERT, O.J. SIMPSON.
>> WHAT?
MAN, I DON'T KNOW WHY EVERYBODY
THINKS I'M AN EXPERT ON THIS.
SHOOT, BOOKING ME ON THE SHOW
WITHOUT TELLING ME WHY.
MAKES ME SO MAD I COULD JUST --
NAH, I'M OKAY.
AND HEY, MAN, LIVE FROM NEW
YORK, IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, TRAVIS
KELCE!
YOU SO VERY MUCH.
IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE.
AND IF YOU DON'T KNOW, I JUST
WON MY SECOND SUPER BOWL.
OH, MAN.
WHICH WAS AMAZING.
BUT FOR ME, HOSTING SNL
IS THAT
MUCH BETTER, BABY.
I'M LYING TO YOU ALL.
I'M LYING.
I'M KIDDING.
WINNING THE SUPER BOWL WAS WAY
BETTER.
BUT SERIOUSLY.
SERIOUSLY, I'M HONORED THAT SNL
ASKED ME TO HOST.
I WAS NERVOUS ABOUT DOING A
MONOLOGUE,
BUT THEN I
REMEMBERED, I'M PRETTY GOOD WITH
WORDS.
I'M PRETTY GOOD WITH WORDS, LIKE
DURING GAMES,
I DO THESE SUPER
ELOQUENT PUMP-UP SPEECHES FOR MY
TEAMMATES.
PLEASE WATCH.
MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE,
MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE.
AND SOMETIMES I EVEN DO IT IN MY
PAT MAHOMES VOICE,
MORE, MORE,
DO IT, DO IT.
LOVE YOU, PAT.
PROBABLY THE COOLEST THING ABOUT
THIS SUPER BOWL
IS THAT MY WHOLE
FAMILY WAS THERE.
I GOT TO PLAY AGAINST MY BROTHER
JASON, WHO IS AN EAGLE.
AND MY MOM WAS ON TV MORE THAN
BOTH OF US.
MY MOM, DAD, AND BROTHER ARE ALL
HERE TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, PEOP KEEP ASKING ME
WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO BEAT MY
BROTHER IN THE SUPER BOWL,
AND
IT WAS PRETTY AWKWARD.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE AFTER THE
GAME, WE HAD TO RIDE HOME
TOGETHER.
OUR MOM DROVE US THERE IN HER MINI VAN,
JUST LIKE THE GOOD OLD
DAYS.
EVEN THOUGH HIS TEAM LOST AFTER
BEING UP TEN POINTS AT HALF,
MY
BROTHER IS ACTUALLY REALLY HAPPY
FOR ME.
AND HE AGREES THAT THE REF MADE
THE RIGHT CALL.
IT WAS A HOLDING.
JASON AND I HAVE BEEN PLAYING
FOOTBALL TOGETHER SINCE WE WERE
LITTLE KIDS.
AND HE WAS ALWAYS BETTER THAN
ME -- AT EVERYTHING.
IN HIGH SCHOOL, HE WAS AN HONOR STUDENT,
AND I GOT KICKED OFF
THE TEAM BECAUSE I FAILED FRENCH,
AND ENGLISH TOO, BUT
FRENCH SOUNDS WAY BETTER.
AND THEN, WHEN WE WERE IN
COLLEGE, I ACTUALLY GOT KICKED OFF THE TEAM
BECAUSE I TESTED
POSITIVE FOR MARIJUANA.
SO IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU, IF
YOU SMOKE WEED AND ARE BAD AT SCHOOL,
YOU CAN WIN THE SUPER
BOWL TWICE.
THIS ISN'T MY FIRST TIME HOSTING
A TV SHOW.
I ACTUALLY HAD MY OWN DATES SHOW ON E
CALLED CATCHING KELCE.
IT WAS LIKE THE BACHELOR EXCEPT
INSTEAD OF HANDING OUT ROSES, I
HANDED OUT FOOTBALLS,
AND
INSTEAD OF WATCHING, PEOPLE DID
NOT.
WHICH WAS A LITTLE BIT
EMBARRASSING.
BUT I HAVE TO SAY, I GOT PRETTY
GOOD AT REALITY TV.
CHECK THIS ONE OUT.
WHAT DO WE NAME THIS?
>> STANLEY.
>> AVERY IS HYSTERICAL.
RIGHT?
THAT SHOW IS OWNED BY NBC
UNIVERSAL, SO IT SHOULD BE ON PEACOCK,
BUT PEACOCK SAID, NAH,
WE GOOD.
I KNEW SOMETHING WOULD MAKE HIM
SMILE.
BUT REALLY, IT'S COOL TO BE
HERE.
I GREW UP WATCHING SNL WITH MY
MOTHER.
I LOVE FARRELL, THE SANDMAN CHRIS FARLEY,
AND TO BE STANDING ON THIS STAGE,
WHEW, PRETTY
SURREAL.
AND TONIGHT, I'M GOING TO GIVE
IT EVERYTHING I GOT.
AS A WISE MAN ONCE SAID,
MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE AND MORE!
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT!
KELSEA BALLERINI IS HERE!
STICK
>>> AND SOME MORE TEA FOR
CLAIRABELLE?
BUT MAKE SURE YOU TELL
CLAIRABELLE IT'S H, OKAY?
>> OKA
>> THANK YOU.
HI THERE!
WELCOME TO AMERICAN GIRL CAFE.
I'M SHANE, I'LL BE TAKING CARE
OF YOU THIS AFTERNOON.
I STILL SEE YOU'RE WAITING ON
SOME FOLKS?
>> NOPE.
GANG'S ALL HERE.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU'RE NOT WAITING FOR YOUR
DAUGHTER OR YOUR NIECE?
>> NOPE.
IT'S JUST ME AND THE GIRLS.
THIS IS CLAIRE, THAT'S ISABELLE.
>> OKEYDOKEY.
I ALWAYS START BY ASKING IF
THERE ARE ANY FOOD ALLERGIES I
SHOULD BE AWARE OF?
>> NO.
BUT THIS ONE IS DOING KETO RIGHT
NOW.
>> AND ARE YOU ALLOWED WITHIN A
THOUSAND FEEOF A SCHOOL?
>> YES.
WHY?
>> JUST A STANDARD QUESTION WE
ASK ALL OF OUR PATRONS.
CAN I START YOU OUT WITH
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
>> A GLASS OF ROSE.
I'LL NEED A DRINK TO GET ME
THROUGH LUNCH WITH THESE TWO
DRAMA QUEENS.
>> WONDERFUL.
I JUST NEED TO SEE YOUR ID.
SO SORRY.
THEY MAKE US ASK EVERYONE.
THANKS.
AND SO YOU DON'T HAVE ANY OTHER
NAMES YOU USE, RIGHT?
THIS IS THE NAME THAT WOULD
APPEAR ON ANY ONLINE COURT
DOCUMENTS OR REGISTERED ON ANY
GOVERNMENT LIST?
>> THAT'S THE ONE.
BUT THE ONLY LIST YOU'LL FIND ME
ON IS THE HUNGRIEST CUSTOMER
LIST.
>> RIGHT.
OKAY.
SHALL I BRING YOU SOME MENUS
THEN?
>> NO NEED.
I ALREADY KNOW WHAT I WANT.
I'LL HAVE A 64-OUNCE PORTER
HOUSE, RARE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, WE DO NOT
SERVE GIANT STEAKS HERE.
IT'S JUST A CAFE.
>> OH, WELL, WE'LL NEED MENUS
THEN.
FYI, DON'T BRING OUT ANY KIDS
MENUS FOR THE GIRLS.
ISABELLE JUST HAD HER PERIOD,
AND SHE THINKS SHE'S A WOMAN
NOW.
>> WONDERFUL.
THANK YOU FOR TELLING ME THAT.
LET
AROUSED.
NOPE.
ALL CLEAR.
OKAY.
I'LL BE BACK SHORTLY.
>> HI.
MY DAUGHTER'S SHY, BUT SHE
WANTED TO KNOW IF YOUR DOLLS
WANTED SOME OF HER PIZZA.
>> THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
THEY DON'T NEED THE CALORIES,
AND FRANKLY, NEITHER DOES YOUR
DAUGHTER.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ME?
>> THE TRUTH, HONEY.
BYE NOW.
>> HI THERE.
I'M LUCY, THE MANAGER.
JUST A SAFETY THING WE DO HERE.
YOU MIN ALWAYS KEEPING BOTH
HANDS ON THE TABLE, JUST SO WE
KNOW YOU'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING
UNAPPROPRIATE UNDER THERE?
SORRY IT'S A VESTIGE OF THE
COVID ERA.
ENJOY.
>> WOW.
HOW COOL IS THIS SWEETHEART?
I HOPE LOGAN IS HUNGRY.
>> UH-OH, CHECK YOUR MAKEUP,
GIRLS.
BOY ALERT.
>> UMM, HELLO.
IS THERE A REASON THAT YOUR
DOLLS ARE LOOKING AT US, SIR?
>> YOU BRING A STUD LIKE THAT IN
HERE, HE'S GOING TO TURN A FEW
HEADS.
>> YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
THAT GENTLEMAN AT THAT TABLE --
>> OH, HE IS HERE ALONE, BUT HE
SEEMS TO BE HARMLESS.
>> SO HE'S NOT --
>> AROUSED?
NO, I CHECKED.
>> AND YOU'RE SURE HE'S
HARMLESS?
>> ISABELLE SAID SHE WAS HOT,
BUT I THINK SHE WANTED TO SHOW
HER BODY OFF.
>> YEAH, HE TALKING ABOUT
SHOWING OFF THE BODY OF A DOLL.
THAT'S NOT MY FAVORITE THING
I'VE HEARD TODAY.
HE'S COMING OVER HERE.
OKAY.
>> LET THE FLIRTING BEGIN.
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S ON THE PILL.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME JUST -- DARIUS, CAN
YOU --
>> WHAT'S UP?
LUCY SAID WE HAVE A POSSIBL
CREEPER IN HERE.
>> YEAH, OVER THERE.
>> DON'T WORRY, SIR.
I'M ON IT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HEY, LISTEN UP, PERVERT!
YOU DO ANYTHING SHADY IN HERE,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A PROBLEM.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
>> WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY TO ME?
>> THE TRUTH, HONEY.
>>> WHERE ARE OUR COFFEES?
WASN'T AN INTERN SUPPOSED TO
GRAB THEM?
>> LET ME CHECK.
LOOKS LIKE THEY SAID, WE DON'T
GET COFFEES FOR LITTLE BITCH
BOYS.
>> AGAIN?
>> COME ON, MAN, ARE WE LITTLE
BITCH BOYS?
>> WE NEED TO LEARN HOW TO STICK
UP FOR OURSELVES.
>> WE CAN'T KEEP GETTING BULLIED
BY INTERNS.
I THINK I KNOW SOMEONE WHO CAN
HELP US.
SELF
>> I'M KURT LIGHTNING,
AND I KNOW WHY YOU ALL SIGNED UP FOR
MY CLASS.
YOU'RE SEARCHING FOR CONFIDENCE.
THE CONFIDENCE OF NOT ONLY
KNOWING YOU CAN DEFEND YOURSELF,
BUT THAT YOU'RE SOMEBODY WORTH
DEFENDING.
SAY IT WITH ME, I AM WORTH IT.
>> I AM WORTH IT.
>> SAY IT LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
>> I AM WORTH IT!
>> FEEL IT!
YOU, GET UP HERE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, SON?
>> JOHN.
>> OH, JOHN, I CAN HEAR IT IN
YOUR VOICE.
YOU FEEL SMALL, DON'T YOU, SON?
>> YES.
>> YOU GOT TO OWN IT, SON, OWN
YOUR TRUTH.
>> I FEEL SMALL.
>> BUT YOU'RE NOT SMALL.
PUT YOUR HANDS UP.
I AM GOING TO STRIKE,
AND WHEN I
STRIKE, YOU DEFLECT, AND I WANT YOU TO HIT ME BACK,
AND WHEN YOU
DO, IMAGINE I'M THE VOICE IN YOUR HEAD
TELLING YOU YOU AREN'T
WORTH IT.
BECAUSE WHAT ARE YOU?
>> I AM WORTH IT!
>> NOW, ARE YOU READY?
>> I AM RED --
>> DUDE!
>> TOO SLOW, FATSO.
WHO'S NEXT?
>> TOM, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT TO HIM?
>> YOU'RE NEXT.
>> I'M --
>> WHY ARE YOU SO AFRAID, SON?
>> YOU PUNCHED MY FRIEND, AND
I'M WORRIED HE'S DEAD.
>> YOU'RE AFRAID YOUR FATHER WAS
RIGHT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
HIM.
>> THAT'S NOT AN OPTION
BECAUSE
YOUR FATHER WAS WRONG.
>> KURT, PLEASE.
>> YOU ARE A MAN, AND I NEED YOU
TO TELL HIM.
>> HOW?
>> CLOSE YOUR EYES.
>> DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE, BUCKO!
HE REALLY CLOSED HIS EYES.
>> IS THIS WHAT THE CLASS IS?
>> YOU HAVE BEEN SCARED YOUR
WHOLE LIFE.
>> OH, NO.
>> YOU LOST YOUR MOTHER AT A
YOUNG AGE.
>> THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
>> BECAUSE YOUR FATHER WASN'T
THERE TO PROTECT HER.
>> YOU'RE MAKING STUFF UP, MAN.
>> AND I'M HERE TO SHOW YOU A
MAN CAN DEFEND THE ONES HE
LOVES.
I WANT YOU TO PUNCH THIS WOMAN
RIGHT HERE.
>> NO WAY.
>> AND I WILL DEFLECT YOUR
STRIKE.
>> WHY ARE WE DOING THIS?
>> BECAUSE I WANT TO SHOW YOU A
REAL MAN DEFENDS THE WOMAN HE
LOVES.
>> BUT YOU'RE POSITIVE YOU WILL
BLOCK IT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> BECAUSE IF I HIT THIS WOMAN,
SHE WILL DIE.
>> PUNCH HER OR I'M GOING TO
PUNCH YOU.
>> OKAY.
YOU GOT IT.
>> NICE TRY, BITCH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BOOM, SHELLY, YOU DID THAT
DAMN THING.
>> DID A REVOLVER COME OUT OF
YOUR PANTS?
WHY DO YOU HAVE THIS?
>> BECAUSE I LIVE IN FEAR.
WHY DO YOU THINK I'M IN THIS
CLASS?
>> GIVE ME THAT.
>> YOU WANT TO PLAY A GAME?
>> WHAT?
RUSSIAN ROULETTE?
>> FEELING LUCKY, SLICK?
>> COME ON, DON'T DO IT!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, MY GOD.
>> GREAT WORK, GUYS.
YOU FINALLY STOOD UP FOR
YOURSELVES.
>> WHAT THE HELL YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
>> I THINK SOMEBODY OWES YOU
SOME COFFEES.
>> WHAT?
THE INTERNS.
>> HEY, GUYS.
AFTER YOU SHOVED THAT OLD LADY
INTO THE TROPHY CASE,
I FINALLY
RESPECT YOU.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> AND HERE'S YOUR COFFEE.
MOTHER, GRANDMOTHER, AND LOVER
MS. GLENDA.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T KNOW
ME, MY NAME IS DYLAN.
I WAS GLENDA'S NURSE, AND WE HAD
AN INTIMATE LOVING RELATIONSHIP
IN HER FINAL MONTHS.
>> WAIT.
MAMA STARTED DATING HIM?
>> WELL, GOOD FOR YOU, MAMA.
THAT MAN IS FINE.
>> I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT GLENDA
WAS TO YOU ALL, SO I ORGANIZED
AND FUNDED THIS HOME GOING
SERVICE IN HER HONOR.
IF YOU KNEW GLENDA, YOU KNEW SHE
WAS A FREE SPIRIT.
>> YEAH, WHAT YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> SO I THOUGHT SHE WOULD BE
LAID TO REST HOW WE ALL KNEW
HER.
TA DA.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
>> THIS WHITE BOY GOT OUR DEAD
MAMA SITTING UP!
>>
DO.
SHADES ON, WORLD OUT, PUFFING ON
A MENTHOL, THAT'S MY GLENDA.
>> HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO HER?
SHE LOOKS CRAZY.
>> AT LEAST HE GOT HER IN A NICE
SHIRT.
>> THAT'S GLENDA.
LITTLE MAMA ALWAYS DOING.
YOU KNOW IT HIT DIFFERENT WHEN
THEY IN THE NIGHT GOWN.
NOW, I WOULD LIKE TO OPEN THE
FLOOR TO FRIENDS AND FAMILY SO
THEY CAN SHARE A FEWOR IN
GLENDA'S MEMORY.
>> HI.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M NOT GOING TO
LET VANILLASAURUS REX OVER HERE
RUIN MY MAMA'S FUNERAL.
SHE WAS A GOOD MAMA, TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING I KNEW.
SHE WAS STRONG.
STOP IT.
SHE HAD A SMILE FOR EVERY
STRANGER AND A STORY FOR EVERY
OCCASION.
I SWEAR, IT'S LIKE I CAN ALMOST
HEAR HER VOICE NOW.
>> CLOSE THAT DOOR.
YOU LETTING ALL THE GOOD AIR
OUT.
>> HOLD ON.
WHAT THE --
>> DON'T YOU EMBARRASS ME IN
FRONT OF THESE WHITE PEOPLE.
>> DOPE, RIGHT?
THEY RIGGED HER UP, PUT A
SPEAKER IN HER.
AND ALL OF HER FAVORITE SAYINGS
ARE RIGHT THERE.
>> JAY JAY ACTING STUCK UP
BECAUSE HE GOT THAT SMALL-HEADED
WHITE GIRLFRIEND WITH HIM.
>> ME?
MY HEAD ISN'T SMALL.
>> WAIT, YOU PROGRAMMED HER TO
>> CLOSE THAT DOOR, YOU LET --
LET -- LET -- LET.
>> OH, SHE'S STUCK.
I GOT THIS.
>> LET -- LET -- LETTING ALL THE
GOOD AIR OUT.
>> HEY, MAN.
YOU JUST BLOW OUT MY MAMA'S HEAD
LIKE SHE WAS A NINTENDO
CARTRIDGE?
>> LET'S MOVE ON.
GLENDA DIDN'T WANT THIS TO BE A
SAD SERVICE.
D.J. ROSCOE, HIT IT.
♪
GO AHEAD, MS. GLENDA, WITH YOUR
BAD SELF.
>> YOU PUT HYDRAULICS ON MY
GRANDMA?
>> WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH
YOU?
>> HEY, I SPENT $30,000 ON THIS,
AND THAT'S EVERY PENNY THAT SHE
HAD.
AND I'LL BE DAMNED IF I SPEND IT
IN VAIN.
Y'ALL ARE GOING TO SIT BACK AND
WATCH YOUR MAMA GO TO HEAVEN.
>> CLOSE THAT DOOR.
YOU LETTING ALL THE GOOD AIR
OUT.
>> CHEERED!
LIKE MOST GAY MEN, I HAVE A LOT
OF STRAIGHT FEMALE FRIENDS,
AND I LOVE MY GIRLIES,
BUT THEY CAN
BE A LOT, BOTH FINANCIALLY.
>> WAIT, CARSON, YOU'RE COMING
TO TULUM, RIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW IT, SIS.
AND EMOTIONALLY.
>> TULUM IS WHERE DYLAN AND I
WERE SUPPOSED TO GO BEFORE WE
BROKE UP.
>> I'M SO SORRY, BABE.
AS MUCH AS THESE GIRLS MEAN TO
ME, SOMETIMES I NEED A BREAK.
THAT'S WHEN I DISCOVERED,
STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND.
>> WHAT'S UP?
YO, WATCH ME HEAD CHOP THIS
BITCH.
BOOM TO THE DOOM.
>> AMAZING.
STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND IS A
LOW-EFFORT, LOW-STAKES RELATIONSHIP
THAT REQUIRES NO
EMOTIONAL COMMITMENT, NO
FINANCIAL INVESTMENT,
AND OTHER
THAN THE OCCASIONAL VIDEO GAME
OUTBURST --
>> THIS GAME'S STUPID!
>> -- NO DRAMA.
>> YO, YOU WANT TO GO GET WINGS?
>> IF I DIDN'T CHECK IN WITH MY
GAL PALS EVERY DAY OR TWO,
IT WOULD
BECOME A WHOLE THING.
NO
HANG OUT AS LITTLE OR AS MUCH AS
YOU WANT.
IT WON'T AFFECT THE FRIENDSHIP
AT ALL.
WATCH THIS.
HEY, I MIGHT BE MOVING TO EUROPE
FOR SEVEN YEARS.
>> DOPE.
JUST HIT ME WHEN YOU'RE BACK.
STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND IS EASY,
AND EVEN IF HE'S HAVING A TOUGH
TIME EMOTIONALLY, HE'LL NEVER
BRING ME INTO IT.
YOU OKAY?
YOU SEEM A LITTLE UPSET.
>> MAN, MY DAD DIED LAST WEEK.
>> BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW?
>> YOU WANT TO GET SOME WINGS?
>> YEAH.
STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND ISN'T PERFECT
AND MAY ASK BLUNT
QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SEX LIFE.
>> SO DO GAY GUYS LIKE WHEN A
GUY HAS A BIG ONE,
OR IS IT A
BAD THING?
>> DEPENDS ON THE GUY.
BUT HE'S ONLY ASKING BECAUSE
HE'S HONESTLY CURIOUS,
AND
THERE'S SOMETHING SWEET ABOUT
THAT.
DOES STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND
PROVIDE THE SAME DEEP REWARDING
RELATIONSHIP I HAVE WITH MY
GIRLS?
NO.
DOES STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND KNOW
MY LAST NAME?
NO.
THAT'S KIND OF THE BEAUTY OF
IT.
BUT IF YOU ARE MISSING A LITTLE
DRAMA, JUST SAY THIS.
I BET I'M FASTER THAN YOU.
>> DOG, BRO, FOR REAL?
YOU THINK YOU'RE FASTER THAN ME?
I WILL GO OUTSIDE ON THE STREET
AND DUST YOUR ASS RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
>> SO IF YOU'RE A GAY MAN WHO NEEDS A BREAK,
COME ENJOY THE
CASUAL RELATIONSHIP GAY WOMEN
HAVE KNOWN ABOUT FOR YEARS.
STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND.
>> SORRY FOR BEING A PUSSY ABOUT
MY DAD DYING EARLIER.
THAT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> STRAIGHT MALE FRIEND,
AVAILABLE EVERYWHERE.
EXCEPT THERAPY.
>>> OKAY.
THAT MOVIE WAS WILD.
>> YEAH, "PADDINGTON 3" WAS NOT
WHAT I EXPECTED.
>> THAT WAS "COCAINE BEAR."
>> OKAY.
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT
PADDINGTON.
>> SHOOT, ABBY, GRAHAM IS HERE.
>> ABBY, WE CAN TOTALLY LEAVE.
>> LOOK, Y'ALL, IT'S BEEN THREE
YEARS, I CAN BE AROUND MY EX.
M TOTALLY COOL.
HEY, STRANGER.
HOW ARE YOU, BUBBA?
>> WHOA, ABBY, IS BEEN A
MINUTE.
WHAT'S NEW?
>> I'M ACTUALLY IN THE BEST
PLACE I HAVE BEEN IN A LONG
TIME.
I'M WITH SOMEONE NEW, AND LIFE
IS PRETTY RAD.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU LOOK LIKE HELL.
JUST KIDDING.
YOU LOOK AWESOME.
>> OH, YEAH, I'VE BEEN GOOD.
WORKING OUT A LOT.
OH, AND THANKS FOR PAYING ME
BACK ABOUT MY CAR GETTING FIXED.
>> YEAH.
SORRY I THREW THAT KETTLE BELL
THROUGH YOUR WINDSHIELD.
I HAD A LOT TO PROCESS, BUT NOW
I CAN LOOK AT YOU WITH NO
ATTACHMENT, AND I THINK THAT'S
PRETTY FREAKING RAD.
>> SORRY, BABE.
THE LINE FOR THE BATHROOM WAS
CRAZ
>> HI, BABE.
THIS IS MADISON.
>> OH, YOU TWO ARE TOGETHER.
CONGRATS.
YOU GOT YOURSELF A STUNNING
GIRLFRIEND.
>> THIS IS MY FIANCE.
>> YOUR --
>> ABBY, ARE YOU CRYING?
>> NO.
REMEMBER I JUST HAD THAT THING
WITH MY EYES WHERE I HAVE TO
POKE AT THEM.
>> I DON'T.
BUT IF YOU SAY SO.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
SO HOW DID YOU TWO MEET?
>> WE MET ON A LITTLE CRUISE.
>> WELL, IT WASN'T A CRUISE FOR
ME.
I'M A BOSUN ON BELOW DECK.
>> THAT'S MY DREAM JOB.
>> ABBY, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> IT'S THE EYE THING AGAIN.
I'M FINE.
I MIGHT JUST HAVE TO HOLD THEM.
YOU GUYS CAN KISS IF YOU WANT.
I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S ASS.
>> WE'RE REALLY NOT TRYING TO
KISS AT THIS MOMENT.
>> SO HOW DO YOU GUYS KNOW EACH
OTHER?
H, GOD, GIRL, HOW LONG DO
YOU HAVE?
>> ABBY AND I WENT ON ONE DATE
IN 2019.
>> OKAY.
WE WENT ON THREE DATES.
DINNER, MOVIE, AND A
WALK.
>> THE WALK WAS FROM DINNER TO
THE MOVIE, AND THE WHOLE THING
WAS LIKE TWO HOURS.
>> IRREGARDLESS, GRAHAM AND I
HAVE HISTORY, BUT NOW I THINK
WE'RE KILLING THIS FRIENDS
THING, BUBBA.
>> WE'RE MOVING NEXT MONTH, BUT
YOU'LL HAVE TO COME VISIT US IF
YOU'RE EVER IN NEW ORLEANS.
>> WHERE THE SAINTS GO MARCHING
IN?
>> OH, MY GOD, ABBY, DO YOU NEED
A TISSUE?
>> NO.
BECAUSE THESE ARE HAPPY TEARS.
>> WELL, THANKS.
WE'RE REALLY HAPPY TOO.
IT FEELS LIKE A GREAT PLACE TO
RAISE A KID.
>> YOU'RE PREGNANT?
YES!
>> WE'RE DUE IN AUGUST, BUT
MAYBE WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE?
I'M STARTING TO FEEL BAD.
>> YOU SHOULDN'T.
IT WAS ONE DATE.
>> OKAY.
LOOK.
NONE OF THAT MATTERS NOW,
BECAUSE LIKE I SAID, I'M IN A
RELATIONSHIP, AND IT'S SO GOOD.
HE'S A LITTLE BIT OLDER, AND
HE'S TOTALLY RIPPED.
>> ABBY, THAT'S GREAT FOR YOU.
I'M HAPPY.
>> HEY, BUBBA.
SORRY I'M LATE.
IS THIS GUY BOTHERING YOU?
DO YOU NEED ME TO BEAT HIM UP?
BECAUSE I DEFINITELY COULD.
>> WAIT.
THAT'S YOUR BOYFRIEND?
IT'S TOTALLY COOL.
OH, MY GOD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ WERE YOU ON THE OTHER LINE
OR DRIVING IN YOUR CAR
WERE YOU HIDING UPSTAIRS
OR PLAYING YOUR GUITAR ♪
♪ WAS THERE NOTHING
EVER WRONG
'CAUSE YOU WERE
ALWAYS RIGHT ♪
♪ TELL ME
WERE YOU BLINDSIDED
OR WERE YOU JUST BLIND ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU'RE SAYING
THAT YOU'RE LOST
AND THAT'S LOST ON ME ♪
♪ YEARS OF SITTING
ACROSS FROM ME IN THERAPY ♪
♪ I KNOW THE TRUTH
IS HARD TO HEAR
BUT IT WASN'T HARD TO FIND ♪
♪ BABY WERE YOU BLINDSIDED
OR WERE YOU JUST BLIND
WERE YOU JUST BLIND ♪
♪ I'D GO WRITE A SONG
AND YOU'D GO FOR A WALK
WE HAD TO T DRUNK
TO EVER REALLY TALK ♪
♪ I TOLD YOU AT I NEEDED
DIDN'T HAVE TO READ MY MIND
SO WERE YOU BLINDSIDED
OR WERE YOU JUST BLIND ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU'RE SAYING
THAT YOU'RE LOST
AND THAT'S LOST ON ME ♪
♪ YOU DIDN'T EVER
WANNA LEAVE THE HOUSE
OR DIDN'T WANT A FAMILY ♪
♪ I KNOW THE TRUTH
IS HARD TO HEAR
BUT IT WASN'T HARD TO FIND ♪
♪ BABY WERE YOU BLINDSIDED
OR WERE YOU JUST BLIND
WERE YOU JUST
WERE YOU JUST ♪
♪ LIKE THAT ONE TIME IN 2019
BEFORE THAT BIG SHOW
WE HAD A BIG FIGHT ♪
♪ I SLEPT ON THE COUCH
AND THEN THE NEXT NIGHT
YOU PUT ON YOUR SUIT ♪
♪ I PUT ON A SMILE
AND SANG ABOUT
HOW IT'S OKAY TO CRY
DYING INSIDE ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU'RE SAYING
THAT YOU'RE LOST
AND THAT'S LOST ON ME ♪
♪ TELL ME
WHEN DID I START
LOOKING LIKE THE ENEMY ♪
♪ I KNOW THE TRUTH
IS HARD TO HEAR
YOU'VE GOT YOURS
AND I'VE GOT MINE ♪
♪ BABY WERE YOU BLINDSIDED
OR WERE YOU JUST BLIND
WERE YOU JUST BLIND YEAH
WERE YOU JUST BLIND ♪
♪ WHOA YEAH
WERE YOU WERE YOU JUST BLIND
BABY YEAH ♪
♪
♪ NOW YOU'RE SINGING
OUT LOUD ON THE RADIO
YOU COULDN'T SAY
IT TO MY FACE ♪
♪ YOU WOULD'VE
SEARCHED THE WHOLE WORLD OVER
YEAH SURE OKAY ♪
♪ NOW YOU'RE SINGING
OUT LOUD ON THE RADIO
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY HEART
THAT BREAKS ♪
♪ YOU WOULD'VE
SEARCHED THE WHOLE WORLD OVER
YEAH SURE OKAY ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
TENNESSEE GOVERNOR BILL LEE
SIGNED A NEW LAW BANNING PUBLIC
DRAG PERFORMANCES
WITH A
SIX-YEAR PRISON SENTENCE FOR
REPEAT OFFENDERS
AS FIRST
PREDICTED IN THE
NOW-DOCUMENTARY,
MADEA GOES TO JAIL.
A TENNESSEE STATE SENATOR SAID
THAT THE BILL WILL PREVENT KIDS
FROM BEING, QUOTE
BLIND SIDED FROM A
SEXUALIZED PERFORMANCE IN
PUBLIC.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DRAG SHOWS DON'T POP UP LIKE FLASH MOBS
AND SPRINKLE GAY DUST
ON YOUR KIDS.
ACC
NEW YORK
I HAVE BEEN BLINDSIDED BY A
SEXUALIZED PERFORMANCE A FEW TIMES,
BUT THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
WHEN YOU TAKE THE BUS.
>> THE U.S. ENERGY DEPARTMENT
CONCLUDED THAT COVID LIKELY ORIGINATED
FROM A WUHAN
LABORATORY LEAK AND NOT A WET
MARKET.
SO I GAVE UP EATING BATS FOR
NOTHING?
NEWSPAPERS AROUND THE COUNTRY
DROPPED THE CARTOON STRIP DILBERT
AFTER CREATOR SCOTT
ADAMS SAID HE CHOSE TO LIVE
IN ACOMMUNITY
WHERE NO BLACK PEOPLE
LIVE.
SO HE LIVES IN YOUR BUILDING,
HUH, COLIN?
>> NO.
NEWSPAPERS DROPPED THE CARTOON
STRIP EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY,
AND
TO RUB IT IN, THEY'RE REPLACING DILBERT
WITH PEANUT'S OOPS ALL
FRANKLIN.
DILBERT CREATOR SCOTT ADAMS'
RACIST RANT WAS IN RESPONSE TO A POLL
THAT ASKED THE QUESTION, IS
IT OKAY TO BE WHITE.
OH, I WOULD SAY IT'S MORE THAN
JUST OKAY.
>> THE HOUSE ETHICS COMMITTEE
HAS ANNOUNCED AN INVESTIGATION
INTO GEORGE SANTOS.
WELL, THANK GOD I'M NOT GEORGE
SANTOS, SAID GEORGE SANTOS.
DONALD TRUMP ACCUSED RON
DeSANTIS OF WANTING TO CUT
SOCIAL SECURITY AND MEDICARE
AND CALLED THE FLORIDA GOVERNOR A
WHEELCHAIR-OVER-THE-CLIFF KIND
OF GUY.
THAT'S ALSO HOW MELANIA WILL
FINALLY GET RID OF HIM.
>> HOUSE REPUBLICANS CONCERNED
THAT CHINA COULD USE TIKTOK TO
ILLEGALLY GATHER INFORMATION
ON AMERICANS
HAVE VOTED ON A BILL
THAT WOULD BAN THE APP
NATIONWIDE.
REPLIED TIKTOK USERS --
WE
NEED
STORM
>> THAT'S HOW HE REALLY DANCES
TOO.
>> FIRST LADY JILL BIDEN SAID IN
AN INTERVIEW
SHE MAINTAINS A
GOOD BALANCE IN THE TYPES OF
ADVICE SHE OFFERS PRESIDENT BIDEN,
BUT IT'S MOSTLY, HOLD ON
TO THE RAILING.
THIS WEEK, SOUTH CAROLINA
ATTORNEY ALEX MURDAUGH WAS FOUND
GUILTY OF MURDER
AND ALSO FOUND
GUILTY OF LOOKING LIKE WILL
FERRELL DRESSED AS CONAN
O'BRIEN.
>> NEWSPAPERS AROUND THE COUNTRY
ARE DROPPING BELOVED COMIC STRIP
DILBERT, AS ITS CREATOR SCOTT
ADAMS WENT ON A RACIST RANT LAST
WEEK ADVOCATING FOR WHITE PEOPLE
TO GET THE HELL AWAY FROM BLACK
PEOPLE.
OFF THE RECORD, HE'S GOT A
POINT.
HERE TO COMMENT -- THAT'S WHAT
THE CARD SAYS.
BUT HERE TO COMMENT IS DILBERT!
>> HEY, MICHAEL.
>> HI, DILBERT.
SO HAD YOU EVER SEEN THIS SIDE
OF SCOTT ADAMS BEFORE?
>> MICHAEL, I THINK I CAN SPEAK
FOR MYSELF AND THE ENTIRE ALL
WHITE STAFF AT THE DILBERT
OFFICES WHEN I SAY THIS WAS A
TOTAL SHOCK.
I MEAN MOST CARTOONISTS ARE
WEIRD, BUT RACIST WEIRD?
LET'S JUST SAY I NEVER GOT THAT
MEMO.
RIGHT?
MEMOS.
WORK IS BORING, BUT I CAN BE
FUNNY TOO.
THAT'S KIND OF MY THING.
>> SO YOU JUST THOUGHT SCOTT WAS
WEIRD?
>> NO.
I KNEW HE WAS BAD.
HE MADE ME GO INTO THE OFFICE
EVERY DAY DURING COVID, AND HE
KNOWS I'M
AUTOIMMUNE.
>> YOU'RE AUTOIMMUNE?
>> DO I LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY WHO'S
NOT AUTOIMMUNE?
I'M A REAL ATHLETE.
MY HAIR IS SKIN, MICHAEL.
>> YOUR HAIR IS SKIN?
>> YES.
I CANNOT STRESS THIS ENOUGH.
MY HAIR IS ENTIRELY SKIN, AND IT
HAS BEEN THE GREAT TRAGEDY OF MY
LIFE.
>> I'M VERY SORRY.
>> NO.
I'M SORRY, MICHAEL, FOR RACISM.
MAYBE I WAS JUST BLIND TO IT.
I MEAN, MY GLASSES ARE LITERALLY
OPEC WHITE.
TO ME, HE WAS JUST SCOTT, THE
FUNNY GUY, THE TRUMP-SUPPORTING
CARTOONIST WHO DID MAGIC IN HIS
SPARE TIME.
HAD A GREAT KEVIN HART
IMPRESSION.
>> WELL, THAT SOUNDS LIKE A
RACIST TO ME.
>> WELL, TURNS OUT HE WAS A
RACIST.
I'M HIS PRIZED CREATION.
WHAT DOES THAT MAKE ME?
I WANTED ANSWERS, SO I TOOK A --
GOD FORBID -- PERSONAL DAY, AND
REALLY STARTED TO DIG IN ON
THE CONCEPT OF WHAT IS WORK,
READING LOTS OF BLACK RADICALS,
AND I REALIZED SOMETHING.
EVEN MUNDANE WORK SERVES TO
UPHOLD A CAPITALIST SYSTEM BASED
ON MAINTAINING RACIAL HIERARCHY,
BUT THAT'S ALL ABOUT TO CHANGE.
RACE WAR IS COMING.
YOU READY, MICHAEL?
>> WHAT?
>> ARE YOU READY?
BECAUSE DILBERT'S READY.
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING READY TO
TAKE THE STREETS AND PAINT THE
CITY WITH THE BLOOD OF THE WHITE
MAN.
>> THAT'S PRETTY INTENSE, MAN.
>> YEAH.
THEN I HAD A CUP OF COFFEE, AND
LIKE I ALWAYS SAY, DON'T EVEN
TALK TO ME BEFORE MY COFFEE.
>> I GOT IT.
WELL, DILBERT, EVERYBODY.
>> THIS COULD HAVE BEEN AN
EMAIL.
>> AS THIS YEAR'S AWARD SEASON
GETS UNDERWAY, THERE'S GROWING
MOVEMENT TO GET RID OF THE
GENDERS CATEGORIES OF BEST ACTOR
AND ACTRESS, AND INSTEAD CALL
THEM BEST ACTOR WITH AND BEST
ACTOR WHO GOD PAID LESS.
>> A MAN IN MISSOURI IS PLANNING
TO TURN AN ABANDONED JAIL INTO
AN AIRBNB RENTAL, WHICH WILL
MAKE IT THE FIRST JAIL THAT
REFUSES TO ACCEPT BLACK PEOPLE.
IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT PUERTO
RICO'S ONLY ZOO WAS CLOSING
AFTER YEARS OF ALLEGED ANIMAL
NEGLECT.
WORSE THE ZOO'S CLOSING IS BEING
ADVERTISED AS ALL YOU CAN EAT.
>> BIOLOGISTS IN FLORIDA ARE
WARNING THE JESUS CHRIST LIZARD
COULD SPREAD HARMFUL DISEASES TO
HUMAN.
THEY HOPE TO CONTROL THE
POPULATION BY INTRODUCING A
PUNCTIOUS PILOT LIZARD.
IT WAS REPORTED THE JAMES BOND
BOOKS ARE BEING REWRITTEN TO
ELIMINATE OFFENSIVE MATERIAL.
SO NOW THE CHARACTER PUSSY
GALORE WILL NOW BE CALLS COOTER
APLENTY.
>> A CALIFORNIA MAN HAS SET A
NEW WORLD RECORD BY VISITING
DISNEYLAND FOR 2,995 CONSECUTIVE
DAYS, BUT STILL NO SIGN OF HIS
KID.
I TRIED TO PLOW RIGHT THROUGH.
A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT MARRIED
MEN LIVE A LONGER, HEALTHIER
LIFE.
YEAH, BUT, FOR WHAT?
>> WELL, THE OSCARS ARE ALMOST
HERE.
HERE TO BREAK DOWN THE NOMINEES
AND ALL THINGS HOLLYWOOD ARE
PUNKIE JOHNSON AND MIKEY DAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, SO WHAT CAN
WE EXPECT FROM THIS YEAR'S
OSCARS?
>> WELL, COLIN, I WOULD LOVE TO
TELL YOU BUT WHEN PUNKIE AND I
SAT DOWN TO WORK ON THIS, WE
REALIZED THAT PUNKIE DOES NOT
KNOW ANY OTHER CELEBRITIES OR
ENTERTAINERS.
>> THIS IS TRUE.
>> SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW THEIR
NAMES REALLY.
HERE ARE SOME EXAMPLES, AND
THESE ARE ALL 100% TRUE STORIES.
I ONCE SAW PUNKIE CALL TONY
HAWK, TONY HAWKING TO HIS FACE.
>> YOU CONFUSED THE MOST FAMOUS
SKATEBOARDER OF ALL TIME WITH
THE GENIUS PHYSICIST STEVEN
HAWKING?
>> I MEAN, LOOK, THEY BOTH WHITE
MEN WITH WHEELS, SO I MEAN --
>> BUT THE BEST THING THAT HAS
EVER HAPPENED WAS A FEW WEEKS
AGO WHEN PUNKIE TOLD ME ALL OF
HER FRIENDS COULD NOT
BELIEVE SHE MET RICK BERNSTEIN.
>> AND WHO IS RICK BERNSTEIN?
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> SO I SAID, IT'S THE GUY WITH
THE JEANS.
>> THE GUY WITH THE JEANS.
I EVENTUALLY FIGURED OUT THAT
PUNKIE WAS REFERRING TO LIVING
LEGEND BRUCE SPRINGSTEEN.
RICK BERNSTEIN!
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, I GREW UP ON EDDIE MURPHY
AND RICHARD PRYOR.
THAT DUDE AIN'T BIG IN MY HOUSE.
SUE A BITCH.
>> SO INSTEAD OF A OSCARS PIECE,
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE WAY MORE
FUN TO PLAY A GAME CALLED WHO
DOES PUNKIE MEAN.
ARE YOU DOWN TO PLAY?
>> I FEEL LIKE I DON'T HAVE A
CHASE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
EVERYONE, YOU CAN PLAY ALONG
IT'S SUPER FUN.
NUMBER ONE.
PUNKIE REFERRED TO THIS
CELEBRITY IN REAL LIFE AS CLAIRE
BLANKENSHIP.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
CLARA DANES, MAYBE.
>> LET'S SEE.
IS IT CLARA DANES?
NO.
IT'S ANNE HATHAWAY.
>> WAIT.
>> THAT REALLY HAPPEN ED
>> NO.
WAIT, TIME-OUT.
PUT THE PICTURE BACK UP.
BUT DOES THIS BITCH NOT LOOK
LIKE A CLAIRE?
>> SHE DOES.
THAT'S FAIR.
NUMBER TWO, ZOE DECHANESE.
WHO DOES PUNKIE MEAN?
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
COLIN.
>> I'M THINKING THIS ONE HAS
TO BE ZOE DESCHANEL.
>> LOCK IT IN.
NOPE.
IT'S ZOE KRAVITZ.
>> WHAT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOK.
SEE, WHAT HAD HAPPENED WAS, I
WAS GETTING MY MAKEUP DONE FOR
SATURDAY'S SHOW BECAUSE I GOT TO
LOOK GOOD FOR NORA MICHAELS.
>> NORA MICHAELS?
>> ANYWAY, I SEE ZOE WALK PAST,
AND I SAID, HEY, DON'T I KNOW
YOU?
>> YES, YOU DID BECAUSE SHE WAS
HOSTING THIS SHOW.
THAT HAPPENED THAT WEEK.
>> MY BAD, MS. DACHANESE.
>> OKAY.
LAST ONE.
HERE WE GO.
PATRICK DEMPSEY.
>> I THINK THERE'S NO WAY SHE
KNOWS WHO PATRICK DEMPSEY IS.
I GUESS I'M GOING TO SAY PATRICK
STEWART.
>> NOPE.
SHE ACTUALLY DID MEAN PATRICK
DEMPSEY.
>> YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT I KNOW
DR. DEREK SHE EVER, BABY.
>> YOU WATCH "GREY'S ANATOMY?"
>> OF COURSE I DO.
I KNOW EVERY SHOW WITH SHONDA
RHIMES.
>> I THINK YOU MEAN RHONDA
>> I THINK YOU MEAN BUSTA RIMES.
>> A PORN STAR IN AUSTRALIA
REVEALED WHILE RECENTLY FILMING
A NEW MOVIE, HE BROKE HIS PENIS
-- IT'S REALLY SAD, MA'AM.
HE BROKE HIS PENIS AND SAID IT
WENT COMPLETELY BLACK, WHICH YOU
KNOW IT MEANS IT'S NEVER GOING
BACK.
THE MAN HAS ADJUSTED TO HIS NEW
BLACK PENIS BY FILMING ALL HIS
SEX SCENES IN TIMBER LANDS.
IT'S REALLY SAD, MAN.
>> A NEW TREND AMONG YOUNGER
WORKERS IS BARE MONEY MAXIMUM
MONDAY, IN WHICH THEY DO AS
LITTLE AS POSSIBLE AT THE
BEGINNING OF THE WORK WEEK,
WHILE A NEW TREND AMONG VETERANS
IS REALIZING THEIR SACRIFICE
MEANT NOTHING.
>> PEOPLE ARE REALIZING A CLAM
THAT WAS BORN THE SAME YEAR AS
ABRAHAM LINCOLN.
THE CLAM CREDITS ITS LONGEVITY
TO STAYING AWAY FROM THE
THEATER.
>> SOME OWNERS OF McDONALD'S
FRANCHISES ARE CONCERNED ABOUT A
CAMPAIGN PARTNERSHIP WITH CARDI
B.
ESPECIALLY THE ADD WHERE THEY
CLAIM THEIR BURGERS HAVE A WET ASS PATTY.
>> WELL, USUALLY THIS DOESN'T GO
WELL FOR ME,
BUT SINCE IT'S HER
BIRTHDAY IN THREE DAYS,
WE DECIDED TO LET HER DO IT.
HERE IS SARAH SHERMAN WITH THE
SARAH NEWS.
SARAH
>> THANKS, COLIN.
I PROMISE YOU WON'T REGRET IT.
>> I'M SURE NOT.
>> IN SARAH NEWS, THIS WEEK, I'M
FINALLY TURNING 30,
OR AS COLIN
CALLS IT, 15 YEARS TOO OLD.
>> COME ON.
COME ON.
NO.
>> WHAT?
WHEN I INVITED YOU TO MY
BIRTHDAY PARTY,
YOU RSVP'd, I'M
NOT GOING TO BE THERE
UNLESS
IT'S A QUINCEANERA.
>> I DON'T GO TO QUINCEANERAS.
>> OH, REALLY?
THIS JUST IN.
COLIN JOST REFUSES TO CELEBRATE
HISPANIC CULTURE.
IN SCIENCE NEWS, NASA ENGINEERS
PREPARING FOR A TRIP TO MARS
RECENTLY SENT A TEAM OF
RESEARCHERS TO THE DRIEST PLACE
ON EARTH.
SAID MY BOYFRIEND, HEY, GET OUT
OF MY GIRLFRIEND'S UNDERWEAR.
GOOD LUCK DOWN THERE, BOYS.
WE SALUTE YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY REAL NEWS,
SARAH?
>> OF COURSE.
REAL
THE U.S. IS FACING A THREAT FROM
A HIGHLY INTELLIGENT BREED OF PIG
DUBBED THE SUPER PIG,
WHICH IS FUNNY BECAUSE SUPER PIG IS
ALSO WHAT COLIN WRITES ON MY
DRESSING ROOM MIRROR
ANY TIME HE
CATCHES ME EATING WITHOUT HIS
PERMISSION.
>> I DON'T GIVE YOU PERMISSION
TO EAT.
>> I KNOW.
ME AND ALL THE OTHER GIRLS ARE
STARVING, COLIN.
CAN'T YOU HEAR MY STOMACH
GURGLING?
>> YES, I CAN.
DO YOU HAVE LIKE A STOMACH ISSUE
OR SOMETHING?
>> NO.
I'M JUST JEWISH, COLIN,
WHICH
ISN'T A DISEASE, DESPITE WHAT
YOU WROTE IN YOUR BOOK.
>> THAT'S CHAPTER ONE?
COME ON.
>> IN OTHER NEWS, JUST THREE
WEEKS AFTER A CHEMICAL TRAIN DERAILMENT,
OFFICIALS NOW SAY
THE WATER IN EAST PALESTINE IS
SAFE TO DRINK.
YEAH, ABOUT AS SAFE AS ANY
COCKTAIL COLIN GETS ME AT AN
AFTERPARTY.
EVERY TIME I COME BACK FROM THE BATHROOM,
MY DRINK IS FIZZING
LIKE A SCIENCE FAIR VOLCANO.
>> MY FAMILY WATCHES THIS SHOW.
>> COLIN, SERIOUSLY, STOP TRYING
TO LIFT UP THE BOTTOM OF MY PANT
LEG WITH YOUR BARE FEET.
>> I'M WEARING SHOES.
>> SHOES DON'T HAVE TOENAILS,
COLIN.
IN OTHER NEWS, I JUST FOUND OUT
PEACOCK IS STREAMING
EVERY EPISODE OF COLUMBO
FEATURING
GOD'S GIFT TO WOMEN, PETER
FAULK.
OH, MY GOD,
AN OLD GUY WITH A
LOOSE EYEBALL AND RESTING CIGAR
FACE.
MAYBE HE CAN SOLVE THE MYSTERY
OF MY SOPPING WET CHAIR.
GET TO THE HIGH GROUNDS,
THE LEVY IS BROKE AND THE CITY IS
FLOODED.
>> ABSOLUTELY DISGUSTING.
WELL, SARAH, IT IS YOUR BIRTHDAY,
SO WE'VE DECIDED TO
GET YOU A VERY SARAH-STYLE
BIRTHDAY CAKE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SARAH.
THANKS, COLIN.
AND BY THE WAY, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR THE CARD YOU MADE ME,
COLIN.
>> OH, I DON'T REMEMBER WRITING
A CARD.
>> GO AHEAD.
READ YOUR BIRTHDAY MESSAGE TO ME
THAT YOU WROTE.
>> SARAH, TOO BAD YOU CAN'T EAT THIS CAKE
SINCE YOU FAILED WEIGH
IN.
SARAH ERMAN, EVERYONE.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE, GOOD NIGHT!
>> WELL, WHEN YOU SAID IT WAS AN
EMERGENCY, WE FLEW IN RIGHT
AWAY.
>> YOU'RE KIND OF FREAKING US
OUT.
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
>> OH, WE ARE BETTER THAN OKAY.
>> TRUTH IS, WE HAD A HARD TIME
FIGURING OUT HOW TO BREAK THE
NEWS.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE SONG IS FOR.
>> THE SONG?
>> I'M SURE YOU ALL HAVE A LOT
OF QUESTIONS, BUT DON'T WORRY.
THE SONG WILL EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING.
♪ WHEN I THINK ABOUT LOVE, I'M
SO GRATEFUL FOR THE TIMES WE'VE
HAD ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE, OUR
WONDERFUL CHILDREN, A THOUSAND
MEMORIES GOOD AND BAD ♪
♪ BUT WE HAVE BEEN DRIFTING
APART FROM ONE ANOTHER, EVEN
THOUGH WE STILL LOVE EACH
OTHER ♪
♪ AND NOW SHE'S GIVING OUR BED
TO ANOTHER, BUT I'M COOL WITH
IT, AND I WATCH, I WATCH FROM
THE CORNER ♪
>> WAIT, MOM, YOU'RE CHEATING ON
DAD?
>> GOD, NO.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR THE PART WHERE
HE SAID HE'S COOL WITH IT?
>> I BELIEVE MY EXACT WORDS WERE
I'M COOL WITH IT AND I WATCH.
♪ I WATCH FROM THE CORNER ♪
>> WELL, WHO'S THE OTHER MAN?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I WOULD
GUESS IT'S THE GUY SITTING
IN DAD'S CHAIR PLAYING STREETS
OF RAGE TWO.
>> WHAT UP?
>> I'M SO CONFUSED RIGHT NOW.
>> WELL, I AM SO GLAD YOU SAID
THAT.
>> BECAUSE NEXT PART OF THE SONI
♪ HIS NAME IS SUCRE, AND HE'S A
FELON, HE'S EXPLORED MY WHOLE
BODY LIKE MAGELLAN ♪
♪ HE PLAYS STREETS OF RAGE TWO
AND THEN HE PLEASURES ME IN
BED ♪
♪ AND I'M COOL WITH IT AND I
WATCH, I WATCH FROM THE CORNER ♪
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE
SO PUMPED ABOUT WATCHING FROM
THE CORNER.
>> AND I'M SORRY.
HIS NAME IS SUCRE?
>> YEAH, SUCRE WOLODARSKY.
>> SO, WHAT, YOU'RE IN A
THROUPLE NOW WITH A MAN NAMED
SUCRE WOLODARSKY?
>> DAMN, YOU GUYS ARE BEING MAD
ANNOYING RIGHT NOW.
HOW MANY TIMES DO YOUR PARENTS
HAVE TO SAY THIS?
THE NEXT PART OF THE SONG WILL
EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
>> THANK YOU, SUCRE.
>> AND BY THE WAY, I'M NOT HAPPY
I HAD TO STOP JUST NOW.
YOU DISTRACTED ME SO BADLY THAT
A GUY WITH A MOHAWK PUNCHED ME
AND MY HEALTH WENT DOWN.
>> I THINK YOU GUYS SHOULD
APOLOGIZE TO SUCRE ABOUT THAT.
>> I'M NOT APOLOGIZING TO SUCRE.
YOU GUYS NEED TO TELL US WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> WE'RE TRYING TO, BUT YOU GUYS
KEEP INTERRUPTING.
>> THE NEXT PART OF THE SONG
REALLY SPELLS THINGS OUT.
MY NAME'S SPELLED S-U-C-R-E
W-O-L-O-D-ARSKY,
>> THE SPELLING OF YOUR NAME WAS
NOT THE PART WE WERE CONFUSED
ABOUT.
>> CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
>> YES, SUCRE.
>> HOW ARE THESE THREE YOUR
KIDS?
>> WELL, I WAS ON TOP FOR HIM.
>> YEAH, AND I WAS ON TOP FOR
HER.
>> THEN WE DID IT FROM THE SIDE
ONE TIME, AND HE CAME OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
>> LOOK, YOU GUYS ARE ADULTS.
YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU
DIDN'T TOUCH THE GRAND KIDS'
COLLEGE FUND.
>> OF COURSE.
WE GO OVER THAT IN THIS NEXT
PART.
♪
♪ THE MONEY'S ALL GONE NOW ♪
>> YOU GAVE ALL THE COLLEGE
MONEY TO SUCRE?
>> SUCRE THIS, SUCRE THAT.
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF THE GUITAR
SOLO?
>> THIS IS A NIGHTMARE.
>> GUYS, I KNOW THIS IS A LOT TO
TAKE IN, BUT I HAVE SOME GOOD
NEWS.
I JUST BEAT STREETS OF RAGE TWO.
THIS IS THE BEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
>> SUCRE.
>> ALSO, I'M NOT 100% SURE, BUT
I'M ALMOST POSITIVE I'M
PREGNANT.
>> SUCRE!
♪ AND I WATCHED FROM THE
CORNER ♪
>>> I CAN'T BELIEVE WE JUST DID
THAT.
EVERY TIME YOU'RE IN TOWN, YOU
SUCK ME BACK IN.
>> IT'S BECAUSE WE WERE MEANT
FOR EACH OTHER, BABY.
>> GOD, YOU KNOW, I BAILED ON A
DATE TONIGHT BECAUSE OF YOU?
>> OH, YOUR BAD.
NOW, COME ON.
SHOULD I MAKE SOME PANCAKES?
DADDY'S SPECIAL RECIPE.
>> HEY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN MY
HOUSE?
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> I'M GARRETT FROM HINGE.
WE HAD PLANS FOR 7:00 AT
BUCCACINOS.
>> WHAT?
KYRA, THIS IS THE GUY YOU BLEW
OFF?
>> AFRAID SO.
NOW I'M HERE, AND YOU'RE IN BED
WITH LIKE A HEMSWORTH BROTHER I
DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT?
HOW DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME
FEEL?
>> DUDE, YOU BROKE INTO MY
HOUSE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOU.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
I'M GARRETT, FROM HINGE.
AKA THE GUY WHO HAS BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU AT BUCCACINO'S
LIKE SOME KIND OF SUCKA.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
LEAVE.
>> GOD, THIS IS SO OVERWHELMING.
I'M GOING TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
AND WHEN I COME BACK, WE CAN
FIGURE THIS ALL OUT, OKAY?
THIS ALL OUT, OKAY?
>> THERE IS NOTHING TO FIGURE
OUT.
WE GOT TO CALL THE COPS.
>> NO, NO, YOU CAN'T.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
I CAN'T EVEN LEAVE THE STATE
BECAUSE OF MY PAROL.
>> WAIT, WHAT PAROL?
>> GARRETT, I KNOW YOUR FEELINGS
ARE HURT, AND THAT'S HARD, BUT
NO MATTER WHAT, YOU CANNOT KILL
THEM.
OKAY.
I'M BACK
I HAVE BEEN THINKING A LOT ABOUT
IT, AND I'M OPEN TO BEING A
THROUPLE.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT,
GARRETT.
>> KYRA, YOU MADE ME LOOK LIKE
AN ABSOLUTE SUCKA.
I MEAN, I LEFT EARLY FROM WORK
TO CHANGE.
>> YOU CHANGED INTO THAT STEWIE
GRIFFIN T-SHIRT?
>> CAN I GIVE YOU SOME ADVICE,
KYRA, IF YOU'RE NOT EMOTIONALLY
AVAILABLE, MAYBE DON'T BE ON THE
APPS, RIGHT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ESPECIALLY HINGE, BECAUSE
HINGE IS THE APP THAT'S DESIGNED
TO BE DELETED, RIGHT?
>> WILL YOU STOP MAKING THE SAME
POSE AS YOUR SHIRT.
>> OH, KYRA, KYRA, KYRA.
WANT A LITTLE FOOT RUB?
>> NO.
DON'T RUB MY FOOT!
>> HEY, IT'S JUST ME, GARRETT
FROM HINGE.
THE DATING APP FOR PEOPLE WHO
HATE DATING APPS.
>> DO YOU LIKE WORK FOR HINGE?
>> HEY, THIS LITTLE PIGGY LEFT
ME AT BUCCACINOS.
>> STOP!
>> OH, MY GOD.
I NEED TO USE THE RESTROOM
AGAIN, AND I DON'T MEAN TO MAKE
THIS AWKWARD, PLUS COULD YOU
PLEASE RAPID TEST?
THE THERE'S A PLANDEMMIC GOING
ON.
>> DID HE SAY PLANDEMMIC?
>> GARRETT, I KNOW THIS IS HARD,
BUT YOU CANNOT KILL THEM, EVEN
THOUGH IT WOULD BE SO EASY.
OH, MAN, REALLY WISH I DIDN'T
BRING POISON HERE.
GUYS!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M JUST GOING TO STAY
THE NIGHT IF THAT'S COOL.
>> NO, GARRETT, GET YOUR PSYCHO
PATH ASS OUT OF HERE NOW.
>> DAMN IT, WOMAN!
SORRY, THAT WAS MY STEWIE
IMPRESSION.
>> NO, GARRETT, THAT WAS
ACTUALLY AN AMAZING IMPRESSION.
AND TO BE FAIR, KYRA, YOU DID
MAKE HIM LOOK LIKE A SUCKA AT
BUCCACINOS.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE WE'RE IN THE WRONG TOO
NOW.
GET IN HERE WITH US.
>> WOW.
THANKS GUYS.
THAT'S SO NICE.
OH.
>> OH, DAMN.
I'M POSITIVE.
>> WAIT, YOU TOOK IT?
>>> ONCE AGAIN, KELSEA
BALLERINI!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ WE MOVED TO A PLACE
WITH A VIEW OFF
OF EIGHTH AVENUE
AFTER WE SAID I DO ♪
♪ AND WE WATCHED
CARSF BAELORETTES
TWO AM CIGARETTES AND
TRAFFIC HEADED DOWNTOWN ♪
♪ AND THE INTERSTATE
WAS SO LOUD
THERE WAS A LOT
IT HAD TO DROWN OUT ♪
♪ WE PLAYED THE PART
FIVE NIGHTS
BUT WE WERE NEVER THERE
ON THE WEEKENDS BABY ♪
♪ WE GOT ALONG REAL NICE
BUT WHEN I LEFT TOWN
DID YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ ONE DAY THE CURTAIN
STARTED COMING DOWN
YOU CHANGED THE SECOND
WE WERE MOVING OUT ♪
♪ I GUESS WRONG
CAN LOOK ALRIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING HOME
IN A PENTHOUSE BABY ♪
♪ I BOUGHT THE HOUSE
WITH A FENCE
ENOUGH ROOM FOR SOME KIDS
A BACKYARD FOR DIBS ♪
♪ AND I THOUGHT THAT
WOULD MAKE IT ALL BETTER♪
♪ AND MAYBE FOREVER
WOULDN'T FEEL LIKE
THE WALLS CLOSING IN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HOW DOES THAT
EVEN MAKE SENSE
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT
IT NEVER DID ♪
♪ WE PLAYED THE PART
FIVE NIGHTS
BUT WE WERE NEVER THERE
ON THE WEEKENDS BABY ♪
♪ WE GOT ALONG REAL NICE
BUT WHEN I LEFT TOWN
DID YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ ONE DAY THE CURTAIN
STARTED COMING DOWN
I CHANGED THE SECOND
WE WERE MOVING OUT ♪
♪ I GUESS WRONG
CAN LOOK ALRIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING HOME
IN A PENTHOUSE BABY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE WERE
PLAYING HOME
IN A PENTHOUSE BABY ♪
♪ IT HURTS PUTTING
STUFF IN A BOX
AND NOW WE DON'T TALK ♪
♪ AND IT STINGS
ROLLING UP THE WELCOME MAT
KNOWING YOU GOT HALF ♪
♪ I KISSED
SOMEONE NEW LAST NIGHT
AND NOW I DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE SLEEPING BABY ♪
♪ WE GOT ALONG REAL NICE
UNTIL I WANTED OUT
NOW I KNOW YOU HATE ME ♪
♪ ONE DAY THE CURTAIN
STARTED COMING DOWN
WE CHANGED THE SECOND
WE WERE MOVING OUT ♪
♪ I GUESS WRONG
CAN LOOK ALRIGHT
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING HOME
IN A PENTHOUSE BABY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE WERE
PLAYING HOME
IN A PENTHOUSE BABY ♪
♪ I JUST BOUGHT
THAT HOUSE THAT WE SAW
YOU SAID IT WAS WRONG
BUT I WANTED IT ALL ALONG ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL OVER THE PLACE, BUT THE
PREMISE IS SIMPLE.
ABSTAIN FROM PHYSICAL INTIMACY,
AND YOU'LL WIN 200 Gs.
CAN YOU BELIEVE NETFLIX HAS MADE
FIVE SEASONS OF THIS?
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> HI, LANA.
>> I INTRODUCED THE GROUND RULES
OF THIS RETREAT JUST 24 HOURS
AGO.
>> AND WE HAVE BEEN SO GOOD,
LANA, ME AND IZZY HAVEN'T DONE
NOTHING.
>> EVEN THOUGH DOM IS PROPER
FIT, YEAH.
>> WE HAVEN'T EVEN DONE HAND
STUFF, AND I ALWAYS DO HAND
STUFF.
>> IT'S ALL GOING TO BE WORTH IT
TO WIN THIS 200 GRAND.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THAT WON'T BE
HAPPENING.
LAST NIGHT, EAK COSTING THE VIL
>> NO!
>> BLOODY HELL.
>> IT WAS THEM TWO, WASN'T IT?
>> ACTUALLY, IT WAS A KISS
SHARED BETWEEN RODNEY AND GLENN
BECHAMEL.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
I TRIED NOT TO KISS RODNEY, BUT
THEN I WANTED TO, SO I DID.
GUESS I'M KIND OF WILD LIKE
THAT.
>> WAIT, WAIT, RODNEY, YOU
HOOKED UP WITH GLENN?
>> I KNOW.
WE LOST THE PRIZE MONEY.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S NOT WHY WE'RE SHOCKED.
>> YOU COULD HAVE SNOGGED
ANYONE, AND YOU WENT WITH GLENN?
>> IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT HER.
LISTEN TO HER VOICE.
>> SORRY.
I HAD TO SNEEZE.
>> THERE WAS ANOTHER RULE BREAK
LAST NIGHT COSTING THE GROUP
$20,000.
>> NO!
>> IT WAS HEAVY PETTING IN THE
GRILL AREA BETWEEN RODNEY AND
GLENN BECHAMEL.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'VE JUST NEVER MET ANYONE LIKE
GLENN.
SHE'S SO UNPREDICTABLE.
>> RODNEY MADE RIBS, AND I LET
HIM USE MY BODY AS A NAPKIN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I PACKED 16 OF THESE SHIRTS.
RODNEY TOLD ME NOT TO TOUCH THE
GRILL.
OOPS, I DID IT ANYWAYS.
>> MAYBE THIS IS A QUESTION FOR
PRODUCERS, BUT WHY IS GLENN EVEN
HERE.
>> BECAUSE I'M A HORNED-UP
SINGLE LIKE YOU GUYS.
I'VE HAD SEX EIGHT TIMES.
BUT WHO'S COUNTING?
ME.
I ALWAYS COUNT.
EXCEPT CALORIES, YOU ARE WHAT
YOU EAT.
SO I'M RODNEY'S ASS.
>> I HOPE YOU GUYS AREN'T
JEALOUS.
>> I'M ACTUALLY NUMB FROM THE
WASTE DOWN.
>> GLENN IS SO WEIRD AND OLD.
>> ACTUALLY, I'M 28.
I'VE JUST BEEN THROUGH HELL.
>> ANOTHER RULE BREAK IS
HAPPENING NOW.
>> WHAT ARE THEY EVEN DOING?
>> SHE'S KISSING UP HIS ARM LIKE
SHE'S GNAWING ON CORN.
>> IS THIS A RULE BREAK?
>> TECHNICALLY NO, BUT IT MAKES
ME SICK, SO I'M DRAINING THE
PRIZE FUND.
SOMEONE UNPLUG ME.
>> GUESS I'M KIND OF WILD LIKE
THAT.
>>> THANK YOU TO KELSEA
BALLERINI,ASON