>>> GOOD EVENING
GOOD EVENING I'M JUDGE JEANINE PIRRO,
ALSO
IF ANYONE WATCHING IS WEARING A
HEARIN AID,
SORRY YOU'RE DEAD NOW
OUR TOP STORY, KYLE RITTENHOUSE,
ACQUITTED OF ALL CHARGES
THAT LOVEABLE SCAMP, WAS PUT
THROUGH A NIGHTMARE OF A TRIAL
JUST FOR DOING THE BRAVEST THING
ANY AMERICAN CAN DO,
PROTECTING
AN EMPTY CAR LOT IN SOMEONE
ELSE'S TOWN.
ON TO OUR NEXT GUEST
HE'S AS IMPARTIAL AS A DANCE MAN,
JUDGE BRUCE SCHRODER
>> THANK YOU
AKNOWLEDGE
YOU MAY REMEMBER THAT I WAS IN
CHARGE OF INVESTIGATING
ROBERT
DURST FOR MURDER BACK IN 1983,
WELL, FOLKS, 30 YEARS AND ONE
ADDITIONAL MURDER LATER, WE GOT
HIM.
NOW, IF I MAY SAY, JUDGE TO
JUDGE,
WHAT TURNED ME ON THE MOST
WAS HOW YOU RULED THAT
COURTROOM WITH AN IRON FIST.
TELL US HOW YOU DID IT
>> WELL, IT WAS ALL STANDARD
PROCEDURE.
THAT'S WHY I ORDERED THAT THE
PROSECUTION NOT USE THE WORD
"VICTIMS."
THEY WERE RIOTERS,
AND THEY WEREN'T SHOT, THEY WERE
GADOINKED.
BUT THAT DID NOT GIVE MY CLIENT
AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE IN ANY WAY
>> NOW, YOU SAID MY CLIENT, DO
YOU MEAN THE DEFENDANT
>> OH, YES
SURE
I KEEP DOING THAT.
>> WELL, YOU DO YOU, JUDGE
YOU DO YOU
THANKS FOR COMING.
PREDICTABLY, THE LOONEY LIBERAL
OUTRAGE MACHINE'S IN OVERDRIVE,
AND YOU KNOW HOW MUCH WE LOVE
LIBERAL TEARS AROUND HERE,
SO I
DECIDED TO INVITE TWO OF THEM
HERE TONIGHT
PLEASE WELCOME LEGAL ANALYST FOR
NASTY NPR SANDRA CUMMINGS
AND
PROFESSOR OF LAW AT HOWARD
UNIVERSITY, DANIEL FIELDS,
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
>> WE WERE TOLD YOU INVITED US
IN THE INTEREST OF FAIRNESS.
>> AND YOU FELL FOR IT, THAT'S
ON YOU DUMB DUMBS.
SANDRA, WERE YOU SURPRISED BY
YESTERDAY'S VERDICT?
>> SURPRISED THAT HE WAS
EXONERATED ON ALL CHARGES?
YEAH, THAT'S PUTTING IT MILDLY
I WAS SHOCKED.
>> YOU WERE?
BECAUSE I WASN'T
>> I HAVE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT BEFORE
>> OH I HAVE, MANY TIMES
>> I MEAN, THIS IS NOT WHO WE
ARE.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT KIND OF IS
>> AND ALL THIS DOES IS SEND A
MESSAGE THAT ANY AMERICAN
CAN JUST PROWL THE STREETS WITH AN
AK-47.
>> ANY AMERICAN?
I THINK YOU'RE MISSING A KEYWORD
THERE.
>> ALL WE CAN HOPE FOR IS THAT
AT THIS POINT,
THIS WILL BE A CALL
TO FINALLY CHANGE THE
SYSTEM
>> AND THAT CALL WILL GO TO
VOICE MAIL AND THAT INBOX IS
FULL, OKAY
>> WOW, VERY INTERESTING
WELL, YOUR SEGMENT IS OVER, AND
MY MUG IS EMPTY,
TEARS
SO YOU GOT TO
GO
NOW ON A MORE INSPIRING NOTE,
KEVIN McCARTHY ROCKED THE HOUSE DOWN
WITH HIS AWE INSPIRIN
EIGHT-HOUR TIRADE AGAINST THE
BUILD BACK BETTER BILL,
DEMONSTRATING WHY KEEPING THE
FILIBUSTER IS VITAL TO OUR
DEMOCRACY.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT HOUR SIX OF
HIS RHETORICAL MASTERPIECE
>> DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO FLIP
THIS THING AROUND.
EXCUSE ME.
DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO FLIP
THIS AROUND.
EXCUSE ME.
FLIP IT AROUND
WHOOPS
I COULD DO IT BEFORE
>> AND THAT BRAVE MAN STOPPED
THE BUILD BACK BETTER BILL FROM BEING PASSED
UNTIL THE NEXT DAY
WHEN IT PASSED IN TWO MINUTES.
MEANWHILE, WHAT WAS PRESIDENT
BRANDON DOING?
GETTING SOCIALIZED BUTT PLAGUE
PAID FOR BY YOUR TAX DOLLARS
DEMOCRATS ARE PRAISING PASSED
OUT JOE FOR HIS BIG DEAL
INFRASTRUCTURE BILL.
BUT WHERE'S THE THANKS FOR THE
REAL MUCHACHO WHO GOT THIS DONE?
PLEASE WELCOME THIS PEOPLE'S
SEXIEST MAN ALIVE,
PRESIDENT
DONALD J. TRUMP!
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, JENNIE
IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE HERE.
>> WELL, I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT
OF THOUGHTS ON THE INFRASTRUCTURE BILL,
SO IF IT'S
OKAY, I'M JUST GOING TO LET YOU RIP
WHILE I SIT HERE AND GET
ABSOLUTELY ROCK HARD
>> YOU KNOW, I'M GLAD YOU
BROUGHT THAT UP BECAUSE THAT TERRIBLE BILL,
YOU KNOW WHAT,
THE TRUTH IS NOBODY DID MORE FOR
THE INFRASTRUCTURE THAN ME,
AND MEEPLE IS SAYING,
AND MEEPLE ARE PEOPLE WHO ARE
ME
THEY'RE SAYING, OKAY, BUILD IT
BACK EVEN A LITTLE BIT BETTER,
BECAUSE I DID, WALL,
OKAY
BIG BEAUTIFUL WALL
OKAY IT'S NOT JUST WALL.
WHEN YOU PUT WALL IN A GRASSY
FIELD, FRANKLY, THAT'S ROAD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT IF YOU TAKE
WALL AND LAY IT ACROSS THE
RIVER, FRANKLY, WE'RE DOING
BRIDGE
>> WOW, I AM EDGING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT
CAN I JUST SAY 60 SECONDS ON THE
CLOCK, PLEASE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SLEEPY JOE BIDEN IS SUCH A
DISASTER
WE'RE COMING BACK.
EVERYBODY LOVES THE REBOOT
JUST LIKE I-CARLY.
JOE BIDEN TRIED TO REBOOT OBAMA,
AND IT FLOPPED JUST LIKE THE
FEMALE "GHOSTBUSTERS."
WHY DID THEY REBOOT "GOSSIP
GIRL."
YOU CAN'T MATCH IT
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BAD FRIEND
THIS WAS TRUE.
SOMETIMES SERENA WAS THE BAD
FRIEND TO BLARE.
>> OH, I HOPE THIS NEVER ENDS.
ANOTHER
>> WHY DON'T WE TRY A WORD
SEARCH THIS TIME
I'D LOVE IT IF IT WAS WORD
SEARCH
LOVE
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS TREATED VERY UNFAIRLY BY
CHRIS CRISTIE.
HE WAS VERY NASTY, AND HE SAID
VERY NASTY THINGS ABOUT ME ON
BILL MAHR.
WE LOVE HIM.
HE'S A WONDERFUL PERSON.
BUT I DON'T THINK WE LOVE HIM A
LOT.
WE HATE HIM A LOT.
MAN
INTERVIEW
SIT
WATCH BILL
NEW RULES
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, SPEAKING OF
NEW RULES, DUA LIPA IS ONE OF OUR BEST SINGERS,
SING
AND HER
HUSBAND, YOU KNOW WHAT, IS NOT
VERY ATTRACTIVE.
IT'S TERRIBLE WHAT THEY'RE DOING
WITH DUA LIPA'S HUSBAND NOT
BEING VERY ATTRACTIVE.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
IT
SHE'S TALL, SHE'S ARMENIAN,
WHICH IS BASICALLY WHITE
AND YOU KNOW WHO ELSE IS WHITE
BOB THE BUILDER ERBUILDER
BUILD THE WALL
WORRIES
BINGO, BABY.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, SIMU LIU
>> THANK YOU
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MY NAME IS SIMU LIU, AND SOME OF YOU --
SOME OF YOU MIGHT KNOW ME
FROM MARVEL'
"SHANG-CHI AND THE LEGEND OF THE
10 RINGS."
I AM OFFICIALLY MARVEL'S FIRST
OPENLY
CHINESE SUPERHERO.
I'M ALSO THE FIRST CHINESE HOST ON "SNL,"
TO BE THE FOURTH
CHINESE HOST ON "SNL."
I'M ACTUALLY CHINESE CANADIAN,
AND I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE FOR
THE THANKSGIVING SHOW.
NOW, IN CANADA, THANKSGIVING IS
ACTUALLY IN OCTOBER,
AND MARKS
THE START OF THE HARVEST SEASON.
AND HERE IN AMERICA, THINGS ARE
A LITTLE DIFFERENT
IT'S IN NOVEMBER, AND IT MARKS
THE START OF BLACK FRIDAY WEEK
ON AMAZON PRIME.
BUT I DO HAVE A LOT TO BE
THANKFUL FOR
NOW, A LOT OF PEOPLE ASKED ME
HOW I LANDED A ROLE IN A MARVEL
MOVIE.
AND THE TRUTH IS I GOT SHANG-CHI
HOW HOW EVERY CANADIAN GETS
THEIR BIG BREAK.
BY ASKING POLITELY
FOR REAL
BACK IN 2014, AND THIS IS A TRUE
STORY, I TWEETED,
"HEY, MARVEL
GREAT JOB WITH CAPTAIN AMERICA
AND THOR
HOW ABOUT AN ASIAN SUPERHERO?"
I THINK THAT TWEET GOT LIKE TEN LIKES,
WHICH IS LIKE, TEN MORE
THAT I USUALLY GOT,
AND I WORKED
HARD, AND FIVE YEARS LATER,
MARVEL DID MAKE THEIR FIRST
ASIAN SUPERHERO MOVIE,
AND AFTER
I GOT THE PART, I WENT ONLINE
AND TWEETED "THANKS FOR GETTING
BACK TO ME."
CLEARLY, I'M CANADIAN.
I REALLY CAN'T BELIEVE MY LIFE
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE TEN YEARS AGO
I HAD A JOB DRESSING UP AS
SPIDERMAN AT KIDS BIRTHDAY
PARTIES.
PAY
DRINK
AND I'LL NEVER FORGET THIS ONE
BIRTHDAY BOY
HIS NAME WAS TREVOR,
AND I DON'T
WANT TO SAY ANYTHING BAD ABOUT
HIM, BUT LET'S JUST SAY HE WAS A
REAL TREVOR.
HE KEPT KICKING MY SHINS AND
SCREAMING YOU'RE NOT SPIDER-MAN,
YOU'RE NOT SPIDER-MAN.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE
BEEN KICKED BY A 7-YEAR-OLD
WHILE WEARING A $30 WALMART SPIDER-MAN SUIT,
BUT IT WILL
BREAK YOU.
IT WILL BREAK YOUR SPIRIT.
BUT IT ALSO LIT A FIRE UNDER ME,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS
NOW.
BUT, TREVOR, IF YOU ARE
WATCHING, I JUST WANT TO SAY,
YOU WERE RIGHT
I'M NOT SPIDER-MAN
I'M SHANG-CHI, BITCH
>> WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
STICK
* I FOUND YOU MISS NEW BOOT
AND BRING THEM BACK TO ME *
>> WELCOME TO KARAOKE RECAP IN
WILMINGTON, NORTH CAROLINA.
>> THANK YOU FOR COMING TO MY
BAR.
>> AND WE'RE JUST GOING TO SHOW
YOU SOME OF THE HIGHLIGHTS
SOME OF Y'ALL SOUNDED LIKE A
REGULAR JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE.
I'M YOUR HOST, ALONG WITH ROB.
>> JUST A REMINDER, THIS
EQUIPMENT IS RENTED.
KARAOKE RULE NUMBER ONE, YOU
MUST RESPECT THE MICROPHONE.
DON'T TAP THE MIC.
DON'T SWING THE MIC.
IF YOU DROP THE MIC, I WILL DROP
YOU.
>> THANK YOU, BABY
NOW IT'S TIME FOR OUR FAVORITE
SEGMENT, KARAOKE ALL STARS
>> LET'S START WITH OUR BAD
CHOICE ALL STARS
THESE ARE FOLKS WHO JUST PICKED
THE WRONG SONGS.
>> FIRST UP, GUY WHO WAS DOING
GREAT UNTIL THE HIGH NOTE CAME
IN
* TAKE ON M
OH N
TAKE ME ON
HELP M
I'LL BE GONE *
*
>> AND LET'S NOT FORGET WOMAN
WHO HAS BEEN OVERSERVED SINGING
"SU SOPPA LAYLA.
* SU SOPPA LAYL
SU SOPPA LAYLA
>> BE CAREFUL WITH THAT FAKE
IF IT BREAKS, I GOT TO GET A NEW
ONE FROM RADIO SHACK
YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO FIND
A RADIO SHACK THESE DAYS
A STORE WHOSE NUMBER ONE SELLER
IS WIRES
>> ROB, YOU LITTLE GRUMPIST.
ALRIGHT, OUR NEXT KARAOKE ALL
STAR IS SOMEONE WHO COMES HERE
BY HIMSELF AND ALWAYS DOES THE
SAME SONG.
IT'S "MAD WORLD" BY NEAL, THE
QUIET GUY IN THE HOODIE.
* ALL AROUND ME
ARE FAMILIAR FACES
WORN OUT PLACE
WORN OUT FACES *
>> I GOT TO BE HONEST, THAT GUY
GIVES OFF REAL COLUMBINE VIBES
>> YOU KNOW.
LET'S KEEP IT GOING WITH OUR
NEXT ALL STAR, GUY WHO MUST HAVE
CHOSEN THE WRONG SONG, BUT WAIT
A SECOND
* YO CHECK IT
MUST WANT TO BEA
YOU ALL YOU KNOW
WHAT IT IS *
* SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GON
I CAN'T BREATH
FOR THE FIRST TIME *
*
>> OH, MAN, HE WAS SO TALENTED
BUT I THINK HE WAS BETTER THAN
JUSTIN BOOBY
>> JUSTIN --
>> BOOBY
YOU KNOW HIM
YOU KNOW, HE SING THAT -
* OWE M
OWE ME *
>> OH, JUSTIN BIEBER
MISSY, I LOVE YOU BUT YOU'RE
STARTING TO WORRY ME
LET'S MOVE ON TO TONIGHT'S
CRINGE ALL STARS
>> OH, THESE ARE THE ROUGH ONES.
OKAY
OKAY, FIRST WE HAVE COUPLE WHO
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE FUN TO SING
LIKE HOMER AND MARGE SIMPSON
* ISLANDS IN THE STREAM
THAT IS WHAT WE AR
NO ONE IN BETWEE
HOW CAN WE BE WRONG
* SAIL AWAY WITH ME
TO ANOTHER WORLD
AND WE RELY ON EACH OTHE
DOH DOH *
>> NOT REALLY MUSIC.
NOT REALLY MUSIC
NOT REALLY COMEDY.
BASICALLY NOTHING.
SPEAKING OF NOTHING, OUR NEXT
ALL STAR IS OUR TWO GERMAN
TOURISTS TRYING THEIR BEST
* HEY BOSS IT'S M
IT IS A CRAZ
DON'T CALL ME MAKE ME *
>> NOW I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY
SAID, BUT I DID LIKE THEIR
ENERGY
I DID.
AND OUR NEXT CRINGE ALL STAR
COMES HERE EVERY WEEKEND
STRAIGHT FROM "THE OFFICE," IT'S
FINANCE BRO TRYING TO GET LAID
>> SUP
THIS ONE'S DEDICATED TO ALL THE
LADIES IN THE HOUSE.
I DON'T LIKE THIS SONG, BUT I
KNOW YOU DO.
* YOU ARE MY FIRE
* THE ONE
* DESIRE
* BELIEVE.
>> I MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
* I WANT IT THAT AWAY *
* TELL ME WHY *
>> I GOT TO SAY IT MAKES ME
REGRET SLEEPING WITH HIM THOSE
SEVEN TIMES.
>> ALL RIGHT
TIME TO LOOK BACK AT OUR
CRAZIEST ALL STARS
"MY PONY," BY GENUINE SUNG BY A
FATHER AND A DAUGHTER.
* IF YOU'RE HORNY
LET'S DO I
RIDE IT MY PONY *
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, DAD
>> YOU TOO, HUN.
>> YOU -- YOU -- YOU CAN'T UNSEE
THAT
>> NO, YOU CAN'T
NO, YOU CAN'T.
>> NOW, IT'S TIME FOR OUR FINAL
KARAOKE ALL STAR
IT'S GIRL WHO CLAIMS HER FRIEND
SIGNED HER UP, BUT WE ALL KNOW
THE TRUTH.
>> WAIT, JESSICA -- NO, WHO PUT
MY NAME IN
YOU GUYS
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SONG YOU
PICKED
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
JESSICA!
* AND I WILL ALWAYS -
* LOVE YOU *
>> JESSICA, SERIOUSLY.
>> WELL, THAT'S IT
THAT'S IT FOR THIS WEEK'S
KARAOKE RECAP.
TAKE IT DOWN, MISSY
>>> HOSTING THANKSGIVING IS A
BIG JOB.
LUCKILY, TARGET'S GOT YOU
COVERED WITH INCREDIBLE SAVINGS
ON EVERYTHING YOU NEED FOR A
PERFECT FEAST.
BUY ONE GET ONE DEALS ON CLASSIC
SIDES AND SAUCES
AND OF COURSE
BUTTER BALL TURKEYS FROM $1.49 A
POUND.
BUT HOSTING THANKSGIVING ALSO
MEANS HOSTING YOUR FAMILY,
AND
THAT CAN BE A WHOLE DAMN THING
>> I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING BIG.
>> THIS TURRY DRY AS THE DAMN
BOWL
>> WE WANT FOOD!
>> IT'S COMING, YOU FREAKING
DOUCHE BAG
>> HEY, WHAT'S THE WI-FI
>> THAT'S WHY TARGET'S ALSO GOT
GREAT DEALS ON A BUNCH OF STUFF
YOU'LL NEED SPECIFICALLY FOR THEM,
LIKE HALF OFF NATE'S
HUMANE TURKEY LOAF
FOR YOUR
NIECE'S ANNOYING NEW BOYFRIEND
>> I DON'T EAT ANYTHING WITH
FEATHERS ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW, I WATCHED THAT NETFLIX
DOCUMENTARY.
HORRIFYING
HORRIFYING WHAT THEY DO TO THESE
BIRDS.
>> AND AFTER DINNER, THE SAVINGS KEEP ON COMING,
WITH DISCOUNTS ON WILSON BRAND FOOTBALLS
SO YOU
CAN WORK OFF DINNER IN THE
BACKYARD WITH THE UNCLE WHO
TAKES THE GAME TOO SERIOUSLY
>> AND TAKE THAT
SECOND DOWN.
>> AND FOR YOUR DIRT BAG COUSIN,
TAKE 20% OFF MOTION SENSOR LIGHTS
SO HE CAN SMOKE
CIGARETTES IN THE DRIVEWAY
>> YOU WANT TO TRY, LITTLE MAN
>> AND $50 OFF APPLE
NOISE-CANCELLING AIR PODS
FOR
WHEN GRANDPA WEIGHS IN ON SOCIAL
ISSUES
>> THE DEMOCRATS WANNA LET THE
GAYS CHANGE FOOTBALL TO --
>> PLUS, TAKE 30% OFF PURINA BRAND DOG FOOD,
SINCE SOMEONE IN
YOUR FAMILY IS BRINGING THEIR
DOG EVEN THOUGH YOU ASKED THEM
NOT TO
AND FOR KIDS, GREAT DEALS ON
TOYS THEY CAN DESTROY
WHEN
THEY'RE LEFT UNSUPERVISED IN THE
BASEMENT
>> PLUS, EVERYDAY LOW PRICES ON
WINE AND BEER TO GET YOU THROUGH
THIS CONVERSATION.
>> YOU KNOW WHO DIED
>> JUDY FELDMAN.
>> AND THIS CONVERSATION
>> THE THING ABOUT CRYPTO IS SO
EXCITING, BECAUSE IT'S ESSENTIAL
LIKE IF YOU THINK ABOUT THE
BLOCK CHAIN.
>> OR THIS ONE
>> YOU GOT A NEW GIRLFRIEND.
GOT SOME NICE -- HUN
>> PLUS, HUGE SAVINGS ON HOLIDAY
MUST HAVES
BAND-AIDS, PAIN RELIEVERS,
AND, OF COURSE, MORE WINE
>> NICE ASS ON HER TOO
GOT TO THOUGHT OUT THAT THING.
>> HEY, SOMEONE'S GOT TO HOST
YOUR FAMILY FOR THANKSGIVING,
SO
IF YOU DREW THE SHORT STRAW --
>> ANYONE GOING TO HELP ME WITH
THESE?
TURN TO TARGET FOR
EVERYTHING YOUR FAMILY NEEDS.
>> HEY, JUST GIVE MY KEYS.
I DRIVE DRUNK ALL THE TIME
>> TARGET, LET'S DO IT ALL AGAIN
AT CHRISTMAS
>> WELL, WHEN YOU ALLOCATE
$500 MILLION OF TAXPAYER MONEY
TO DEVELOP A NEW WEAPONS SYSTEM,
YOU FIND THE TIME.
>> YEAH, WE'RE EAGER TO SEE WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING ON
>> OF COURSE
MY ORDERS IN HEADING THIS
PROJECT WERE CLEAR
MAKE AMERICA THE TECHNOLOGICAL
LEADER IN THE BATTLEFIELD, BUT
THE BATTLEFIELD HAS CHANGED.
SO MUST OUR SOLDIERS
>> ENOUGH WITH THE FOREPLAY,
MAJOR.
YOU GOING TO WHIP IT OUT OR
WHAT
>> A BIT OF A CRUDE WAY TO PUT
IT, BUT YES.
YES.
IMAGINE A SOLDIER WITH UNDYING
LOYALTY, BUILT IN NIGHT VISION,
SUPER SONIC HEARING AND THE
ABILITY TO TRACK AN ENEMY SCENT
WITH 15,000 TIMES THE ACCURACY
OF A NORMAL HUMAN NOSE
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU HAVE
MADE AN AI DRIVEN ROBOTIC
SOLDIER WITH THAT KIND OF
CAPABILITY
>> EVEN BETTER
WE'VE MADE THIS.
>> OKAY.
MAJOR, WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
>> PROJECT DOMINOES, SUBJECT
119 C ALSO KNOWN AS "DOG HEAD
MAN.
>> YOU PUT A DOG'S HEAD ON A
HUMAN BEING'S BODY
>> A DOG'S HEAD AND NECK, MA'AM.
>> AND YOU WANT TO SEND THIS
THING INTO ACTIVE COMBAT
>> ABSOLUTELY.
DOG HEAD MAN IS AN EXTREMELY
WELL TRAINED BATTLEFIELD ASSET
IN FACT, HE CAN ASSEMBLE A TACK
9 COMBAT RIFLE FASTER THAN ANY
HUMAN SOLDIER.
OBSERVE.
>> AND GO, DOG HEAD MAN.
>> I JUST HAVE ONE QUESTION,
MAJOR, DOES THIS THING GO TO THE
BATHROOM ON A TOILET OR DOES IT
GO OUTSIDE AND YOU GOT TO CLEAN
UP AFTER IT?
>> THAT'S YOUR ONE QUESTION?
>> I THINK THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
WOULD WANT TO KNOW
>> AND TIME.
>> 11 SECONDS.
GOOD GIRL, DOG HEAD MAN.
DID YOU SAY "GOOD GIRL"?
>> YES, IT'S A FEMALE DOG'S HEAD
ON A HUMAN MAN'S BODY.
>> SHALL WE BEGIN PREPPING FOR
MASS PRODUCTION?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
WHERE DID YOU EVEN GET THE PARTS
TO MAKE THIS THING
>> UMM, THAT -- LET'S NOT WORRY
ABOUT THAT
I SHOULD ALSO MENTION THAT DOG
HEAD MAN IS TRAINED IN OVER 46
FORMS OF HAND-TO-HAND COMBAT
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, MAN, BUT
IF I SAW THIS COMING AT ME ON
THE BATTLEFIELD, I'D DROP MY
WEAPON AND RUN
>> YEAH -- YEAH, WELL, OF COURSE
YOU WOULD.
LOOK AT YOU.
I'M SORRY, I DON'T THINK THE
U.S. MILITARY CAN GET BEHIND
THIS PROCESS
>> HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT, MA'AM
LOOK AT HIM.
THAT IS THE FINEST SOLDIER THIS
COUNTRY HAS EVER PRODUCED.
>> REALLY?
MAJOR, YOU THINK THAT THING
COULD HANDLE A HIGH LEVEL
MISSION?
YOU THINK THAT SHY THING COULD
HAVE TAKEN BIN LADEN
>> OH, OH.
NOT ONLY WOULD DOG HEAD MAN HAVE
TAKEN BIN LADEN OUT, HE WOULD
HAVE EATEN HIM TOO
>> WELL, OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S A WAR PRIZE
>> MA'AM, I JUST DON'T THINK
YOU'RE SEEING THE BIGGER PICTURE
HERE
>> I AM, AND IT'S EXTREMELY
DISTURBING
>> I HAVE TO AGREE, I'M NOT
GOING TO SIGN OFF ON THIS UNTIL
I KNOW WHERE THAT THING GOES TO
THE BATHROOM
>> LOOK -- LOOK, IF -- IF I
DIDN'T BELIEVE THIS WOULD SAVE
AMERICAN LIVES, I WOULD NOT HAVE
CONVINCED MY FATHER TO DONATE
HIS BODY AND HIS DOG TO THIS
PROJECT.
I MEAN, LOOK AT WHAT HE'S DOING
RIGHT NOW, HE'S DIFFUSING A BOMB
FOR GOD'S SAKE
>> GOOD JOB.
>> HE'S STILL EATING HIS
SANDWICH
>> GOOD.
GOOD DOGHEDMAN
RED WIRE
>> WOW
GOOD
HE'S CUTTING THE DETONATOR WIRE
FIRST.
>> AND JUST LICKING IT.
>> WHATEVER.
YOU GUYS WENT INTO THIS HATING
IT
NOTHING WE COULD SAY WOULD
CHANGE YOUR MIND
GUESS WE'LL CLOSE THE PROJECT
DOWN AND LET CHINA TAKE THE LEAD
IN DOG HEDMAN SOLDIERS
WHOA
CHINA IS MAKING THESE?
GET MASS PRODUCTION STARTED
IMMEDIATELY.
>> OH, YES, MA'AM.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED TO FIND A
LOT OF ANIMAL SHELTERS THAT WILL
LOOK THE OTHER WAY
TIME TO PLAY
"REPUBLICAN OR NOT,"
WITH YOUR
HOST BENSON DUBOIS
>> HELLO, AND WELCOME TO THE
SHOW
THE GAME IS SIMPLE
WE'RE GOING TO MEET SOME PEOPLE.
AND OUR CONTESTANTS HAVE TO
GUESS WHETHER THEY'RE REPUBLICAN
OR NOT
IT SEEMS EASY, RIGHT
HELLO, CONTESTANTS
>> HI, BENSON.
I'M JIM LEE.
HONESTLY, SEES PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD.
SO, I THINK I GOT THIS
>> I BET YOU DO.
AND HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> HELLO, BENSON. I'M MICHELLE FLYNN.
I GREW UP IN
OHIO, SO I'VE BEEN PLAYING THIS
GAME MY WHOLE LIFE
KIND OF AN EXPERT.
>> I'M SURE YOU ARE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
BRING ON OUR FIRST GUEST
THIS IS BRADY.
NOW, HE'S GOING TO MAKE A FEW
STATEMENTS
RING IN AS SOON AS YOU'RE READY
TO GUESS
REPUBLICAN OR NOT?
ALL RIGHT, BRADY, GIVE US OUR
FIRST CLUE
>> I THINK FACEBOOK IS EVIL.
>> OH, WOW?"Kñ÷
BECAUSE THEY'RE SPREADING
DISINFORMATION
OR BECAUSE THEY
BANNED DONALD TRUMP.
>> NOT SO EASY, IS IT?
>> WELL, MAYBE WE NEED ANOTHER
HINT
>> I WOULD SAY YOU DO.
>> I BUY ALL MY PRODUCE STRAIGHT
FROM THE FARM.
>> BECAUSE YOU WANT TO OR
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MISS OHIO
YOU THE EXPERT
KEEP GOING, BRADY.
>> I RESPECT PRO ATHLETES WHO
STAND UP FOR THEIR BELIEFS
>> WHICH ATHLETE
>> AND WHICH BELIEF?
>> WHO KNOWS
IT COULD BE HER
OR HIM
NO GUESSES
ALL RIGHT THEN
GIVE THEM THEIR LAST CLUE,
BRADY.
>> GOD, I HATE COPS.
>> OKAY.
HE IS NOT A REPUBLICAN
>> OH, SO CLOSE.
BUT NO
BRADY IS INDEED A REPUBLICAN
>> BUT HE SAID HE HATES COPS
>> YES, BUT HE WAS TALKING ABOUT
THESE COPS
BETTER LUCK NEXT ROUND
LET'S MEET OUR SECOND GUEST.
LACY
LACY CAME HERE FROM MANHATTAN.
>> NEW YORK CITY OR KANSAS
>> I CAN'T SAY
>> LET'S START THE CLOCK
>> ON TWITTER MY PINNED TWEET IS
"MY BODY, MY CHOICE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S A TRICK, RIGHT, SHE'S
TALKING ABOUT VACCINES, RIGHT?
>> OH, IF WE ONLY KNEW
ANOTHER HINT, LACY?
>> I SUPPORT CAITLYN JENNER.
>> IN WHAT WAY, POLITICALLY
OR -
>> Y'ALL ARE DOING GREAT, JUST
GREAT.
>> JUST GIVE US ANOTHER CLUE
>> OKAY.
MY FAVORITE COMIC IS
DAVE CHAPPELLE
>> STARTING WHEN
>> I LOVE MY JOB.
GIVE THEM ANOTHER ONE.
>> LAST MONTH I WENT TO A BOARD MEETING
AND COMPLAINED ABOUT A
BOOK BEING TAUGHT IN MY
DAUGHTER'S SCHOOL.
>> OKAY, I DEFINITELY KNOW THAT
ONE, SHE'S A REPUBLICAN.
>> NO, SORRY
>> WHAT?
SHE WAS COMPLAINING ABOUT A BOOK
IN HER KID'S SCHOOL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THAT BOOK, THE BIBLE
ALL RIGHT.
BEFORE WE BRING OUT OUR NEXT GUEST,
LET'S HEAR ABOUT TODAY'S
SPONSORS
JIMMY!
>> "REPUBLICAN OR NOT" IS
SPONSORED BY -
THE CITY OF ORLANDO.
WHERE DEMOCRATS VISIT AND
REPUBLICANS LIVE
ORLANDO, BACK TO YOU, BENSON
THANK YOU, JIMMY
LET'S BRING OUT OUR NEXT
GUEST --
LIZ.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> IS THAT -- I FEEL LIKE I
RECOGNIZE HER.
>> MAYBE YOU DO.
START THE CLOCK
>> I'M A CONGRESSWOMAN FROM
WYOMING.
I'M ENDORSED BY THE NRA,
AND HAVE AN 80% RATING FROM THE
AMERICAN CONSERVATIVE UNION.
>> NOBODY WANTS TO RING IN
>> I REALLY WANT TO BECAUSE IT
SEEMS SO OBVIOUS BUT THIS GAME
IS WEIRD
>> MY NAME IS LIZ CHENEY
I'M THE DAUGHTER OF VICE
PRESIDENT DICK CHENEY.
>> SHE'S THE DAUGHTER OF
DICK CHENEY.
>> OKAY.
Y'ALL ARE BEING REAL TRICKY
HERE, AREN'T YOU
>> I'M A REPUBLICAN.
REPUBLICAN, SHE JUST SAID SHE'S
A REPUBLICAN
>> NO, I AM SORRY.
AGAIN, THAT IS WRONG
>> WHAT?
HOW?
>> WELL, THE WYOMING REPUBLICAN
PARTY ACTUALLY VOTED
REPRESENTATIVE CHENEY OUT THIS WEEK
FOR OPPOSING DONALD TRUMP
>> BUT I AM A REPUBLICAN
>> YOU MIGHT TELL EVERYBODY THAT,
BUT IT'S NOT WHAT YOUR
OTHER REPUBLICANS SAY.
LIKE IT OR NOT, YOU ARE THE
RACHEL DOLEZAL OF THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
>> WELL, I DON'T CARE.
I HAVE BEEN FIGHTING FOR
REPUBLICAN VALUES ALL MY LIFE.
>> THAT IS SO CUTE
WE WILL SEE YOU ON MSNBC IN
ABOUT A WEEK
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE WILL ASK
ARE THESE CAMOUFLAGE PANTS
REPUBLICAN OR NOT?
>> WHO'S WEARING THEM?
A GUY PLAYING PAINT BALL OR
RIHANNA?
>> YOU STILL DON'T GET IT.
* PUT ON MY BLU
FAKE JORDANS
AND I BOARDED THE TRAIN *
* TOUCHDOWN IN TH
LAND OF COLIN JOSTO5G÷
AND THE LEGENDARY WU-TANG *
* DRIVE ON BY
THE GARBAGE DUMP
SO BIG YOU COULD
SEE IT FROM SPACE *
* YEAH WE GOT
LIKE 80 BAGEL SPOT
AND EVERY BLOC
HAS A PIZZA PLACE *
* AND I'M WALKING IN STATEN
ALL THE WAY FROM STAPLES
INTO GREAT CUBES *
* WALKING IN STATEN
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF
COPS AND A TON OF PILLS *
* SO THE GHOST OF ROBERT LOZZIA
I SAID AND WHERE DO I KNOW YOU
HE SAID I WAS THE GU
ON THE PIANO IN "BIG" *
* AND HE SPARKE
A MAJOR DOOB
SO SECURITY SURE
DID SMELL THIS *
* THEY SAID
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU *
* MAN IT'S -- AND WET
AND YOU BEST BET
THAT ALL -- GONNA DO *
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO BE IN A
PARODY OF MY OWN SONG.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN I'M ALREADY IN
IT
* AND NOW WE'RE
WALKING IN STATE
IT'S JUST A PIECE OF BAGEL PLACE
* WALKING IN STATEN
IT'S ACTUALLY A PIECE OF
-- INSIDE A BAGEL PLACE *
* WE'VE GOT THE -- *
>> IT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY WHITE.
* THEY'VE GOT -- *
>> HEY, IT'S KRISTEN -- *
* AND WHEN YOU SEE WILD TURKEYS
BY THE HOSPITAL *
* LIKE AN ALARMING AMOUNT
NO ONE EVEN BATS AN EY
MAN, IT'S REALLY WEIRD
IN STATEN *
*
* I THINK THIS STRIP CLUB
USED TO BE A MCDONALD'S *
* AND OUR ZOO
IS SHOCKINGLY SMALL *
* ONCE I SAW A MAGIC MA
HE HIT A HOLE IN ONE
AT THE SAFARI MINI GOLF *
* STATEN ISLAND
WHERE I'M WALKIN
REAL IS WHAT I BE TALKING *
* SEE Y'ALL PROCEED
WITH CAUTION
DON'T CROSS TH
STATE OF NEW YORK'EN *
* YOU KNOW EMPIRE STATE
* MY YANKEE HAT A STATEMENT
A MIDDLE FINGER TO BOSTO
MORE LIKE I'
WALKING IN MEMPHIS *
* FEEL IT ALL IN MY BRITCHE
MADE IT LITTLE RICHE
BY STEALING FROM LITTLE -- *
* WHERE I'M FRO
A LITTLE DIFFERENT
WE TRAPPIN' AND EASY PASSING
CROSS THE -- *
* WELCOME TO STATEN *
WE WERE DRINKING WHITE CLAWS AND
BOOTLEGS *
* AND THE COPS HAVEN'
STOPPED TO FIGHT *
* HE SAID TELL ME
ARE YOU ITALIA
AND I SAID MAN
I AM TONIGHT *
* WE'RE WALKING
THROUGH STATEN
THIS PLACE IS THE REASON
I TURNED OUT WEIRD *
* WALKING IN STATEN
AND THANKS TO NEW JERSEY
WE'RE NOT -- *
* WE'RE WALKING IN STATEN
WHERE EVERYBODY'S DREAMS
GO RIGHT DOWN THE DRAIN *
* WALKING IN STATEN
MAYBE HEAR A -
WITH A GOLDEN CHAIN *
*
>> WOW, LOOK AT THE OCEAN, GUYS.
IMAGINE IF WE COULD ACTUALLY
SWIM IN IT
>> WHAT'S THAT OUT IN THE WATER?
>> A DEAD BODY
>> GREAT
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
SAWEETIE
BABY TAP I
TAP TAP TAP IN *
* DIAMONDS DANCIN
ON YOUR NECK
BETTER TAP I
TAP TAP TAP IN *
* GET MONEY
GET RICH
BABY TAP I
TAP TAP TAP IN *
* M-O-B
ICY GANG
LET US TAP I
HMM *
* TAP TAP TAP I
AY
ON CENTER IC
WAIT ON CENTER ICE *
* I'MA SHOW YOU HOW
TO BAG A
EIGHT-FIGURE
HOO *
* FACE ON MY ZADD
SHEESH
POCKETS ON JIGGA
HOO *
* YOU BETTER GET THE CARD
OR MAKE IT SWIPE
LIKE TINDER PHEW
PRIVATE VILLA *
* AND THE FUR CHINCHILLA HA
WHEN HE POST M
ALL THE -- GET
SICKER BLAH *
* KILLE
I DON'T NEED FILLERS
NOPE
NEVER BEEN A LAME *
* SO THE REAL ONE'S THINNER
FEEL IT YEAH
DADDY ON THE FACETIM
YOU COULD NEVER TAKE MINE *
* END UP ON THE DATELIN
UH UH UH
RICH WITH NO DAY JOB
GIRL HIT YOUR WOP WOP *
* ALWAYS ON THE COURT SID
UH-HUH HUH
BILLIONAIRE BOYS
WANNA SIGN ME UP *
* HA HA H
YOU'RE LIKE ON
THE WEST COAST
I JUST WANNA GO *
* DOWN SOUT
ALL THESE LAME
LITTLE PEPPERS TRYIN
US FOR CLOUT *
* HMM I WON'T LET HIM HIT
BUT HE CAN PUT I
IN HIS MOUTH *
* LIL' WAIS
FAT FA
BABY TAP I
TAP TAP TAP IN *
* DIAMONDS DANCIN
ON YOUR NECK
BETTER TAP I
TAP TAP TAP IN *
* GET YOUR MONE
GET RICH BABY TAP IN
TAP TAP TAP IN
M-O-B ICY GANG *
* BETTER TAP IN
MM-HMM YEA
TAP TAP TAP IN *
*
* GOT MY DATE PLANNED
SHE A REAL BAD -
GOT HER OWN MONE
SHE DON'T NEED NO -- *
* ON THE DANCE FLOO
SHE HAD TW
THREE DRINKS
NOW SHE'S TWERKIN' *
* SHE THROW IT OU
AND COME BACK IN
THAT'S MY BEST FRIEN
SHE A REAL BAD -- *
* PICK UP HER OWN CAR
SHE DON'T NEED NO LYFT
IN THE STRIP CLU
KNOW MY GIRL GOING TIP *
* NOW SHE TWERKIN
SHE THROW IT OUT
AND COME BACK IN
BEEP-BEEP *
* IS THAT MY BESTIE
IN A TESSI
FRESH BLOW OUT
SKIN ON TAN *
* OOH SHE READY
GIRL YOU LOOK GOOD
WITH A T AT THE EN
I'MA HYPE HER EVERY TIME *
* THAT MY -
SHE BEEN DOW
SINCE THE JELLIE
AND THE VOLVOS *
* GOT ME STEPPIN'
OUT THAT JEE
GOT MANOLO'S
WHEN WE PULL UP *
* TO THE SCEN
THEY BE FILLED
WITH JEALOUS
IF A -- *
* GET FINICKY
SHE GON' BRING
THAT ENERG
I HIT HER PHONE *
* WITH THE TEA LIKE GIRL, GUESS
WHAT
ALL THE RICH BOY
WANNA -- ON US *
* ALL THIS SITTING UP
YOU CAN LOOK
DON'T TOUC
IN OUR BAG *
* BUST SOME BANDS
EVERY TIME
WE LINK UP
THAT MY BEST FRIEND *
* SHE A REAL BAD --
GOT HER OWN MONE
SHE 'ON'T NEED NO --
ON THE DANCE FLOOR *
* SHE HAD TWO
THREE DRINKS
NOW SHE TWERKING
SHE THROW IT OUT *
* AND COME BACK I
THAT'S MY BEST FRIEN
SHE A REAL BAD -
DRIVE HER OWN CAR *
* SHE DON'T NEED NO LYF
IN THE STRIP CLU
KNOW MY GIRL GOING TIP
NOW SHE TWERKIN' *
* SHE THROW IT OU
AND COME BACK IN
HE
SHE'S BEST FRIEND *
* YOU WILL NEVER SAY NO
UH OH GIRL
I THINK YOUR
BOOTY GROWING *
* F IT UP
AND THE MIRROR
HIT SOME POSES
BEST FRIENDS *
* AND YOU MUST GO I
BEST FRIEN
IF YOU'RE MOVING
LIKE A STOW IN *
* UH OH GIR
I THINK YOUR
BOOTY GROWIN
F IT UP *
* AND THE MIRRO
HIT SOME POSES
BEST FRIEN
YOU MUST LOVE *
* MY SOULMATE *
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE
>> THANK YOU
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> WELL, YESTERDAY WAS A WEIRD
ONE FOR PRESIDENT BIDEN.
HE WENT UNDER ANESTHESIA FOR A
COLONOSCOPY,
AND WHEN HE WOKE
UP, THE HOUSE HAD PASSED THE
$2 TRILLION SOCIAL SAFETY NET BILL,
THE RITTENHOUSE VERDICT
WAS ANNOUNCED
AND A WOMAN HAD
TECHNICALLY BEEN PRESIDENT FOR
THE FIRST TIME EVER.
AND WHILE BIDEN WAS PROCESSING ALL OF THAT,
HE WAS RUSHED OFF
TO PARDON A TURKEY NAMED PEANUT
BUTTER
I MEAN, COME ON.
THE GUY JUST TURNED 79
AND
HALF THE COUNTRY ALREADY THINKS
HE'S SENILE.
YOU CAN'T DROP ALL OF THAT ON
HIM THE SECOND HE COMES OUT OF
THE GAS.
I HONESTLY CAN'T BELIEVE HOW
WELL IT WENT
REMEMBER DAVID AFTER THE
DENTIST?
I'M KIND OF SURPRISED WE DIDN'T
GET BIDEN AFTER THE COLONOSCOPY.
>>> ON FRIDAY, KYLE RITTENHOUSE
WAS FOUND NOT GUILTY
IN THE
MURDER OF TWO MEN DURING THE
BLACK LIVES MATTER PROTESTS.
SO HOPEFULLY HE GOT ALL OF THAT
SHOOTING OUT OF HIS SYSTEM
BEFORE HE BECOMES A COP.
PROTESTS ARE BEING HELD ALL
AROUND THE COUNTRY IN RESPONSE
TO THE ACQUITTAL OF KYLE RITTENHOUSE
WHICH IS BRAVE
BECAUSE RITTENHOUSE JUST GOT OFF
FOR SHOOTING PROTESTERS.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE DON'T TEMPT
HIM.
>>> MATT GAETZ SAID HIS OFFICE
WOULD BE OPEN TO HIRING KYLE
RITTENHOUSE AS A CONGRESSIONAL INTERN
BECAUSE GAETZ HAS ALWAYS
LOVED TEENAGERS WHO ARE WILLING
TO DO TERRIBLE THINGS.
>>> STEVE BANNON, SEEN HERE
ORDERING "ONE NEW LIVER, PLEASE,"
SURRENDERED TO THE FBI
ON CONTEMPT OF CONGRESS CHARGES
AND SAID, "WE'RE TAKING DOWN THE
BIDEN REGIME."
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
STEVE, BUT I THINK BIDEN'S GOT
THAT COVERED ALL ON HIS OWN.
BANNON ADDRESSED HIS SUPPORTERS
IN A LIVE STREAM ON GETTR,
A
SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORM POPULAR
WITH TRUMP ALLIES.
GETTR IS NAMED AFTER WHAT ITS
USERS SAY WHENEVER THEY SEE A
WOMAN WALKING ALONE.
>> WASHINGTON, D.C. ART SCHOOL
IS POSTPONING RENAMING ITS THEATER
AFTER ALUMNI
DAVE CHAPPELLE FOLLOWING HIS
NETFLIX SPECIAL CONTROVERSY.
WELL, OF COURSE.
I MEAN, GOD FORBID YOU SHOULD NAME A BUILDING
AFTER SOMEONE
PROBLEMATIC IN WASHINGTON, D.C
MEANWHILE, MY OLD HIGH SCHOOL
INSISTS ON KEEPING
THE
"MICHAEL CHE SUCKS BUTT"
BATHROOM STALL
>> SOME OF MY BEST WORK.
>>> ARIZONA CONGRESSMAN PAUL GOSAR,
SEEN HERE WATCHING AN
INTERRACIAL COUPLE WALK BY -
HE HAS BEEN OFFICIALLY CENSURED
AFTER POSTING A VIOLENT ANIME VIDEO
THAT DEPICTED HIM KILLING
ALEXANDRIA OCASIO-CORTEZ
BUT I DON'T KNOW
HE'S
A 60-YEAR-OLD MAN MAKING HIS OWN ANIME
WHEN HE HEARD HE WAS GETTING
PUNISHED, HE'S LIKE, IS IT
NIPPLE CLAMP
I JUST HOPE AN OCTOBER PUS
DOESN'T DO ANYTHING TO ME.
>>> THIS YEAR'S MACY'S
THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE WILL
FEATURE SEVERAL EXCITING NEW
BALLOONS INCLUDING STAR OF "THE
MANDALORIAN," GROGU, AKA BABY
YODA
HERE TO COMMENT IS BABY YODA
*
>> YA BOY IS BACK!
WHAT UP NEW YORK CITY!
>> YEAH, IT IS GREAT TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, BABY YODA
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A PARADE
BALLOON.
YOU MUST BE EXCITED.
>> WELL, I'M GETTING PAID
$2 MILLION JUST TO GET WITH
PIKACHU, RONALD McDONALD, AND
THE DUDE FROM "DIARY OF A WIMPY
KID" ON LIVE TV.
HIGH AS HELL
WOOOHOO!
MY LIFE'S A MOVIE, SON
>> THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN, BUT YOU
GOT ANY OTHER FUN PLANS FOR
THANKSGIVING
>> HELL YEAH
ME AND THE SQUAD ARE DOING A
LITTLE FRIENDSGIVING THING OVER
AT POST MALONE'S CRIB.
YEAH, IT'S GOING TO BE ME,
MILLIE BOBBY BROWN, THE GEICO
GECKO, LOU, AND MY BOY CLIFFORD
THE BIG RED DOG.
>> GOSH.
AND I NOTICE YOU GOT A NEW LOOK.
>> I GUESS IT'S OBVIOUS, I'M
PUNK NOW
LIKE, REALLY AUTHENTIC, STICK IT
TO THE MAN, POP PUNK
YEAH
I GOT A NEW ALBUM COMING OUT.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
IT'S CALLED "CONFESSIONS
OF THE DIARY OF A LOSER.
IT'S ABOUT THAT UNIVERSAL
FEELING WHEN YOU'RE UNPOPULAR IN
HIGH SCHOOL, AND NO ONE WILL
DATE YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE A LITTLE
GREEN JEDI
AND CHE, I'M NOT GOING TO LIE,
YOU KNOW, THE WORLD AIN'T READY
FOR HOW GOOD THIS MUSIC IS
OOH!
>> THAT'S VERY EXCITING.
CAN WE HEAR A LITTLE
>> HE GOING TO TWIST MY ARM LIKE
THAT
OKAY
YEAH, I'LL DROP ONE A CAPPELLA
THIS SONG IS CALLED "10th GRADE
IS HARD.
* JUST ANOTHER BORING DAY
IN HIGH SCHOOL WHO
WHY CAN'T I BE ON THE TEAM
YEAH YEAH YEAH *
* I GUESS I'M JUST
STEREOTYPICAL BOY *
OH, MY GOD
YEAH
>> WOW, I LIKE IT.
I LIKE IT.
EVERYBODY LIKES IT
AND ABOUT THE WHOLE HIGH SCHOOL
THING, HOW OLD ARE YOU AGAIN
>> OH, I'M IN MY 50s
BUT, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, YOUR BOY AIN'T EXACTLY
POPULAR ANYMORE.
YEAH
IT TURNS OUT BEING ON DISNEYPLUS
HAS ITS PLUSES
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
SPECULATION ABOUT YOUR DATING
LIFE.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S ACTUALLY PRIVATE.
I DON'T REALLY TALK ABOUT THAT
STUFF, BUT YEAH, I'LL TELL YOU
EVERYTHING
YEAH, I'M DATING MAMA BEAR FROM
THE BERENSTEIN BEARS
YOU KNOW, WE'RE HAVING FUN
AND BRO, YOU KNOW, WHEN SHE SHOW
UP WITH THAT BLUE NIGHTGOWN, AND
A CAP ON
UM -
YEAH
LET'S JUST SAY WE GOING TO
BEREN-STAIN THE SHEETS
>> BABY YODA, I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S APPROPRIATE
>> NO, IT IS, THOUGH
I GOT A MESSAGE FOR HER EX
BABY GROOT, IT'S OVER.
IF YOU TEXT MY GIRL AGAIN, I
WILL THROW YOUR TWIG ASS INTO
THE CHIPPER, THEN TURN YOU INT
SOME PAPER, AND THEN WIPE MY
LITTLE GREEN ASS WITH YOU.
AMEN
>> WELL, BABY YODA, EVERYBODY.
>>> A MAN SURPRISED HIS
GIRLFRIEND BY BRINGING HER ONSTAGE
TO PROPOSE TO HER DURING
AN ADELE CONCERT
THEN THEY SAT DOWN AND LISTENED
TO AN HOUR OF SONGS ABOUT
DIVORCE.
>>> MEL GIBSON SAYS HE IS IN
TALKS TO DIRECT THE NEXT "LETHAL
WEAPON" MOVIE.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO SEE A BROKEN
DOWN BLACK GUY TEAM UP WITH A HANDSOME RACIST,
JUST WATCH
"WEEKEND UPDATE.
THANKS
>> THAT WASN'T ADDRESSED
ANYWAY
>>> A SELF-PORTRAIT BY
FRIDA KAHLO WAS SOLD AT AUCTION
FOR THE RECORD SUM OF
$34 MILLION
A PRICE THAT
DEFINITELY RAISED SOME EYEBROW
>>> A PROFESSOR AT A COLLEGE IN
VIRGINIA IS BEING CRITICIZED
AFTER SAYING THAT IT IS NOT
IMMORAL FOR ADULTS TO BE
SEXUALLY ATTRACTED TO CHILDREN
FIND OUT WHY IN HIS NEW BOOK
CALLED "WAIT, HOLD ON, HEAR ME
OUT.
>>> NEW RESEARCH SHOWS THAT
BEFORE HONEY BEES ARE KILLED BY MURDER HORNETS,
THEY SCREAM A
RALLY CRY TO OTHER BEES
WHO
SADLY JUST FILM THE ATTACK WITH
THEIR iPHONES.
>> IT'S NOT REAL, GUYS
>>> IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT FOR
THE FIRST TIME EVER, DISNEY
PARKS WILL FEATURE BLACK SANTA
CLAUSES.
UNFORTUNATELY, AS PART OF THE
VILLAINS PARADE.
>>> ROYAL EXPERTS ARE SAYING
THAT QUEEN ELIZABETH'S HEALTH
HAS ENTERED A DIFFERENT PHASE
AND THE PUBLIC MAY NOT SEE HER
UNTIL FEBRUARY
SO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
NEW TITTIES.
>>> THIS WEEK, THE U.S
EXPERIENCED
THE LONGEST PARTIAL
LUNAR ECLIPSE IN NEARLY 600
YEARS.
SCIENTISTS SAY THE ECLIPSE BEGAN
WHEN YO MAMA GOT ON THE
TRAMPOLINE.
>>> THE U.N. CLIMATE CHANGE
CONFERENCE ENDED THIS WEEK WITH
MANY SAYING THAT NOT NEARLY
ENOUGH WAS DONE TO ADDRESS THE
ALARMING RISE IN GLOBAL
TEMPERATURES
HERE TO COMMENT IS MOTHER EARTH.
>> HELLO
HELLO, EARTH CREATURES, ONE AND
ALL.
NO, I'M KIDDING.
I ACTUALLY TALK NORMAL
YEAH, I'M JUST THE NORMAL MOM
WHO'S HOT AND PISSED
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE, MOTHER EARTH.
>> OH, YOU CAN CALL ME MOMMA.
>> OKAY, MOMMA
SORRY, MAMA.
DOES THAT SOUND NATURAL COMING
FROM ME?
>> NO, NO, NO.
SOUNDS REALLY BAD.
>> WELL, YOUR DRESS IS COOL.
I LOVE THAT.
IS IT LIKE A MYTHICAL EARTH
ROBE
>> NO, I GOT IT AT CHICO'S
BECAUSE IT HAD A MOON ON THE
BOOB
YEAH, I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT
PEOPLE SAY THE EARTH IS FLAT
I MEAN, LOOK AT THESE HONKERS.
>> HR SAID I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO
LOOK
SO THE CLIMATE SUMMIT JUST
FINISHED
HOW ARE YOU?
>> WELL, NOT WELL, BETTY
I MEAN, HERE'S THE THING, I AM
NOT A HARD ASS
I MEAN, YOU GUYS GOT TO ADMIT I
HAVE BEEN A VERY COOL MOM, OKAY?
I LET A LOT OF WEIRD STUFF
SLIDE.
LIKE
I LET YOU DO SEA WORLD
I LET YOU PUT MASCARA ON RATS
AND MONKEYS.
NEW YORK IS LIKE A MIX OF CABS
AND HORSES AND I'M LIKE, "I
DON'T LOVE IT, BUT DO YOUR
THING.
YOU KNOW
BUT NOW I AM WORRIED
I THINK I'M SICK
>> IS THERE ANYONE TO HELP YOU
OUT?
IS THERE LIKE A FATHER EARTH
>> NO.
NO, I'M A SINGLE MOM
OKAY, I MEAN, I DO HAVE A CASUAL
HOOK UP SITUATION WITH FATHER
TIME
WE KIND OF GET FREAKY NASTY.
>> WOW
>> I KNOW.
I WISH IT WAS A WOW.
BUT IT'S MORE LIKE A "OKAY,
THANK YOU?
>> WHAT CAN WE DO TO HELP
REVERSE THE CURRENT CLIMATE
CRISIS
>> WELL, THAT'S THE THING, IT'S
ALL THE THINGS THAT YOU DON'T
WANT TO DO, YOU KNOW
LIKE NO MORE HAMBURGER OR
FOREVER 21, OKAY
STOP THROWING iPHONES IN THE
OCEAN.
AND CAN I JUST SAY ONE THING -
COAL IS FROM MY ASS.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT
LIKE YOU'RE LITERALLY GOING DOWN
DIGGING AROUND IN MY ASS AND
GRABBING COAL NUGGETS.
AND THEN YOU'RE LIKE, "OH, I
THINK WE SHOULD LIKE BURN OUR
MOM'S ASS ROCKS.
AND THE SUN IS LIKE RIGHT THERE,
LITERALLY BEGGING FOR A JOB, BUT
YOU GUYS ARE LIKE, NO, WE HAVE A
GRAND TRADITION OF BURNING MOM'S
ASS.
>> DON'T YOU THINK WE CAN MAKE
NEW TECHNOLOGY THAT CAN HELP
WITH SOME OF THIS STUFF?
>> HMM, I DON'T KNOW
I FEEL LIKE ALL I SEE IS LIKE
DIVORCED NERDS TRYING TO
COLONIZE MARS, YOU KNOW?
AND HONESTLY, I KNOW MARS.
SHE'S A HOT, DRY, WINDY WHORE.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT, COLIN?
>> I HEARD THAT.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU
I GUESS I JUST AM STILL HOPEFUL
THAT WE CAN MAKE IT BETTER
>> AW, SEE, THAT'S WHY I'M GOING
TO MISS HUMANS AFTER YOU BURN.
YOU GUYS WERE SO CUTE,
BEFORE YOU GO, IS THERE ANYTHING
ELSE YOU WANT HUMANS TO KNOW
>> OH, SURE.
YES, THERE IS.
*
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I CARE ABOUT YOU
I LOVE YOU
AND THIS CAN GO ONE OF TWO WAYS.
YOU HELP ME, OR --
I'M GONNA KILL YOU
MOMMA GONNA KILL YOU DEAD.
NAH, I'M KIDDING
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
I THINK THE CORPORATIONS ARE
REALLY GONNA HELP YOU.
of the year.
*
>>> WE NOW RETURN TO THE
THANKSGIVING BAKING
CHAMPIONSHIP
>> OKAY, BAKERS, TIME IS UP.
TODAY'S THEME WAS GIVING THANKS
AND YOU HAD TWO HOURS TO CREATE
CAKES BASED ON WHAT YOU'RE MOST
THANKFUL FOR THIS TIME OF YEAR
FIRST TIME -- FIRST UP IS HOME
BAKER STACY.
>> HI, JUDGES, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M HERE
>> WELL, WE'RE GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
TELL US WHAT YOU MADE TODAY?
>> WELL, I ALWAYS WORRIED I
WOULD NEVER HAVE CHILDREN.
THIS YEAR I'M THANKFUL FOR
MY BEAUTIFUL BABY GIRL WHO TURNS
THREE THIS THANKSGIVING.
SO MY CAKE IS BUBBLE GUM FUN
COVERED IN SWEET VANILLA
FONDANT.
AND MY LITTLE GIRL JUST HAD HER
FIRST DANCE RECITAL SO SHE'S
WEARING A PINK TUTU MADE OF FUN
SUGAR.
>> AW, THAT IS ADORABLE, I'M
DYING.
>> THANK YOU
THANK YOU.
I'M ALWAYS AS PROUD OF HER AS I
AM THE CAKE.
>> OH.
WELL, LET'S SEE IT
>> YEAH, I MESSED UP
STACY, LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD A
LITTLE TROUBLE THERE
>> YEAH, I MESSED UP
I THOUGHT IF I PRETENDED TO CRY,
YOU GUYS WOULDN'T NOTICE THAT MY
CAKE WAS BAD
>> SO WHERE DID YOU GO WRONG
>> YEAH, I HAD TROUBLE WITH HER
HEAD SO I TURNED IT INTO A
DIAPER
AND THEN I PUT YELLOW LEGS ON
HER.
AND I JUST KIND OF SHUT DOWN
>> WELL, LET'S GO AHEAD AND
SAMPLE THE CAKE.
>> ALL RIGHT
I'M KIND OF GETTING A LOT OF
MUSTARD.
>> YEAH.
I DO NOT KNOW HOW TO BAKE.
I ALSO DO NOT HAVE A DAUGHTER.
I MADE THAT ALL UP
>> WOW, YOU ARE A MESS
NEXT UP IS HOME BAKER AND
AMATEUR RAPPER MIKE.
>> HI, JUDGES, HAPPY BAKES
GIVING
>> OH, CUTE PUN.
AND MIKE, I HAVE TO ASK, DO YOU
RAP?
>> OH, I REALLY DO, AND IF I
MAY --
* MY NAME IS MIKE
AND I'M HERE TO BAKE
THE MAKE THE CAKE -- *
>> WOW, GOT A LITTLE TONGUE TIED
THERE.
BUT LET'S HEAR WHAT YOU'RE
THANKFUL FOR
>> WELL, THIS YEAR I'M THANKFUL
FOR THE HOLIDAY ITSELF
SO IN THE SPIRIT OF ABUNDANCE, I
MADE TWO CAKES
*
THE FIRST IS A PILGRIM MADE FROM
BUTTERSCOTCH POUND CAKE AND
EUROPEAN BUTTER CREAM.
THE SECOND CAKE IS A FAUX TURKEY
MADE WITH ANGEL FOOD AND CARAMEL
ICING.
SAVE ME A DRUMSTICK.
>> WOW
TWO CAKES, THAT'S A FIRST.
LET'S SEE THEM
>> YEAH, I DID IT WRONG.
>> OH, MIKE, WHAT HAPPENED
>> I THINK JUST A TOTAL LACK OF
IMAGINATION AND ABILITY.
YOU KNOW LIKE WHEN YOUR BRAIN
SAYS, "YOU GOT THIS," BUT YOU
DON'T.
>> NOW, WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T REMEMBER DOING ANY OF
THIS
>> WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
NEXT UP IS RETURNING CONTESTANT
SANDY.
>> HI, JUDGES.
SO I PULLED OUT ALL THE STOPS
TODAY WITH MY THREE LAYER
FANTASIA MAPLE BOURBON WEDDING
CAKE
>> OKAY.
>> NEXT UP IS RALPH.
>> WHAT?
NO, THIS IS GOOD
>> WELL, YOU SAID IT'S THREE
LAYERS, AND THERE'S ONLY TWO,
SO
>> HIS CAKE IS HORRIBLE, AND YOU
DIDN'T EVEN TASTE IT
>> OKAY.
MIKE, CAN WE TASTE YOUR CAKE
>> REALLY?
YEAH, SURE
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MIKE, NOW DID YOUR CAKE JUST
OPEN ITS EYES AND SCREAM
IS IT POSSESSED OR SOMETHING
>> WELL, WE STILL NEED TO TASTE
IT
>> RIGHT
OF COURSE.
>> MIKE, DID THE PILGRIM JUST
BARF ON THE TURKEY
>> I BELIEVE IT DID, MA'AM
IT'S SQUEAMISH, I GUESS.
>> THAT'S SO DISGUSTING.
THAT IS NOT UP TO BAKING
CHALLENGE STANDARDS.
EWW, OH, MY GOSH
OH, MY GOSH.
>> WELL, SANDY, YOU ASKED FOR
THAT
>> SHOULD WE GO?
>> NO, MIKE, IT'S ANYONE'S GAME,
SO RALPH
>> WELL, IT'S EASY TO LOOK BACK
AT THANKSGIVINGS OF OLD.
BUT WHAT WILL THANKSGIVINGS BE
IN THE FUTURE.
THANKS TO A NEW ERA OF SPACE
TRAVEL, WE MAY KNOW SOONER THAN
YOU THINK.
MY CAKE IS A TRIBUTE TO THAT
>> OKAY.
AND THE WHITE STUFF IS LIKE
REENTERING THE ATMOSPHERE?
>> YES, MA'AM, AND THE SPUNK IS
ICING.
>> YOU KNOW, WE HAVE A REALLY
TOUGH DECISION TO MAKE
>> NO, YOU DON'T
*
>>> KNOCK KNOCK.
>> SIMU, WHAT'S UP, MY FELLOW
YELLOW FELLOW?
>> WHAT?
>> NOTHING
I'M JUST NERVOUS I THINK,
I MEAN, THIS HAS NEVER
HAPPENED BEFORE, RIGHT
ASIAN MALE HOST.
ASIAN MALE CAST MEMBER
>> I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE THE SPIDER-MAN
MEME
EXCEPT, YOU HAVE ABS
AND I HAVE -- IBS.
>> IBS
>> I-B-S
ANYWAY, CONGRATS, MAN.
I MEAN, FIRST ASIAN MARVEL LEAD,
THAT'S HUGE.
>> OH, THANK YOU
I ALMOST CAN'T WRAP MY AHEAD
AROUND IT.
I MEAN, YOU GET IT, RIGHT?
LIKE, FIRST FULLY ASIAN CAST
MEMBER ON SNL?
AMAZING.
>> OH, YEAH.
THANKS
I JUST THINK IT'S WEIRD THAT
PEOPLE KEEP TRACK OF THIS STUFF,
THOUGH
>> AH, YEAH.
TOTALLY.
I MEAN, I JUST GOT THIS.
FIRST ASIAN MAN TO MOVE FROM
CANADA TO AMERICA.
>> I HAVE ONE THAT SAYS BOWEN.
>> OH, NICE.
YEAH, I JUST FORGET TO TAKE MINE
OFF.
>> HEY, BOWEN, I HAVE AN AWARD
FOR YOU.
YOU ARE THE FIRST GAY ASIAN CAST
MEMBER TO MISPRONOUNCE BOUTIQUE.
>> IS IT NOT BOUTIQUEA
>> NO.
>> AW, MAN, THAT'S SO HISTORIC
>> AND SIMU, YOU WERE JUST NAMED
THE FIRST ASIAN MAN
TO DEAD PAN
ON SPLASH MOUNTAIN
>> WOW, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> BUT SERIOUSLY, "SHANG-CHI"
WAS SO GOOD.
>> THANK YOU
YEAH, I GUESS THEY'RE SAYING I'M
THE FIRST ASIAN MAN TO BLOW UP A
DRAGON FROM THE INSIDE
>> I GOT THE SAME ONE TOO BUT IT
MEANS SOMETHING ELSE
>> ANYWAY, DON'T YOU THINK IT'S
KIND OF -- KIND OF RIDICULOUS.
>> TOTALLY
LIKE, THE STATE OF MICHIGAN GAVE ME
"THE GOOD JOB PARENTHESES ASIAN" AWARD,
I DO NOT CARE.
>> TO EVERY ASIAN ON THE PLANET,
I DID THIS FOR YOU
>> I KNOW.
FIRST ASIAN MAN TO BEAT
"STARCRAFT 2."
I DIDN'T EVEN GO TO THE
CEREMONY
THERE'S JUST NO TRUE WAY TO SAY
THIS
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HEY, MR. ASIAN PANERA, THESE
ARE FOR YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD, FOR ME.
>> WHAT IS MR. ASIAN PANERA?
>> OH, I GUESS I WAS THE FIRST
ASIAN TO YOU-PICK-TWO A PANERA
OR SOMETHING
>> I DID IT.
I DID IT
I PICKED TWO
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S ALMOST
EMBARRASSING
LIKE I DIDN'T EVEN TELL ANYONE
ABOUT BEING ONE OF PEOPLE'S
SEXIEST MEN ALIVE.
>> MOM, I'M HOT.
>> WEREN'T YOU THE FIRST OPENLY
BOTTOM GUY ON THAT LIST?
>> I'M NOT OPEN ABOUT THAT
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
>> SORRY, I JUST GUESSED
>> OH, NICE.
GOOD JOB
>> HEY, I HAVE ANOTHER AWARD
FOR FIRST ASIAN MAN TO DO A CHER IMPRESSION ON NBC,
BUT IT
DOESN'T SAY WHO IT'S FOR
* IF I COULD TURN BACK TIME *
>> SIMU WINS
>> YES
>> CONGRATULATIONS
BUT JUST REMEMBER, SIMU.
WHATEVER FIRST THING YOU DO,
I'LL ALWAYS BE GAY
FIRST GAY
>>> ONCE AGAIN, SAWEETIE
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
>> "SNL," LET'S GO
*
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* MY HAIR MY MONE
COME BUNDL
I SPENT YOUR REN
ON MY FRONTAL *
* GIRLS SEE M
AND GET HUMBLE
COULD TAKE YOU
BUT I DON'T EVEN WANT TO *
* BIRKIN BA
CROCODILE DUNDEE
MINK ON MY BODY LIKE
I JUST WENT HUNTING *
* TELL PETA I'M
BEING ONE HUNNID
THAT ICY GIRL STIL
ROCK A FUR IN THE SUMMER *
* LEFT FASHION WEEK
HELLA CASUALTIES
I THINK I KNOW WHY
THEY MAD AT ME *
* I'M PRETT
I'M IN EVERY CIT
BUT WON'T HIT THE CLUB
UNLESS IT'S A BAG FOR ME *
* DADDY ANSWER ME
I NEED TO KNOW WHY
YOU'RE MAD AT ME
'CAUSE YOU BE COMPLAINING *
* YOU STAY IN YOUR FEELINGS
I'M STARTING TO THIN
YOU CAN'T HANDLE ME *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* GET LOVE IN THE BAY
LIKE I'M 4
BIG C LOVE T
SIP ON THE 40s *
* THIS ROLLIE UP ON M
COST FORTY
I'MA BE FINE IN MY FORTIES
OOH FAKE BOOTY GALORE *
* MAKE SURE IT CLAP
WHEN YOU SEE ME ON TOU
HE SWEATIN' ME LIKE A SPOR
I PLAY IN PRADA *
* WHENEVER I'M BORE
CONCEALER TAN SAND
I'MA GET THESE BAND-BAND
BET' NOT SMELL NO *
* WHEN YOU POP IT
ON A HANDSTAND
ALL OF MY -- SMELL GOO
DON'T WORRY 'BOUT US *
* WE GOOD
I AIN'T GON' LIE
YOU ACTIN' TOO SHY *
* COME POP THAT
LIKE A FROM THE HOOD *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
*
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
* TWERK THA
FOR A ICY CHAI
TWERK THAT
FOR A ICY CHAIN *
*
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
>> YES, HI
I THINK I MIGHT BE DEAD.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE DEAD, SIR?
>> YES
I'M AT A FRIENDSGIVING PARTY AND
I SMOKED SOME MARIJUANA.
AND I OD'D, AND NOW I'M DYING OR
I BELIEVE MYSELF TO BE DEAD.
SO CAN YOU SEND THE HOSPITAL TO
HERE, PLEASE
>> OKAY, SIR
YOU CANNOT OD ON MARIJUANA
>> BUT I DID BECAUSE WHEN I
WILL I BE LIKE THIS FOREVER,
MA'AM?
>> ALL RIGHT
ARTHUR, WHO DID YOU CALL
HELLO?
>> HELLO, MA'AM.
THIS IS 9-1-1 EMERGENCY
SERVICES
>> I AM SO SORRY, MISS
MYSELF AND SOME OTHER PROFESSORS
FROM CREMBLY COLLEGE ARE HAVING
A LITTLE GET TOGETHER AND WE
SMOKED A JOINT ONE OF MY GRAD
STUDENTS GAVE ME
>> YOU TELL HER I'M DEAD
>> WE'RE FINE.
GOOD NIGHT, HON.
>> GOOD NIGHT, MA'AM
[ PHONE RINING ]
9-1-1, WHAT'S YOUR EMERGENCY
>> YES, HELLO.
MY NAME IS ALAN, AND I AM DEAD
>> NOW SIR, ARE YOU AT THE SAME
FRIENDSGIVING GET TOGETHER WITH
THE GENTLEMAN WHO JUST CALLED?
>> OH YES, YES
YOU MUST COME HERE
BUT I'M NOT WHERE TIME IS.
WILL YOU STILL BE ABLE TO GET
HERE EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT WHERE
TIME IS?
>> NOW SIR, I PROMISE YOU YOU'RE
FINE AND YOU ARE WHERE TIME IS
HAVE YOU EVER SMOKED MARIJUANA
BEFORE
>> YES, ONCE AT A COUNTING CROWS
CONCERT OF 1992.
>> THE WEED IS MUCH STRONGER AND
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HAVING THIS
REACTION
>> OH, ARE YOU MAD AT ME
>> NO, SIR
IS THERE SOMEONE MORE MELLOW I
CAN SPEAK TO
>> OH YES, YES
MY WIFE HELEN IS RIGHT HERE.
>> OH.
YES?
>> IS THIS ALAN'S WIFE
>> WELL, I WAS
BUT I'M DEAD NOW
>> GREAT, OKAY
YOU, TOO
>> DOES EVERYONE KNOW YOU'RE
HIGH
DO PEOPLE KNOW
>> I DO.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS,
EVERYONE KNOWS
[ DIAL TONE
>> OLD PEOPLE GOT TO STOP
SMOKING WEED
[ PHONE RINING ]
HELLO, 9-1-1
WHAT'S YOUR EMERGENCY?
>> YES
WELL, COULD YOU PLEASE SEND THE
HOSPITAL TO HERE, PLEASE?
[ DIAL TONE
[ PHONE RINING ]
>> GROWN ADULTS TAKING UP MY
DAMN TIME.
>> HI, SWEETIE
>> LET ME GUESS, YOU'RE DEAD
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T KEEP TAKING
THESE CALLS FROM YOU ALL
THERE ARE REAL EMERGENCIES WE
NEED TO DEAL WITH.
>> WELL, I GOT ONE FOR YOU
I PUT A BOOK IN THE OVEN INSTEAD
OF A TURKEY, AND NOW MY
KITCHEN'S ON FIRE.
CLASSIC STONER MOVE.
>> THAT'S OUR SHOW FOR TONIGHT,
FOLKS.
THANK YOU TO SAWEETIE.
AND THANKS TO EVERYBODY
WATCHING
GOOD NIGHT