>>> HELLO, AND WELCOME BACK TO
THE OSCARS RED CARPET PRESHOW.
>> I'M THE MAN INSIDE YOUR HOTEL TV
WHO TELLS YOU WHAT THE MOVIES
ARE, MARIO LOPEZ.
>> AND I'M EITHER MARIA MENOUNOS
OR KIT HOOVER.
THEY HAVEN'T TOLD ME YET.
>> AND YOU'RE ABOUT TO WATCH THE
95th ANNUAL ACADEMY AWARDS
SPONSORED BY OZEMPIC.
>> "OZEMPIC". I GUESS EVERYONE IN HOLLYWOOD
HAS DIABETES.
>> AND WE'RE SO EXCITED TO HAVE
BEEN STANDING OUTSIDE THE DOLBY THEATE
FOR ALM 153 HOURS.
>> WE HAVE NOT SLEPT OR USED THE
BATHROOM.
OUR ONLY FOOD IS A HANDFUL OF
SARDINES THEY THROW AT US.
SEALS IN ZOO
>> BUT IT'S ALL WORTH IT TO ASK
ANGELA BASSETT IF SHE REALLY DID
THE THING.
>> OOPS. WE ALMOST FORGOT,
EVERY 30
SECONDS, WE HAVE TO DO A FEW
AWKWARD PAN-DOWNS TO WOMEN'S
FEET.
HERE WE GO.
>> EVERYONE NEEDED TO SEE THAT.
>> NOW LAST YEAR'S OSCARS HAD
THE SLAP, WHICH IS AWESOME --
I
MEAN BAD, SO BAD.
>> WE HATED ALL THE ATTENTION.
>> SO THIS YEAR, TO MAKE SURE
NOTHING CRAZY HAPPENS,
THE
ACADEMY HIRED A NEW HEAD OF SECURITY
NOTORIOUSLY CALM AND
SANE PERSON, MIKE TYSON.
>> THANK YOU.
MY GOODNESS.
OH, WOW.
THANK YOU.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
THAT'S SO NICE OF Y'ALL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I AM READY TO HANDLE THE
PROCEEDINGS JUDICIOUSLY AND EXPO
DISHSLY.
THE FOLLOWING THINGS WILL SET MF
CLAPPING, STATUES OF
PE THAT LAST MORE THAN TWO HOURS,
AND ALSO HEARING
THE PH, THE MAGIC OF MOVIES.
>> ARE THERE ANY NEW SECURITY
MEASURES IN PLACE?
>> THANK YOU FOR THAT QUESTION.
THIS YEAR, ALL THE NOMINEES HAVE
BEEN GIVEN TASERS.
ALL THE SEAT FLE HAVE BEEN GIVEN GUNS,
KIMMEL HAS
GIVEN A FLAME THROWER.
>> AND NOT THAT WE'RE HOPING FOR THIS,
BUT ARE YOU WORRIED WILL
SMITH IS PLANNING A SECOND
ATTACK?
>> YES.
WE ARE PLANNING THAT THREAT VERY
SERIOUSLY.
LUCKILY, WE WERE ABLE TO SLIP
ONE OF THOSE APPLE AIR TAGS INTO
WILL SMITH'S POCKET.
SO WE KNOW EXACTLY WHERE HE WILL BE AT ALL TIMES
UNLESS HE
CHANGES HIS PANTS.
STAY FROSTY, EVERYBODY.
>> UH-OH, I'M LEGIT SCARED.
>> AND NOW, OF COURSE, THE SHOW
HAS FACED A LOT OF COMPLAINTS
ABOUT A LACK OF DIVERSITY.
BUT REMEMBER, OSCAR TURNS 95
THIS YEAR.
>> SO IF YOU THINK ABOUT HOW
RACIST AND SEXIST YOUR GRANDPA WAS AT 95,
OSCAR'S LOOKING
PRETTY DARN GOOD.
>> SPEAKING OF LOOKING GOOD,
IT'S FIRST TIME NOMINEE FOR BEST
SUPPORTING ACTRESS, JAMIE LEE
CURTIS.
>> I MEAN, SERIOUSLY, HOW GREAT
IS THIS?
I SOLD YOGURT THAT MADE YOU POOP,
AND NOW I'M NOMINATED!
>> NOW, YOU HAVE BEEN
REFRESHINGLY DOWN TO EARTH THIS
WHOLE AWARDS SEASON.
WHO ARE YOU WEARING TONIGHT?
>> KIRKLAND BY COSTCO.
>> JAMIE, YOU'VE ALSO BEEN SO
VOCALLY SUPPORTIVE OF ALL YOUR
FELLOW NOMINEES.
>> WELL, BECAUSE THESE ACTRESSES
RULE!
CATE BLANCHETT, ARE YOU KIDDING
ME?
SHE IS SO -- AM I ALLOWED TO
CURSE?
>> NO.
>> SHE IS SO -- HOT.
AND TAR, OH, MY GOD,
TAR WAS ICONIC, VIVACIOUS,
CARN
QUEER, VAGUE,
CONFUSING, LONG,
PARTIALLY IN GERMAN,
AND IT WAS HANDS DOWN
THE FUNNIEST MOVIE OF THE YEAR.
AND CAN I SAY ONE MORE THING IN.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA.
>> WHAT ARIANA DeBOSE DID AT THE
BAFTAS WAS FUN.
IT WAS BY FAR THE BEST RAP
PERFORMANCE I'VE SEEN ALL YEAR.
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
>> WELL, GOOD LUCK, AND HAVE FUN
TONIGHT.
>> OH, NO.
I'M ON MY WAY HOME.
IT'S WAY PAST MOMMY'S BEDTIME.
>> OH, I JUST LOVE HER.
NOW, ONE GROUP THAT DOESN'T
TRADITIONALLY WATCH THE OSCARS
ARE DEGENERATE GAMBLERS,
AND
THAT'S WHY THIS YEAR, WE'RE
PARTNERING WITH DRAFTKINGS
TO OFFER
WHAT'S THE LATEST UPDATE,
FELLAS?
>> WELL, HERE ARE SOME OF THE
LATEST BETTING LINES.
THREE TO ONE ODDS THAT A YOUNG
ACTOR BRINGS OUT AN OLD ACTOR IN A WHEELCHAIR
AND REGRETS IT
IMMEDIATELY.
>> AND TWO TO ONE THAT SOMEONE
ALL
TEN TO ONE
IN THE END MEMORIAM IS STILL
ALIVE.
>> WE'RE ALSO SEEING A LOT OF
MOVEMENT IN THE WHO'S GOING TO
MAKE A SURPRISE APPEARANCE POLL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SOME OF THE FAVORITE LONG SHOT
PICK SOS FAR ARE
CHRIS ROCK,
JARED FROM SUBWAY,
ARMIE HAMMER,
THE JUDGES THAT OVERTURNED ROE V WADE,
GEORGE SANTOS PRETENDING
TO BE TOM CRUISE.
AND HARVEY WEINSTEIN INTRODUCES
KANYE WEST.
>> WOW.
A GIRL CAN DREAM.
BUT HOLD THAT THOUGHT BECAUSE
I'M TOLD WE HAVE THE STARS OF THE BANSHEES
COLIN FARRELLND
BRENDAN DEGREESON.
HOW DO YOU GUYS LIKE YOUR
CHANCES TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, WORDS FOR TROOPS IN
THE BAY.
GREEN
SAY
LONGER
CAA
>> WOW.
AND THEY HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
DRINKING YET.
>> AND THIS IS SO EXCITING.
I'M BEING TOLD WE HAVE MICHELLE
WILLIAMS.
>> CLOSE.
IT'S MICHELLE WILLIAMS' JEWISH
ACTING COACH FOR THE FABLEMANS.
>> HELLO.
IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE HERE
EVEN
THOUGH MY HAIR IS -- BUT, I'M
HERE.
>> SO WAS THE FABLEMAN'S YOUR
FIRST HOLLYWOOD PROJECT?
>> OH, SWEETIE, NO.
I WAS ALSO THAT JEWISH ACTING COACH
FOR MARVELOUS MISS MAISEL,
AND WEIRDLYOR AVATAR.
COMMUNITY
I BELIEVE WE HAVE A PHOTO.
>> AND HOW DID YOU THINK THAT
MICHELLE'S PERFORMANCE TURNED
OUT?
>> OH, SHE WAS AMAZING.
AND IF I CLOSE MY EYES AND EARS,
I THINK SHE IS JEWISH.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I HAVE
TO GO FIND MY ACTING COACH,
CHUCK SCHUMER.
>> WOW, I LOD GETTING THAT
INCITE.
>> AND FINALLY, THIS IS A SURPRISE,
BUT WE ARE JOINED BY
THE ONE AND ONLY TOM CRUISE.
>> HELLO.
HI.
IT'S TOM CRUISE HERE.
WONDERFUL TO BE HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GEORGE SANTOS.
>> NO, NO.
I'M DEFINITELY THOMAS Q. CRUISE.
STAR OF THIS YEAR'S BLOCK BUSTER
FILM "TOP GUN" 2, TOP BOTTOM.
>> GEORGE, YOU'RE NOT FOOLING
ANYONE.
>> YEAH.
EXCEPT I DID, AND NOW I'M IN
CONGRESS.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I HAVE
TOO BE EVERY EVERYWHERE ALL
AT ONCE.
>> OKAY.
HE'S A HOOT.
>> NOW, LET'S TAKE A QUICK
BREAK, AND WHEN WE RETURN,
WE'LL
BE TALKING WITH PINOCCHIO.
>> I'M GOING TO SCARE SO MANY
KIDS.
>> AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, JENNA
ORTEGA!
THANK
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
MY NAME IS JENNA ORTEGA.
I'M 20 YEARS OLD, WHICH MAKES ME
THE YOUNGEST HOST THIS SEASON.
I ACTUALLY HAVE BEEN ACTING SINCE I WAS SEVEN
WHEN MY MOM
PUT ME ON FACEBOOK.
TIKTOK
CRAZY
I WAS IN "WEDNESDAY ", "X" AND NOW
"SCREAM 6."
A LOT OF PEOPLE ASSUME I AM DARK
AND TWISTED BECAUSE OF THESE
ROLES I PLAY.
I'M NOT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
I THINK THERE'S JUST SOMETHING
ABOUT MY FACE WHEN PEOPLE SEE IT,  THEY'RE LIKE
LET'S THROW
BLOOD ON THAT.
BUT I WASN'T ALWAYS IN HORROR
FILMS.
MY FIRST ACTING ROLE WAS IN A
COLGATE TOOTH PASTE COMMERCIAL
WHEN I WAS NINE.
TAKE A LOOK
>> WANT TO CATCH THOSE LITTLE NASTIES,
YOU KNOW THOSE LITTLE
GERMS THAT HIDE IN YOUR MOUTH?
I'LL BE BACK TONIGHT, INVISIBLE
NASTIES.
>> I AM STILL THAT EXACT SAME
GIRL.
SAME ONE.
IT'S JUST THAT SCARY MUSIC AND
EDITING CAN MAKE ANYTHING SEEM
LIKE A HORROR FILM.
WATCH.
>> WANT TO HELP ME CATCH AN
INVISIBLE GERM?
I'LL BE BACK TONIGHT, INVISIBLE
NASTIES.
FALL 2023
>> I LOVE HORROR MOVIES, BUT
HONESTLY, I DON'T GET SCARED
VERY EASILY.
PART OF THE REASON I WANTED TO HOST SNL
IS I WANTED TO FACE MY
BIGGEST FEAR.
HAPPY EXTROVERTED PEOPLE ALWAYS
TRYING TO PERFORM.
EVERYONE HERE HAS BEEN SO KIND,
AND THIS WEEK HAS BEEN A DREAM
COME TRUE.
I'VE GOT A COUPLE OF FRIENDS TONIGHT,
INCLUDING ONE OF MY
COSTARS FROM "WEDNESDAY", FRED
ARMISON.
HI
>> DON'T LET ME DISTRACT YOU.
I'M JUST HERE TO WATCH
WITH
THESE PEOPLE THAT ARE BELOW ME.
>> DID YOU WANT TO COME UP AND
JOIN ME ON STAGE?
>> ME, GO UP THERE IN FRONT OF
THE CAMERAS?
I COULD NEVER.
>> I'M SORRY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
>> FINE, I WILL.
SO THIS IS WHAT IT FEELS LIKE TO
BE ON "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
>> YOU WERE ON THE SHOW FOR 11
SEASONS.
>> THAT'S SWEET.
THANK YOU.
>> SERIOUSLY, FRED, I AM SO
HONORED THAT YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE THE REASON I STARTED
WATCHING SNL ACTUALLY.
MY FAVORITE SKETCH OF ALL TIME
IS THE CALIFORNIANS.
>> THANKS, JENNA.
THAT'S SO NICE.
YOU KNOW, THE ORIGINAL IDEA CAME
TO ME BECAUSE I WAS GIVING
DIRECTIONS --
>> WE FIGURED IT WAS SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
THANK YOU, FRED.
LIKE I SAID, THIS FEELS LIKE A
DREAM.
WHEN I WAS A KID, I WASN'T OLD
ENOUGH TO WATCH SNL YET,
SO I
TOOK A TOUR OF THE SNL STUDIO
WITH MY PARENTS LIKE SIX YEARS AGO,
AND THEY SAID, MAN,
WOULDN'T IT BE AMAZING IF YOU
HOSTED SOME DAY,
AND IT SEEMED
IMPOSSIBLE THEN,
BUT NOW I'M
HERE TONIGHT, AND MY PARENTS ARE
IN THE AUDIENCE,
AND THEY GET TO
HEAR ME SAY WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOIG
HERE
STICK
">>> WELCOME EVERYBODY TO SCHOOL
VERSUS SCHOOL
WHERE TEACHERS
TEAM UP WITH THEIR STAR STUDENTS
TO WIN BIG BUCKS.
I'M YOUR HOST JAY McCORMICK.
AFTER
I WAS THE KEY WITNESS
IN A HARASSMENT TRIAL OF THIS SHOW'S
COVID REPRESENTATIVE
WHO SWABBED
MY ANUS IN LIEU OF MY NOSE
EVERY
DAY FOR FIVE MONTHS,
BUT THAT'S
ALL IN THE PAST NOW, SO LET'S
MEET OUR TEAMS.
FROM WEST GROVE HIGH IN NEW JERSEY,
TEACHER SHEILA CASHMAN
AND HER STUDENTS GABE AND MANNY.
I'M TOLD YOUR SCHOOL HAS ONE OF
THE BEST SCIENCE DEPARTMENTS IN
THE COUNTRY.
>> YES, AND YOU CAN SAY IT'S A
PLUS.
>> YEAH, THAT'S CUTE.
NOW LET'S MEET THEIR OPPONENTS
FROM PROFESSOR ZANDER'S ACADEMY
FOR EXTRAORDINARY CHILDREN,
PROFESSOR CHANDLISS ZANDER AND
HIS STUDENTS ZENA AND KNOCKOUT.
IT SAYS HERE THAT YOUR SCHOOL IS
A 100 ROOM VICTORIAN MANSION
LOCATED WITHIN A 10,000 ACRE
PRIVATE FOREST.
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
WE NEED AMPLE SPACE IN WHICH TO
TRAIN OUR STUDENTS
TO HARNESS
THEIR INCREDIBLE GIFTS.
>> IF MY GIFTS ARE SO
INCREDIBLE, THEN WHY WON'T YOU
LET ME USE THEM?
>> BECAUSE YOU CANNOT YET
CONTROL THEM, CHILD!
>> OKEYDOKEY.
LET'S JUST GET TO THE GAME.
ARE WE FEELING CONFIDENT TEAMS.
>> HECK YEAH.
PROFESSOR ZANDER'S ACADEMY,
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
>> WE COULD ENSLAVE YOU!
>> NO!
>> WELL, THAT'S FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST QUESTION GETS CONTROL OF
THE BOARD.
NAME FOR A RANDOM MODIFICATION
OF DNA FROM PARENT TO OFFSPRING.
ZENA.
>> MUTATION.
>> CORRECT.
>> OH, YES, MUTATION IS A TOPIC
IN WHICH WE ARE WELL-VERSED.
>> IT'S WHY THEY HATE US.
>> ZENA.
>> THEY THINK WE'RE FREAKS!
>> ENOUGH, CHILD!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, ZENA, YOU HAVE A CHANCE
FOR EXTRA CREDIT.
THE SUBJECT IS ENGLISH LIT.
HOW'S YOUR SCHOOL'S ENGLISH
DEPARTMENT?
>> OUR CURRICULUM FOCUSES MORE
ON HARNESSING OUR STUDENTS'
ABILITIES.
>> YOU ALWAYS DOUBT ME.
ASK YOUR QUESTION.
>> OKAY THEN.
TO BE OR NOT TO BE IS SPOKEN BY
WHICH SHAKESPEARIAN PROTAGONIST?
>> TOBY.
>> WRONG.
>> I FAILED!
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE ALL
THINKING?
THE FREAK FAILED?
>> NO, I PROMISE YOU, SWEETIE.
NO ONE IS THINKING THAT.
>> OH, YOU LIE, YOU PATHETIC
HUMAN!
>> ZENA, NO, YOU COULD KILL HER!
>> HEY, ALL RIGHT.
HEY!
NOW, I JUST GOT BLASTED AND HIT
IN THE FACE
WITH WHAT I CAN ONLY
DESCRIBE AS ELECTRIC WIND.
BUT SINCE NO POINTS WERE AWARDED,
CONTROL NOW GOES OVER
TO WEST GROVE HIGH
WHO ARE YET
TO GET ON THE BOARD.
ALL RIGHT, WEST GROVE, HERE'S
YOUR QUESTION.
NAME THE TRIANGLE WHICH HAS
THREE SIDES EQUAL OF LENGTH.
>> I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH OUR TEACHER.
>> OKAY.
NO POINTS THERE.
CONTROL BACK TO PROVFESSOR
ZANDER'S SCHOO I GUESS.
SIZE
>> LET ME INTO YOUR MIND.
>> I CAN FIGURE IT OUT ON MY
OWN!
>> I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU, ZENA!
>> GET OUT OF MY HEAD!
LET
>> STOP FIGHTING!
>> GET ON OUT OF HERE.
WE WERE LOOKING FOR EQUAL
LATERAL TRIANGLE.
>> I SHOULDN'T BE HERE!
I SHOULD BE ON THE TEAM USING MY
POWERS.
>> YOU ARE NOT READY, CHILD!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE JUST GOING TO TAKE A BREAK,
LET THINGS CALM DOWN AND SEE IF
WE CAN GET THAT LADY'S BRAIN
BACK ONLINE.
THIS IS JAY McCORMICK REMINDING
YOU THAT COVID SWABS
GO IN THE
NOSE AND NOT THE KEISTER.
FOOL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU.
FOOL ME EVERY DAY FOR FIVE
MONTHS, SHAME ON ME.
KEEP IT RIGHT HERE.
>>> I'VE JUST BEEN DOING A LOT
OF PRESS AND THESE DIFFERENT JOBS,
AND DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I'M REALLY, REALLY GRATEFUL.
I'M STARTING TO FEEL A LITTLE
BURNT OUT.
>> THAT SUCKS.
MARK, ARE YOU READY WITH THE
PLAY LIST?
>> AND I GOT THE SLURPIES!
>> DUDE, NICE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> WE'RE GOING ON A BEAUTIFUL
CROSS-COUNTRY AMERICAN ROAD
TRIP.
>> JUST US AND THE OPEN ROAD.
GOING TO BE AWESOME.
>> WAIT, CAN I COME?
♪ HIT THE OPEN ROAD AND CATCH A RIDE,
ARMS GETTING TAN ON THE
SUNNY SIDE ♪
♪ I'M ON THE WHEEL,
- I'M ON NAV,
- I'M ON SNACKS ♪
♪ AND JENNA'S JOB IS TO JUST
RELAX
ON A ROAD TRIP,
A GREAT
AMERICAN ROAD TRIP ♪
♪ WE'RE GOING ON A ROAD TRIP,
GOING ON A ROAD TRIP
♪ ROLL DOWN THE WINDOWS TO CLEAR
YOUR --
>> WE MISSED THE EXIT.
>> RECALCULATE YOUR ROUTE.
>> JUST LOOK OUT FOR THE NEXT
ONE.
NEED A LITTLE HEADS UP.
>> OKAY.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE HARD DOING
MUSIC AND NAV.
>> PRICE OF BEING SHOTGUN.
>> YEAH.
NO, IT'S FINE.
LET'S TRY TO FOCUS ON NAV, ALL
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I'LL FOCUS ON THE NAV.
>> YEAH, THANKS.
YOU'RE NOT IN CHARGE OF ME
♪ NOD TO CONVERTIBLES WHEN THEY PASS
MOON A TRUCK OR PUT YOUR
CHEEKS ON THE GLASS ♪
WATCH
♪ SEE A SIGN THAT SAYS WE'RE
GOING TO HELL
ON THE ROAD TRIP,
A GREAT AMERICAN ROAD TRIP ♪
>> I'M SORRY.
CAN WE COOL IT WITH THE SLURPY
FOR A SECOND?
IT'S JUST RIGHT IN MY EAR.
>> SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAPPY TO BUY EVERYONE A SLURPY,
BUT YOU'RE SUCKING ON
THE -- THERE'S NONE LEFT.
OKAY.
CAN YOU SCOOT OVER, YOUR LEG
HAIRS ARE SCRATCHING ME.
>> FINE, I'LL MOVE MY LEG.
>> DID YOU JUST VENMO REQUEST ME
FOR THE SLURPY?
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY, SO.
♪ WE'RE GOING ON A ROAD TRIP --
>> RECALCULATING ROUTE.
>> DID WE MISS THE GOD DAMN
COMMIT AGAIN?
GETTING
>> WHO COULD YOU POSSIBLY BE
TEXTING THAT'S NOT IN THIS CAR.
>> IT WAS MY MOM, MAN.
MY DAD HAD A STROKE.
SORRY
SORRY I'M NOT FOCUSSING ON THE
NAV!
I DON'T KNOW WHY I SAID THAT.
HE DID NOT HAVE A STROKE.
>> LIAR!
>> COME ON, MAN.
>> EVERYBODY, WE'RE HAVING QUIET
TIME.
READ A BOOK OR SOMETHING.
♪ FINALLY TIME TO CHILL,
I CAN DO WHAT I WANNA,
DIVE INTO THE
THE NEW MICHELLE OBAMA.
>> I'M GOING TO PUKE!
- ALREADY
- EXIT
PULL OVER RIGHT NOW!
SHUT
>> 0.3 MILES!
>> MARK, THAT MEANS NOTHING TO
ME.
>> YOU TOLD ME TO FOCUS ON THE
NAV.
HAPPENING
>> WE'RE GOING HOME!
♪ LATE AT NIGHT AND I FEEL SO FREE,
EVERYONE ASLEEP EXCEPT FOR
ME, ♪
♪ BIG BRIGHT MOON HANGING IN THE SKY,
NAV IN MY LAP --
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> NOTHING.
GO BACK TO SLEEP EVERYONE.
THANKS.
WILL YOU TURN THE AC ON?
>> YEAH.
YOU HOT OR COLD?
>> BOTH.
>> I SAW WHAT YOU DID.
♪ ON A ROAD TRIP ♪
>>> WE'RE SO EXCITED TO BE DOING
THIS REMAKE OF "THE PARENT
TRAP."
WE FOUND SOME PLACES TO UPDATE
THE ORIGINAL, BUT THE SCENE IN
THE CABIN WHERE HALLIE AND ANNIE
REALIZE THEY'RE TWINS IS SUCH A
CLASSIC.
WAS. NTED TO LEAVE IT THE WAY IT
>> THIS IS SO SPECIAL.
I'M REALLY GLAD TO BE HERE.
>> OBVIOUSLY SINCE YOU'RE
PRAYING BOTH TWINS, TODAY YOU'LL
BE HALLIE IN THE SCENES, AND
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE ONE OF OUR
ND REAOU,
OK
>> YOU KNOW, YOU CAN JUST CALL
ME RAY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN.
I THINK I GET THE GIST.
>> OKAY.
LET'S START WITH TH SEQUENCE
WHERE HALLIE AND ANNIE ARE
HAVING A LITTLE DISAGREEMENT
OVER WHETHER IT'S BEDTIME OR
NOT.
YOU CAN HEAD TO YOUR COTS AND
WE'LL GET STARTED ALL RIGHT?
GREAT AND ACTION.
>> OFF.
>> ON.
>> TURN THEM OFF!
>> YOU ARE SO ANNOYING.
>> I'M STARTING TO THINK YOU'RE
A REAL BITCH!
>> OKAY.
CUT.
UMM, SIR, I DON'T THINK THE
SCRIPT SAID BITCH.
>> YEAH, YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DID A LITTLE OFF THE CUFF
THING LIKE THEY DO ON "CURB."
YOU GUYS WATCH THAT?
>> MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE WANTS TO
READ THE LINES LIKE THE ONES
THAT ARE IN THE SCRIPT.
>> WE'RE NEVER GOING TO SEE HIM
IN THE MOVIE, SO IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHAT HE SAYS.
>> SHOULD I GO TO THE TOILET AT
SOME POINT AND SHE GETS MAD.
THAT COULD BE FUN LIKE HER TWIN
IS ALWAYS ON THE TOILET.
>> ARE YOU ASKING THAT BECAUSE
YOU NEED TO GO TO THE BATHROOM
NOW?
>> WELL, I THINK MY CHARACTER
MIGHT, BUT YOU'RE THE DIRECTOR.
>> LET'S MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
DAY.
IT STORMED OUTSIDE, SO YOUR
BELONGINGS GOT WET, AND NOW
YOU'RE TALKING BY THE WINDOW
GETTING TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
AND ACTION.
>> OH, NO.
>> ARE ANY OF YOUR PICTURES
RUINED?
>> ONLY THE BAUFL SHAWN MENDEZ.
>> WOW, HE IS HOT.
YOU KNOW WHO I LIKE?
LISA RENA.
I WOULD LET HER WRECK ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO HERE.
>> LET'S MOVE ON TO THE OREO
SCENE.
YOU'RE BONDING, REALIZE YOU HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON, AND GO.
>> WANT TO EAT SOME OREOS?
MAY SOUND WEIRD, BUT I EAT THEM
WITH PEANUT BUTTER.
>> WELL, F ME.
SO DO I!
>> WOW, NO WAY.
I WONDER WHAT ELSE WE HAVE IN
COMMON.
>> YOU LIKE SCHLITZ BEER?
>> WHAT?
NO.
ANYWAY, HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 56.
OH, FOR THIS, 11.
MY BIRTHDAY'S IN OCTOBER.
>> ME TOO.
>> THIS IS TRIPPING ME OUT.
LET'S SEE IF WE HAVE A PICTURE
OF OUR PARENTS THAT WAS RIPPED
IN HALF TO SEE IF WE'RE TWIN
SFWLS NOT THERE YET.
JUST JUMP AHEAD TO WHERE
HALLIE'S PACING, PUTTING IT ALL
TOGETHER.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
I ONLY HAVE A FATHER, AND YOU
ONLY HAVE A MOTHER.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> YOU'VE NEVER SEEN YOUR DAD,
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN MY MOM.
>> SO YOU THINK WE'RE TWINS OR
NOT YET?
>> YOU HAVE ONE OLD PICTURE OF
YOUR MOM, AND I HAVE ONE OLD
PICTURE OF MY DAD.
>> YEAH, LIKE IN THAT LINDSEY
LOHAN MOVIE ABOUT THE TWIN.
>> AT LEAST YOURS IS A WHOLE
PICTURE.
>> A WHOLE PICTURE?
YOU'RE 11.
DON'T LOOK AT THOSE.
>> MY PICTURE IS PATHETIC AND
RIPPED DOWN THE MIDDLE.
>> NOW BOTH RUN AND GET YOUR
HALVES OF THE PICTURE.
>> HERE IT IS.
THE PICTURE OF MY DAD.
>> OKAY.
I GOT MINE.
>> ON THE COUNT OF THREE, WE'LL
SHOW THEM TO EACH OTHER, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> WHOA.
LESLIE MAN AND ED HELMS.
IS THIS FOR STREAMING.
>> SO IF YOUR MOM IS MY MOM AND
MY DAD IS YOUR BAD AND WE'RE
BOTH BORN ON OCTOBER 11th, THEN
YOU AND I ARE LIKE SISTERS.
>> SISTERS?
HALLIE, WE'RE FREAKING TWINS.
>> ANNIE.
>> OH, MY GOD, WOW, I'M LIKE
CRYING NOW.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
>> SO THEY JUST SPLIT US UP?
WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT TO US?
WE'VE GOT TO KILL EM.
>> THERE'S TWO OF US.
>> IF WE WORK TOGETHER, WE CAN
KILL THEM.
I'M KIDDING.
I LOVE YOU.
>> AND CUT.
WOW, THAT WAS IT.
THANK YOU BOTH FOR THOSE
PERFORMANCES.
I'M BLOWN AWAY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A HIT, AND
I'LL SEE YOU BOTH AT THE
PREMIER.
AT NINE, IT'S THREE STRAIGHT
DAYS OF "RIDICULOUSNESS."
BUT FIRST, AN ALL NEW
RIDICULOUSNESS.
>>> WHAT IS UP, WHAT IS UP?
WELCOME TO "RIDILOUSNESS."
I'M ROB DYEK, AND YOU WOULDN'T
KNOW IT FROM MY CLOTHES, BUT I'M
ALMOST 50, Y'ALL.
JOINING ME AS ALWAYS, STEELO
BRIM AND CHANEL WEST COAST.
>> WHAT UP, ROB?
>> I'M ALREADY LAUGHING.
>> AND TODAY'S SPECIAL GUEST,
YOU KNOW HER FROM TIKTOK, IT'S
LEE LEE TWO TIMES.
>> YO, WHAT UP, WHAT UP?
>> YO, CONGRATS ON ALL YOUR
SUCCESS AND FOR LOOKING FINE AS
HELL.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
JUST TURNED 17 LAST WEEK!
>> 17!
OOPSY!
I MEANT FINE AS HELL AS A
FRIEND.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S WATCH SOME VIDS, KIDS.
THIS IS FALLING OFF.
FIRST, PEEP THESE FOOLS PARTYING
ON A BOAT UP IN HERE.
OH, OOPSY.
>> WHITE GIRL OVERBOARD.
>> THAT LOOKED LIKE IT HURT, YO.
>> SEE THAT'S WHY MY ASS DON'T
MESS WITH BOATS.
>> YEAH, I FEEL YOU.
I WAS ON THIS FAMILY VACAY ONE
TIME.
MY COUSIN HAILEY WAS DOING THAT
WHITE GIRL SELFIE POSE AND WE
HIT A WAVE, AND BAM!
SHE FELL RIGHT OFF THAT BOAT AND
FELL UNDER, BUT THE PROPELLER
HIT HER AND HER HEAD FELL OFF.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT IS HORRIFIC.
>> AND THE WORST PART WAS
BECAUSE LIKE ALL THE BLOOD, A
HUNTING FINDING NEMO FISH CAME
AROUND AND STARTED EATING AT HER
HEAD.
>> I'M SO SORRY, GIRL.
>> YEAH, YEAH, ME TOO.
LET'S PEEP ANOTHER VID.
LET TRY TO KEEP OUR ANECDOTES
MORE FUN, LESS TRAGIC AND
UPSETTING.
CHECK THIS OUT.
YO, THIS CAT, DUDE, WHAT, UH-OH,
CUP HEAD.
UH-OH, YO THAT CAT WAS TRIPPING.
CHANEL LIKED THAT ONE RIGHT
THERE.
>> YO, I CAN'T, I CAN'T, YO.
>> YO, CATS ARE A TRIP.
>> YEAH, MAN, THEY CRAZY.
>> LIKE GROWING UP, OUR CAT
SADIE WAS ALWAYS GETTING
PREGNANT.
>> SO SADIE A HO.
>> FOR REAL.
SHE WAS GIVING BIRTH ONE TIME
AND SIX KITTENS COMING OUT.
>> ALL OF THEM LOOKING DIFFERENT
THAN THEY DADDY.
SADIE, WHO YOU SMASHING?
>> THEY CAME OUT FUSED INTO ONE
BIG FURRY BALL OF CAT PARTS.
EARS, TAILS, ALL STICKING OUT.
IT WAS NOT FIRE.
>> HA-HA-HA.
CHANEL, YOU GOT A CAT.
YOU GOT ANY FUNNY CAT STORIES,
GIRL?
>> WAS THE CAT ALIVE?
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
BUT LIKE IT DIDN'T HAVE A MOUTH,
SO IT WAS SCREAMING FROM THE
INSIDE LIKE MM!
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KEEP MAKING
THAT NOISE, LEE LEE, WE GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOING TO PLAY WHAT'S GOING TO
GO DOWN.
HERE'S THE FIRST FRAME OF OUR
NEXT VID.
UH-OH, WE GOT A DUDE IN THE
LAUNDRY BASKET AT THE TOP OF
SOME STAIRS.
STEELO, WHAT'S GOING TO GO DOWN?
>> I THINK THAT DUDE'S FLYING
OUT OF THAT THING ON THE FIRST
STAIR, MAN.
WHAT YOU THINK, CHANEL?
>> SAME.
SO HOW LONG DID THAT CAT HAVE TO
LIVE?
>> YO, NO MORE CAT BALL.
OKAY?
THE CAT BALL'S WEIRD AND SAT.
IT'S NOT THE VIBE OF THE SHOW,
OKAY?
>> YEAH, I GOT TO AGREE ON THAT,
MAN.
LET KILL THE CAT BALL.
>> ACTUALLY, THE MOM CAT KILLED
THE CAT BALL.
>> YO, NO MORE CAT BALL, YO.
THAT CAT BALL IS DONE.
PLEASE.
OKAY, LEE LEE, WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS GOING TO GO DOWN IN THIS VID?
>> I THINK THIS WHITE BOY GOING
TO MAKE IT ALL THE WAY DOWN TO
THE BOTTOM OF THE STAIRS AND
JUMP OUT AND START WILDING.
>> THEN HE'S GOING TO FALL ON
HIS ASS?
>> NO.
HE'S GOING TO GET A TEXT THAT
SAYS HIS PARENTS WERE MURDERED.
>> NOPE, NOT THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A QUICK
BREAK, RESET THE VIBE, AND WE'LL
BE BACK WITH MORE
RIDICULOUSNESS.
>> I GOT A PICTURE OF THE CAT
BALL IF ANYBODY WANTS TO SEE.
>> I MEAN, I'LL TAKE A LOOK.
VARSITY VALLEY
>>> ZACK.
>> HEY.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU GUYS
LATER, ALL RIGHT?
HEY, CASEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I KNOW YOU AND THE GUYS
USUALLY HANG OUT AT WAFFLE HOUSE
AFTER YOUR GAMES,
SO I FIGURED
YOU WOULD BE HERE.
I HAVE SOMETHING I NEED TO TELL
YOU.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO STATE NEXT
YEAR.
>> HEY!
THESE WAFFLES ARE TOO SMALL!
>> WE HAD A PLAN.
WE WERE BOTH GOING GO TO STATE
THEN MOVE BACK TO TOWN AFTER AND
GET MARRIED.
THAT'S WHAT WE WANTED.
>> NO.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED, ZACK.
ALL RIGHT?
I WANT MORE.
MORE THAN STATE, MORE THAN THIS
TOWN.
>> MORE THAN ME.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
>> NOTHING.
I APPLIED TO THIS MUSIC PROGRAM
IN NEW YORK CITY.
I GOT IN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHOSE DOG IS THIS?
>> THAT'S MY DOG.
>> AREN'T YOU GOING SAY
ANYTHING?
>> GET THIS DOG OUT OF HERE!
>> I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO SAY, CASEY?
CONGRATS?
I'M LOSING THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
>> I'M JUST THE LOVE OF YOUR
LIFE SO FAR.
COUNTER
YOU'LL FIND OTHER GIRLS.
>> THEY WON'T BE YOU.
I JUST --
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S
OVER.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SINCE 8th
GRADE.
>> I KNOW.
AND THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
I DON'T KNOW WHO I AM WITHOUT
YOU.
>> I OWE IT TO MYSELF TO FIND
THAT OUT.
TRUST ME.
THIS WASN'T AN EASY DECISION.
>> YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE,
CASEY.
>> WE GOT A 724 IN PROGRESS.
>> MAYBE I AM MAKING A MISTAKE,
BUT ISN'T THAT WHAT GROWING UP
IS?
IT'S ABOUT TAKING THE BIG
CHANCES, MAKING THE BIG
MISTAKES.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S HOW WE BECOME
WHO WE'RE MEANT TO BE.
>> DO IT!
>> I'LL DO IT.
>> IF YOU SAY SO.
>> YOU KNOW WHERE I'M PUTTING
THESE?
RIGHT DOWN MY PANTS, BABY.
HURT
>> I KNOW THIS IS THE RIGHT
DECISION.
WHO KNOWS,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE A FEW
YEARS FROM NOW, WE'LL FIND EACH
OTHER AGAIN.
IF IT'S MEANT TO BE, IT'LL BE.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE MY FIRST LOVE.
NOTHING CAN CHANGE THAT.
>> I GUESS.
>> COME HERE.
>> BIG MISTAKE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> EVERYTHING.
>> I GUESS THANK YOU TOO.
DO YOU NEED A RIDE HOME?
>> NO.
MY DAD DROVE ME.
>> YOU READY TO GO, BABY GIRL?
>> YEAH, DAD.
>> FREE BIRD GOT TO FLY, SON.
♪ HEARTBEAT IS COMIN' ♪
♪ IN SO STRONG
OH IF YOU
DON'T STOP
I'M GONNA NEED ♪
♪ A SECOND ONE
OH THERE'S SOMETHIN'
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
SAY TO YOU BABY ♪
♪ HOLD THAT THOUGHT
YEAH THERE'S SOMETHIN'
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
SAY TO YOU BABY ♪
♪ BUT I JUST CAN'T DO IT
WHAT A CALL MOVING IN
I FEEL LIKE I CAN
LOOSEN MY LIPS ♪
♪ COME ON SO STRONG
I CAN SUMMARIZE IT FOR YOU
AH
IT'S SIMPLE ♪
♪ AND IT GOES LIKE THIS
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
SHE'S GOT A BROADSHEET
SHE'S READING
DOWN THE LIST ♪
♪ OF THE GOING WRONGS
OH YEAH YEAH YEAH
M GETTIN' NO SLEEP
BECAUSE I'M ♪
♪ TOSSIN' AND TURNIN'
ALL NIGHT LONG YEAH
OH THERE'S SOMEWHERE I'VE
SOMEWHERE I'VE ♪
♪ BEEN MEANING TO
MEANING TO
TAKE THE CONVERSATION
HOLD THAT THOUGHT ♪
♪ OH THERE'S SOMEWHERE I'VE
SOMEWHERE VE
BEEN MEANING TO
MEANING TO ♪
♪ TAKE THE CONVERSATION
BUT I JUST CAN'T DO IT
YOU SHOW ME YOUR
YOU SHOW ME YOUR ♪
♪ BLACK GIRL THING
BLACK GIRL THING
PRETENDING THAT I KN
WHAT IT IS ♪
♪ I WASN'T LISTENING
I APOLOGIZE
AND YOU MEET MY EYES
YEAH IT'S SIMPLE ♪
♪ AND IT GOES LIKE THIS
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I-I
AND YEAH I GOT IT
I FOUND IT
I'VE JUST GOTTA KEEP IT ♪
♪ DON'T HEY YOU MUPPET
IT'S NOT THAT DEEP
BUT I'VE BEEN
COUNTING MY BLESSINGS ♪
♪ THINKING THIS THROUGH
IT'S LIKE ONE TWO YEAH
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
YEAH
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU
I-I-I-I
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ I-I-I-I
♪
>> Announcer: IT'S "WEEKEND
UPDATE" WITH COLIN JOST AND
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THIS WEEKEND, BITTER RIVALS WHO
HAVE BEEN DESPERATELY PANNING
FOR VOTES
AND TRYING TO FORCE
THEIR POLITICS ON AMERICA
WILL
FINALLY FACE OFF IN PERSON.
I'M OF COURSE TALKING ABOUT
TOMORROW'S OSCARS.
THEY REAPOLOGETICED A REQUEST
FROM UKRAINIAN PRESIDENT
VOLODYMYR ZELENSKYY
TO MAKE AN
APPEARANCE DURING THE OSCARS,
BUT THEY PROMISE VOLODYMYR
ZELENSKYY WILL BE
HOW JOHN
TRAVOLTA ANNOUNCES VIOLA DAVIS.
ORGANIZERS SAID THEY CHANGED THE
COLOR OF THE ARRIVAL CARPET FROM
RED TO CHAMPAGNE
SO THE MOOD
WOULD BE MORE MELLOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
SWITCHING FROM RED TO CHAMPAGNE
USUALLY TURNS ME INTO A FULL ON
BITCH.
>>> PRESIDENT BIDEN PROPOSED HIS
BUDGET THAT WOULD HELP FUND MEDICARE
WITH A 25% TAX ON
MILLIONAIRES.
HA, TAKE THAT, RIHANNA.
PRESIDENT BIDEN'S PROPOSED
BUDGET INCLUDED $400 MILLION TO
CHINESE DISINFORMATION
TARGET THE NUMBER ONE SOURCE OF
CHINESE DISINFORMATION, FORTUNE
COOKIES.
>>> TUCKER CARLSON SEEN HERE
LAUGHING AT A DOG LOCKED IN A HOT CAR
RELEASED SECURITY
FOOTAGE FROM THE JANUARY 6
ATTACKS WITH THE VIOLENCE EDITED OUT
AND SAID IT PROVES IT WAS A
PEACEFUL GATHERING.
WHICH IS LIKE EDITING ALL THE
SEX OUT OF A PORN VIDEO
AND
SAYING IT'S A SHORT FILM ABOUT
BEING A STEP MOM.
>>> NEW DOCUMENTS FROM THE
DOMINION LAWSUIT REVEALED TEXTS
FROM TUCKER CARLSON
IN WHICH HE
SAYS HE HATES DONALD TRUMP
PASSIONATELY
AND CAN'T WAIT
UNTIL HE'S ABLE TO IGNORE HIM.
THAT MUST SUCK TO GO ON TV
SMILE
AND MAKE FRIENDS WITH SOME PSYCHOTIC
BIGGOT JUST BECAUSE IT'S GOOD
FOR THE SHOW.
ANYWAY, BACK TO YOU, COLIN.
>> I DON'T GET IT.
RUE PAUL HARSHLY CRITICIZED
LAWMAKERS WHO BANNED DRAG SHOWS,
POLITICIANS
AND LET ME JUST SAY,
HALELU
I GOT TO
SERVE REALNESS ON THIS ONE.
THESE DUSTY BREEDERS ARE RESTING ON UGLY,
AND I AM GAGGING ON IT.
I'M SORRY, GUYS, BEFORE THE SHOW,
I SWITCHED FROM RED TO
CHAMPAGNE.
>>> OH, BOY.
PRESIDENT BIDEN SAID THAT HE
SUPPORTS A BILL
THAT WOULD ALLOW
THE GOVERNMENT TO BAN TIKTOK.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE BIDEN THINKS
TIKTOK IS A GANG MEMBER FROM HIS
OLD NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> AFTER WALGREENS ANNOUNCED
THEY WILL STOP SELLING ABORTION PILLS IN 21 STATES,
CVS HAS
REMAINED SILENT.
WHILE OVER AT RITE AID, YOU CAN
JUST GRAB A PILL
FROM THE TAKE
ABORTION LEAVE ABORTION TRAY.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT THE
ORGANIZERS OF KING CHARLES' CORONATION
HAVE OFFICIALLY
INVITED MEGHAN MARKLE --
AND
THIS IS NICE -- AT A STARTING
SALARY OF $19 AN HOUR.
THAT SEEMS VERY GENEROUS, GUYS.
>>> THIS WEEK, TENNESSEE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR RANDY
McNALLY WAS CAUGHT USING HIS
VERIFIED INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT TO
ENGAGE WITH PROVOCATIVE PHOTOS
OF A GAY YOUNG MAN.
HERE TO COMMENT THE GOVERNOR
McNALLY.
>> SORRY I'M LATE.
I SPENT ALL DAY PRINTING OUT MAP
QUEST DIRECTIONS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU NOTICED, BUT
I'M NOT GOOD AT THE INTERNET.
>> YOU'RE A MARRIED MAN WHO
SUPPORTS TENNESSEE'S ANTI-DRAG
LAWS.
CAN YOU KU EXPLAIN WHY YOU
COMMENTED ON A THIRST TRAP, YOU
CAN TURN A RAINY DAY INTO
RAINBOWS AND SUNSHINE?
I DIDN'T THINK PEOPLE WOULD FIND
OUT BECAUSE I USED A SCREEN
NAME.
>> WHAT IS THE SCREEN NAME?
>> LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR McNALLY.
>> YOU SEE HOW THIS COULD BE A
PROBLEM.
ALSO I WANT TO POINT OUT YOU
COMMENTED THREE HEARTS AND THREE
FIRE EMOJIS ON THIS NAKED PHOTO
OF THE SAME YOUNG GAY MAN.
>> WELL, COLIN, I DON'T
DISCRIMINATE.
I COMMENT ON PHOTOS OF ALL
ORIENTATIONS.
ORIENTATIONS LIKE FROM THE SIDE,
FROM THE FRONT, FROM THE BACK.
THERE DOES NOT HAVE TO BE A
BUTT, BUT IT HELPS.
WHATEVER THE PHOTO, IT'S MY JOB
TO ENCOURAGE MY CONSTITUENTS.
>> I THINK IT'S JUST SOME
CONFUSION ABOUT YOUR BELIEFS.
>> COLIN, I STAND BY MY
TRADITIONAL VALUES.
I BELIEVE A WOMAN SHOULD BE IN
THE HOME, AND A MAN SHOULD BE
143 POUNDS AND DANCING TO DUA
LIPA.
>> OKAY.
YOU -- OKAY.
YES.
YOU'RE VERY CUTE, BUT YOU ARE --
YOU ARE CLAIMING THESE
INTERACTIONS ARE INNOCENT, BUT
IT DOES NOT LOOK GOOD.
>> I'M JUST LOOKING OUT FOR THE
LITTLE GUY, JOE AVERAGE, EVERY
TOM, DICK, AND HAIRLESS.
>> I THINK SO THE PEOPLE OF
TENNESSEE FEEL MISLED.
>> IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I'M JUST LOOKING.
LOOKING AT PICTURES ON ZILLOW
DOESN'T MAKE ME A HOMEOWNER,
ALTHOUGH I HAVE DONE A FEW 3D
TOURS.
>> RANDY.
>> RANDY BY NAME, RANDY BY
NATURE.
>> WHY ARE YOU INTERACTING WITH
THESE YOUNG MEN?
>> BECAUSE I'M TALKING TO VOTERS
OR PEOPLE WHO COULD VOTE IN THE
FUTURE.
I'M A PROUD CONSERVATIVE.
I RESPECT POLICE OFFICERS, FIRE
FIGHTERS, ANY MAN WHO PUTS HIS
BODY ONLINE FOR OTHERS.
>> DO YOU MEAN ON THE LINE FOR
OTHERS?
>> WHAT DID I SAY?
BY THE WAY, ANY CHANCE YOU CAN
PRINT ME OUT ANOTHER MAP QUEST?
I'M TRYING TO GET TO FLAMING
SADDLES.
>> RAN DID I, FOLKS ARE CALLING
YOU A HYPOCRITE FOR ENFORCING
ANTILBGTQ LAWS WHILE SEEMING TO
ENJOY QUEER CONTENT.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
I'M A HYPOCRITE?
THAT I WAS FLIRTING WITH A
20-YEAR-OLD DANCING AROUND IN
HIS FINE WASHABLES?
THAT I MADE IT LEGAL TO HAVE
GUNS IN LIBRARIES BUT NOT DRAG
QUEENS?
THAT I PUBLICLY HATE THINGS THAT
I SECRETLY LIKE?
BOTH REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS
ARE TELLING ME TO GET OFF
INSTAGRAM, AND GUESS THAT, I
WILL BECAUSE I FORGOT MY
PASSWORD.
>> RANDY McNALLY, EVERYONE.
>> MEET ME AT FLAMING SADDLES.
>> ANY TIME.
>>> A DEEP SEA DIVER HAS
ANNOUNCED PLANS TO SET A NEW
WORLD RECORD BY LIVING UNDER
WATER FOR 100 DAYS.
I FEEL LIKE THE RECORD IS LONGER
THAN THAT, SAID THE PEOPLE OF
NEW ORLEANS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THOUGHT THAT
WOULD MAKE YOU LAUGH.
>>> A MAN IN FLORIDA SAID HE WAS
SURPRISED WHEN HE HEARD A KNOCK
AT THE DOOR AND IT TURNED OUT TO
BE AN ALLIGATOR.
EVEN MORE SURPRISING, IT WAS
DOING THE THING FROM "LOVE
ACTUALLY".
>>> OFFICIALS IN BERLIN
ANNOUNCED THAT WOMEN WILL NOW BE
ALLOWED TO GO TOPLESS AT THE
CITY'S POOLS, BUT OFFICIALS ALSO
SAID TO BE AWARE IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE THE ONES YOU WANT.
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW REPORT,
BY 2035, MORE THAN HALF OF THE
WORLD'S POPULATION WILL BE JUST
HOW I LIKE THEM.
>>> A PHOTO HAS GONE VIRAL OF A
98-YEAR-OLD WOMAN IN KENTUCKY
MEETING HER FIRST GREAT GREAT
GREAT GRAND CHILD.
WOW, I WISH I HAD GOTTEN TO MEET
MY GREAT GREAT GREAT GRANDMOTHER
SO I COULD HAVE TOLD HER, DON'T
GET ON THAT BOAT!
I EVEN TRIED ACTING DURING THAT
ONE, MAN.
>>> THERE IS A TREND ON TIKTOK
OF PEOPLE EATING ORANGES IN
SHOWERS CLAIMING THAT IT REDUCES
STRESS AND ANXIETY.
BUT IF YOU'RE COMFORTABLE
FILMING YOURSELF EATING IN THE
SHOWER, I WOULD ARGUE YOU DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH ANXIETY.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT LONG
DISTANCE RUNNING DOES NOT CAUSE
WEAR AND TEAR ON MARATHONERS'
KNEES, BUT IT DOES SAND THEIR
NIPPLES CLEAN OFF.
>>> WEDNESDAY WAS INTERNATIONAL
WOMEN'S DAY -- I SAID WAS.
NEXT JOKE.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS --
A NEW STUDY FINDS SOME NEW YORK
CITY RATS CARRY THE VIRUS THAT
CAUSES COVID, WHICH IS WHY I
ALWAYS ORDER MINE WELL DONE.
>>> WELL, GUYS, WE -- WE ONLY
HAVE ABOUT A MINUTE LEFT OF THE
END OF UPDATE.
HERE TO FILL IT WITH SOME RANDOM
IMPRESSIONS IS JAMES AUSTIN
JOHNSON.
>> WOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JAMES, WHAT IS YOUR FIRST
IMPRESSION?
>> THIS IS ADAM DRIVER AS KYLA
FROM STAR WARS ON THE SHOW
GIRLS.
DO YOU KNOW HOW DIFFICULT IT IS
TO BE ON THE DARK SIDE OF THE
FORCE?
NO, YOU DON'T BECAUSE YOU'RE A
CHILD!
>> OKAY.
GREAT, GREAT.
ALL RIGHT.
WAIT.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
>> BATMAN AND HE'S READING
WHERE'S WALDO.
>> BATMAN READING WHERE'S WAL.
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
I THINK WE'RE ALREADY RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
OKAY.
>> THIS NEXT IMPRESSION WOULD
MAKE A GREAT SKETCH ON THE SHOW.
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER IT.
>> SURE.
>> THIS IS JAY-Z AND HE'S
DOWNSTAIRS.
>> OKAY.
>> BUSEY, BUSEY, BEYONCE.
>> HOLD ON.
HOW WOULD YOU PLAY JAY-Z?
>> HE WOULD BE DOWNSTAIRS.
YOU DON'T SEE HIM BECAUSE HE'S
DOWNSTAIRS.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU PUT MUCH
THOUGHT INTO THIS.
>> I HAVE A STOCK PILE OF
USELESS TWO SECOND IMPRESSIONS
THAT I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH, SO I KIND OF THOUGHT, WHY
NOT DO THEM ON UPDATE WHERE IT
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
BUT I HAVE TO GET THESE
IMPRESSIONS OUT.
IT'S MY BRAND.
BARTENDERS WON'T EVEN LOOK AT ME
AT THE AFTERPARTY IF I DON'T DO
MY TRUMP VOICE.
WE HAVE BEEN WAITING A VERY LONG
TIME FOR THAT NEGRONI.
THIS IS MUCH TOO LONG.
IT'S A THREE INGREDIENT GREEN.
IT'S VERY, VERY SWEET.
I LOVE MY NEGRONI.
>> WE HAVE TIME FOR ONE MORE
IMPRESSION, BUT IT'S GOT TO BE
QUICK.
>> I'VE GOT THE PERFECT ONE.
THIS IS BOB DYLAN'S CELL PHONE
ON VIBRATE.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
>> JAMES AUSTIN JOHNSON,
EVERYONE.
FOR "WEEK
>>> FATHER, CAN YOU SAVE HER?
CAN YOU SAVE MY DAUGHTER?
>> WITHOUT FATHER MURPHY, I
CAN'T PERFORM AN EXORCISM ALONE.
>> YOU WILL ROT IN HELL.
>> HONEY, HEAR MY VOICE.
I KNOW YOU'RE STILL IN THERE,
CLAIRE.
>> DID SOMEONE JUST KNOCK ON OUR
DOOR?
>> HELLO?
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
WHAT IS ALL THE RUCCUS?
>> OH, FATHER, THIS IS OUR
UPSTAIRS NEIGHBOR, MRS. SHAW.
>> AND I SHAWED HAVE BEEN ASLEEP
45 MINUTES AGO, BUT I SUPPOSE
YOU ALL DECIDE TODAY THROW A
PARTY ON A TUESDAY.
>> THIS ISN'T A PARTY.
>> IT'S OUR DAUGHTER.
SHE'S BEEN POSSESSED.
>> WE'RE WAITING FOR FATHER
MURPHY.
>> Y'ALL DON'T HAVE TO WAIT.
I'LL DO IT.
>> DO WHAT?
>> THE EXORCISM.
I'M GETTING MY SLEEP TONIGHT.
>> AHH!
SEE I CAN DO IT TOO, OKAY?
YOU DON'T SCARE ME, SWEETIE.
>> YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
YOU'RE IN OVER YOUR HEAD.
>> I'LL LET YOU KNOW I HAVE BEEN
A CROSSING GUARD AT NASSAU AND
EDGE MONT FOR SIX YEARS.
THAT'S SIX LANES.
EVERY DAY, I'M THE ONLY THING
STOPPING 5th GRADERS FROM
GETTING SENT TO HELL BY A U.P.S.
TRUCK.
HELLO?
OKAY, YOU NEED TO GET OUT.
USE YOUR WORDS.
>> SUCK MY BUTT!
>> NO, MA'AM, I DON'T DO ALL
THAT.
I TOSSED SALAD ONCE, AND I WAS
LIKE, THIS AIN'T FOR ME.
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD WAIT FOR THE
PRIEST, MRS. SHAW.
>> OH, NO.
I NEED TO GET MY EIGHT HOURS.
UH-OH, WHERE'S SHE GOING?
>> YOU'RE GOING TO HELL, YOU
STUPID WHORE.
>> STUPID WHAT NOW?
OH, HONEY, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DO BETTER THAN THAT.
YESTERDAY, A THIRD GRADER CALLED
ME A USED UP SKANK.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
>> YOU'RE AN UGLY -- UMM --
>> UMM WHAT?
LOOK AT YOU STUTTERING.
SIT YOUR ASS DOWN BEFORE I TURN
ON THE CEILING FAN.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> IS IT WORKING?
>> YEAH, IT IS.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> LET ME OUT.
>> SHE'S EXPELLING THE DEMON.
QUICK, WE'LL NEED A NEW VESSEL.
>> I GOT YOU A VESSEL ALL RIGHT.
FRANK!
GET DOWN HERE, FRANK!
>> WOMAN, WHAT YOU WANT?
I'M TRYING TO SLEEP.
>> YOU CAN'T SLEEP IF YOU'RE
TALKING.
AND LITTLE GIRL, YOUR ASS BETTER
NOT BE LEVITATING BACK THERE.
>> SORRY, MRS. SHAW.
>> THANK YOU, BABY.
>> WAKING MY ASS UP AT 9:00 P.M.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
>> WE DOING AN EXORCISM, FRANK.
>> WELL, I SHAWED HAVE BEEN
ASLEEP 47 MINUTES AGO.
>> WE KNOW, BABY.
NOW YOU GOT TO BE A VESSEL FOR
THIS HERE DEMON.
>> I DON'T WANT DO THAT.
>> IF YOU DON'T DO IT, I'LL
CANCEL OUR SEX DATE NEXT WEEK.
>> OKAY.
FOUND MY WEAK SPOT.
LET ME GET SITUATED FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON NOW, DEMON.
DO YOUR WORST.
>> OH, MY GOD.
MOM, DAD, WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
WHY ARE THE SHAWS IN OUR HOUSE?
SHOULDN'T THEY BE ASLEEP?
>> WE CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD.
Y'ALL SLEEP TIGHT NOW.
COME ON, FRANK.
FRANK?
>> I DON'T LIKE DIZZY!
♪ I'VE BEEN SUICIDAL ♪
♪ YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOR WEEKS
IF I'M UNDECIDED
WILL YOU DECIDE FOR ME
BABY I'LL DO ANYTHING ♪
♪ THAT YOU WANNA
I'LL TRY ANYTHING
THAT YOU WANNA
I'LL TRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE
I WANNA GET IT RIGHT
THIS TIME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS
ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE
♪ GETTING SUICIDAL
IT'S HONESTLY NOT FOR ME
I'M GETTIN' ON MY NERVES
BY GETTIN' ON MY KNEES ♪
♪ GETTING CUCKE
I DON'T NEED IT
THE PLACE I WANT TO BE
IS SOMEWHERE IN YOUR HEART ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE GUARANTEED
'CAUSE BABY
I'LL DO ANYTHING
THAT YOU WANNA ♪
♪ I'LL TRY ANYTHING
THAT YOU WANNA
I'LL FIND MYSELF
IN THE MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE BABY
I WANT EVERYTHING
THAT YOU WANNA
AND I'VE TRIED TO ♪
♪ JUST BE ME
LIKE A THOUSAND TIMES
BUT YOU'RE ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE ♪
♪ I WANNAET IT RIGHT
THIS TIME
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS
ON MY MIND ♪
♪ ALWAYS ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE
OH I'VE TRIED TO FIND
ANOTHER NAME ♪
♪ A THOUSAND TIMES
BUT THE ONLY ONE THAT RHYMES
ALWAYS ON MY MIND
IS OH CAROLINE ♪
♪ JUST GIVE ME
ONE MORE CHANCE TONIGHT
I DON'T WANT TO WASTE
MY LIFE WITHOUT YOU BABY ♪
♪ NO I DON'T WANT TO
WASTE MY LIFE WITHOUT YOU
BABY
OH CAROLINE ♪
♪ GET IT RIGHT THIS TIME
ALWAYS ON MY MIND
I WANNA GET IT RIGHT
BUT YOU'RE ON MY MIND ♪
♪ OH CAROLINE
I WANNA GET IT RIGHT
THIS TIME
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS ♪
♪ ON MY MIND
ALWAYS ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE
OH CAROLINE ♪
>> SING IT, JAMIE.
♪ I WANNA GET IT RIGHT
THIS TIME
ALWAYS ON MY MIND
OH CAROLINE ♪
♪
SINCE BREAKING OFF FROM DONALDS
DONALDS DOMINGUEZ TO FORM
DONALDS AND DOMINGUEZ, WE HAVE
NOT LANDED A SINGLE NEW CLIENT.
YOU KNOW WHY THAT IS?
>> IT'S BECAUSE DONALD DONALDS
DOMINGUEZ HAD A PHONE NUMBER TO
REMEMBER, AND EVERYONE IN TOWN
KNOWS THEIR FAMOUS PHONE NUMBER
JINGLE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT.
>> OUR NUMBER IS 1-672-555-0136.
>> WHAT WE NEED IS TO TURN THAT
NUMBER INTO A SUPPER CATCHY
JINGLE.
>> THERE'S NO WAY TO CREATE A
CATCHY JINGLE WITH A NUMBER LIKE
THAT.
>> LAST TUESDAY, MITCHELL AND I
WERE AT LUCCIANO'S.
>> AND YES, I WAS DRINKING --
NO, I WAS GETTING TANKED.
>> MITCHELL GOT TANKED AND
LUCCIANO'S.
BUT THEN THIS BAND GOT UP ON THE
STAGE AND SANG THE MOST IF YOU
THINK HOOKS I HAD EVER HEARD.
COME ON IN, GUY.
>> HEY, THERE.
>> HELLO, LAWYERS.
>> WE ARE SOUL BOOTH.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THIS IS
SOUL BOOTH, AND THEY'RE HERE TO
SAVE US.
>> WORKED OUT A FEW DEMOS FOR
Y'ALL.
>> WE HEARD YOU NEEDED A POP IF
YOU THINK HOOK THAT WILL STICK
ON THE MIND LIKE GRAPEVINES.
>> MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
DO YOU REMEMBER THIS ONE?
>> OH, I DO.
>> THEY AIN'T READY.
>> HERE WE GO.
♪ ONE -- SIX-SEVEN -- TWO ♪
♪ THEN THREE STRAIGHT FIVES, THE
NEXT NUMBER IS O!
♪ ONE -- THREE -- AND SIX ♪
♪ WHO YOU GONNA CALL, WHO YOU
GONNA CALL, TELL THEM ♪
♪ DONALDS AND DOMINGUEZ ♪
>> GUYS, I'M SORRY.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO
WORK FOR US.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> JUST DOESN'T SOUND LIKE WHAT
WE HEARD AT LUCCIANO'S.
>> OH, YOU WANT THAT LUCCIANO
SOUND?
>> YES.
THIS TRACK SHOULD MAKE ME FEEL
LIKE I'M TANKED UP AT LOOCH,
UNDERSTOOD?
>> LOUD AND CLEAR.
CRYSTAL.
>> AND THE NUMBERS SHOULD BE
CLOSER TOGETHER.
>> YEAH.
I THINK THE NUMBERS SHOULD BE
MUCH CLOSER TOGETHER.
>> UH-HUH.
SO MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
DO YOU REMEMBER THIS ONE?
THEY AIN'T READY.
COME ON.
HERE WE GO.
♪ ONE THOUSAND-SIX
HUNDRED SEVENTY
TWO-FIVE MILLION-FIVE
HUNDRED-FIFTY OUSAND-ONE
HUNDRED THIRTY SIX ♪
♪ DONALDS AND DOMINGUEZ ♪
>> GUYS, GUYS, COME ON, THAT'S
TOTALLY WRONG.
YOU CALL THAT A LOOCHED UP
TRACK?
>> I SHOULD FEEL FIVE DEEP
POSTED UP AT LOOCH RIGHT ABOUT
NOW.
>> WHAT'S TO HARD ABOUT THAT.
>> WHAT'S TO HARD ABOUT WRITING
A JINGLE THAT FEELED LIKE I'M
GETTING DAKED DOWN IN THE BACK
OF LOOCH?
THEY'RE ABOUT TO KOOT ME OFF,
BUT THEN THAT BARTENDER IN THE
BACK ACTING LIKE BIALIK.
>> THE NUMBERS SHOULD BE
PRESENTED LIKE A PHONE NUMBER.
>> OR JUST ANYWHERE NEAR THAT
WOULD BE GREAT.
>> I THINK WE MIGHT HAVE JUST
THE THING.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> LET'S TAKE A TRIP.
I WANT TO TAKE YOU SOMEWHERE
WHERE THERE IS NO RACE, NO
RELIGION, A LITTLE PLACE WE CALL
HOME.
BUT YOU MAY KNOW AS LUCCIANO'S.
HERE WE GO.
♪ ONE THOUSAND-SIX
HUNDRED SEVENTY
TWO-FIVE MILLION-FIVE
HUNDRED-FIFTY THOUSAND-ONE
HUNDRED THIRTY SIX ♪
>> ONE MORE TIME.
THAT FEELS SO GOOD.
♪ ONE THOUSAND-SIX
HUNDRED SEVENTY
TWO-FIVE MIL-FIVE
HUNDRED-FIFTY THOUSAND-ONE
NDTHIRIX ♪
SO, WHAT DO YOINK?
IS LUCHI?LL, DID THEY DO IT?
>> NOT ONLY CAN I NOW PERFECT
RE THE PHONE NUMBER OF
LA OFFICE, BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY, I FEEL ABSOLUTELY
ASS-OUT DAKED DOWN AND LOOCHED
UP.
MY ONLY QUESTION IS -- HOW MUCH?
>> $10,000.
>> LESS.
>> 40 EACH.
>> DEAL.
>>
>>> I WANT TO THANK THE 1975.
FRED ARMISON, THE WONDERFUL, SO,
SO FUNNY CAST, JERRY, DONNA,
KATIE, MY TEAM OF COURSE.
THE CREW, I FEEL LIKE THIS HAS
JUST BEEN SUCH A WONDERFUL
EXPERIENCE, AND I'M REALLY,
REALLY GRATEFUL.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR WATCHING AND
LETTING US BE RIDICULOUS AND
LETTING ME DO THIS FOR THE FIRST
TIME.