>>> YOU'RE WATCHING FOX AND
FRIENDS.
GOOD MORNING
>> WELCOME TO FOX AND FRIENDS.
I'M STEVE DUCEY
HERE WITH BRIAN
KILLMEADE AND AMY.
>> HI, EVERYBODY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING AND WAKANDA
FOREVER.
>> I DON'T THINK WE'RE ALLOWED
TO SAY THAT.
>> EVERYBODY CHILL.
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE WEEK FOR THE
GOP.
THE DEMS ARE RETAINING CONTROL
OF THE SENATE,
SO WHAT THE HECK
HAPPENED TO THAT RED WAVE THAT
PEOPLE WERE TALKING ABOUT?
>> YEAH.
WHO WAS PROMISING THAT?
BECAUSE COULDN'T HAVE BEEN US
EVERY DAY.
>> WELL, THANKFULLY THERE'S NO
WAY TO CHECK,
BUT IT DEFINITELY DIDN'T HAPPEN,
AND ACCORDING TO
EVERYBODY, ONLY ONE MAN WAS TO
BLAME.
LOOK AT THESE HEADLINES.
TRUMPTY DUMPTY.
FIRE
>> AND LOOK AT THIS UP ED.
MR. DeSANTIS, WILL YOU BE MY NEW
DADDY?
>> NOW, WHO WROTE THAT?
>> ERIC TRUMP.
>> SEEMS LIKE EVERYBODY IS
TURNING ON TRUMP.
>> AND PER A COMPANY-WIDE EMAIL
WE GOT THIS MORNING, HE'S DEAD
TO US.
>> NEARLY EVERY CANDIDATE,
TRUMP-BACK LOST THIS WEEK,
EXCEPT FOR ONE WHO'S STILL
HANGING ON BY A THREAD,
AND
SHE'S HERE WITH US TODAY.
PLEASE WELCOME KARI LAKE.
>> HELLO THERE.
HI.
GREETINGS FROM ARIZONA
WHERE THE AVERAGE AGE AND TEMPERATURE IS
95.
>> HI, KARI.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE
DURING
WHAT MUST BE A VERY STRESSFUL
TIME FOR YOUR CAMPAIGN.
>> HEY.
MY CAMPAIGN ISN'T DEAD YET
EVEN
THOUGH ANY CAMERA FILTER MAKES
IT LOOK LIKE I'M IN HEAVEN.
>> THIS SEEMS LIKE THIS IS A
RACE YOU WOULD EASILY WIN,
REAL
YOU AND YOUR OPPONENT ARE
CURRENTLY NECK AND NECK.
>> THAT IS BECAUSE THE MARICOPA
COUNTY OFFICIALS ARE INCOMPETENT,
AND IT'S MY BELIEF
THE ELECTION IS RIGGED AND THE
RESULTS SHOULD BE THROWN OUT.
>> SOUNDS LIKE SOME NEW NUMBERS
ARE COMING IN WHICH HAS YOU
TAKING A NARROW LEAD OVER
KATIETY HOBBS.
>> WHICH IS WHY I'VE ALWAYS SAID
TRUST THE SYSTEM, TRUST THE
VOTE.
>> ANOTHER SYSTEM JUST CAME IN,
AND YOU ARE LOSING AGAIN.
>> BECAUSE OUR SYSTEM IS BROKEN.
>> YOU'RE BACK IN THE LEAD.
>> THANKFULLY, IT'S NOW FIXED.
I'M 100% CONFIDENT I'M GOING TO
WIN THIS ELECTION,
AND I WON'T
STOP FIGHTING UNTIL EVERY VOTE
IS COUNTED
AND SOME VOTES ARE
TAKEN AWAY.
BECAUSE WHO DO AARIZONAENS WANT
LEADING THEM?
KATIE HOBBS WHO'S HIDING IN A
BASEMENT
OR ME,  KARI LAKE WHO
LIVES RIGHT HERE IN THIS
BEAUTIFUL POOL OF VASELINE
AND IS OUT THERE EVERY DAY AT CVS
ASKING BLACK CUSTOMERS IF THEY
WORK HERE.
>> WELL, WE ARE ROOTING FOR YOU,
KARI.
WE KNOW THE VOTES WILL GO YOUR
WAY.
>> WELL, IF THEY DON'T, I'LL
BURN ARIZONA TO THE GROUND.
>> SHE WAS NICE.
>> I HOPE THE TRUMP EFFECT DON'T
MESS WITH HER CAMPAIGN.
>> YOU DON'T THINK HE STILL
WATCHES OUR SHOW.
>> WELL, HE'S AT HIS DAUGHTER'S
WEDDING THIS WEEKEND,
SO AT
LEAST WE KNOW HE WON'T CALL IN.
>> HELLO.
IT'S YOUR FAVORITE PRESIDENT.
>> NEW PHONE.
WHO DIS?
>> HE'S JUST KIDDING.
HI, DONALD.
CONGRATULATIONS ON TIFFANY'S
WEDDING.
>> WHO?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S OKAY.
THEY'RE JUST DOING THE VOWS.
>> GREAT.
WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT YOU.
THERE WAS THAT NEW YORK POST
HEADLINE THAT CALLED YOU TRUMPTY DUMPTY
AND SAID YOU HAD
A GREAT FALL.
>> WELL, I AGREE.
I HAD A GREAT FALL AND A GREAT
SUMMER AS WELL.
MANY SAY I WILL HAVE A GREAT
WINTER AS WELL.
HAVING A GREAT FALL.
THE LEAVES ARE TURNING RED.
IT'S A RED WAVE IN TERMS OF TREE
AND WITH REGARD TO LEAF.
>> WELL, WE HEARD THAT YOU'RE
BLAMING BOTH SEAN HANNITY AND
MELANIA.
FOR ADVISING
>> IT'S TRUE.
LET ME TELL YOU, IT'S VERY HARD
BEING IN A FIGHT
WERE YOUR SOUL
MATE AND ALSO MELANIA.
NOW ALL ANYBODY WANTS TO TALK
ABOUT IS RON DeSanctimonious
I KNOW. I'M SURPRISED I KNOW THAT WORD,
TOO.
BUT RON HAD IT SO EASY.
>> YOU SAID DeSANTIS HAS THE
ADVANTAGE OF SUNSHINE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
EVERYONE GOES TO FLORIDA FOR THE
SUNSHINE.
I MADE RON DeSANTIS.
HE WAS GOING TO LOSE UNTIL I
SENT FBI AGENTS TO GO FIX HIS
ELECTION.
>> YOU ADMITTED TO WHAT?
>> BUT HE'S UNGRATEFUL AND HE'S
TRYING TO STEAL MY SUNSHINE JUST
LIKE LYNN.
THEY WERE A ONE-HIT WONDER.
GOT TO GO SEE.
AND THESE ELECTION RESULTS ARE
MAKING US GO, HOW BIZARRE.
HOW BIZARRE.
WE'RE ALL HEARING THAT ALL THE
TIME, RIGHT?
HOW BIZARRE.
>> DON'T YOU NEED TO LIKE WALK
YOUR DAUGHTER DOWN THE AISLE?
>> MISSED IT.
ANYWAY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU SEE
>> MR. PRESIDENT, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO TELL YOU THIS, BUT WE'VE
MOVED ON.
WE CAN'T HAVE YOU ON THE SHOW
ANYMORE.
>> WHAT?
WHAT DID I DO?
WAS IT THE INSURRECTION?
>> NO.
>> THE IMPEACHMENTS?
>> BLACKMAILING UKRAINE?
>> NO.
>> CHARLOTTESVILLE?
- WALL?
- NO.
>> THE MURDER?
KIDDING.
IT WAS BECAUSE YOU LOST.
WE DIDN'T SEE A FUTURE WITH YOU,
BUT WE CAN STILL BE FRIENDS.
BYE
>> WAIT, WAIT.
I HAVE A BIG ANNOUNCEMENT
NOVEMBER 15th.
DON'T PUSH ME OFF.
I HAVE A BIG ANNOUNCEMENT, AND
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
I'M RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT AGAIN.
>> OH, MY.
>> THAT WAS AWKWARD.
BUT WE'RE FINALLY FREE.
CHANGE IS ON THE HORIZON, AND I
HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
WE WON'T
BE HEARING FROM HIM AGAIN.
AND HE'S CALLING MY PHONE.
>> AND MINE.
>> MINE TOO.
>> WHOA.
KARI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> YOU THINK IF I LOSE, I'M JUST
GOING TO GO AWAY?
NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
WE'LL BE BACK FOR MORE KARI AND
FRIENDS.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, DAVE
CHAPPELLE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
BUT BEFORE I START TONIGHT, I
JUST WANTED TO READ
A BRIEF
STATEMENT THAT I PREPARED.
I HAVE STIGMATISM IN ALL ITS FORMS,
AND I STAND WITH MY
FRIENDS IN THE JEWISH COMMUNITY.
AND THAT, KANYE,
IS HOW YOU BUY YOURSELF SOME TIME.
I GOT TO TELL YOU GUYS,
I PROBABLY BEEN DOING THIS 35
YEARS NOW.
AND EARLY IN MY CAREER, I
LEARNED THAT THERE WERE TWO
WORDS IN THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE
THAT YOU SHOULD NEVER SAY
TOGETHER IN SEQUENCE,
AND THOSE WORDS
ARE "THE" AND "JEWS."
I'VE NEVER HEARD NO ONE DO GOOD
AFTER THEY SAID THAT.
Kanye's gotten into some scrapes before.
NORMALLY WHEN HE'S IN TROUBLE, I
PULL UP IMMEDIATELY.
BUT THIS TIME, I WAS LIKE, YOU
KNOW WHAT?
LET ME SEE WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN FIRST.
SEE
I CAN'T REMEMBER HOW IT STARTED.
VAGUELY I REMEMBER IT STARTED
WITH A TWEET, STRANGE TWEET.
IT WAS LIKE, I'M FEELING A
LITTLE SLEEPY.
I'M GOING TO GET ME SOME REST,
BUT WHEN I WAKE UP,
I'M GOING TO
GO DEFCON THREE ON THE JEWS.
AND THEN HE JUST WENT TO BED.
I WAS UP ALL NIGHT WORRIED.
WHAT IS HE TRYING TO DO TO THE
JEWS?
I GREW UP AROUND JEWISH PEOPLE.
I HAVE A LOT OF JEWISH FRIENDS,
SO I'M NOT FREAKED OUT BY YOUR
CULTURE.
I KNOW A LITTLE BIT ABOUT IT
HANGING AROUND.
LET'S HANG OUT AFTER SCHOOL
TOMORROW.
WE CAN'T GO OUT.
IT'S SHA-NA-NA TOMORROW.
WHAT?
WHAT IS SHA-NA-NA?
QUESTIONS
WHY DO SO MANY OF YOUR PEOPLE
DRESSILY R.E.M. DMC?
WOKE UP FROM A TINY NAP AND WENT
TO WORK.
A YEAR AGO, I'VE SEEN HIM ON A
PODCAST CALLED DRINK CHAMPS.
GREAT SHOW, AND IT WAS AN
AMAZING APPEARANCE.
Noreaga
RAPPERS THAT I LOVE WERE THERE
AND THEY ALL HAD THEIR GOLD
CHAINS AND STUFF ON.
KANYE SAID, ONLY MILLIONAIRES
WEAR CHAINS.
THEY SAID WHAT?
HE SAID, I'M A BILLIONAIRE.
BILLIONAIRES DON'T WEAR THEIR
MONEY ON THEIR BODY.
I TUCKED MY CHAIN, AND I SAID,
OH, SNAP.
GOOD APPEARANCE.
FUN AND FUNNY.
WHEN HE WOKE UP, HE WENT ON
DRINK CHAMPS AGAIN.
THIS TIME, HE WAS MAD ABOUT
SOMETHING.
HE SAID, I CAN SAY ANTI-SEMITIC THINGS,
AND ADIDAS CAN'T DROP ME.
NOW WHAT?
THEY DROPPED THAT NIGGER
IMMEDIATELY.
IRONICALLY, ADIDAS WAS FOUNDED BY NAZIS,
AND THEY WERE
OFFENDED.
PASS THE TEACHER.
IT'S A BIG DEAL.
HE BROKE SHOW BUSINESS RULES.
IS THIS A RULE?
YOU KNOW, THE RULES OF
DECEPTION.
IF THEY'RE BLACK, THEN IT'S A
GANG.
IF THEY'RE TINY, IT'S A MOB.
IF THEY'RE JEWISH, IT'S A
COINCIDENCE
AND YOU SHOULD NEVER
SPEAK ABOUT IT.
KANYE GOT IN SO MUCH TROUBLE,
KYRIE GOT IN TROUBLE.
KYRIE IRVING POSTED A LINK TO A
MOVIE HE HAD SEEN ON AMAZON.
NO CAPTION
APPARENTLY IT HAD SOME
ANTI-SEMITIC JOKES OR SOMETHING.
IT WAS SOME WEIRD TITLE LIKE
FROM HERO TO NEGRO OR SOMETHING.
THE NBA TOLD HIM TO APOLOGIZE,
AND HE WAS SLOW TO APOLOGIZE.
SO THE LIST OF DEMANDS GOT
LONGER AND LONGER.
AND THIS IS WHERE I DRAW THE
LINE.
I KNOW THE JEWISH PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN THROUGH TERRIBLE THINGS ALL OVER THE WORLD,
BUT YOU CAN'T
BLAME THAT ON BLACK AMERICANS.
JUST CAN'T
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THANKS THE ONE PERSON.
I'M SAYING PUNISHMENT WOULD BE
JUST TO POST A LINK TO SHINLER'S LIST
AND Y'ALL WRITE YOUR OWN
CAPTIONS.
KYRIE IRVING'S BLACK ASS WAS
NOWHERE NEAR THE HOLOCAUST.
IN FACT, HE'S NOT EVEN CERTAIN
IT EXISTS.
I SAW ONE NEWS WOMAN SCREAMING
ABOUT KANYE.
SHE SAID, MENTAL HEALTH IS NO
EXCUSE FOR THAT TYPE OF
LANGUAGE.
YES, IT IS, BITCH.
IF YOU MENTALLY ILL
LISTEN.
OKAY.
I DON'T THINK KANYE IS CRAZY AT
ALL.
I THINK HE'S POSSIBLY NOT WELL.
I'VE BEEN TO HOLLYWOOD.
I DON'T WANT Y'ALL TO GET MAD AT
ME.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
I HAVE BEEN TO HOLLYWOOD.
THIS IS WHAT I SAW.
IT'S A LOT OF JEWS.
LIKE A LOT.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
There's a lot of Black people in Ferguson, Missouri.
It doesn't mean we run the place.
I CAN SEE IF YOU HAD SOME KIND
OF ISSUE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
MIGHT GO OUT TO HOLLYWOOD AND
START CONNECTING SOME KIND OF LINES,
AND YOU CAN MAYBE ADOPT
THE ILLUSION THAT JEWS RUN SHOW
BUSINESS.
NOT A CRAZY THING TO THINK.
BUT IT'S A CRAZY THING TO SAY
OUT LOUD
in a climate like this
NOW THE MIDTERMS ARE OVER
AND IT'S CRAZY CLIMATE.
AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I FEEL
LIKE THIS MIDTERM IS LIKE ALL OF
HUMANITY DEPENDS ON IT.
And it's an ominous sign.
THE MOST OMINOUS SIGN I BELIEVE
WOULD BE HERSCHEL WALKER,
WHO I
DON'T WANT TO SPEAK BAD OF
BECAUSE HE'S BLACK.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT, HE'S
OBSERVABLY STUPID.
EVEN WHEN HE'S NOT TALKING, HIS
MOUTH BE OPEN A LITTLE BIT
LIKE --
HE'S THE KIND OF GUY THAT LOOKS
LIKE HE THINKS BEFORE HE MAKES A
MOVE ON TIC TAC TOE.
WATCHING THE NEWS NOW, THEY'RE
DECLARING THE END OF THE TRUMP
ERA.
I CAN SEE HOW IN NEW YORK YOU
BELIEVE IT'S THE END OF HIS ERA.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU, I LIVE
IN OHIO AMONGST THE POOR WHITES.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY TRUMP
WAS SO POPULAR.
I GET IT.
I HEAR HIM EVERY DAY.
HE'S VERY LOVED.
THE REASON WHY IS BECAUSE PEOPLE
IN OHIO HAVE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY
LIKE HIM.
HE'S WHAT I CALL AN HONEST LIAR.
I'M NOT JOKING.
HE IS AN HONEST LIAR.
THAT FIRST DEBATE, I'D NEVER
SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
I'D NEVER SEEN A WHITE MALE
BILLIONAIRE
SCREAMING AT THE TOP
OF HIS LUNGS,
THIS WHOLE SYSTEM
IS RIGGED, HE SAID.
AND ACROSS THE STAGE WAS A WHITE
WOMAN, HILLARY CLINTON AND BARACK OBAMA
sitting there looking at him like
NO, IT'S
NOT.
I SAID, WAIT A MINUTE, BRO.
IT'S WHAT HE SAID,
AND THE
MODERATOR SAID, WELL,
IF IN FACT
THE SYSTEM IS RIGGED AS YOU SUGGEST,
WHAT WOULD BE YOUR
EVIDENCE?
REMEMBER WHAT HE SAID, BRO?
HE SAID, I KNOW THE SYSTEM IS RIGGED
BECAUSE I USE IT.
I SAID, GOD DAMN!
THEN PULLS OUT AN ILLUMINATI
MEMBERSHIP CARD
chopped a line of cocaine up in it
NO ONE'S EVER HEARD ANYONE SAY
ANYTHING SO TRUE.
and then Hillary Clinton tried to punch him in the taxes.
She said, 'This man doesn't pay his taxes,'
HE SHOT RIGHT BACK -- THAT MAKES
ME SMART!
AND THEN HE SAID, IF YOU WANT ME
TO PAY MY TAXES,
THEN CHANGE THE TAX CODE
BUT I KNOW YOU WON'T
BECAUSE YOUR FRIENDS AND DONORS
ENJOY THE SAME TAX BREAK THAT I
DO.
AND WITH THAT, MY FRIENDS, A
STAR WAS BORN.
NO ONE HAD EVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THAT.
NO ONE HAD EVER SEEN ANYONE COME
FROM INSIDE THAT HOUSE
OUTSIDE
AND TELL ALL THE COMMONERS,
WE'RE DOING EVERYTHING YOU THINK
WE'RE DOING INSIDE THAT HOUSE.
HE WENT RIGHT BACK IN THE HOUSE
AND STARTED PLAYING A GAME
AGAIN.
DEMOCRATS ARE SORE LOSERS.
I'M A DEMOCRAT.
I'M TELLING YOU, AS SOON AS HE WON,
THEY STARTED SAYING, HE'S
COLLUDING WITH RUSSIA.
IT'S VERY EMBARRASSING AS A
DEMOCRAT.
BUT AS TIME WENT ON,
WE ALL CAME TO LEARN,
HE WAS PROBABLY
COLLUDING WITH RUSSIA.
I EVEN LOOK AT HIS WIFE
DIFFERENT NOW.
HIS WIFE THE BEAUTIFUL, NO
QUESTION ABOUT IT.
BUT SHE LOOKS LIKE THE SAME
CHICK THAT JAMES BOND WOULD
SMASH BUT NOT TRUST.
WHY ALL THEM DOCUMENTS AT HIS
HOUSE?
THIS GUY IS FAMOUS FOR NOT
READING HIS press briefings
AND NOW HE GOT
10,000 DOCUMENTS
and won't take them
I HAVE BEEN FIRED FROM JOBS MANY
TIMES IN MY LIFE,
AND I WILL BE
VERY HONEST WITH YOU.
SOMETIMES WHEN I WAS FIRED,
I
STOLE THINGS FROM THE OFFICE.
STAPLE GUNS, COMPUTER MOUSES,
ALL THAT KIND OF STUFF.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I NEVER STOLE
FROM WORK?
WORK.
War in Ukraine brought it all into focus.
LUCKY FOR EVERYBODY IN THE
WESTERN WORLD,
THE UKRAINIANS
ARE WAY BETTER FIGHTERS THAN WE
THOUGHT THEY WOULD BE.
I mean these guys, God bless them.
>> THEY KILLED 10,000 RUSSIANS
THE FIRST WEEK OF THE WAR.
EVEN VIETNAMESE WERE LIKE, THEM
ARE SOME GOOD NUMBERS!
THIS WAS BEFORE THEY HAD
WEAPONS.
BEFORE WE STARTED SENDING THEM
WEAPONS, THEY WERE KILLING
RUSSIANS WITH STUFF YOU CAN FIND
AROUND THE HOUSE.
That whole country of Ukraine
was littered with traps
LIKE HOME ALONE.
THEY WERE STEPPING ON RAKES
AND LIKE AHH!
HOW IS RUSSIA LOSING TO THE
UKRAINE?
THAT WOULD BE LIKE AMERICA
LOSING A WAR TO COLORADO.
NOW THE MIDTERMS ARE OVER AND
EVERYBODY'S AWAKE.
THESE NEW WHITES, THEY'RE LIKE
NEWBORN BABIES WHO JUST WOKE UP.
EVERYTHING WHITE PEOPLE MAD
ABOUT, WE HAVE BEEN ON THAT.
MAN, I CAN'T SEE MY FAMILY.
WE BE LIKE, WE BEEN ON THAT!
MAN, WE CAN'T TRUST THE
GOVERNMENT.
WE BEEN ON THAT?
WHY DON'T YOU DISMANTLE THE FBI?
WORD TO MARTIN LUTHER KING, BRO.
WE'VE BEEN ON THAT.
Nobody listens to me when I tell these jokes,
you ignore me.
MY FIRST NETFLIX SPECIAL, WHAT
DID I SAY?
I SAID, I DON'T WANT TO SNEAK A
DEAL BECAUSE THE MINUTE I SAY
SOMETHING THAT MAKES THOSE
PEOPLE MAD,
THEY'RE GOING TO
TAKE MY SNEAKERS AWAY.
AND THE WHOLE CROWD WAS
LAUGHING.
Now you see Kanye walking
around L.A. barefoot with his chain on.
THIS GUY LOST 1.5 BILLION IN A
DAY.
$1.5 BILLION A DAY.
I SAW THAT AND I SAID, PUT YOUR
CHAIN ON.
WELCOME BACK.
IT SHOULDN'T BE THIS SCARY TO
TALK ABOUT ANYTHING.
IT'S MAKING MY JOB INCREDIBLY
DIFFICULT.
AND TO BE HONEST WITH YOU, I'M
SICK OF TALKING TO A CROWD LIKE
THIS.
I LOVE YOU TO DEATH, AND I THANK
YOU FOR YOUR SUPPORT.
AND I HOPE THEY DON'T TAKE
ANYTHING AWAY FROM ME,
WHOEVER
THEY ARE.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW TONIGHT!
Brooklyn's finest
BLACK STAR IS IN THE BUILDING!
>>> WELCOME BACK TO PM IN THE
AFTERNOON.
COMING UP LATER, CHEF CINDY IS
GOING TO BE HERE.
>> AND ONCE AGAIN, WE ARE
HONORED TO BE JOINED BY WILLY T.
HOPKINS.
HE'S BEEN SITTING IN ALL MORNING
PLAYING SOME TASTY LICKS OFF HIS
NEW ALBUM, MY POTATO HOLE.
INTERESTING TITLE.
>> I'M SORRY, WILLY T.
I ALMOST DON'T WANT TO ASK BUT
WHAT ON EARTH IS THE POTATO
HOLE?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> I'M CURIOUS.
WHAT IS IT?
DO I HAVE A POTATO HOLE?
CAN I TOUCH MY WIFE'S POTATO
HOLE?
>> CAN WE SEEN SAY IT ON
TESTIFY.
WHAT IS A TO PO DAY TOE HOLE?
>> I WOULD RATHER NOT SAY.
>> OKAY.
JILL, WHAT ARE WE LOOKING AT?
>> IF YOU'RE GOING OUT, YOU'RE
GOING TO WANT TO BRING AN
UMBRELLA, ESPECIALLY IF YOU
DON'T WANT TO GET RAIN INSIDE
YOUR POTATO HOLE.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S SO FUN TO SAY.
>> IF YOU'RE JUST JOINING US,
FOLKS, WE ARE ABSOLUTELY TICKLED
BY WILLY T.'S NEW ALBUM, MY
POTATO HOLE.
SPEAKING OF TICKLE.
WHAT HAPPENED HAPPEN IF I TICKLE
MY WIFE'S.
>> JOSH, I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
IN THERE FOR FIVES.
THE ETERNAL QUESTION, WHAT IS A
POTATO HOLE, THE WORLD MAY NEVER
KNOW.
LET GO TO SPORTS.
>> THANKS, DEBORAH.
THE PGA TOUR IS IN FULL SWING,
PUN.
WITH RORY McLLROY SINKING A HOLE
IN ONE.
COULD YOU SINK A POTATO HOLE?
ONE?
>> BEFORE WE GO TO BREAK, WILLY
T., YOU GOT TO TELL US, WE GOT
TO KNOW, WHAT IS A POTATO HOLE.
>> SPILL THE TEA.
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, MAN.
TELL US WHAT A POTATO HOLE IS.
>> IT'S A HOLE THAT SLAVES USED
TO HIDE THEIR FOOD AND
POSSESSIONS FROM PLANTATION
OWNERS.
WHATEVER THESE SLAVES HAD, THEY
WOULD KEEP IN THEIR POTATO HOLE,
EVEN THOUGH THEY KNEW THAT IF
THEY MESSED WITH OTHER FAMILIES'
POTATO HOLES, THEY WOULD BE
WHIPPED OR BEAT, OVER TIME, IT
CAME TO RESEMBLE BLACK LIVES IN
THE FACE OF OPPRESSION.
THAT'S WHAT A POTATO HOLE IS,
BITCH.
>> UH-HUH.
I DID NOT SEE THAT AS WHAT IT
COULD BE.
COULD HAVE TOLD US SOONER.
BUT, YEAH.
NO.
I THINK WE ARE ALL SORRY.
>> WILLY T., WANT TO PLAY US OUT
WITH A TASTY LICK?
>> I DO NOT.
>> DIDN'T THINK YOU WOULD.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> ANYONE OUT HERE WATCHING
THIS NEW SHOW, HOUSE OF DRAGONS?
I AM THE BIGGEST GAME OF TLOENS
FAN.
I LOVE THEIR NEW SHOW.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, I LOVE
THEY'RE INCLUDING BLACK CHARACTERS,
BUT TO BE HONEST,
THE BLACK CHARACTERS
TAKE ME OUT
OF IT A LITTLE BIT WITH
THE STEP
BOND HAIR AND OLD TIME ACCENTS.
JARRING
WHERE ARE THESE PEOPLE FROM?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
AND THEN THEY'RE COMING OUT WITH
SEASON TWO, I GUESS SOON.
AND SOMEHOW LAUREN MICHAELS
ARRANGED A SNEAK PEEK FOR HOUSE
OF DRAGONS TWO.
SO CHECK IT OUT.
NEXT SEASON
>> BEFORE WE GO TO WAR WITH
KINGS LANDING, WE MUST KNOW WHO
OUR TRUE ALLIES ARE.
>> THESE REPRESENT ALL OUR PARTS
OF ALLIANCES, YOUR GRACE.
- THANK YOU
FAMILY TREE
>> YES.
OUR NAMES ARE INSANE AND SOUND
IDENTICAL.
>> I'VE ALSO PREPARED A CHART OF
WHO'S HAVING SEX WITH WHOM.
SAME
VISITOR, YOUR GRACE.
LORD OF THE TIDES, THE SEA
SNAKE HIMSELF, CORLIF.
>> THIS IS A MOST WELCOME
SURPRISE.
WHERE HAVE YOU COME FROM?
>> THE MATRIX.
KIDDING
>> YOU MUST HAVE BEEN AT SEA LONG
>> OF COURSE.THIS IS WHERE T
COMFORTABLE.
THE OCEAN.
WE ESPECIALLY LOVE BEING ON
SHIPS.
NEVER HAVE ANY CONCERN BEING ON
SHIPS OR WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN TO US
IF WE COME ON SHIPS.
>> DID YOU COME ALONE?
>> NO.
GREETINGS
40 DAYS
>> IT'S WONDER TO SEE YOU.
SINCE YOU KNOW JASON LUKE.
>> YES.
I LOOK AT MY FUTURE HUSBAND
AND
KNOW HE'S GOING TO SATISFY ME
SEXUALLY.
>> TO WHAT DO WE OH THE HONOR OF
YOUR VISIT?
>> I KNOW YOU NEED SOME ALLIES
NOW THAT YOUR FATHER HAS DIED.
>> DIED?
FACE
THE DOCTOR SAID IT'S NOTHING.
JUST A LITTLE COUGH.
SKIN
EYE
>> WELL, I FOUND YOU SOME NEW
ALLIES
THAT HAVE COME TO PAY
THEIR RESPECTS TO THE TRUE
QUEEN.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
GOOD TO SEE YOU
COUSIN
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN A LONG
TIME.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO HAVE SEX
WITH YOUR NIECE?
YUCK.
WHOLE FAMILY
NO THANK YOU.
>> YOUR MAJESTY, LOOKS LIKE YOU
GOT A CASE OF THE MONKEY POX.
YOU GOING TO DIE IN THE MINUTE,
AIN'T YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, IF IT ISN'T OUR COUSIN,
LIGHT-SKINNED LARRY.
TITIES
MILK
>> YOU LOOK LIKE E.T. WHEN THEY
DRESS HIM UP FOR HALLOWEEN.
>> HEY, ALL THAT WAS HATEFUL,
MAN.
>> YOU'RE GETTING A LITTLE DRY.
>> THAT'S THAT DRAGON SPRAY.
>> MORE VISITORS APPROACH.
>> PARDON ME, GRACE.
BUT PENIS JUST FELL OFF.
BETTER SET SOME MONEY FOR
THAT.
>> WHO IS THIS FOUL MAN?
>> I CAME HERE FOR A DRAGON
ROCK.
I'M DOWN TO MY LAST 40.
HOW
MIND IF I GET A LIGHT?
>> BE GONE, ALL OF YOU!
>> OH, NO.
THERE'S MORE.
>> I'M ONE OF THE BADDEST
[ BLEEP ] YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
BITCH
DRAGONS
WANT TO RIDE MINE YOUR
FREAKING MAJESTY?
>> TAKE ME TO FLEE BOTTOM SO I
CAN CHECK ON MY HOLES.
>> I GOT A DRAGON NOW.
DAMN
>> IT'S THE POLICE.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING ALL THE WAY
UP HERE?
NO MATTER HOW I FLY, THEY ALWAYS
FIND YOU, DON'T THEY?
>>> MAN, OH, MAN.
I STILL CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT
KANYE MESSED UP ALL THAT MONEY.
>> HOW YOU GOING TO LOSE
$2 BILLION IN A DAY?
>> BECAUSE IT COULD BE ME.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
THEN HE DID ALL THEM DAMN
INTERVIEWS MAKING THINGS WORSE
AND WORSE.
>> YOU AIN'T GOT TO SAY EVERY
DAMN THING YOU'RE THINKING ALL
THE TIME.
>> HE LOST ME WHEN HE PUT ON
THAT WHITE LIVES MATTER SHOW.
>> OR WHEN HE SAID THAT MESSAGE
ABOUT GEORGE FLOYD.
>> EXACTLY AND HIS COMMENTS
ABOUT JEWISH PEOPLE.
WAY OFF THE MARK.
>> I AIN'T GOING TO LIE,
I WAS WITH A COLLEGE DROPOUT EARLIER
TODAY IN THE CAR.
STILL SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
WORD.  IT'S GOING TO BE HARD TO
LISTEN TO KANYE IN A WHILE.
>> SAME.
THAT'S WHY I SET ALL MY YEEZIES
ON FIRE.
THEY'RE ONLY SNEAKERS, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
THAT KYRIE IRVING STUFF AIS A
TRIP.
PLAY
>> I HEARD THEY HAVE A BUNCH OF
STUFF FOR HIM TO DO BEFORE THEY
LET HIM BACK IN.
>> IT'S LIKE WHEN HE SAID THE
WORLD WAS FLAT.
EXACTLY
>> OR WHEN HE REFUSED TO TAKE
THE VACCINE.
I HAD UNDERSTAND THE INITIAL
SKEPTICISM
BUT IF THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES SAYS IT'S
SAFE.
>> I'M STILL MAD AT MY GIRL
STACEY ABRAMS LOST.
>> HOW DID SHE LOSE?
BUT HERSCHEL WALKER GETS A
RUNOFF.
WHAT IS GOING ON IN GEORGIA?
>> IT'S THE BIBLE BELT, AND THIS
COUNTRY WILL NEVER PROGRESS
UNTIL WE SEPARATE GOD AND
POLITICS.
>> HEY.
Y'ALL HEARD GERMANE GOT ROBBED
LAST NOTICE?
>> YEAH.
I HEARD THEY TOOK A $3,500 CHAIN
OFF HIS NECK TOO.
>> DAMN.
>> NOW WHO WOULD SPEND THAT MUCH
MONEY ON A NECKLACE?
>> MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I FINALLY WATCHED?
THAT DAHMER THING THEY HAD ON
NETFLIX.
>> OH, THAT WAS SO GOOD, RIGHT?
NOT GOOD AS IN HE'S GOOD.
I THOUGHT IT PROVIDED SOME
NEEDED INCITES ON SOME --
>> I WISH THEY MADE MORE SHOWS
THAT EVERYBODY COULD ENJOY.
>> LIKE ATLANTA.
THEY'RE KILLING IT THIS SEASON.
>> OR ABBOTT ELEMENTARY.
>> OR YELLOW STONE.
>> YELLOW WHAT?
>> YELLOW STONE.
IT'S LIKE THE MOST STREAMED SHOW
IN THE WORLD.
>> OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> OH, I GUESS IT'S ALREADY
6:05
THAT'S IT FOR MY SHIFT.
TROY, THANK YOU AGAIN FOR
LETTING ME WORK IN YOUR
BARBERSHOP.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD, PHILLIP.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
>> HOPEFULLY TOMORROW I'LL GET A
CUSTOMER.
MAYBE
I HOPE I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
THAT WAS TOO OFFENSIVE TO
ANYBODY.
>> NO.
YOU ALL GOOD, PHILLIP, MAN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH AND I WILL SEE
YOU BRIGHT AND EARLY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU GUYS TAKE CARE.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> OKAY.
BYE BYE.
>> OKAY, PHILLIP.
>> HE'S THE POLICE, AIN'T HE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
YEAH
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BROOKLYN'S FINEST, BLACK STAR.
♪
♪ AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, HEY
♪ BEY, BEY, BEY
YASIIN, YASIIN, YASIIN ♪
♪ SHARPER THAN A
STRAIGHT RAZOR SHAVED ♪
♪ COOLER THAN A STEEL
I PUT THE BLADE TO A POINT ♪
♪ IT'S WORLDWIDE CURRENTS
YEAH, THEY WISHING
WELL COINS ♪
♪ IT'S HIGH FIDELITY BANG
THAT SPEAKER LEAK NOISE ♪
♪ AND AT A CHUCK D LEVEL
Y'ALL AT PETITE LEVEL ♪
♪ HOW A GUN DO A
CHOPPER SPREAD
LOVE BEAT DEVILS ♪
♪ WALK SOFT AND CARRY
THE CROW MAGNUM ♪
♪ SHOTS CLUB AND SMASH 'EM
THEY SHOW UP ANY FRAGMENT ♪
♪ BREATHE FIRE, SPIT SMOKE
BLOW AWAY ASHES ♪
♪ SMARTEN UP, DUMBASS
THIS AIN'T BUMP CLASS ♪
♪ ATMOSPHERE ABOVE THAT
YOU CAN'T TOUCH THAT ♪
♪ REAL, FOREVER REAL
THEY CAN HATE IT
OR LOVE THAT ♪
♪ IT'S BIGGER THAN HIP-HOP
HYPES AND
WICKED GOVERNMENT ♪
♪ BROOKLYN AWARD-WINNING
A NOT GIVE A GUINNESS ♪
♪ YOU IN IT FOR THE MOST
SUCKER-ISH, DUMMIEST ♪
♪ NO GETTING LOVE IN THIS
SOME REAL RIDERS
UP IN THIS BEYOTCH ♪
♪ BUILDS MORE BITCH
THAN BITCH REEBOX ♪
♪ THEY ARMS CAN'T BITCH
THE BASE OF A THREE-OX ♪
♪ THESE DUDES DOPE
DEALING'S DETOX ♪
♪ CIRCU WENT CLEAN UP
YOUR ACT IF YOU
ACT LIKE CRACK, HA ♪
♪ HOP IN ALADDIN
I WILL NEVER BE THAT ♪
♪ I GOT THE WHITE AND EXACT
AND A TRAP FOR THE RAPS ♪
♪ THE LIARS AND THE SAPS
THE POSERS AND THE HACKS ♪
♪ LAYING MY MAIN LINE
YOUR SPINE GOES SNAP, BEY ♪
♪ VANGLORIOUS
FANTASMIC OREA ♪
♪ CRACK-PANNED OREO ON EACH
AND EVERY ALL OF YOU ♪
♪ WHOEVER YOU CAN CALL
THEN YOU BETTER STOP
CALLING 'EM ♪
♪ THEN CALL THE CORONER
WHITE DRAPES FOR
ALL OF YOU'S ♪
♪ GREATEST AIN'T
GREATER THAN ♪
♪ STRONGEST AIN'T
STRONG ENOUGH ♪
♪ BIGGEST AIN'T BIGGER
THAN A REAL SMALL
PORTION OF ♪
♪ THE LEGENDARY TRILOTARY
TOP RANK OFFICER ♪
♪ GET LOST, BIG BOSS
THIS BOSS'LL BOSS YOU ♪
♪ CHIP ON YOUR SHOULDER
I'MA KNOCK IT
RIGHT OFF YOU ♪
♪ BEY, TORPEDO
BLAST MATCH THE EGO ♪
♪ SNIPER ON THE RANGE
SNIPER BANG ENOUGH, RELOAD ♪
♪ RPG TO GIVE FREE
POWER PEOPLE, BRRAP ♪
♪ ONE CLIP IN THEY EVIL
DONE WITH TALKING ♪
♪ LIKE THEY WANT TROUBLE
AND REALLY WANT -- ♪
♪ THEY PROBABLY WANT TRICK
LIKE A SKI ON THIS TRIP ♪
♪ GET MONEY AND
YOUR MRS. NEVER
KILL A PIMP ♪
♪ LIE OUT MY RHETORICALS
AND THEY AIN'T SAID ♪
♪ YOU CAN TALK 'TIL YOU DIE
AND YOU AIN'T SAID THIS ♪
♪ UNLESS YOU REPEATING THE
PHRASE OF Y'ALL BEESIEST ♪
♪ 17 VERSE OF
THE 25th EZEKIEL ♪
♪ LEAKIO, LET US PRAY 'FORE
THEY SOLDIER THESE SUCKERS ♪
♪ AIGHT, I'M BACK MOTHER
YEAH, JANUARY, FEBRUARY
MARCHING WITH THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ APRIL, MAY I HAVE A
BLACK STAR SEQUEL
SAID THE BLACK CAUCUS ♪
♪ JUNE, JULY
THE BLACK AUGUST ♪
♪ SEPTEMBER TO OCTOBER
YOU FIND YOU A BLACK ♪
♪ THOUGHT IS NOVEMBER
WHEN WE COME
FOR THAT OFFICE ♪
♪ THE BLACK POTUS
THE BLACK LOTUS FLOWER ♪
♪ FALL IN DECEMBER
GO ASK THE WEATHERMAN ♪
♪ COLDER THAN
THE WINTER WIND ♪
♪ DAY AFTER DECEMBER 10 WE
CELEBRATING
YASIIN BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ BROOKLYN, NEW YORK CITY
THAT'S THE SCENE
OF MY BIRTHPLACE ♪
♪ I'M SO ON TOP OF THIS BOP
WITH THE METROPOLITAN FROLIC ♪
♪ WITH THE POPULOUS TOPPLIN'
ALL THE CHARLATANS ♪
♪ MY SONGS IS KNOWLEDGE
TO HEROES THAT
NEED HONORING ♪
♪ A PROMISE WE DEMOLISHING
ALL CONFEDERATE MONUMENTS ♪
♪ I'M NOTICING HOW THESE
NAZIS BECOME CONGRESSMEN ♪
♪ IT'S SOFTER THAN SOME
MOCCASINS AND WAY FAKER
THAN COLLAGEN ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER IF THESE
SCHOLARS HAVE
GOT DOCTORATES M
♪ THEY'RE HIDING BEHIND
FAKE NAMES LIKE ♪
♪ TOMMY ROBINSON
I'M BOMBING 'EM ♪
♪ PLUS THE SLEEVE
IS MONOGRAM ♪
♪ IF I DIE AND COME BACK
AND PERFORM AS A HOLOGRAM ♪
♪ CAN'T TELL IF IT'S
A BOY OR A GIRL
GET A SONOGRAM ♪
♪ MY NAME IS FLOATING UP
AND DOWN THE AVE
LIKE DOLLAR VANS ♪
♪ DAMN, MY SYRUP
IS MAPLE LEAF ♪
♪ AND I'M PACKIN' THIS
IS A PASS ♪
♪ AND I'M STABBING
THESE FAKE EMCEES ♪
♪ IT'S SHARP AND
MAKING 'EM BLEED ♪
♪ GOT HALF OF THEM
MAKE BELIEVE ♪
♪ I COME FROM A PLACE
OF PEACE BUT THEY ONLY
RESPECT THE VIOLENCE ♪
♪ YOU GET ARRESTED
FOR DOMESTIC SILENCE ♪
♪ RAPPERS IS VAMPIRES
WE THE LYCANS ♪
♪ EVEN THE VIKINGS
KNOW SOME MAGIC AND SOME ♪
♪ FROM THE
CONQUERED ALLIANCE ♪
♪ BRING IT TOGETHER
LIKE A HYPHEN ♪
♪ JUST LIARS
TESTING MY PATIENCE ♪
♪ NEVER STOP BECAUSE
MY PARENTS AIN'T NEVER
HAD A VACATION ♪
♪ RELOCATING
LOOKING AT PLACES
ALONG THE OCEAN ♪
♪ SMOKING TREES
AND THE TREES AS SHADY ♪
♪ AS RAPPER MOTIVES
CALAMITIES ♪
♪ FLASH CATASTROPHE
ADD AN APOSTROPHE ♪
♪ YOUR WHOLE PHILOSOPHY
IS MEDIOCRITY ♪
♪ ATROCITIES COMMITTED
IN THE NAME
OF OWNING PROPERTY ♪
♪ MONOPOLIES
THAT'S MY HYPOTHESES
>>> IT'S WEEKEND UPDATE WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, EVERYONE, DEMOCRATS HAVE
RETAINED CONTROL OF THE SENATE.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S REALLY OFFICIAL,
BUT WE'RE NOT A REAL
NEWS PROGRAM, SO I'M JUST GOING
TO CALL IT.
I WAS ACTUALLY SURPRISED THEY
WON GIVEN PRESIDENT BIDEN'S LOW
APPROVAL RATINGS.
I GUESS HE'S KIND OF LIKE THE
JURASSIC WORLD MOVIES,
EXTREMELY
SUCCESSFUL DESPITE A 42% RATING.
REPUBLICANS ARE NOT TAKING IT
WELL.
TUCKER CARLSON SEEN STRUGGLING
TO MAKE IT THROUGH NO NUT
NOVEMBER.
HE CRITICIZED THE VOTING --
YOU GUYS ARE ALL DOING IT TOO?
OKAY.
CRITICIZED THE VOTING PROCESS
AND CALLED ELECTRONIC VOTING
MACHINES A THREAT TO DEMOCRACY.
I'M ACTUALLY NOT THAT WORRIED
ABOUT THE VOTING MACHINES.
I'M WORRIED THEY'RE BEING OPERATED
BY THE OLDEST PEOPLE I'VE EVER
SEEN.
TRULY THIS YEAR, THE WOMAN WHO
GAVE ME MY BALLOT WAS WEARING
TWO STICKERS.
ONE THAT SAID I VOTED,
AND ANOTHER THAT SAID I SURVIVED THE
TITANIC.
>>> THE KEY SENATE RACE IN GEORGIA
WILL MOVE THE A RUNOFF
IN DECEMBER.
BUT HE'S OFFERED WARNOCK TO
JUST, TAKE CARE OF IT, BABY.
MANY BLACK VOTERS IN GEORGIA
WERE FRUSTRATED WITH ANOTHER
RUNOFF ELECTION
BECAUSE THE
BURDEN OF SAVING THE SENATE FELL
ON THEM ONCE AGAIN.
IT'S HAPPENED SO OFTEN, THERE'S
ALREADY A MOVIE ABOUT IT.
MADEA
>> IN A SPEECH YESTERDAY,
HERSCHEL WALKER CALLED AMERICA
THE GREATEST COUNTRY IN THE
UNITED STATES.
BUT ON THE PLUS SIDE, AT LEAST
HE HAS A GENERAL IDEA OF WHERE
HE IS.
WALKER THEN APOLOGIZED FOR
MISSPEAKING SAYING,
I KNOW I'M
NOT ALWAYS THE SHARPEST TOOL IN
THE REFRIGERATOR.
SENATOR MARK KELLY DEFEATED
CHALLENGER BLAKE MASTERS IN THE
ARIZONA SENATE RACE.
MASTERS CAN NOW RETURN TO HIS
TRUE PASSION OF
I'M GOING TO
GUESS STRANGLING HITCHHIKERS.
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN SAID HE PLANS
TO RUN AGAIN IN 2024,
BUT WON'T
MAKE A FINAL DECISION UNTIL
EARLY NEXT YEAR.
BECAUSE IT'S LIKE HIS DOCTOR
TOLD HIM, I WOULDN'T PLAN TOO
FAR AHEAD.
AFTER THIS YEAR'S ELECTION,
A RECORD-SETTING 12 STATES WILL
HAVE FEMALE GOVERNORS
WHILE THE OTHER 38 STATES WILL
HAVE DINNER READY ON TIME.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> A 25-YEAR-OLD FROM FLORIDA
WILL BECOME THE FIRST GEN-Z
MEMBER OF CONGRESS.
YOUNGER, SAID MATT GATES.
RUE PERT MEASURE DOCK TURNED ON
DONALD TRUMP.
HE CALLED RON DeSANTIS RON DEFUTURE,
EVEN THOUGH THAT
SOUNDS MORE LIKE A DRAG QUEEN
FROM OUTER SPACE.
EGG ON THE WALL
THEN THE HEADLINE,
TRUMPTY DMMPTY,
EASIEST
AND NOW TRUMP IS
THREATENING TO REVEAL
UNFLATTERING INFORMATION ABOUT
RON DeSANTIS.
FOR EXAMPLE, DID YOU KNOW HE WAS
IN CHARGE OF THE STATE
WHERE
SOME MANIAC WAS HIDING NUCLEAR
SECRETS?
>> APPLE WAS SAYING THAT COVID IN CHINA
HAS LED TO A SLOW DOWN
IN iPHONE PRODUCTION.
WOW.
SO I GUESS THE NEW VARIANT DOES
AFFECT CHILDREN.
I LOVE THIS CROWD.
>> NEARLY HALF A BILLION DOLLARS
WAS SPENT IN CALIFORNIA
ON
CAMPAIGNS AIMED AT LEGALIZING
SPORTS GAMBLING ONLINE
BUT
FAILED BY A WIDE MARGIN.
SAID SUPPORTERS OF THE BILL,
OKAY, DOUBLE OR NOTHING.
EXIT POLLS FROM THIS YEAR'S
MIDTERMS SHOW THAT LATINOS WERE
A LARGEST SHARE OF THE ELECTOR
RAT THAN EVER BEFORE.
HERE TO TELL US WHY HE WILL ONE
DAY RUN FOR PRESIDENT IS JOSE
SUAREZ.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> WELCOME.
DO YOU THINK OF YOURSELF AS A
REPUBLICAN OR DEMOCRAT?
>> I'M JUST HAPPY TO BE HERE,
COLIN.
EVERYBODY COMPLAINING ALL THE
TIME ABOUT EVERYTHING.
GUESS WHAT?
IT'S FINE.
EVERYTHING IS BASICALLY FINE.
AND THAT'S GOING TO BE MY
CAMPAIGN SLOGAN.
JOSE SUAREZ.
EVERYTHING IS BASICALLY FINE,
OKAY?
SO RELAX, OKAY?
IT'S BASICALLY FINE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT OUTLOOK.
>> MY GOSH, IT'S TOO EXPENSIVE.
NEWS FLASH, EVER HEARD OF LEGS?
MY MOTHER WALKED TO WORK EVERY
DAY, AND HER LEG DIDN'T WORK.
SHE HAD TO PULL IT.
>> THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
>> AND INFLATION, EVERYBODY
COMPLAIN INFLATION IS SO BAD.
THE PRICE OF MILK IS TOO HIGH.
HOW ABOUT JUST DON'T DRINK MILK?
WHO'S EVEN COMPLAINING ABOUT THE
PRICE OF MILK?
THE BABIES?
DO YOU DRINK MILK, COLIN.
>> I MEAN MAYBE JUST A WARM
GLASS BEFORE BED.
>> AND THE WI-FI COLIN,
EVERYBODY COMPLAIN OH, THE
WI-FI, IT'S TOO SLOW.
THE WI-FI, MY POOR LITTLE WI-FI.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S A MAJOR
COMPLAINT.
>> GROWING UP IN CUBA, COLIN,
THERE WAS NO WI-FI.
IT WAS ONLY WHY.
WHY IS IT SO HOT?
WHY DID THE POWER GO OUT?
WHY IS THE PRESIDENT TAKING ALL
OUR STUFF?
COLIN, THE YOU WANT SOMETHING IN
AMERICA, YOU JUST PRESS A BUTTON
ON YOUR PHONE AND THEY'LL SEND
IT TO YOUR HOUSE.
>> CAN WE GO BACK TO YOU WERE
BORN IN CUBA.
WELL, THEN YOU CAN'T RUN FOR
PRESIDENT, RIGHT?
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL
CARE ABOUT THAT.
>> I'M SURE THEY ARE.
BUT WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON
ROE VERSUS WADE?
>> I SAY ROW IF YOU CAN.
BUT IF YOU DON'T HAVE A BOAT,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT.
I'M JUST KIDDING COLIN.
ALL I KNOW IS IF I AM THE
PRESIDENT, EVERY MOTHER GOING TO
GET ONE CHUNKLETA.
>> AND WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S A SANDAL, COLIN.
>> AND WHAT IS A MOTHER GOING DO
WITH ONE SANDAL?
>> YOU NEVER KNOW.
THAT'S THE SCARY PART.
SOMETIMES THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO USE IT.
THEY JUST SHOW IT, SEND A
MESSAGE, AND THEY PUT IT AWAY.
WHAT YOU SAY TO ME?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I WILL REMEMBER THAT.
MY 1-YEAR-OLD HAS BEEN ACTING
UP.
SO, JOSE, WHAT IS YOUR FINAL
MESSAGE TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE?
>> THAT WE SHOULD ALL BE
GRATEFUL, COLIN.
THIS IS A GREAT COUNTRY, AND I
THINK WE NEED TO REMEMBER HOW
LUCKY WE ARE.
>> TRUE.
ALTHOUGH IT DOES SEEM LIKE
YOU'RE IGNORING SOME REALLY BIG
PROBLEMS IN THE COUNTRY.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY, COLIN?
>> JOSE, EVERYONE.
>> ARCHAEOLOGISTS IN EGYPT HAVE
DISCOVERED A TUNNEL THEY THINK
LEADS TO THE LONG-LOST TOMB OF
CLEOPATRA WHO GOT MARK ANTONY.
I ASSUME BECAUSE SHE'S REALLY
FUNNY OR SOMETHING?
>> A WOMAN IN DELAWARE WON
$400,000 AFTER HITTING
BACK-TO-BACK LOTTOS IN THE SAME
DAY.
BUT SHE SAYS SHE'S STILL GOING
TO KEEP HER DAY JOB, FORGING
LOTTERY TICKETS.
THE U.S. AIR FORCE IS DENYING
THAT THE FLIGHT PATH THAT
CREATED A GIANT PENIS POINTED AT
RUSSIA.
EVEN WORSE, THEY THEN FIRED
MISSILES.
>> A WHITE STUDENT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF KENTUCKY WAS
ARRESTED AFTER SHE WAS CAUGHT ON
VIDEO USING A RACIAL SLUR AND
ASSAULTING TWO BLACK STUDENTS.
SHE HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH ONE
COUNT OF IMPERSONATING A POLICE
OFFICER.
>> A 10-YEAR-OLD BOY IN FLORIDA
FACES MISDEMEANOR BATTERY
CHARGES AFTER HE TOUCHED A
TEACHER'S BREAST.
BECAUSE UNDER FLORIDA LAW,
STUDENTS ARE REQUIRED TO WAIT
FOR TEACHERS TO MAKE THE FIRST
MOVE.
WELL, GUYS, WE'RE SIX SHOWS INTO
THE NEW SEASON.
HERE TO DISCUSS A PERSONAL GRIPE
WITH ME IS OUR VERY ON SARAH
SHERMAN.
>> COLIN, I'VE GOT A BONE TO
PICK WITH YOU.
>> WHAT DID I DO NOW?
>> NONE OF THESE JOKES ARE ABOUT
ME.
IT WAS ALL MID MATERIALS THIS,
TRUMP THAT, BUT WHAT ABOUT
SARAH?
>> WE CAN'T DO JOKES ABOUT YOU,
SARAH.
>> WELL, I CAN, AND I'M GOING TO
DO THEM ALL HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU BROUGHT YOUR OWN SET?
>> OF COURSE I DID BECAUSE YOURS
LOOKS UGLY.
I'M SARAH, AND THIS IS THE SARAH
NEWS.
A TUNNEL BELOW NIAGARA FALLS
RECENTLY OPENED TO THE PUBLIC
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN OVER A
CENTURY.
A MUSCLETY OLD TUNNEL LETTING
PEOPLE BACK IN AFTER YEARS OF
DISUSE.
I CAN ONLY HOPE, SAID MY
BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S RIGHT, AMERICA.
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
DON'T LET THE QUEER HAIR CUT
FOOL YOU, HONEY.
I'M AS STRAIGHT AS MICHAEL CHE'S
UPDATE PERSONA.
EARLIER THIS WEEK, ELON MUSK
SUSPENDED TWITTER'S PAID
VERIFICATION SYSTEM.
WELL, I GUESS THE ONLY CHECK
MARK NEXT TO MY NAME WILL BE THE
ONE ON KANYE'S LIST OF JEWS TO
KEEP AN EYE ON.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH JOKES
ABOUT SARAH.
>> BRO, I'M ONLY GOING TO SAY
THIS ONCE, STOP TOUCHING MY LEG
UNDER THE TABLE.
>> I'M NOT DOING THAT.
>> IT'S TIME FOR WORLD NEWS.
♪
TODAY, I'LL BE DOING A STORY ON
PICKLE MANIA!
>> WHY IS IT THE MIDDLE OF THE
OCEAN?
>> WHAT ARE YOU A GEOGRAPHER?
RELAX, BRO.
IN PENNSYLVANIA NEWS, SENATOR
ELECT AND BIG, GORGEOUS MONSTER
JOHN FETTERMAN, HAS RECEIVED
CRITICISM FOR HIS CASUAL DRESS.
AND I AGREE, THOSE CARGO SHORTS
AND HOODIES DON'T BELONG ON THE
SENATE FLOOR.
THEY BELONG CRUMPLED UP ON MY
BEDROOM FLOOR.
THANKSGIVING MUST HAVE COME
EARLY THIS YEAR BECAUSE THAT
HUNK IS GIVING THE TURKEY WADDLE
BETWEEN MY LEGS SOMETHING TO BE
THANKFUL FOR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT IS DISGUSTING.
>> SOMEBODY'S JEALOUS!
SPEAKING OF DISGUSTING, I
RECENTLY HAD AN ALLERGIC
REACTION THAT MADE MY FACE LOOK
LIKE THIS.
BUT ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, NOW YOU
HAVE A PICTURE TO SHOW THE HR
LADY WHEN SHE ASKS, WHAT DID
COLIN EVER DO TO YOU?
>> SARAH, THAT IS HORRIBLE.
WE HAVE TO END THIS.
>> WHY?
SO YOU CAN GET BACK TO LIKE
WHATEVER THIS CRAP IS?
GUYS, BY THE WAY, THESE AREN'T
NOTES.
THEY'RE JUST COLIN'S LITTLE
DRAWINGS OF ME.
>> YOU PLANTED THAT!
>>> HEY, FOLKS.
IT'S ME, DAVE.
AND I'M HERE TO REMIND ALL THE
KIDS WATCHING THAT SMOKE IS NOT
SCHOOL.
SMOKERS ARE.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU GUYS A HEADS
UP THAT I'M NOT GOING TO BE IN
THIS NEXT SKETCH BECAUSE I'M A
LITTLE OLDER AND I NEED A LITTLE
REST.
BUT THE SKETCH IS REALLY FUN AND
I WANTED YOU GUYS TO SEE IT.
AND SO MY MAN STEPPED UP, SO I
HOPE YOU ENJOY THIS.
>> HELLO?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
AM I DEAD?
>> INDEED YOU ARE, YOUNG MAN.
>> SO THIS IS HEAVEN?
>> IN A SENSE.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WHERE AM I?
>> YOU IN BLACK HEAVEN, BIOTCH.
♪ BLACK HEAVEN ♪
>> SO THEY HAVE A DIFFERENT
HEAVEN FOR BLACK PEOPLE?
>> YEAH, YOUNGIN.
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU IS?
>> SO EVERYBODY UP IN HERE IS
BLACK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE WHOLE AFTERLIFE OF BEAUTIFUL
BLACK KINGS AND QUEENS.
>> THOUGH ERY NOW AND THEN,
SOME -- I CAN'T SAY THAT LINE.
>> YOU'RE ALLOWED TO SAY IT.
>> ERY NOW AND THEN, SOME WHITE
CHICKEN HEAD HOES CLUCK THEY WAY
THROUGH THE GATE LOOKING FOR
SOME CHOCOLATE.
>> AND WE HAPPY TO OBLIGE.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO LIKE IT
HERE, FAM.
>> OF COURSE YOU WILL.
THIS IS BLACK HEAVEN WHERE YOUR
JORDANS NEVER HAVE A CREASE.
>> WHERE YOUR WAVES ALWAYS 360.
>> I SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS
SKETCH.
DAVE'S NOT EVEN RESTING.
HE'S RIGHT THERE.
>> YOU'RE KILLING IT, MIKEY.
KEEP GOING.
>> ANYWAY, IN BLACK HEAVEN, ALL
THE WOMEN ARE BADDIES AS I KNOW
YOU CAN SEE.
>> PREACH.
EVERY SHAWTY UP HERE GOT ONE OF
THEM TSA BOOTIES.
>> YEAH.
AROUND HERE, THE ASSES GO UP TO
THE TOP OF THE PANTS.
>> AND THE FOOD IS ON POINT.
>> THERE'S FOOD IN HEAVEN?
>> OF COURSE, CUZ.
AND AUNTIE ALWAYS KEEPS YOU A
PLATE.
>> AND UP HERE, THE MAC AND
CHEESE LOOKS LIKE THIS.
>> NO OFFENSE, BUT I'VE NEVER
BEEN A FAN OF MAC AND CHEESE.
>> EXCUSE ME?
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
MY MAC AND CHEESE.
>> SHE ABOUT TO THROW HANDS.
>> UH-OH, WORLD STAR.
>> LET'S GO!
>> OH, BUT YOU GOT TO TRUST ME,
BABY, BECAUSE YOU GOING TO LOVE
THIS MAC AND CHEESE, ON GOD.
>> AND I ASSUME YOU LIKE HENNY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> IT SAYS GESTURE TO HENNY.
ISN'T YOUR CHARACTER HENNY?
>> HENNY IS HENNESSY, MAN.
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
>> MAN, YOU WAS ON WILD AND OUT
SEASON 1.
YOU AIN'T ABSORBED NOTHING?
>> I DON'T KNOW!
I SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS!
I THINK DAVE IS JUST MESSING
WITH ME.
HE'S GOT ALL HIS FRIENDS WITH
HIM NOW.
LOOK.
>> KEEP GOING.
KEEP GOING.
GO, GO, GO.
>> COME ON, MIKEY, MAN, YOU A
PRO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ANYWAY, CUZZO, YOU A REAL ONE.
NOW BRING IT IN AND GET SOME
LOVE MY -- NO!
I'M NOT SAYING THAT!
I'M NOT!
>> THAT'S A GOOD CALL.
>> ANYWAY, WELCOME TO BLACK
HEAVEN.
>> AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THAT WAS SO MUCH FUN, I FORGOT
TO TAKE MY REST, SO I THINK I'M
ABOUT TO SIT THE NEXT SKETCH
OUT.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
MY MAN CAN FILL IN FOR ME.
IT'S ABOUT THE HORRORS AND
ATROCITIES ON THE UNDERGROUND
RAIL ROAD.
>> I CANNOT DO THAT.
>> OH, YES YOU CAN.
>> I CANNOT.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, MY BROTHERS,
BLACK STAR.
♪
♪ AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, HEY
AUTOMATIC, UH
AUTOMATIC, UH ♪
♪ AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, HA
AUTOMATIC AS AN AUTOMATIC, HA
I'M AUTOMATIC ♪
♪ AS A MEDITATION, HA
AUTOMATIC AS A TRAIL
OF TEARS, HA
ALRIGHT, THIS WAY ♪
♪ TRY AND FEEL, HA
THE ROGUE SOUL
DON'T BE THE LIGHT, HA
SHED THE LIGHT ♪
♪ INTO THE DARKROOM, HA
THE LIGHT IS NOT AFRAID
THAT PART, HA ♪
♪ GANG-GANG VARIATES
DREAM TEAM, HA
THE LOCAL DREAM
TIME ALWAYS, HA ♪
♪ THE ADDRESS
ON SPECTRUM ROAD, HA
FROM THE RIVERS OF
THE TRUE AND REAL, HA ♪
♪ SENSE OVER SENSATION, HA
SWEATING ON A HOT TEMPLATE HA
TWENTY CELL PANORAMA, HA
SILENCE OF ♪
♪ THE CLARION CALL
WAVEFORMS BIRD SONGS HA
RECOGNITION IS INVITATION HA
GRACE THE GIFT ♪
♪ YOU COULDN'T EARN, HA
THANKS AGAIN
REPORT THE WORK, HA
NOT FOR FREE
FREEDOM, HA ♪
♪ HOW YOU MADE IT
ASK YOURSELF, HA
LOOK TO EVERYTHING
THAT YOU DESIRE ♪
♪ LOOK AT THE CONDITIONS
THAT IT'S PUT YOU IN, HA
THROUGH THE HONEST MATH
PASSIVE FIGURES, HA ♪
♪ PASS THE FIXERS
FRIENDLY NEIGHBOR, HA
FRESHEST LABOR
MARRY HIS NATIVE, HA ♪
♪ LOCAL TIME, ALL AGES
FOREVER IS THE CURRENT EVENT
THE FUTURE
LIFE ON THIS SIDE IS QUICK ♪
♪ QUICK TRADE TRICK
SORCERER INSECURE SYNONYM
FRANKENSTEIN TRYNA
GET ESTRANGED, HA ♪
♪ AN ANCIENT SOURCE
MATTER STRANGE ENOUGH, HA
I HEARD DILLA SAY
TURN IT UP, HA
I HEARD HIM TWICE ♪
♪ WHEN HE SAID IT FIRST
AND THAT'S AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC ♪
♪ EVERYTHING IS NOT FOR SALE
EVERYBODY PAYS A PRICE
COCAINE CRACKER
THAN A HONKEY TONK ♪
♪ TRAILER PARK TRASH
CAN'T TRAP HOUSE
ALL-TIME
ALL BLACK EVERYTHING ♪
♪ TMT EFF WHITE SUPREMACY
COCAINE CRACKER
THAN A HONKEY TONK
TRAILER PARK TRASH ♪
♪ CAN'T TRAP HOUSE
STAR LINE
ALL BLACK EVERYTHING
TMT EFF WHITE SUPREMACY ♪
♪ TMT, TMT, TMT, TMT
TMT, TMT, TMT, TMT
WHAT'S WHITE SUPREMACY
YIKES ♪
♪ MENTAL ILLNESS
WE BRING THE NOISE
YOU BRING THE
GENTLE STILLNESS ♪
♪ THE TRAP DOOR
IN THE CITY IS CAT CALL
WE WITH THE NO NEED FOR
THE BACK AND FORTH ♪
♪ IT'S A TRAP
I'M SURE OF IT
LET'S GET INTO IT
DON'T BELIEVE YOU SUPERIOR ♪
♪ TO THE DARKER RACES
JUST MEANS YOU INFERIOR
LIVING DARKER PLACES
GOD'S AMAZING ♪
♪ WE ARTISTS
THIS AIN'T
A PRODUCT PLACEMENT
LOVE IS ♪
♪ A SPIRITUAL TECHNOLOGY
I GIVE IT UP TO GOD
WHEN THEY CLAP FOR ME
I LOVE TO GIVE CREDIT ♪
♪ WHERE THE CREDIT DUE
IT'S BEAUTIFUL
IT'S THE STRUGGLE
FACED BY THE DESTITUTE ♪
♪ WE CELEBRATE DIVERSITY
WITH CARNIVALS AND FESTIVALS
WHITE SUPREMACY AUTOMATICALLY
GOING AGAINST US ♪
♪ HUH, THE THIRD EYE
IS THE POINT OF ENTRY
HUH, AUTOMATIC LIKE A
REPLY FROM A HIPSTER ♪
♪ AUTOMATIC
AS A POINTER SISTER
TRYNA CONQUER US
WITH THE PESTILENCE, HA ♪
♪ THIS IS COMMON AS
BLACK EXCELLENCE, HA
THEY REWARDED FOR MEDIOCRITY
HUH, I AIN'T BEGGING ♪
♪ FOR MY EQUALITY
NO, I'M TOO BIG TO FAIL
GRAB THE BULL BY THE HORN ♪
♪ THEN WAG THE DOLL
BY THE TAIL
THE OGS IS IN JAIL
THE MILLENNIALS FOR SALE ♪
♪ AM I DREAMING
OR DO OUR DEMONS
HAVE TENTACLES AND SCALES, HA
AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC ♪
♪ CAUSE OF STATIC
THIS A TRUST EXERCISE
LIKE FALLING BACKWARDS
GOTTA TRUST WE YOUR GUYS ♪
♪ AND WE GON' CATCH YA
AND THAT'S AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC
AUTOMATIC, AUTOMATIC ♪
♪ EVERYTHING IS NOT FOR SALE
EVERYBODY PAYS A PRICE
YIKES ♪
♪
CHAUS CHAUS
>>> WHAT ARE THE MIDTERMS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE AT ALL.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> MOLLY!
>> DO YOU GUYS KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT POLITICS?
>> WHY?
YOU NEED HELP WRITING A SKETCH?
>> NO.
SOMETHING VERY BAD HAS HAPPENED.
>> YOUR NEW ATTORNEY GENERAL OF
OHIO IS NEWCOMER, MOLLY KEARNEY.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> OH, NO.
>> OH, GOD.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE ETERNAL
GENERAL.
>> HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> FOR A LOOK AT HOW IT ALL
STARTED, WE GO TO OUR POLITICAL
CORRESPONDENT STEVE KORNAKI.
>> FROM WHAT WE CAN TELL, IT ALL
BEGAN WITH A VIRAL TWEET.
I WOULD MAKE A GOOD OHIO TERN
GENERAL, LMAO, HASHTAG, IN MY
FEELINGS.
THIS IS AN UNPRECEDENTED WIN FOR
THE SNL BACKGROUND EXTRA.
>> COME ON, MAN.
I'M ON THE CAST.
>> DON'T YOU HAVE TO BE A LAWYER
TO DO THIS?
HAVE YOU PASSED THE BAR?
>> I DON'T PASS THE BAR.
I GO IN.
>> THIS IS ALL GOING TO BE OKAY.
WE HAVE TIME TO FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WE'LL BE HEARING HER BIG
SPEECH IN 20 MINUTES.
>> 20 MINUTES?
I THINK I KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO
DO.
THIS ELECTION IS A FRAUD!
>> WE CAN HELP YOU.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
WE'LL BE YOUR CHIEF OF STAFF.
FIRST THINGS FIRST, YOU HAVE TO
GET A NEW LOOK.
>> I LIKE MY LOOK.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE A LITTLE LEAGUE
UMPIRE.
>> ARE PEOPLE GOING TO LIKE
THIS?
I LOOK LIKE LEGO GUY.
>> AND WE GOT YOU A CAMERA READY
CHRISTIAN FAMILY.
>> WE'RE SO PROUD OF YOU, HONEY.
>> WELL, HELLO, MRS. KEARNEY.
>> MOLLY, YOU'RE GOING TO WANT
TO SEE THIS.
>> IS THIS REALLY WHO OHIO
DESERVES?
>> BROTHER, I DON'T PASS THE
BAR.
I ONLY GO IN.
>> ALCOHOLIC AND NEARLY
40-YEAR-OLD SNL STAGE HAND.
>> I'M ON THE CAST!
>> WE'RE FIVE MINUTES AWAY NOW
FROM THE BIG SPEECH.
ACCORDING TO OHIO LAW, IF THAT
SPEECH IS BAD, MOLLY WILL BE
SENT TO JAIL.
>> JAIL?
>> I'M GOING TO THROW UP.
>> WE NEED A PLATFORM.
WHAT'S SOMETHING YOU BELIEVE IN?
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE DEALT
PENALTY?
>> IT'S A GOOD TITLE FOR A
MOVIE.
>> WE NEED ONE GOOD POLICY.
>> EVERY DAY IS CHRISTMAS.
>> THAT WOULD NEVER WORK YOU
DUMB SON OF A BITCH.
>> LUCAS, OUT!
NOW!
>> SECURITY.
>> IT'S TIME FOR MOLLY'S SPEECH.
>> I'M HERE.
>> I'M'S UP, MOLLY.
AMERICA'S WATCHING.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> WELL, I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT
I MAY NOT HAVE A LOT OF GREED,
BUT WHAT I DO HAVE IS A REAL BIG
HEART.
OHIO, LET'S DO THIS THING.
>> MOLLY WENT ON TO BE THE WORST
ATTORNEY GENERAL OHIO EVERY SAW,
AND SHE W
>>> I WOULD LIKE TO THANK BLACK
STAR.
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK --
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK MAD LIB.
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK DARNELL
ROLLENS.
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK ICE-T.
I COULDN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH, AND
I GOT TO SAY REST IN PEACE TO
OUR BROTHER.
WE WILL FOREVER REMEMBER YOU,
AND MAY YOU REST IN POWER.
EVERYBODY, I'LL SEE YOU NEXT
WEEK.
GOOD NIGHT.