DRAFT
WADE
NO RIGHT
CRIME
TREATISE
FOETUS
SECOND
MISPRISION
MORAL CLARITY
YEARS AGO
LAWS 2022
WHAT IS THE MATTER?
LOOK
IT'S NOTHING, BUT
IT'S JUST, WHILST I WAS CLEANING
THE HOLE IN THE SIDE OF THE
CASTLE WHERE WE POOP
AND IT
FALLS INTO A SKY INTO A MOAT
FULL OF HUMAN FECES,
I STARTED
TO THINK ABOUT ABORTION.
OH, REALLY?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
WELL, DO YOU THINK WE OUGHT
TO MAKE A LAW AGAINST IT?
YOU MEAN LIKE THE LAW WE HAVE
AGAINST POINTY SHOES?
OR THE LAW THAT IF YOU HUNT A
DEER IN THE ROYAL FOREST, THEY
CUT OFF YOUR GENITALS?
EXACTLY.
SOMETHING FAIR AND REASONABLE
LIKE THOSE LAWS.
WE SHOULD MAKE A LAW THAT WILL
STAND THE TEST OF TIME
SO THAT
HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS OF YEARS
FROM NOW THEY'LL LOOK BACK AND SAY,
NO NEED TO UPDATE THIS AT
ALL, THEY NAILED IT BACK IN
1235.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE WE
SHOULDN'T BAN ABORTION IN ALL OF
ENGLAND.
WE COULD DECIDE IT ON AN FEIFDOM
BY FEIFDOM BASIS.
OH, GOOD IDEA.
AND THEN IF YOUR CONCUBINE NEEDS ONE,
YOU CAN SEND HER TO GET IT
IN OLD YORK CITY.
IF WE OUTLAW ABORTION, HOW
WOULD WE PUNISH THE MOTHER?
BECAUSE SHE'LL NEED TO BE PUNISHED.
SHE'LL BE SO HAPPY ABOUT HER
CRIME.
WE COULD
PUT HER ON A BOAT AND LET HER
SAIL OFF THE CLIFF AT THE EDGE
OF THE WORLD.
SHE WOULD OF COURSE, TUMBLE DOWN
WHERE THE FOUR TURTLES ARE
HOLDING UP THE EARTH
AND PERHAPS
ONE OF THEM WILL EAT HER.
ALMOST TOO OBVIOUS.
DRUNK
SEX
TOWN
BURNED
MAYBE
WHAT IF THE DONKEY GETS HER PREGNANT.
THEN WE'D LEGALLY HAVE TO
PROTECT HER FETUS.
IF THE HALF DONKEY IS A MAN, HE
COULD BECOME A KING.
THE PROPHECY!
LET'S BE CAREFUL.
THE WORST THING THAT COULD HAPPEN
IS IF SOMEONE LEAKS THE
CONVERSATION TO THE TOWN CRYER.
KNOCK KNOCK!
JUST KIDDING.
WE DON'T HAVE DOORS.
ANYHOO, I WAS OUTSIDE WATCHING
THE SHERIFF THROW LEFT-HANDED
CHILDREN INTO THE RIVER,
AND
OVER HERE YOU'S TALKING ABOUT
THE NEW LAW?
OH-OH, WOMAN HEAR IDEAS AND
MAKE ME THINK, WHY I HAVE THOSE?
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
SO I HAVE A COUPLE QUESTIONS.
CAREFUL, MARGARET, DON'T MAKE
US MAKE ANOTHER HOLE IN YOUR
SKULL SO YOUR BRAIN CAN BREATHE.
RIGHT.
I WAS JUST WONDERING SINCE I'M
ALMOST AT THE CHILDBEARING AGE OF 12,
SHOULD IT BE THE WOMAN'S
DECISION?
SINCE HAVING A BABY OFFERS A 50%
CHANCE OF DYING?
YES, BUT THAT'S WHY WE'RE
ALSO OFFERING MATERNITY LEAVE.
WHEN YOU'RE DONE WITH 20 YEARS
OF CONTINUOUS MATERNITY, YOU CAN
LEAVE.
SHOULDN'T WE MAKE EXCEPTIONS
IN CASE OF RAPE OR INCEST?
BUT THOSE ARE THE ONLY KINDS
OF SEX.
YEAH, I GUESS I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE SO
OBSESSED WITH THIS ISSUE.
WHAT ABOUT THE FACT THAT NO ONE
CAN READ AND WRITE?
AND EVERYONE'S DIYING IN A
PLAGUE?
YOU THINK JUST BECAUSE I HAVE
ACTIVE PLAGUE
THAT MEANS I NEED
TO WEAR A MASK?
IT'S MY BODY, MY CHOICE.
LIMIT
HAIRCUT
WHEN HAPPY
CHURCH
CHILDREN
BIRTH CONTROL
CAN'T PREGNANT
THERE'S ALWAYS PLAN B,
LETTING 1,000 BEES STING YOU FOREVER.
ALL
- I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE A
VOTE.
- AYE!
- AND THOSE OPPOSED?
- NAY.
PLAY
YOU EVER GET THE FEELING THIS
IS NOT GOING TO BE YOUR CENTURY?
ENOUGH
MY GOD, AN OGRE.
NO, JUST A WOMAN IN HER 30s.
WEIRD
I CAN SEE THE FUTURE.
AND WHETHER OR NOT, DEAR GIRL,
THESE BARBARIC RULES WILL BE OVERTURNED
BY SOMETHING CALLED PROGRESS.
AND THEN ABOUT 50 YEARS AFTER THE PROGRESS,
THEY'LL BE LIKE
HEY, MAYBE WE SHOULD UNDO THE PROGRESS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY MY VISIONS FROM
THAT TIME ARE CONFUSING.
IT SEEMS LIKE ALL OF THEM COME
FROM A HOLE FROM A PLACE CALLED FLORIDA.
WEIRD
AND YOU SHOULD WATCH THE TRIALS
OF JOHNNY DEPP AND AMBER HEARD.
I KNOW IT DOESN'T SOUND GREAT,
BUT NO MATTER HOW MANY CHOICES
THEY TAKE AWAY FROM WOMEN,
WE'VE
ALWAYS GOT THE CHOICE TO KEEP
FIGHTIN'!
THAT'S REALLY INSPIRING.
AFTER HEARING YOUR PERSPECTIVE,
I'VE SUDDENLY REALIZED,
YOU'RE A
WITCH, AND WE'RE GOING TO SET
YOU ON FIRE.
IT WOULDN'T BE THE FIRST
TIME.
AND LIVE, FROM NEW YORK,
IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- BENEDICT
CUMBERBATCH!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I REALLY AM THRILLED TO BE BACK
HOSTING "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
IT'S BEEN A REALLY FUN, GREAT WEEK.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST, BECAUSE
MOST OF THE SKETCH WRITERS
WERE
PITCHING ME AS DR. STRANGE.
I LIKE THE CHARACTER,
BUT I HAVE BEEN IN OTHER FILMS,
AND ONE SAID TO ME, LIKE WHAT?
AND I SAID, WELL, "THE POWER OF
THE DOG", FOR EXAMPLE.
AND HE SAID, "NOBODY SAW IT."
I SAID COME ON, MAN, I WAS
NOMINATED FOR AN OSCAR FOR THAT.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T WIN.
I WAS BEAT BY WILL SMITH.
NO, NOT PHYSICALLY.
NOT PHYSICALLY.
BUT I'M REALLY HONORED TO BE
HOSTING THE MOTHER'S DAY SNL SHOW.
AND OF COURSE I WANT TO WISH A
VERY SPECIAL HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY
TO MY MUM.
SHE'S ACTUALLY ON HOLIDAY IN
GREECE AT THE MOMENT.
AND SNL OFFERED TO FLY HER HERE
FIRST CLASS,
AND SHE SAID NO,
I'M ON A BEACH IN GREECE, ARE
YOU INSANE?
I LOVE YOU, MUM.
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER, WE USED
THESE WEIRD FUNNY NAMES WE USED TO CALL EACH OTHER,
AND I CALLED HER POOKIE,
AND SHE CALLED ME
BENEDICT CUMBERBATCH.
AND THEN I WENT TO A BOARDING
SCHOOL OUTSIDE OF LONDON,
YOU
MAY HAVE HEARD OF IT, CALLED HOGWARTS.
AMAZING
AND THERE ARE BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL DRAWING AND ILLUSTRATIONS.
I CAN'T DO THAT FOR HER,
OBVIOUSLY, BUT I THOUGHT I'D USE
A BIT OF THIS MONOLOGUE
TO THANK
HER FOR ALL THAT SHE'S DONE FOR
ME, SO.
HEY, MUM, IT'S ME, YOUR SON,
LITTLE BENEDICT.
THANK YOU FOR ALWAYS BEING THERE
FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, GROWING UP, EVERY
TIMELY A PROBLEM, HUNDRED A SOLUTION.
FOR INSTANCE, WHEN I LOST MY
FRONT TEETH I WAS WORRIED ABOUT BEING TEASED,
YOU SAID IT'S
OKAY.
JUST TRY TO SMILE WITHOUT
OPENING YOUR MOUTH.
GREAT ADVICE,
BUT IT ALSO EXPLAINS TO THIS DAY AND IN
EVERY RED CARPET PHOTOGRAPH
I'M SMILING LIKE THIS.
SERIOUSLY, THOUGH, MUM, YOU'VE
SHOWN ME LOVE EVERY STEP OF THE WAY,
I LOVE YOU, POOKIE.
AND SPEAKING OF MOTHERS, MY WIFE
SOPHIE IS IN THE AUDIENCE TONIGHT,
AND I'D LIKE TO WISH
HER A HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY, TOO.
HI, SOPHIE.
IT'S ME, YOUR HUSBAND.
LITTLE BENEDICT.
I'M CONSTANTLY IN AWE OF YOU.
YOU GAVE BIRTH TO OUR BOYS AND THAT IS A MIRACLE,
AND ACCORDING
TO YOU, I WAS OFF DRESSING UP AS
A WIZARD.
SORCERER
DON'T WORRY
BUT SERIOUSLY, SOPHIE, I HOPE
THAT WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT
YOU
REALIZE THAT IT EVENS OUT.
IF YOU THINK BEING A MUM IS HARD,
TRY DOING THIS.
YEAH, I JUST OPENED A PORTAL,
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY TO ALL THE
MOTHERS, ALL THE GRANDMOTHERS,
ALL THE CAREGIVERS, TO EVERYBODY
WHO DOES A WONDERFUL JOB DOING THAT,
TWO MOMS
SEEING ALL YOU'VE DONE FOR
ME AND OUR CHILDREN WARMS MY
HEART AND PUTS A SMILE ON MY FACE,
A SMILE LIKE THIS.
TONIGHT.
ARCADE FIRE IS HERE.
STICK AROUND WE'LL BE BACK
PRESENT!
COME ON, JUST OPEN IT.
OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT A MOTHER'S DAY.
YOU DID TOO MUCH.
WELL, YOU DESERVE IT.
AFTER ALL, YOU'RE OUR MOM. WELL.
I'M -- I'M YOUR WIFE.
THAT'S WHAT I MEANT.
WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
I DO, I DO.
OH, OKAY.
OH, YOU KNOW I LOVE THESE LITTLE
WOODEN SIGNS.
LET ME SEE.
OH, "LIFE DOESN'T COME WITH A
MANUAL, IT COMES WITH A MOTHER."
OH, WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
WE GOT IT AT HOME DEPOT.
THEY SELL ART THERE TOO.
THIS ONE'S FROM ME.
OH, THANK YOU, JOHN. OKAY.
"MOM TURNED UPSIDE DOWN SPELLS
'WOW.'"
TURN IT UPSIDE DOWN, IT
ACTUALLY WORKS.
OH, NOW I SEE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THESE ARE -- THESE ARE GREAT.
HERE MOM, THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE
THIS ONE.
OH, OKAY, LET'S SEE HERE.
THANK YOU.
"DEAR MOM, WE SUCKED YOUR TEATS
DRY, AND NOW YOU LOOK WEIRD IN A
BATHING SUIT.
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY."
GOOD ONE.
I GUESS I THOUGHT THAT --
THAT WOULD HAVE A FUN RHYME OR SOMETHING.
BUT THANK YOU.
YOU, KIND OF, LOOK LIKE THE
WOMAN IN THE SIGN.
YEAH, I'M -- I DON'T KNOW.
OH, HONEY, GIVE HER YOURS.
HERE YOU GO, MRS. M.
JUST WANTED TO SAY THANKS FOR
WELCOMING ME TO THE FAMILY.
OH, GOSH.
OF COURSE, DANNY.
HAVING A MOTHER-IN-LAW IS LIKE
HAVING CRABS.
AWW!
WHAT -- IS THERE MORE ON THE
BACK?
I FEEL LIKE THEY DIDN'T FINISH
THE JOKE.
WELL, YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE
THIS ONE. OKAY.
WELL -- OH, I LIKE THE COLOR,
HEY.
"WERE YOUR EARS RINGING?
I WAS IN THERAPY."
WELL, THAT ONE DOESN'T EVEN SAY
"HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY."
I PICKED THIS ONE ALL OUT BY
MYSELF.
IT'S A BIG ONE.
DEAR WIFE, NOW THAT THE KIDS ARE
GROWN, WE DON'T HAVE SEX
ANYMORE, BUT WE DO SOMETIMES,
AND THAT'S FUN.
WHAT?
THIS ONE ACTUALLY GOES
THROUGH IT.
DON'T READ INTO IT AS ME ASKING
FOR MORE SEX.
THE AMOUNT THAT WE ARE DOING IS
GOOD FOR ME, HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY.
OKAY, THESE ARE GETTING
REALLY SPECIFIC AND PERSONAL.
YEAH, THEY'RE GREAT, RIGHT?
I THINK YOU SPENT TOO MUCH.
OH, NO, THEY'RE LIKE $1.99.
OKAY, I WANT TO READ THIS ONE.
DEAR MOM, IF YOU DIED AND MOM
REMARRIED, I'M NOT FINISHED, IT
WOULD BE AN ADJUSTMENT, BUT I
FEEL LIKE WE WOULD GET TO A
PLACE WHERE WE WERE ABLE TO CALL
THE NEW WOMAN "MOM."
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY.
OKAY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND, YOU KNOW.
USUALLY THESE SIGNS SAY
SOMETHING LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"CAUTION, MOM NEEDS WINE", OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WE HAVE ONES LIKE THAT HERE.
OKAY, IT SAYS IT'S WINE
O'CLOCK.
I JUST LOVE WATCHING THE SUN RISE.
DOES THAT IMPLY I'M GETTING
DRUNK AT DAWN?
HERE'S A GOOD ONE.
OKAY.
I ONLY DRINK ON DAYS THAT END IN
"Y", AND DURING HOURS THAT HAVE
NUMBERS IN THEM.
HERE'S ANOTHER.
OH, MY.
OKAY.
I'M NOT DRUNK, IT'S JUST THE
WINE TALKING.
OH.
AS IN OH, MY GOD, A BOTTLE IS
TALKING TO ME, AND IT HAS LIPS
AND EVERYTHING.
DID I GET SO DRUNK I DID SHROOMS.
OH, YEAH, I DID.
I'M AN EFFING MESS.
I DON'T DRINK THAT MUCH!
YOU DO.
I THINK MOTHER'S DAY CAN BE
DONE NOW, THANK YOU EVERYONE.
MOM, WE'RE SORRY.
I GUESS WE GOT CARRIED AWAY.
IT SEEMED REALLY CLEVER IN
THE STORE.
DON'T BE MAD, THIS IS YOUR DAY.
THERE IS ONE LAST ONE IF YOU
WANT TO LOOK.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T, THOUGH. OKAY.
FINE, JUST GIVE IT TO ME.
MOM, FOR ALL THE TIMES WE
FORGOT TO THANK YOU FOR ALL THE
SPECIAL THINGS YOU DO THERE'S
JUST ONE THING WE NEED TO MENTION.
YOU'RE THE BEST, WE LOVE YOU.
OKAY, WELL THAT ONE IS PRETTY COOL.
THAT PART FLIPS DOWN.
SECRET FAMILY.
WHO WANTS MORE PANCAKES!
OH, WAIT, DO YOU?
WE'RE READY TO GET STARTED.
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE MORE
FLIRTATIOUS OF AN INTRO THAN WE
NEED, BUT IT'S ALL GOOD.
HI, GANG.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT TO THIS
FOCUS GROUP.
WE ARE FROM BLUE BUNNY ICE
CREAM AND WE'VE GOT SOME NEW
PRODUCTS THAT WE'D LOVE YOUR
FEEDBACK ON.
LIKE BOMB POPS?
NO, NO SIR, NO BOMB POPS TODAY.
I LOVE BOMB POPS.
OKAY, AGAIN, NO B-POPS BUT I
DO THINK YOU'LL FIND OUR OTHER
TREATS, THE ICE CREAM OF THE
CROP.
NO OFFENSE BUT I SIGNED UP TO
TRY ICE CREAM, NOT TO HEAR JOKES
ABOUT IT.
CAN WE GET TO THE TASTING?
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
HEY.
THOSE TWO ARE JUST TRYING TO DO
THEIR JOB.
THEY GOTTA TELL A JOKE OR TWO,
LET THEM.
THIS IS THEIR DANCE, NOT YOURS.
DO YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
NO, MA'AM.
JUST HERE TO TRY SOME ICE CREAM,
GET MY CHECK, AND BE ON MY WAY.
SAME HERE.
CAME IN A STRANGER, I'LL LEAVE
ONE AS WELL.
OKAY, FUN.
THE FIRST FLAVOR WE'RE GOING TO
TRY TODAY IS PEANUT BRITTLE PIE
ICE CREAM.
SO GIVE THOSE A TRY.
JACOB, HOW ABOUT YOU GO FIRST?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, WOW, IT'S DELICIOUS.
YOU GREAT?
WHAT ABOUT YOU, LISA?
IT'S A LITTLE WET.
BUT YUMMY. NOTED.
BOBBI, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS TASTES
LIKE?
YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU WAS A KID,
YOU'D BE PLAYING OUT IN ALL THE
DIRTY BUCKETS LIKE A HOG?
AND PAPPY'D CALL YOU IN TO WASH
UP BECAUSE NANA SPENT THE LAST
THREE HOURS CHURNING?
THAT WOMAN WOULD CHURN TILL SHE
WHIPPED.
THE BLOOD FROM HER PALMS, LEGS,
AND THE CARAMEL RIBBONS IN THE
ICE CREAM.
THIS IS THAT.
THIS TASTES LIKE THAT.
OH, THANK YOU.
VERY DESCRIPTIVE.
YOU'RE TRYING TO MAKE A GROWN
WEAK, MISS?
NO, I'M JUST TRYING TO EAT
ICE CREAM, SIR.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, MUTTON.
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF THE PEANUT
BRITTLE PIE?
I'LL SAY THIS.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU'D BE DOWN BY
THE POND ALL DAY, HANDS CUPPED
TRYING TO CATCH ONE STUPID
LITTLE TADPOLE?
IT WOULD MEAN NOTHING TODAY, BUT
BACK THEN, HELL, THAT TAD WAS
KING CRAB.
AND THEN SCOOTER'S MAMA, THE
ONE WITH THE PRETTY TEETH AND
EYES LIKE BUTTER, WHO'D INVITE
YOU INSIDE FOR A BOWL OF ROCKY
ROAD.
DIDN'T MATTER THE FLAVOR, THOUGH.
IT WAS JUST THAT A BEAUTIFUL,
MATURE WOMAN HAD OPENED HER DOOR
TO YOU.
FARMER'S WIFE.
BOSOM HEAVY.
THIS IS THAT.
THIS TASTES LIKE THAT. OKAY.
TASTES LIKE SCOOTER'S MAMA.
WRITING THAT DOWN.
YOU'VE SEEN THINGS, HAVEN'T
YOU?
NAH.
ONLY ICE CREAM, MISS.
HEY, MAN.
I JUST TASTE ICE CREAM.
AM I DOING THIS WRONG?
NO.
GUYS, WE'RE NOT REALLY LOOKING
TO TASTE MEMORIES OF THE DUST
BOWL HERE.
YOUR ICE CREAM CARRIES A
WEIGHT TO IT, SIR.
SHE'S RIGHT.
I CAN TASTE GENERATIONS OF WOMEN
IN IT. YEAH.
WILL NOT BE WRITING THAT DOWN.
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE.
GALACTIC MINT FROST.
WHY DON'T YOU ALL GIVE THAT ONE
A LITTLE TASTE. YEAH.
BOBBI, YOU TASTING THAT FRESH
MINT IN THERE?
NO.
TASTES MORE LIKE WIND.
LIKE THE WIND WHEN YOU HAVEN'T
QUITE REACHED 5 FEET TALL.
WIND BACK THEN WOULD KNOCK YOU
RIGHT INTO YOUR NEIGHBOR.
THE ONE THAT HAD LOST HIS WIFE
AND DAUGHTER IN THE HOSPITAL FIRE.
AND IN YOUR EYES, HE SAW THEM
BOTH.
SO YOU'D SIT WITH HIM ON THE
PORCH WATCHING THE WORLD GO BY.
JUST AS THE SUN WENT DOWN, HE'D
HAND YOU A BOWL OF CREAM.
JUST VANILLA, THOUGH.
HE KEPT IT SIMPLE SINCE THE
GIRLS HAD DIED.
THIS IS THAT.
THIS TASTES LIKE THAT.
GOT IT.
SO IT TASTES LIKE A WIDOWER IN
PAIN.
WHO HURT YOU?
WHY, YOU LOOKING TO SAVE
SOMEONE TONIGHT?
MAYBE.
EAT YOUR ICE CREAM.
I'M SORRY, WHAT IS HAPPENING?
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT I
TASTE?
YES, BUT IN LIKE SIX WORDS
THIS TIME. FINE.
REMEMBER THE FOURTH OF JULY --
OKAY, PLEASE STOP.
THE AIR WAS SO THICK WITH
SMOKE, YOU COULD BARELY FIND
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER'S HAND.
DADDY LET YOU BOTH STAY OUT LATE
AS LONG AS YOU KEPT YOUR LITTLE
BROTHER CLOSE.
NEVER DID FIND HIM.
WALKED HOME ALONE, WENT STRAIGHT
TO THE ICEBOX, SCOOPED
OUT SOME CHOC CHIP, NOTHING TOO
FANCY ON THE NIGHT YOUR BROTHER DISAPPEARED.
THIS IS THAT.
THIS TASTES LIKE THAT.
DAMMIT, I CAN'T TAKE YOUR
PAIN AWAY BUT I CAN GIVE IT A
BED TO REST IN.
LET ME NAP WITH YOUR HURT.
YOU WANT TO NAP WITH MY HURT?
I SAID AS MUCH.
LET ME NAP WITH YOUR HURT!
DON'T SAY SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, YOU MIGHT JUST END UP
TAKING A NAP WITH MY HURT.
ALL RIGHT!
WELL, THANKS FOR COMING OUT, EVERYBODY.
JUST LIKE YOU
NO PHONE.
YOU'RE GROUNDED, REMEMBER?
OH, MY GOD, I DIDN'T EVEN DO
ANYTHING THAT BAD, MOM.
REALLY?
TAYLOR, YOU CAME HOME DRUNK.
YOU'RE 17 YEARS OLD.
OH, COME ON, LIKE YOU NEVER
DRANK WHEN YOU WERE MY AGE?
IN HIGH SCHOOL, NO.
NOT EVEN A SIP. NEVER.
ALCOHOL WAS NOT EVEN ON MY
RADAR AT YOUR AGE.
YO, IT'S NOT A PARTY UNTIL
BUFFY SANDY PUKES!
I'M OKAY!
* HE DRINKS A WHISKEY DRINK
HE DRINKS A LAGER DRINK *
WELL, SORRY I'M NOT JUST LIKE
YOU, MOM.
SORRY I'M NOT PERFECT.
I WASN'T PERFECT, TAYLOR.
I MADE MISTAKES.
I DID THINGS I REGRET.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE NOT
VIRGINS ANYMORE.
I DID A COUPLE THINGS I REGRET.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE NOT
VIRGINS ANYMORE.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
NAME ONE MISTAKE YOU MADE.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
FINE, HERE'S ONE.
I FAILED A TEST ONCE.
IT WAS A BIG TEST.
I'M SORRY!
THE POINT IS, I NEVER DID
ANYTHING SO STUPID
IT FOLLOWED
ME THROUGH MY WHOLE LIFE.
- EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT IN HERE?
- YEAH, GRANDMA, WE'RE FINE.
MOM, YOU WANT TO KEEP TELLING ME
HOW MUCH OF A DUMBASS I AM?
WHAT?
TAYLOR!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THE WAY SHE
SPEAKS TO ME?
I WOULD NEVER HAVE SPOKEN TO
YOUR GRANDMA BY WAY.
SUCK MY -- YOU OLD --!
YEAH, WE ALWAYS GOT ALONG
PRETTY WELL.
SANDY, IF I CATCH YOU SMOKING
CIGARETTES AGAIN,
I WILL SHAVE
YOUR --
HEAD!
TAYLOR, YOUR MOM TOLD ME IT
GOT A LITTLE WILD AT A PARTY?
NOW, I'M ALL FOR HAVING FUN, BUT
CALL ME OLD-FASHIONED,
I THINK
THERE IS A CERTAIN WAY THAT A
YOUNG LADY OUGHT TO BEHAVE.
DAVID BOWIE!
I LOVE YOU, DAVID!
TAKE MY PANTIES!
DAVID!
KNOW
DAVID
OKAY, I'LL SAY IT THEN.
YOU TOLD GRANDMA?
OF COURSE I DID, HONEY.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- WHAT ARE WE WORRIED ABOUT?
- NOTHING, I'M FINE.
I WENT TO ONE PARTY.
MEANWHILE, MOM'S ACTING LIKE SHE
NEVER HAD FUN IN HER LIFE.
WELL, WHEN I MET YOUR MA IN
COLLEGE, SHE CERTAINLY KNEW HOW
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- HEY.
- BUT SHE ALWAYS KEPT IT IN CONTROL.
- HOW MANY PILLS DID YOU TAKE?
- THREE.
- WHAT IS THE PROBLEM?
- YOU BLEW MY ROOMMATE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS YOU.
IF SHE'S HARD ON YOU, IT'S
ONLY 'CAUSE SHE LOVES YOU SO
MUCH.
I KNOW.
I'M JUST TRYING TO LOOK OUT
FOR YOU.
COME HERE.
GIVE ME A HUG.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE STILL GROUNDED.
BUT YOU CAN HAVE YOUR PHONE BACK.
TEXT MESSAGE FROM RYAN,
"PARENTS GONE, COME OVER FOR
EGGPLANT EMOJI."
NEVER MIND.
NO, I KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS. YEAH.
PERFECT
MOM
HAPPY
THAN A BLISTER BUG IN A PEPPER PATCH.
DON'T THE WARDEN KNOW IT.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS, BACK TO WORK NOW.
THESE ROCKS AIN'T GONNA BREAK
THEMSELVES.
AND GET HAPPY, I WANT TO SEE
SOME SMILES.
♪ I WAS BORN ON A FARM
ON A MOONLESS NIGHT
MAMA NEVER TAUGHT ME WRONG
FROM RIGHT *
* NOW I'M DOING TIME
IN GEORGIA
DOING TIME IN GEORGIA
LONG TIME IN GEORGIA *
* LONG TIME IN GEORGIA
HAPPY AS CLAIMS
IS A GOOD LORD SET ME FREE
LORD SET ME FREE YEAH ♪
♪ NOW THE GOOD BOOK SAID
BE A RIGHTEOUS MAN
THE DEVIL PULLED ME DOWN
AND AWAY WE RAN *
* SO THEY LOCKED ME
UP IN TOWN
LOCKED ME UP IN TOWN
WORKING FOR THE COUNTY *
* WORKING FOR THE COUNTY I'LL BE
IN CHAINS TILL THE GOOD LORD
SETS ME FREE ♪
TAKE IT, TOMMY!
* IF I SEE SOMETHING BAD
YOU KNOW I'M GONNA TELL
THAT'S WHY THEY PUT ME IN A
BETTER PRISON CELL, BECAUSE I
SNITCHED TO THE WARDEN ♪
♪ I'M SNITCHING TO THE WARDEN
SNITCHING TO THE WARDEN
♪ SNITCHING TO THE WARDEN *
OH LORD PRISON'S
NOT SO BAD ♪
WAIT, TOM.
DID YOU JUST SAY YOU WERE
SNITCHING TO THE WARDEN?
YEP, THAT'S THE WAY THE OLD
PRISON SONG GOES.
I AIN'T NEVER HEARD NO PRISON
SONG ABOUT NO SNITCHING.
YOU GETTING SPECIAL
TREATMENT, TOM?
NAH, JUST SINGING TO PASS THE TIME.
WHOO-WEE, IT'S HOT.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT FANCY
DRINK?
YOU FELLAS DIDN'T GET ONE?
DEFINITELY NOT.
WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, HELL, THEY CAUGHT LENNY!
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO WE FOUND HIDING IN THE
STORM DRAIN DOWN BY THE HIGHWAY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE, HOW DID YOU
FIND ME?
LET'S JUST SAY A LITTLE
BIRDIE TOLD US YOUR PLAN.
ON AN UNRELATED NOTE, TOM, HERE
IS A CHERRY PIE.
CHERRY PIE?
MMM-MMM!
AND AS FOR YOU, LENNY?
YOU KNOW WHAT WE DO WITH
ESCAPEES.
PUT THEM IN THE BOX!
NO, NO.
NOT THE BOX!
YOU ANIMALS!
YOU LOUSY ANIMALS!
HE'S A GOOD MAN, DON'T PUT
HIM IN THE BOX!
OR MAYBE JUST FOR A COUPLE OF
DAYS, YOU GUYS KNOW BEST.
ALL RIGHT, SHOW'S OVER.
NOW UNLESS YOU GOT A PIE IN YOUR
HAND, GET BACK TO WORK!
* WHEN I DREAM AT NIGHT
THAT'S THE ONLY TIME
I'M FREE
I WAKE UP EVERY MORNING *
* IN A PENITENTIARY
NOW I'M GOING
TO THE QUARRY
* DOING TEN TO 20 ♪
♪ WORKING FOR THE COUNTY
WORKING FOR THE COUNTY
I'LL BE IN CHAINS
TILL THE GOOD LORD *
* SETS ME FREE
LORD SET ME FREE
IF YOU TELL ME YOUR SECRETS
I'LL PASS THEM ALONG *
* YOU'LL BE IN THE BOX
WHILE I'M SINGING THIS SONG
I MADE A DEAL
WITH THE WARDEN ♪
♪ DEAL WITH THE WARDEN
I'LL TELL HIM
ALL YOUR SECRETS
TELL HIM ALL YOUR SECRETS *
* EVERY TIME I SNITCH
THEY BRING ME
A BIG CHERRY PIE *
**
SHH, HERE COMES THE WARDEN'S
WIFE!
MA'AM.
WHY, IF IT ISN'T MY LOVELY
WIFE, MARY.
WHAT YOU DOING HERE, WOMAN?
OH, I WAS JUST PASSING BY ON
MY WAY INTO TOWN.
FIGURED I'D TAKE A GANDER AT ALL
THESE BAD, BAD BOYS.
THIS ONE LOOKS ESPECIALLY NAUGHTY.
ARE YOU A NAUGHTY BOY?
YES, MA'AM.
VERY NAUGHTY, MA'AM.
LOOKS LIKE YOU MISSED A BIT
OF CHERRY PIE.
OH, THANK YOU KINDLY.
IT'S NOT LIKE ME TO WASTE A GOOD
BIT OF CHERRY PIE.
WHAT THE HELL?
ALL RIGHT, MARY.
I KNOW YOU GOT SOME SHOPPING TO DO.
BYE, BOYS.
SEE YOU LATER.
THAT'S ENOUGH YAPPING FOR ONE DAY.
BACK TO WORK, ALL OF YOU.
* WELL I CAN'T COMPLAIN
ABOUT MY LIFE
I GET TO SLEEP WITH
THE WARDEN'S WIFE *
* I'M SLEEPING WITH
THE WARDEN'S WIFE
SLEEPING WITH THE
WARDEN'S WIFE ♪
♪ SLEEPING WITH HIS
PRETTY WIFE
SLEEPING WITH HIS
PRETTY WIFE *
* WATCHES FROM THE CLOSET
SMILING IN THE DARK ♪
WARDEN, I DO BELIEVE TOM IS
SLEEPING WITH YOUR WIFE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I CAN'T PLEASE HER MYSELF.
BEST TO LET HER BE HAPPY.
* WAY TO BE HAPPY
WAY TO BE HAPPY
VERY VERY HAPPY
VERY VERY HAPPY ♪
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ARCADE
FIRE!
EDDIE, I LOVE YOU.
**
* LOOKOUT KID
TRUST YOUR HEART
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PLAY THE
PART THEY WROTE FOR YOU ♪
♪ JUST BE TRUE
THERE ARE THINGS
THAT YOU COULD DO ♪
♪ THAT NO ONE ELSE
ON EARTH COULD EVER DO
BUT I CAN'T TEACH YOU
I CAN'T TEACH IT TO YOU *
* LOOKOUT KID
TRUST YOUR MIND
BUT YOU CAN'T
TRUST IT EVERY TIME *
* YOU KNOW IT
PLAYS TRICKS ON YOU
AND IT DON'T GIVE A DAMN *
* IF YOU ARE HAPPY
OR YOU'RE SAD
BUT IF YOU'VE LOST IT
DON'T FEEL BAD ♪
M 'CAUSE IT'S ALL RIGHT
TO BE SAD ♪
♪
TRUST YOUR BODY
YOU CAN DANCE
AND YOU CAN SHAKE ♪
♪ THINGS WILL BREAK
YOU MAKE MISTAKES
YOU LOSE YOUR FRIENDS
AGAIN AND AGAIN *
* 'CAUSE NOTHING
IS EVER PERFECT
NO ONE'S PERFECT *
* LET ME SAY IT AGAIN
NO ONE'S PERFECT
RIGHT *
* A LIFETIME
OF SKINNED KNEES
AND HEARTBREAK
COMES SO EASY *
* BUT A LIFE WITHOUT PAIN
WOULD BE BORING
AND IF YOU FEEL IT
IT'S FINE ♪
♪ I GIVE YOU EVERYTHING
THAT'S MINE
I GIVE YOU MY HEART
AND MY PRECIOUS TIME *
♪
♪ LOOKOUT KID
TRUST YOUR SOUL
IT AIN'T HARD
TO ROCK N' ROLL *
* YOU KNOW HOW
TO MOVE YOUR HIPS
AND YOU KNOW GOD
IS COOL WITH IT *
* BUT SOME PEOPLE WANT
THE ROCK WITHOUT THE ROLL
BUT WE ALL KNOW THERE'S
NO GOD WITHOUT SOUL ♪
♪ RIGHT
A LIFETIME OF SKINNED KNEES
AND HEARTBREAK COMES
SO EASILY *
* BUT A LIFE WITHOUT YOU
WOULD BE BORING
FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME *
* AND IF YOU FEEL IT
IT'S FINE
I GIVE YOU EVERYTHING
THAT'S MINE *
* I GIVE YOU MY HEART
AND MY PRECIOUS TIME
* PRECIOUS TIME *
* GIVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
I GIVE YOU MY HEART
AND MY PRECIOUS TIME ♪
♪ UNCONDITIONAL
IT'S UNCONDITIONAL
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO *
* IT'S UNCONDITIONAL
IT'S UNCONDITIONAL
UNCONDITIONAL
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO *
* IT'S UNCONDITIONAL
IT'S UNCONDITIONAL *
♪
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
GOOD EVENING. HELLO.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> WELL, GUYS, TOMORROW IS
MOTHER'S DAY.
WHETHER YOU WANTED TO BE ONE OR NOT.
ROE WADE
IN AN UNPRECEDENTED MOVE THAT
COULD CAUSE LASTING DAMAGE TO THE SUPREME COURT,
A DRAFT
OPINION WAS LEAKED WHICH
INDICATES THAT THEY INTEND TO
OVERTURN ROE V. WADE.
SO THE COURT IS USUALLY CAREFUL
BUT THEY SLIPPED UP JUST THIS
ONCE, NOW THEY'VE GOT TO LIVE
WITH IT FOREVER.
THAT WAS REALLY UNFAIR.
THE OPINION WAS WRITTEN BY
JUSTICE SAMUEL ALITO,
AND HE
BASES HIS ARGUMENT ON LAWS FROM
THE 1600s.
SO IT'S AN OUTDATED OPINION FROM
AN ANGRY 70-YEAR-OLD?
THIS SHOULDN'T BE A SUPREME
COURT DECISION, IT SHOULD JUST
BE A FACEBOOK POST.
THE OPINION ALSO SEEMS LIKE IT
WAS WRITTEN IN A WEIRD
CONSERVATIVE BUBBLE.
HERE'S HOW YOU KNOW.
HE QUOTES HIS OWN COLLEAGUE,
BRETT KAVANAUGH SIX TIMES,
ONE
FOR EACH BEER IN THE PACK.
HE EVEN CITES KAVANAUGH ON CIVIL RIGHTS,
WHICH IS LIKE CITING
AMBER HEARD ON HOW TO MAKE A BED.
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS SAID
THE LEAK WAS THE WORK OF "ONE
BAD APPLE."
ONE BAD APPLE IS ALSO A LEGAL
ARGUMENT CITED IN ALITO'S
OPINION.
AS A MAN THERE'S NO WAY I CAN
UNDERSTAND THE FULL IMPACT OF
THIS ISSUE.
BUT I ASKED A BUNCH OF WOMEN
AROUND THE OFFICE WHAT THEIR
PERSONAL EXPERIENCE WAS WITH
ABORTION.
AND I GOTTA ADMIT, I LEARNED A
LOT FROM THE HR MEETING THEY
MADE ME GO TO AFTER.
I DO KNOW THIS RULING WILL HAVE
A DISPROPORTIONATE EFFECT ON
POOR PEOPLE.
MOST AMERICANS DON'T HAVE ACCESS
TO THE SAME RESOURCES THAT EVEN
I DO.
THE AVERAGE PERSON CAN'T JUST
TEXT LORNE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND SAY, "YO, IT HAPPENED
AGAIN."
ARE SO AGAINST THIS.
I MEAN, MAYBE DON'T THINK OF IT
AS AN ABORTION,
THINK OF IT AS A
PATRIOT STORMING THE UTERUS
TO
OVERTURN THE RESULTS OF A PREGNANCY.
FORMER NEW YORK CITY MAYOR
AND CURRENT RUMPLE STILT SKIN
RUDY GIULIANI
CANCELED AN
LAST MINUTE FRIDAY
DENY RECORD THE INTERVIEW
VCR
REPORTS
CANCER SURGERY.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SAY THIS,
BUT GOOD LUCK, CANCER
HERE WITH US IS AMY CONEY BARRETT.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
I'M JAZZED AND JUICED.
I WOULD IMAGINE YOU'RE HAPPY
WITH THE RULING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WOULD MAKE
YOU THINK THAT.
I LISTENED TO THE CASE AND ASKED
ALL MY QUESTIONS.
YOU WERE ASKING ABOUT SAFE
HAVEN LAWS WHERE CAN YOU LEGALLY
LEAVE A BABY AT A FIRE STATION,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU NEED ABORTION, BECAUSE YOU
CAN LEAVE A BABY ANYWHERE IN THE
UNITED STATES.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
JUST POP IT.
JUST DO THE NINE AND PLUS.
JUST DOT NINE AND WHAT?
DO YOUR NINE, LEAVE IT ON THE
SIDEWALK, WRAP IT UP IN, LIKE A
LITTLE MOSES, PUT IT IN A
BASKET, DO YOUR NINE.
IT'S SIMPLE.
YOU ARE AN AMURDERER IF YOU HAVE
AN ABORTION, BUT ARE YOU NOT A
MURDERER IF YOU PUT A BABY IN A
MAILBOX.
NOT EVERYONE IS GOOD WITH THAT.
GIVE IT TO A STORK AND A
STORK WILL GIVE IT TO LESBIAN.
I HAVE SEVEN CHILDREN AND A JOB.
AND I MAKE IT WORK.
WHY EVERY SINGLE OTHER WOMAN
CAN'T GET IT DONE IS BEYOND ME.
ARE YOU ALSO SUGGESTS WE
DON'T NEED ABORTION BECAUSE
THERES NO LONGER THE SAME SIGMA
AGAINST UNWED MOTHERS. EXACTLY.
YOU SEE A GIRL WHO'S PREGNANT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO STONE HER ANYMORE.
IF YOU GET PREGNANT AND YOU'RE
NOT MARRIED, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GO TO A CONVENT ANYMORE.
THAT'S YOUR NINE.
SAFELY ENDING AN EARLY PREGNANCY
OR GIVE BIRTH TO A BABY YOU CAN
NEVER SEE AGAIN BECAUSE YOU PUT
IT ON A FERRIS WHEEL.
THESE LESBIANS WILL BE HAVING A
CRAP LOAD OF BABIES COMING THEIR
WAY.
THEY SHOULD BE KISSING ME.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
FORCE YOUR CONSERVATIVE VIEWS ON
THE COUNTRY.
THE COURT IS NOT PARTISAN.
OUR SPOUSES ON THE OTHER HAND
ARE EFFING CRAZY.
SPEAK OF, CLARENCE THOMAS' WIFE
GINNI IS IN LOVE WITH ME, OKAY,
LOVE, YOU WANT A BABE SNEE.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU'D
LIKE TO SAY?
ARBY'S, WE HAVE THE BABIES.
DO YOUR NINE!
A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT HALF
AMERICANS IDENTIFY AS AFRO LATINOS.
THAT'S WHAT BRUNO MARS CALLS HIS COSTUMES.
NEW YORK CITY HAS LAUNCHED A
NEW CAMPAIGN TO STOP SPEEDING IN
THE CITY WITH A SERIES OF SIGNS
DESIGNED TO SCARE DRIVERS.
THE SIGNS READ SIMPLY "ENTERING
NEW JERSEY."
ANNOUNCED THAT DOLLY PARTON
WOULD BE INDUCTED THIS YEAR
ALONG WITH EMINEM, AND CARLY
SIMON, WHICH BEGS THE QUESTION,
WHAT IS ROCK 'N ROLL?
A BAT USED BY JACKIE ROBINSON
WAS SOLD FOR $1 MILLION.
IT IS CONSIDERED SO VALUABLE
BECAUSE HE USED IT IN THE GAME
BUT ALSO TO GET BACK TO LIIS CAR SAFELY.
QANTAS HAS ANNOUNCE PLANS FOR
NEW FLIGHT.
SPIRIT AIRLINES ALSO ANNOUNCED A
NEW FLIGHT FROM NEW YORK TO
PHILADELPHIA THAT WILL ALSO TAKE
19 HOURS.
ARCHAEOLOGISTS HAVE
DISCOVERED A DRAWING IN A CAVE
IN ALABAMA.
AND GUYS, THEY'RE BAD.
A BRITISH LAWMAKER RESIGNED
AFTER ADMITTING HE WATCHED PORN
ON HIS PHONE IN THE CHAMBERS OF
PARLIAMENT, WHICH SEEMS PRETTY
LAME WHEN OUR CONGRESS ALLOWS
FULL PENETRATION.
A COLLEAGUE KNEW HE WAS WATCHING
PORN WHEN THE COUNT PASSED BY
650 YAYS TO ONE 650 OH, MY GOD
YAY.
AND CAN YOU IMAGINE THE SIZE
OF THE CHILD WHO MINED THIS
DIAMOND?
>>> A WOMAN AT A BACHELORETTE
PARTY WAS ATTACKED WHILE WEARING
AN INFLATABLE PENIS COSTUME.
SHE SAYS SHE'S STILL THROBBING
AND HER HEAD FEELS LIKE IT'S
READY TO EXPLODE.
THE WORLD, THE RECORD FOR THE
WORLD'S OLDEST DOG HAS BEEN
BROKEN BY A CHIHUAHUA NAMED
TIMOTHEE CHALAMET.
>>For "Weekend Update," I'm
Colin Jost.
And I'm Michael Che.
Good night!
>>> WE NOW RETURN TO LANDSDOWNE HOUSE.
AMELIA, KENNETH.
>>>.
ATTENTION, WHAT A MARVELOUS SURPRISE.
MY BROTHER, YOU'RE HERE.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE AWAY IN
CORNWALL?
I'VE LEFT CORNWALL.
I HAVE SOMETHING I MUST TELL YOU.
LET'S HEAR IT OVER TEA.
HENRY, SEND FOR TEA, PLEASE.
YES, MUM.
YOU SAY THE GREAT WAR HAS
COME TO ENGLAND, AND ALL OF US
MUST FIGHT?
NO, I FELT DUTY BOUND TO DO
MY BEST.
NO, CHRISTIAN, NO.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
YOU KNOW YOUR SISTER HAS
HEALTH SPELLS.
AMELIA.
TO THE FAINTING COUCH.
I'VE MADE A HE DO
SIGNIFICANCE.
I'M OFF TO WAR.
SHE'S MISSED THE COUCH.
HENRY, FETCH THE ELIXIRS.
I'M SORRY, IT SEEMS I'VE HAD
A TINY SPELL.
NOT A TINY ONE, MY DEAR.
OH, CHRISTIAN, IT'S YOU.
I JUST HAD THE MOST FRIGHTFUL
DREAM THAT WERE YOU GOING TO WAR.
THAT IS NO DREAM, AMELIA,
IT'S TRUE.
I'M JOINING THE ARMIES ON THE FRONTLINE.
FRONTLINE, OH, NO.
AMELIA, PLEASE, COME TO THE COUCH.
I'M SORRY, SHE MUSS HEAR THE TRUTH.
I MUST SEEK GLORY ON THE
BATTLEFIELD.
ELIXIRS, NOW.
SHE'S MISSED THE COUCH AGAIN.
AGAIN?
HOW?
WE NEED TO STEADY HER NERVES.
HENRY, DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
DON'T WORRY, SIR, I'M FINE.
OH, HEAVENS, I'VE HAD A
SPELL.
DON'T CONCERN YOURSELF, MY DEAR.
YOU CAN STILL CHANGE YOUR MIND.
NO, AMELIA, THE DIE IS CAST.
YOU SEE, I'VE ALREADY ENLISTED?
WHAT, OH.
THIS WAY, MY DEAR.
OOH, AH.
SHE IS PUTTING ON QUITE THE
SHOW, ISN'T SHE?
SHE COULD DIE.
IT MUST RUN ITS COURSE.
STEADY, GIRL, STEADY, STEADY.
CALM NOW.
SHE JUST STEPPED AND ROLLED
RIGHT OVER THE COUCH.
YOUR SHERRY, MA'AM.
THANK YOU, HENRY.
I THINK IT'S PASSED.
YES, I'M FINE. SPLENDID.
LET'S HAVE SOUP.
PIPING HOT.
PIPING HOT SOUP!
YES, SIR.
NOW, MY DEAR, ARE YOU ALL
RIGHT?
OH, YES, I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
I JUST SEEM TO HAVE A TINY CUT
ON MY HANDS.
IS THAT BLOOD?
OH!
OH, TO THE COUCH, FATHER!
FATHER!
TO THE COUCH, PLEASE!
OH!
SOUP IS READY, SIR.
OH, OH. STEADY.
OH, OH --
OH, NO, SIR. PLEASE.
NO!
POPPYCOCK.
OH, MY GOD.
TERRIBLY SORRY.
I SEE.
THE FITS RUNS IN THE FAMILY, MY DEAR.
IT'S TO DO WITH THAT TINY BOUT
OF INBREEDING WE HAD FOR ABOUT
THE PAST 500 YEARS.
AH.
SO -- SO I COULD HAVE THESE
SPELLS?
WELL, THEN, PERHAPS I SHOULD NOT
GO TO WAR.
OH, MARVELOUS, DARLING.
THIS CALLS FOR A CELEBRATION. HENRY.
SIT ON THE TOILET?
THERE'S ONLY ONE ACCEPTABLE
WAY TO SIT ON THE TOILET.
- ONE WAY.
-ONE MUST SIT UPRIGHT.
NO SLOUCHING!
BACK STRAIGHT.
FEET SHOULD BE PLANTED FIRMLY
ON THE FLOOR.
AND WHAT SHOULD SITTING ON
THE TOILET NEVER BE?
- COMFORTABLE OR RELAXING.
- CORRECT.
THAT IS THE NUMBER ONE RULE.
AND RULES ARE MEANT TO BE.
BROKEN!
WHO ARE YOU?
THE NEXT BIG THING.
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?
CHANGING EVERYTHING.
INTRODUCING THE RELINE, FROM KOEHLER,
THE FIRST RECLINING TANK,
BRINGING LAID-BACK COMFORT
INTO THE BATHROOM FOR THE FIRST TIME.
CLASS DISMISSED.
THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY TO SIT
ON THE TOILET.
FROM KOHLER
KOEHLER, NUMBER ONE AND
ALL RIGHT, I THINK THE SHOW
IS STARTING.
HA HA HA!
HEY, EVERYBODY!
LOOK, I KNOW YOU CAME TO SEE
CHUCK E. AND HIS PALS.
BUT WE'RE HAVING SOME TECHNICAL
PROBLEMS AND CHUCKY AND THE
PIZZA TIME BAND ARE NOT RUNNING
RIGHT NOW.
OH, THAT'S WHY WE CAME.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
BUT THE SHOW MUST -- GO ON,
GREAT NEWS, I REACHED OUT TO MY
FAVORITE BAND FROM 1983, AND
THEY WERE ABLE TO HELP US OUT.
PLEASE WELCOME, REFLECTION
DENIED.
AMONGST THE BASIL AND THE
POMODORO DID I EXPERIENCE MY
REFEREE HERE AT CHUCK E. CHEESE.
EXISTING IN THE LITTLE SPACE
BETWEEN THE MALL AND THE
HIGHWAY.
BEFORE THE BIG BANG, THERE WAS PIZZA.
PIZZA!
GREETINGS CHILDREN AND
CHILDREN OF THE MIND.
SO WE ARE REFLECTION DENIED.
BUT TODAY, I'M THE EPONYMOUS
RODENT CHARLES ENTERTAINMENT
CHEESE.
AND I -- JOIN US ON THE SOUND
SCAPE OF PIZZA.
GAMES.
AND SOULFUL LONGING.
* I REACHED
SELF-CONCEPT
AT THE PIZZA *
I FORGOT MY TASTE
AND SMELL *
* KEEP FALLING *
* YOU READ MY MIND
SO WELL *
* OH, PIZZA PIE *
* IN THE PIZZA SKY ♪
DELIVER ME
DELIVER PLEASE *
THIS IS FUN, RIGHT, BUD?
IS THIS FOR KIDS?
I THINK IT'S FOR HIM.
* I CRIED ALONE
IN THE BALL PIT
OH FATHER
WHERE ARE YOU ♪
♪ MR. PIBB
OUT OF DR PEPPER
WHY DO THEY HAVE BOTH ♪
♪ OH PIZZA PIE
IN THE PIZZA SKY
DELIVER ME
DELIVER ME *
IF YOU'D LIKE TO BOOK US FOR
FUTURE GIGS OR TIP US IN DIPPING
DOTS PLEASE SEE JULIE.
WHO IS JULIE?
I'M GUESSING SHE IS.
♪ TOKENS ARE TICKETS
TICKETS ARE PRIZES
PARENTS PAYING
FOR DREAMS *
* WHETHER AN OLD YO-YO
OR iPOD SHUFFLE
THEY'VE BEEN HERE SINCE 2003 *
NOW WE BRING DISPATCHES OF
BIRTHDAY CELEBRATIONS, COLBY G.
AND MASON S., CONGRATULATIONS ON
THE ANNIVERSARY OF EMERGING FROM
YOUR MOTHER'S VAGINA.
YOUR COAT SAYS PIZZA IS FOR WINNERS.
SO TONIGHT, YOU STARVE.
HARK, DO YOU HEAR THAT?
THE RUMBLING OF A THOUSAND HUNGERS.
IS IT?
IT IS.
THE PHYSICAL VOICE OF PIZZA.
THE INSATIABLE MR. MUNCH!
♪
ROW ROW ROW ROW
ROW ROW ROW *
* PIZZA IN MY TUMMY ♪
HUNGRY, RIGHT, BUD?
HUNGRY FOR VALIDATION.
ABANDONED ON A FERRIS WHEEL.
THE BASTARD CHILD OF A CIRQUE DU
SOLEIL PERFORMER AND GRIMACE.
APPLAUD HIM, APPLAUD HIS
BRAVERY.
* OH, PIZZA PIE *
* IN THE PIZZA KAI ♪
♪ DELIVER ME *
* DELIVER ME *
OH, LOOK, INTO THAT'S
PASCUALE THE PIZZA CHEF.
IS HE ALWAYS SO SEXY?
NOW CHILDREN, A CAUTIONARY
TALE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT CHUCK E.
CHEESE HAS A SALAD BAR?
AN UNTOUCHED PLACE WHERE HOPE
GOES TO DIE.
AND HERE TO TELL US ABOUT THIS
CASEY CARROT.
* LOOKING FOR COMCAST
UNDER THE PLASTIC
BROKEN DISPOSABLE TONGS *
* COLD LYNN GENEY *
* GREENIE A PEPERONCINO
WHERE DID WE GO WRONG *
* ROMAINE IS
ALL THAT REMAINS
SHE'S DYING *
* ROMAINE IS
ALL THAT REMAINS ♪
WOW.
I KNOW THAT CARROT.
I'VE BEEN THAT CARROT.
WE ARE ALL THAT CARROT.
TONIGHT, THE CALL GOES OUT TO
ALL THE WORLD, THROW OFF THE
SHACKLES OF YOUR DARKNESS, YOUR
RELIGION, YOUR RACIAL ANIMUS.
AND UNITE UNDER ONE BANNER,
THE BANNER OF PIZZA!
ALSO THE PINK GUN ON THE
CRISIS GAME IS BROKEN.
AND THE BALL PIT.
NOW UNITE AND SING!
* PIZZA PIE
IN THE PIZZA SKY
DELIVER ME
DELIVER ME ♪
DELIVER ME *
* OH PIZZA PIE ♪
♪ FOURTH PLACE ANTHEM
PLAYING TONIGHT
ON A BROKEN RADIO *
* THOUGHT WE REACHED
THE MOUNTAINTOP
BUT NOW WE JUST
FEEL SO LOW *
* THE SKY IS BREAKING OPEN
WE KEEP HOPING
IN THE DISTANCE
WE'LL SEE A GLOW ♪
♪ LIGHTNING LIGHT OUR WAY
'TIL THE BLACK SKY
TURNS BACK TO INDIGO ♪
♪ WE CAN MAKE IT
IF YOU DON'T QUIT ON ME
I WON'T QUIT ON YOU
DON'T QUIT ON ME *
* WE CAN MAKE IT BABY
PLEASE DON'T QUIT ON ME
I WON'T QUIT ON YOU
DON'T QUIT ON ME *
* I'LL NEVER QUIT ON YOU
WE WERE BORN IN PARADISE
BENEATH THE POISONED SKY
UNDER A BAD SIGN ♪
♪ THE MICRO AGE OF GEMINI
AND WE ARE STILL UNLEARNING
TIRES ARE BURNING IN THE
MIDDLE OF RODEO DRIVE *
* YOU KNOW THAT WE'VE BEEN
BEAT DOWN AND BROKEN
BUT NOW WE CAN TESTIFY OOH *
* WE CAN MAKE IT
IF YOU DON'T QUIT ON ME
I WON'T QUIT ON YOU
DON'T QUIT ON ME *
* WE CAN MAKE IT BABY
PLEASE DON'T QUIT ON ME
I WON'T QUIT ON YOU
DON'T QUIT ON ME ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER QUIT ON YOU
IT'S NOT UP TO YOU
SOME YOU WIN
SOME YOU LOSE *
* YOU DON'T GET TO CHOOSE
SOME YOU WIN
SOME YOU LOSE
WHEN THE LIGHTNING COMES *
* ONE TWO THREE FOUR
♪ I HEARD THE THUNDER
ON A BLUE SKY
PERFECT DAY♪
♪ I WONDER WHY
AM I THE ONLY ONE
I HEARD THE THUNDER
AND I FEEL I'M GOING UNDER *
* JESUS CHRIST
WAS AN ONLY SON
A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR *
* A DAY A WEEK
* EVERY SECOND
BRINGS ME HERE
A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR *
* A DAY A WEEK
* EVERY SECOND
BRINGS ME HERE
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING *
* WAITING ON THE LIGHT
WHAT WILL THE LIGHT BRING
I HEARD THE THUNDER AND I
THOUGHT IT WAS THE ANSWER ♪
♪ BUT I FOUND I GOT
THE QUESTION WRONG
I WAS TRYING TO RUN AWAY BUT
A VOICE TOLD ME TO STAY *
* PUT THE FEELING IN A SONG
A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR *
* A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR ♪
♪ EVERY SECOND
BRINGS ME HERE
A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR *
* A DAY A WEEK
A MONTH A YEAR ♪
♪ EVERY SECOND
BRINGS ME HERE
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING *
* WAITING ON THE LIGHT
WHAT WILL THE LIGHT BRING
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING
WAITING ON THE LIGHTNING *
* WAITING ON THE LIGHT
♪ WAITING ON THE LIGHT
WHAT WILL THE LIGHT BRING ♪
I'M CHLOE FINEMAN.
IT'S BEEN A REALLY UNIQUE SEASON.
AND PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS ASKING
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN A CAST MEMBER
HAS TO MISS A SHOW BECAUSE
THEY'RE SICK?
WELL, THAT'S WHERE I COME IN.
I AM THE SHOW'S OFFICIAL UNDERSTUDY.
EVERY WEEK
CASE I NEED TO JUMP INTO THEIR ROLE.
DO YOU THINK WE CAN TAKE IT
FROM THE TOP OF THE SKETCH?
YEAH, YEAH.
EXTERIOR MET GALA, KATE IS AN "E! NEWS"
CORRESPONDENT.
OKAY.
SO -- HEY, GUYS, HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT?
GOD, WHAT?
YOU WANT TO GET MORE INTIMATE
WITH IT.
YOU WANT TO DO A BIGGER SPREAD.
SPREAD AS BIG AS YOU CAN.
JUST MAKE PEOPLE UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
TO REALLY CAPTURE THE ESSENCE
OF A CAST MEMBER,
YOU HAVE TO
SHADOW THEM AS THEY GO ABOUT
THEIR EVERYDAY ROUTINES.
YEAH, WELL, I THOUGHT IT WAS
FUNNY, BUT DURING THE SHOW IT
WASN'T ON THE CUE CARD.
IT WASN'T ON THE CUE CARD,
NO, NO.
SOME OF THE CAST MEMBERS USE
ME AS AN UNDERSTUDY FOR THEIR
PERSONAL LIVES.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR DOING
THIS, CHLOE.
I'M SO BAD AT BREAKUPS.
TRULY, NO PROBLEM.
HEY, CHLOE.
OH, NO.
BUT I SEE IT AS MORE OF A POEM,
YOU KNOW?
SO, IT'S JUST NOT GOING TO WORK OUT.
THANKS PAL, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, MAN.
I FRICKIN' LOVE YOU.
UNDERSTUDIES HAVE A VERY
STRICT CODE OF ETHICS.
LIKE, NO MATTER HOW GOOD MY
ELIZABETH OLSEN IMPRESSION IS, I
WOULD NEVER USE TO IT TRICK BENEDICT.
BENEDICT, IT'S YOUR FRIEND
ELIZABETH OLSEN.
HEY, YOU MADE IT.
YOU'RE IN COSTUME.
I LOVE MARVEL.
HA HA HA!
AND SPEAKING OF, DO YOU KNOW WHO
WOULD BE GREAT IN THE NEXT
DOCTOR STRANGE IS "SNL'S"
UNDERSTUDY CHLOE FINEMAN.
BENEDICT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT I WAS TALKING TO YOU.
NO, I'M ME.
NO, SO AM I.
I AM ME.
I AM ME TOO.
OH, MY GOD.
THE MULTIVERSE IS REAL.
OH.
HAS ANYONE ASKED ME TO BE AN
UNDERSTUDY?
NO.
BUT THEY HAVEN'T ASKED ME TO STOP.
OKAY, GUYS.
RAPID FIRE.
TELL ME IF I GET IT.
AIDY?
GOOGLY, GABBLELY.
NAILED IT, BAD-ASS.
HEIDI.
HEY, DUDE.
WE'RE STRONG SO FAR.
SARAH.
HELLO, HELLO!
WAIT, DO I SOUND LIKE A
JEWISH PARROT?
OKAY, WHO'S LEFT?
PASS.
AND I THANK YOU FOR THAT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS ARE THINKING.
WHAT HAPPENS IF I GET SICK?
WELL I ACTUALLY HAVE MY OWN
UNDERSTUDY WHO DOES A PERFECT
IMPRESSION OF ME.
YO --!
EVERYONE.
ALL THE GREAT WRITERS AND THE CAST.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ONCE
AGAIN, ARCADE FIRE!
HERE WE GO.