-Next up on C-SPAN,
Secretary of War Pete Hegseth
is about to take questions
from the press
about the current
military operation in Iran.
-Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
The Secretary of War has been
preparing all afternoon,
and it looks like
he's about ready.
So please welcome
Secretary Hegseth!
-Alright! Enough!
Cut the track!
Cut it!
Alright.
I finished my Heg-stand.
And relax! It was Sprite!
Alright, listen up,
dipsticks, okay?
'Cause this is
actually serious, okay?
As you may have seen from
our epic Pentagon meme drops...
...we're treating Iran
like the breathalyzer in my car
and blowing it the hell up.
The good news is,
our operation couldn't be going
better,
and everyone loves it!
To quote my personal hero,
Papa Roach...
d Cut Iran into pieces d
d Make it a Trump resort d
Now, this situation's
is complicated, okay?
So let me put it in terms
that I can understand.
We're giving Iran
a third-degree purple nurple.
Alright?
And we've torpedoed
their ships so bad,
their navy's gonna be singing...
d Under the sea d
Yeah, that's right.
We can do Jamaican again.
You're welcome.
Now, a lot of the press
have looks on their
faces like, "Der?!"
So now I'm gonna be
taking your questions
and throwing them
directly into a trash can.
You. Hanson brother. Go.
-Uh, Secretary Hegseth,
you said this war could potent--
-Wait, whoa, wait.
Wait. Wait. War?
Okay. Whoever called this a war?
Except maybe the President
a couple times accidentally.
Okay? This isn't a war.
Also, why do we have to
put labels on everything, okay?
What are you, my high-school
girlfriend? Which I had.
This isn't a war, okay?
It's a situationship.
Right? We're just gonna hook up.
We're gonna see where it goes.
If it feels good,
we'll keep going.
And if we get bored, we'll
start hooking up with Cuba.
Okay? Does anyone
have a not-stupid question?
-Uh, yeah.
Can you just tell us
if there are gonna be
boots on the ground?
-Uh, yeah, your mom's next
to my bed after I bang her.
-I -- I just think
the American people are worried
this could turn into
a total quagmire.
-Uh, yeah. Good.
Quagmire is hilarious.
I mean, he's no Stewie,
but who is?
Giggity.
-What is happening?!
-Okay.
I'll tell you what's happening. Okay?
We don't know. Okay?
And that's the whole point.
If we don't know
what we're doing,
then Iran definitely
doesn't know what we're doing.
We're wild. Okay?
We're unpredictable.
We're like Shia LaBeouf
in Nawlins.
Okay? Shout-out, "Transformers."
Shout-out
Megan Fox back on Insta.
Alright. Next question.
Gaylord says what?
-What?
-Oh, my God.
Brutal.
Okay. Next.
-Yeah, this week, the President
was asked
if Americans should be worried about
Iranian attacks here at home.
And the President said,
"I guess."
Should people be afraid?
-Uh, I dunno. Probably.
I mean, probably you are.
Look, you guys don't understand
what we're doing here. Okay?
Y'all--
Y'all are playing chess.
I'm playing "Grand Theft Auto."
Okay?
Alright. Next question. Girl.
-First of all, I have a name.
-Oh, really? Yeah. Is it
Jessica No Wonder I'm Single?
-Yes.
Reuters
Last week, you said that
the U.S. defense agenda was, quote
"maximum lethality,
not tepid legality...
violent effects,
not politically correct."
Uh, what did you mean by that?
And why did it rhyme?
-Uh, 'cause I'm white Hamilton.
d I'm just like my country,
I'm drunk, angry, and horny d
d And they made me
throw away my scotch d
Yeah.
Like the poster.
Alright. Now, it isn't
all fun news today, okay?
After year, singular,
of hard work,
DHS Secretary Kristi Noem has
been reassigned under the bus.
So let's bring her out
to give her a proper goodbye.
Kristi Noem!
-Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, Secretary Hegseth.
I just want to make it clear
that I didn't get fired.
I self-deported.
And though I may be
leaving this job,
I will not be ending my mission.
As I told my plastic surgeon,
the work is never done.
But I gave my all to the DHS,
and I have no regrets.
Because, like they say,
you miss 100% of the dogs
you don't shoot.
And I'm proud of what
we've accomplished.
I took this job with the goal
of securing our border,
deporting thousands of illegals,
and spending $200 million
on ads of me riding a horse.
And I think I really nailed it.
And by "it,"
I mean my married coworker
in a big, beautiful
flying bedroom
30,000 feet over Minneapolis.
And while I look forward
to what comes next,
leaving is bittersweet,
but the time has come
for me to turn in my badge,
gun, lips, lashes,
teeth, and forehead.
But I'm so excited
about my new job
as Special Envoy
to the Shield of the Americas.
Something about President Trump.
He created it for me!
I just saw my new office,
which is at a WeWork space
outside of Denver,
and it is spectacular.
So this may be goodbye,
but this isn't goodbye forever.
-Yeah, except that it is.
-Oh, okay.
-And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Ryan Gosling!
-Thank you!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm thrilled to be back hosting,
especially now.
This is the perfect time
to be in New York City.
Early March.
Right? No. It's beautiful.
Is that Harry Styles?
What are you doing here, man?
Well, I'm hosting next week,
and it's been a while.
It's been a while,
so I just wanted to watch,
get a feel for it.
-Yeah. That's so professional.
That's awesome.
You're here. I just wish
someone would have told me.
That's, uh -- Anyway, welcome.
Uh, I have a new movie
coming out.
It's called
"Project Harry Styles."
Nope.
Uh, it'd be a good movie,
though.
Uh, it's called
"Project Hail Mary."
That's okay. Thank you.
And, uh, people
are saying it's like
"E.T." meets "Interstellar,"
which is crazy
because those are, like, what--
like, two of the best films
of all time, so...
They're kind of, like,
saying it's like, what?
Like, double that?
I don't know. I didn't say it.
I just-- I've always loved
making films about space.
It's just something about them
gives me perspective.
It reminds me...
...that-- that the Earth,
uh, is just a speck
in the cosmos.
I mean, look at that.
The pale blue dot.
That's us.
On it, everyone you know...
...everyone you've ever heard of
lived out their lives.
Every king. Every peasant.
Every-- I'm sorry.
Why are we on Harry Styles?
-I don't know.
I'm just listening.
-Well, could you
listen less cool?
I think your coolness
is becoming a bit of an issue.
Anyway...
back to the pale blue dot.
Home to every hero,
every villain,
every creator and destroyer
of civilizations.
Every young couple in love.
Every-- What's going on?
I'm just trying to understand
why we'd be in a split screen.
Come on, guys. Let's
get rid of the split screen.
Let's get rid of it. And not--
Not...
Not like that.
Not like that!
No! Not like that.
You know what I meant.
Come on.
What's going on with camera two?
What's going on? Oh, okay.
Okay. Okay.
Hi.
Hi. Look.
We all heart Harry, okay?
Just get the stupid Earth
out of here. Get it out.
-Wait! Ryan! What's going on?!
Are we still gonna do
the big dance number?
-We're not gonna
do the number.
Harry Styles is here, and just--
Everything is different now that
Harry Styles is here, so...
-Harry Styles is here?
-Yeah.
-Get me to God's country.
-What?
But, Sarah...
Where are you going?
-Do you like my body, Harry?
-Okay. Alright.
I'm sorry, ladies.
We're not gonna do the number.
We just--
We're running out of time.
I'll just-- I'll do the song.
Thank you, Jenna.
Uh, do the song
that's in the movie.
There's a song.
It's a karaoke song.
Sandra Huller sings it.
It's just-- It's very poignant.
And it's the anthem of our
generation, some have said.
It's called "Sign of the Times."
And, oh, my God,
it's by Harry Styles!
And now I gotta sing it
in front of him?
I love this for me.
d Just stop your crying,
it's the sign of the times d
Nobody wants this.
d Welcome to the final show d
This is probably my final show.
d Hope you're wearing
your best clothes d
I genuinely hate this.
d You can't bribe your door
on the way to the sky d
Just, like-- Why would
his face be next to mine?
d You look pretty good
down here d
And he does look really good
down there.
d But you ain't really good d
Can we just please
get him off the screen?
No, ladies, I don't want
to bring you into this.
Honestly, this is not...
You're better than this.
-d Why are we always stuck
and running from d
-I don't want to do this to you.
-d The bullets? d
-I'd take a bullet right now.
I'd take a bullet right--
I don't know what to do!
What do I do?!
d I'm just Ken d
Oh, God!
No! No.
No.
I promised myself
I wouldn't do that.
God.
Do you guys remember
when I did that at the Oscars?
It was like--
It was pretty cool.
I just thought I had
another one in me, I guess.
-Hey. Hey.
-Yeah?
-Don't be-- Don't be sad, Ry-Ry.
-Wait. Wait.
The-- Most of the cast? Wow!
You guys all came to help me?
Because I'm, like...
your favorite host of all time?
What?
That's so beautiful!
That's so beautiful, Kenan.
-Yeah. Uh, no.
-What?
-Uh, we just came to
get a better look at Harry.
I mean, that's good.
-But, um, I guess
while we're here...
-d Just stop your crying,
it's the sign of the times d
Everybody!
d We gotta get away from here d
d We gotta get away d
-We got a great show
for you tonight!
Gorillaz are here!
-d It's a sign of the times d
-Harry Styles
is hosting next week!
Stick around!
We'll be right back!
-d We gotta get away d
-Alright, party people.
Give it up for the bride
and groom, Mark and Ellie!
-Whoo! Whoo-whoo! Ooh-ooh!
-Hey, we just wanted
to thank you all for coming.
-Yes, we know it was
a long trip for some of y'all,
but I promise
we plan to be married
for the rest of our lives.
Although. that's not always
the case. Right, Claudette?
-My husband died!
-I did forget that.
And I apologize, Claudette.
-But we genuinely love
everyone in this room today,
and I love this man
a little extra.
-Okay. Uh, we know
what that means!
-Yep. Alright.
Come here. Come here.
What just happened?
-With the clinking of glasses?
It's, like, a wedding tradition.
-Yeah, if someone
clinks their glass,
the bride and groom
have to kiss.
-Yeah.
-They have to?
Interesting.
They have to.
-Well, there are a few people
we want to thank today.
-Mm-hmm.
-Um, my mom,
who went to every Goodwill
in Binghamton
to find the brass candlesticks
on your tables!
-Kiss.
You have to.
-Well, you don't
have to tell me twice.
-And shout-out to my best man
for planning the bachelor party.
Trust me, babe.
Nothing bad happened.
-Kiss.
I don't make the rules.
-Ohp. A lot of kisses.
Let's save some
for the honeymoon.
-Yeah. Okay. Mwah. There you go.
-Okay, anyway, before
everyone hits the dance floor...
...I just wanted to say, um,
a quick word about
someone we lost this year.
Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Um, my favorite person
in the world, my nana.
Yeah, so whenever I pictured
my wedding day, I alw--
-Hm. There you go.
-I always pictured
my nana here,
but unfortunately,
that wasn't God's plan, so...
-Okay, I think we're done
with the kissing!
-Whoever's doing that,
we're all set.
-Yeah.
-It's him!
The guy who's dressed like
Reba McEntire at the Grammys!
-Guilty as charged.
Who let the kiss out?
Smooch, smooch-smooch,
smooch, smooch.
-I'm sorry. Who are you?
-Put it this way.
I'm your favorite comedian's
favorite comedian.
-Uh, no. Uh, that's Donathan.
Uh, I backed into him
with my car,
and he said, in lieu of
going through insurance,
I could just invite him
to my wedding.
-I'm clinking the bottom
of the glass.
When I clink the top of
the glass, you kiss on the lips.
So when I --
Guess-- Guess what body part
I want you to kiss now.
The poozie.
-The poozie?!
I'm not going to kiss
my wife's poozie.
-Wouldn't kill you.
-I don't know about that.
Apparently, that's actually
how Claudette's husband died.
-My husband died of leukemia!
-Well, that just
chilled the room.
Now we need a kiss
more than ever.
-Okay. Someone take
Donathan's knife away, please.
Let's just move on.
Ellie's siblings are gonna
say a quick toast. Whoo!
-Hi.
-Hello, everyone. Hi.
-I'm--
I'm doing the siblings now.
Kiss.
-Stop.
We're brother and sister, man.
-And yet...
the rules are the rules.
-Whoa! Whoa! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?!
Go! Go!
Think about what you just did!
That was insane!
Alright, look, Donathan...bud...
I'm sorry,
but we want you to leave.
-And I want to watch
some kisses.
But before I go...
I have one final question.
This is the groom's glass.
If I clink the stem...
will he kick his--
Will he kiss his own...poonis?
-No. No.
-No, I'm not kissing
my own poonis, Donathan.
We're done kissing!
-Oh, whatever.
Come on, babe.
Let's get out of here.
-I don't know you!
-Then I'll go with
my second choice.
Let's go, Claudette.
-Alright! I don't love
being second, but I'm down.