>>> LIVE FROM HOLLYWOOD, THE
DONALD J. TRUMP CHINESE THEATER,
THE FIRST ANNULL TRUMPS.
THE AWARDS HONORING THE BEST AT
BEING OR SUCCUMBING TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
NOW YOUR HOST, DONALD J. TRUMP!
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT TRULY IS AN HONOR TO BE HERE
HOSTING THE TRUMPS.
AFTER THAT LADY WHOSE NAME I
ALREADY FORGET GAVE ME HER NOBEL
PRIZE,
I THOUGHT, I NEED MORE
AWARDS.
AND AFTER ALL WHAT OUR LITTLE
FREAKS AND PSYCHOS IN I.C.E. HAVE BEEN DOING,
I NEED MORE
DISTRACTIONS.
LOOK,
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO CHINA.
WHAT A CROWD WE HAVE TONIGHT.
SO MANY AWFUL, TERRIBLE PEOPLE
IN THE HOUSE.
I'D LIKE TO GET A ROUND OF
APPLAUSE GOING FOR THE NOMINEES,
BUT MY DOCTORS SAY IF I CLAP
BOTH MY DEAD PURPLE HANDS WILL
EXPLODE WITH BLOOD.
PROBABLY NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
DOCTORS SAY I COULD LIVE TO BE
120, OR CURRENT AGE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS SUCH A SPECIAL
NIGHT.
EVERYONE WANTS TO GO HOME WITH A
TRUMP.
EXCEPT, OF COURSE, MELANIA.
HILARIOUS.
WELL, WE'VE GOT A SIX-HOUR SHOW
AHEAD OF US,
SO LET'S KEEP
THINGS SPIRALING.
HERE TO PRESENT THE AWARD FOR
BEST PICTURE OF ME,
OUR VICE
PRESIDENT FOR NOW, J.D. VANCE.
AND PRESIDENT FOREVER, DONALD
TRUMP.
HI, J.D.
>> HI, DONALD.
SAY, DID YOU KNOW IF THAT I WIN
IN 2028,
I WOULD BE THE FIRST
PRESIDENT IN 100 YEARS TO HAVE A
BEARD.
>> WOW.
AND SPEAKING OF YOUR BEARD,
HOW'S YOUR WIFE, USHA?
>> VERY GOOD, SIR.
>> I'M INSINUATING YOU'RE GAY.
THE NOMINEES FOR BEST PICTURE OF ME
ARE --
>> "STARING INTO THE DISTANCE
WHILE MAN HAT MEDICAL EMERGENCY
NEXT TO HIM."
MOLESTING FLAG.
REDACTED EPSTEIN FILES.
AND RECEIVING ANOTHER FAKE AWARD
HE MADE FIFA INVENT TO GIVE TO
HIMSELF."
AND THE AWARD GOES TO --
IT'S TRUMP RECEIVING ANOTHER FAKE
AWARD.
>> THIS IS DONALD TRUMP'S FIRST
TRUMP AWARD,
EVEN THOUGH HE
COULD HAVE EARNED HUNDREDS OF
THEM BUT NORWAY SOMEHOW BLOCKED
IT.
>> WOW, WOW, THIS FEELS
INCREDIBLE.
I LOVE ME, I REALLY LOVE ME.
I HAVE SO FEW PEOPLE TO THANK.
MYSELF, AND OF COURSE, THE BIG MAN UPSTAIRS,
WHICH IS WHAT I
CALL MY BRAIN TUMOR, YOW!
IF I COULD BE SERIOUS FOR A
MOMENT, THERE IS SO MUCH HORRIBLE STUFF
GOING ON IN OUR
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
BUT I PROMISE YOU, I'M JUST
GETTING STARTED,
THANK YOU.
ERIC, GO TO BED!
>> AND NOW PLEASE WELCOME THE
PRESIDENT OF ARGENTINA, JAVIER
MILEI!
LEADER
VISIONARY
20 BILLIONS
FRIEND
NO.
BUT HE DID INCLUDE A CHECK FOR
ANOTHER $10 MILLION.
THIS GUY IS AWESOME, BRO.
>> ALL RIGHT, ADIOS, AMIGO.
I'M TAKING THIS AWARD.
I'M TAKING GREENLAND.
AND I'M TAKING ZOOTOPIA.
I LOVE THOSE GUYS.
I RECOGNIZE ALL THOSE ANIMALS
FROM MY COGNITIVE EXAM.
NOW HERE TO PRESENT THE AWARD
FOR BEST KISS ARE TWO LEGENDS OF
HORROR.
AUNT GLADYS FROM THE MOVIE
WEAPONS AND MY IMMIGRATION
ADVISER STEPHEN MILLER.
>> HI, EVERYONE.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT I WAS
TERRIFYING UNTIL I MET THIS GUY.
>> AW, THANK YOU.
>> THE NOMINEES FOR BEST KISS
ARE --
>> J.D. VANCE, "TRUMP'S ASS."
KRISTI NOEM, "TRUMP'S ASS."
KASH PATEL, "TRUMP'S ASS."
AND DONALD J. TRUMP, "PUTIN'S
ASS."
>> AND THE WINNER IS -- KRISTI
NOEM!
>> WOW, WELL, I AM HONORED AND
IN NO WAY DEAD INSIDE TO WIN A
TRUMP.
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD DEDICATE
THIS AWARD TO PRESIDENT TRUMP --
>> AND I ACCEPT, THANK YOU!
>> OH, WAIT, BUT I WON --
>> I'MA LET YOU FINISH, BUT
TRUMP HAD ONE OF THE BEST VIDEOS
OF ALL TIME, OF ALL TIME.
KANYE!
YOU CAN GO.
I'LL KEEP THIS SHORT BECAUSE I
HAVE A LOT MORE AWARDS TO WIN
TONIGHT.
I JUST WANT TO THANK MY LONGTIME
AGENT, LOKI, THE GOD OF
MISCHIEF, TRICKERY, AND CHAOS.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO THIS
WITHOUT YOU, MAN.
I LOVE YOU, MAN.
AND NOW, HERE TO ACCEPT THE
LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT AWARD FOR
COMEDY, EVEN THOUGH HE MIGHT NOT
ALWAYS INTEND IT, MY CLOSE
EX-FRIEND, ELON MUSK.
>> GOOD ONE, THANK YOU, THANK
YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
I -- I -- I'M SO EMOTIONLESS TO
BE HERE.
AND IF ANYONE KNOWS HUMOR, IT'S
ME.
YOU KNOW, LEGAL IS COMING, COME
ON, COME ON, COME ON!
UNFORTUNATELY, IT WASN'T ALL
LAUGHS THIS YEAR.
NO, NOT ALL LAUGHS.
THERE ARE A FEW THINGS WE HAD TO
SAY GOOD-BYE TO BECAUSE WE
DESTROYED THEM.
SO HERE TO PERFORM A MOURNFUL
RENDITION OF "AMERICA'S FUNNIEST
HOME VIDEOS" THEME, PLEASE
WELCOME CARRIE UNDERWOOD AND THE
CONSTRUCTION WORKER FOR THE
VILLAGE PEOPLE, LET'S GO, COME
ON!
¶ THE RED WHITE AND BLUE THE
FINE THINGS YOU DO ¶
¶ AMERICA, AMERICA IT IS YOU ¶
¶ AMERICA, AMERICA THIS IS YOU ¶
>> AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
>> Announcer: IT'S "SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE" WITH --
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- TEYANA
TAYLOR!
I AM YOUR HOST, TEYANA TAYLOR.
AND I'M SO HONORED TO BE HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE!
NOW, I'M A HARLEM GIRL, AND I
LOVE NEW YORK.
BUT IT'S FREEZING OUT HERE.
THAT'S WHY I HAD TO GET A SPOT
IN MIAMI BECAUSE THE BITCH WAS
COLD.
NO WONDER WHY US NEW YORKERS, WE
SO AGITATED, BECAUSE WE COLD.
THIS WEEK HAS BEEN VERY INSANE.
I WAS NOMINATED FOR AN OSCAR FOR
ONE BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER.
IT IS A DREAM COME TRUE.
I FOUND OUT THE WAY EVERY LITTLE
GIRL WANTS TO FIND OUT.
GET FITTED FOR A BALL CAP NEXT
TO MIKEY DAY.
ALL OF THIS IS KIND OF
OVERWHELMING BECAUSE I AM A
REALLY SHY PERSON, BELIEVE IT OR
NOT, WHO DOES NOT LIKE A LOT OF
ATTENTION.
FOR EXAMPLE, HERE'S ME AT MY
16th BIRTHDAY PARTY.
YEAH, YEAH.
YES, I WAS ON MTV'S "MY SUPER
SWEET 16."
I'VE HAD THE CHANCE TO DO SO
MANY THINGS IN MY LIFE.
FROM SINGING TO DANCING TO
ACTING TO DIRECTING.
AND YES, I AM CURRENTLY IN
CULINARY SCHOOL, CHEFFING IT UP,
UP UP.
HELL, I RANDOMLY WON "MAD SING
IR"DRESSED AS A FIREFLY, FOR
REAL.
ME, I CONSIDER MYSELF A GLADE
PLUG-IN.
WHY ONLY PLUG ME IN THE BATHROOM
WHEN I CAN MAKE THE WHOLE
BUILDING SMELL GOOD?
ALSO, I AM A MOM.
PEOPLE ASK WHEN I SLEEP.
DON'T WORRY, I GET A FULL EIGHT
HOURS A WEEK.
BOTH MY PREGNANCIES WERE VERY,
VERY PEACEFUL.
I DID ALL THE THINGS I WAS
SUPPOSED TO DO.
I WAS GOING TO YOGA, TAKING
VITAMINS AVOIDING RAW FISH.
I THINK WE HAVE A VIDEO OF ME
PREGNANT RIGHT HERE.
YES.
SO WHOLESOME, SO CALM.
MAN, I REALLY, REALLY LOVE MY
KIDS SO MUCH.
I BRING THEM EVERYWHERE WITH ME.
BUT WHEN I WAS GIVING MY SPEECH
AT THE GOLDEN GLOBES, I LOOKED
UP TO SEE MY BABIES, I WANTED TO
SEE THEY FACES, YOU KNOW?
JUST TO SEE THAT THEY WERE
SCROLLING ON THEIR PHONES.
SO I'M LIKE, THIS IS SO
AMAZING -- GET OFF THEM PHONES!
WHAT AN HONOR -- GET OFF THEM
PHONES!
BUT FOR REAL, I FEEL SO LUCKY.
I'VE WORKED SO HARD THROUGHOUT
MY CAREER TO GET TO THIS POINT,
AND I'M JUST SO GRATEFUL TO BE
HERE WITH MY BABIES CHEERING ME
ON.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR Y'ALL
TONIGHT.
GEESE IS HERE.
ON STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK!
LIKE YESTERDAY.
>> I HAVE FADE, HON.
THEY CAN'T DELAY US FOREVER.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THANK
YOU FOR BEARING WITH US THROUGH
THIS BIG OLD WINTER STORM.
WE KNOW HOW FRUSTRATING THESE
DELAYS HAVE BEEN.
IN THE MEANTIME AND IN BETWEEN
TIME, WE HAVE AN UPDATE FOR YOU.
>> OH, FINALLY, THANK GOD.
>> TO SOFTEN THE BLOW, WE WILL
BE PROVIDING UPDATE THE BEST WAY
WE KNOW, THROUGH SONGS.
HIT IT, BABY.
¶ WE KNOW IT'S FRUSTRATING
WHEN YOU REALLY WANT
TO FLY ¶
¶ BUT TOO BAD
YOUR PLANE IS DELAYED
IT HAS NOT ARRIVED ¶
¶ IF I WERE YOU RIGHT NOW
I WOULD START TO PRAY ¶
¶ 'CAUSE IT'S LOOKIN' LIKE
YOU WON'T BE FLYING TODAY ¶
>> YEAH, WE ARE SUPER DELAYED.
MORE UPDATES COMING REAL SOON.
>> DID THEY SAY WE MIGHT NOT GET
ON THE PLANE TODAY?
>> I DO THINK THEY SANG THAT,
YES.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PLAUS.
WE ARE PRISON GRITS BRINGING YOU
SMOOTH SOUNDS FROM GATE 332 IN
THE MEL GIBSON REGIONAL
TERMINAL.
>> MY NAME IS LASHLEY, AS IN
FIRSTLY AND LASHLEY.
>> I AM PARFAIT, AS IN THE
PARFAIT DON'T START TILL I WALK
IN.
>> I'M SORRY, THESE DELAYS ARE
NOT ACCEPTABLE.
>> OKAY, SO ACCEPT THESE NUTS.
>> ALL RIGHT, ARE WE GOING TO
GET A FLIGHT OUT OF HERE TODAY
OR NOT?
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> LISTEN, IT IS WHAT IT IS,
Y'ALL.
THIS IS TRUMP'S AMERICA.
MAYOR PETE BUDIGREG CANNOT SAVE
YOU, HE CANNOT SAVE YOU.
>> DID YOU SAY PETE BUDIGREG?
>> LISTEN, WE DON'T MAKE THE
RULES, WE JUST SING THEM TO YOU.
>> WE HAVE AN UPDATE ON THE
STATUS OF YOUR PLANE.
>> THANK GOD.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
¶ HONEY HONEY
I CAN SEE THIS PLANE
AIN'T LOOKIN' RIGHT ¶
¶ 'CAUSE IT'S GOT NO WINGS
BASICALLY A BUS ¶
>> WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, IT HAS NO
WINGS?
>> WHAT DO YOU NOT UNDERSTAND
ABOUT THIS?
THE PLANE AIN'T GOT NO WINGS.
THEY NEED TO PUT THEM ON.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A PLANE FLY
WITH NO WINGS?
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO TAKE LONG,
ALL RIGHT?
THEY JUST GOING TO SNAP THEM IN,
CLICK, BOOM, WE OUT.
>> THAT DOES NOT SEEM RIGHT.
>> IT IS NOT RIGHT.
BECAUSE A NORMAL PLANE LOOKS
LIKE THIS.
AND Y'ALL'S PLANE IS LOOKING
>> OKAY, WELL THANK YOU FOR THE
VISUAL AID.
>> OKAY, YOU'VE BEEN A PROBLEM
ALL DAY, OKAY?
WE ARE NOT CHECKING BAGS BUT WE
ARE CHECKING ATTITUDES.
>> OH, LOOK.
Y'ALL MUST HAVE BEEN PRAYING
BECAUSE THE PILOT IS HERE.
HE HAS AN UPDATE FOR YOU.
>> OH, THANK GOD.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
GOOD NEWS IS WE FOUND THE
PLANE'S WINGS.
BAD NEWS IS, I'M DRUNK!
SO I GUESS YOU CAN --
¶ BLAME IT ON THE VODKA
BLAME IT ON THE HENNY
BLAME IT ON THE FIVE SHOTS
GOT ME FEELIN' DIZZY
¶ I CANNOT FLY-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y
THIS PLANE
I CANNOT FLY-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y
THIS PLANE ¶
¶ HEY SHE SAID
USUALLY DON'T ¶
I'M JUST GOING TO -- WE'LL STOP
RIGHT THERE.
I THOUGHT I ORDERED VIRGIN
MARGARITAS, BUT THEM THINGS CAME
SLUTTY.
>> IN THE RIDICULOUS.
I'M CALLING MY WIFE.
HEY, MELISSA, YEAH.
I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO BE
HOME TONIGHT.
>> OH, HONEY, COME BACK TO BED.
>> WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> OKAY, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
LET'S JUST GO.
>> YEP, I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
BABE.
>> OH, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE
THIS.
THE PILOT HAS HAD SOME
PEDIALYTE, AND THE GROUND CREW
SNAPPED THE WINGS ON.
SO HURRY UP, Y'ALL, YOUR PLANE
LEAVES IN FIVE MINUTES.
>> AND AS ALWAYS, WE WILL BE
BOARDING MILITARY AND FINE MEN
FIRST.
¶ NO HESITATIN'
WE ONLY GOT FIVE MINUTES
TO BOARD THIS PLANE ¶
>>> THEY'VE WATCHED IT A
THOUSAND TIMES.
THEY CAN QUOTE EVERY LINE.
AS FAR AS YOUR KIDS ARE
CONCERNED, THE ONLY MOVIE THAT
MATTERS THIS AWARDS SEASON IS --
>> K-POP DEMON --
>> "ONE BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER."
>> BRING IT HOME WITH "ONE
BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER" ACTION
FIGURES FROM MATTEL.
>> PERFIDIA OF BEVERLY HILLS!
>> THIS IS A REVOLUTION, KIDS.
NOW FIGHT THEM DEMONS.
>> AWESOME!
>> ALL YOUR FAVORITE HEROES AND
VILLAINS FROM PAUL THOMAS
ANDERSON'S CRITICALLY LAUDED
MASTERPIECE ABOUT RESISTANCE IN
THE FACE OF RACIAL TYRANNY, NOW
IN THE PALM OF YOUR HANDS.
>> YEAH!
>> LIKE BATTLE ROBE FERGUSON
WITH LIGHT-UP JOINTS AND HOMING
DEVICE.
>> I'M SO HIGH!
>> SENSEI SERGIO WITH REAL
BEER-CHUGGING ACTION.
>> I HAD A FEW SMALL BEERS.
>> COLLECT ALL YOUR FAVORITE
REVOLUTIONARIES.
>> OH, HELLO.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS JUNGLE PUSSY.
THIS IS WHAT BLACK POWER LOOKS
LIKE.
>> DON'T FORGET ABOUT PERFIDIA.
WITH SNAP-ON PREGNANT BELLY AND
MACHINE GUN.
>> TAKE THAT PIG!
>> LOOK OUT.
HOT ON THEIR TRAIL IS THE BUFF,
WEIRD COLONEL LOCKJAW WITH
REALISTIC ARM VEINS AND MOBILE
PATERNITY TESTING KIT.
>> OKAY, YES, SIR!
>> DO YOU LIKE BLACK GIRLS?
>> WHAT?
>> I LOVE 'EM!
I LOVE 'EM!
>> TAKE THE BATTLE TO THE NEXT
LEVEL WITH "ONE BATTLE AFTER
ANOTHER" PLAY SETS.
LIKE SENSEI SERGIO'S APARTMENT
WITH REAL WORKING TRAP DOOR
TO HELP YOUR LATINO FRIENDS
ESCAPE.
ONE MORAL SACRIFICE AFTER
ANOTHER IN THE DIMLY LIT MOTEL
ROOM.
>> OH, NO, WE'RE NOT DOING THAT
SCENE.
>> LIKE BOB'S CRAPPY CAR.
SO MANY ROLLING HILLS.
ONE BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER
ACTION FIGURES, VEHICLES, AND
PLAY SETS FROM MATTEL.
PART OF THE PAUL THOMAS ANDERSON
MASTER SET.
>> I'VE ABANDONED MY CHILD!
I'VE ABANDONED MY CHILD!
I'VE ABANDONED MY BOY!
¶¶
>>> WELCOME BACK TO EMPOWER
FIELD IN DENVER AS THE BRONCOS
TAKE ON THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS
IN THE AFC CHAMPIONSHIP.
AND THIS ONE IS A CLASH BETWEEN
TWO GREAT DEFENSES, RIGHT, TROY?
>> OH, YEAH, THE UNSTOPPABLE
FORCE VERSUS THE IMMOVABLE
OBJECT.
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S GOING TO WIN,
BUT HECK, JUST GET OUT OF THE
WAY.
>> WE'LL GET INTO OUR ANALYSIS
SHORTLY.
DID YOU KNOW HOW LIEU NOW ON
DISNEY PLUS NOW HAS THE ADULT
DRAMAS YOU CRAVE?
THE BR TO "ALIEN EARTH" AND
THE STEAMY NEW LESBIAN CULINARY
DRAMA," QUEFS."
THEY THOUGHT THEY WERE STRAIGHT
UNTIL THEY MET IN THE KITCHEN
AND THAT'S WHEN THINGS STARTED
COOKING.
THESE QUEER CHEFS HAVE AMERICA
GAGGED AND GOOPED, "QUEFS"
STREAMING ON HULU.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK QUEFS IS
SHORT FOR?
QUEER CHEFS?
>> LET'S NOT GUESS, TROY.
LAST WEEK THE BRONCOS LOST BO
NIX TO AN ANKLE INJURY.
OUR SIDELINE REPORTER LISA
SALTERS WITH AN UPDATE.
>> THE BRONCOS HAVE NOTHING TO
BE ASHAMED OF.
THEY HAD A GREAT SEASON AND
SHOULDN'T HOLD BACK THEIR HEADS,
HOLD THEIR HEADS HIGH.
I'M SURE THEY'LL AN TEAM TO
WATCH NEXT YEAR.
>> LISA, THE GAME HASN'T STARTED
YET.
THINK YOU'RE WRITING OFF THE
BRONCOS A LITTLE EARLY?
>> I MEAN, COME ON.
THEY AIN'T GOT NO QUARTERBACK.
LIKE, COME ON.
>> LISA, DENVER IS A VERY
CAPABLE TEAM.
THEY COULD WIN.
>> YEAH.
BUT LIKE -- COME ON.
TROY, BACK TO YOU.
>> WELL.
DENVER WILL START BACKUP JARRETT
STIDHAM, WHO HASN'T PLAYED A
SNAP ALL YEAR.
>> I LIKE THE GUY, I THINK HE
COULD SURPRISE US.
>> SPEAKING OF SURPRISES, ONE
PART SUGAR AND ALL PART SPICE ON
AN ALL-NEW "QUEFS."
THINGS ARE HEATING UP IN THE
KITCHEN.
IF BRIDGETTE HAS HER WAY, IT'S
D-DAY.
FEATURING MUSIC BY SUAVE.
IT'S "QUEFS, THAT PART."
>> I THOUGHT SUAVE WAS JUST AN
ACTOR.
>> THERE'S NO WAY YOU KNOW WHO
THAT IS.
>> I DO NOT, JOE.
>> NOW, I'M SEEING LISA HAS SOME
NEWS ON THE DENVER QUARTERBACK
SITUATION.
IS BO NIX ON THE SIDELINES?
>> NOPE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS BUT I
HAVE AN UPDATE FROM HIS FAN.
SIR, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> JARRETT STIDHAM.
>> WHO, NOW?
I'M DENVER'S STARTING
QUARTERBACK TONIGHT.
>> OKAY, WELL, CONGRATS ON A
GREAT SEASON, AND BETTER LUCK
NEXT YEAR.
>> WAIT, HOLD ON, LISA.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT TEAM HERE.
I THINK WE CAN WIN THIS THING.
>> YEAH, BUT JARRETT -- COME ON.
BACK TO YOU, TROY.
>> OH, WELL, SO THAT'S JARRETT
STIDHAM.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT'S WHAT HE
LOOKED LIKE.
>> NO ONE DID.
ONE THING I DO KNOW IS "QUEFS"
IS BACK AND I AM PHAT.
THIS WEEK ON "QUEFS," FILLETS
WITH A SIDE OF SLAY.
BRIDGETTE AND HER SOFT DOM SUAVE
SORT OUT THEIR SITUATIONSHIP
WITH THE HELP OF GUEST STAR
GOVERN GAVIN NEWSOM.
SEE THE SHOW THAT HAS "THE NEW
YORK TIMES" RAVING, "NOT MY ASS
WATCHING QUEFS."
QUEFS, IT'S GIVING QUEFS.
>> TOLD YOU SUAVE WAS AN ACTOR.
>> I THINK YOU JUST GOT LUCKY
THERE.
>> SURE DID, JOE, YOU GOT ME.
>> I'VE BEEN TOLD WE HAVE AN
UPDATE FROM LISA ON THE
SIDELINES.
ANY BO NIX NEWS?
>> I ACTUALLY HAD A QUESTION
ABOUT "QUEFS."
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THE
TITLE?
QUEFS.
IT SOUNDS WEIRD, RIGHT?
ADD ONE MORE LETTER AND IT'S --
>> OKAY, THANK YOU SO MUCH,
LISA.
NO NEED TO SAY IT OUT LOUD.
I THINK EVERYBODY CLOCKED THAT.
LET'S GO NOW TO OUR "KEYS TO THE
GAME" BROUGHT TO YOU BY FAN
DUEL.
AND OH, MY GOD.
TALKING "QUEFS."
TALKING QUEFS IS THE "QUEFS"
AFTER SHOW.
RENEE RAPP AND TREVOR NOAH ARE
JOINED BY TAYLOR TOMLINSON, BOB
THE DRAG QUEEN, AND DENVER
QUARTERBACK BO NIX.
INTERESTING.
QUEFS.
THEY AIN'T BEEN HAD TO DO ALL
THAT, MAMA.
>> WHOA, BO NIX IS ON "TALKING
QUEFS."
THAT'S HUGE.
>> I DON'T THINK IT IS, TROY.
KICKOFF OF THE AFC CHAMPIONSHIP
IS IN TWO MINUTES.
IF YOU WANT TO SEE THAT, FLIP
OVER TO CBS.
IF YOU STAY ON ESPN, WE DO HAVE
WORLD CORNHOLE QUARTERFINALS
COMING UP.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
JOE, I'M GOING TO HEAD OUT.
>> I DON'T BLAME YOU, TROY.
>> Announcer: NEXT WEEK,
ALEXANDER SKARSGA
I'M CASS CASSIDY FLASK, WELCOME
TO MY CONFIDENCE CLASS, "THE
POWER OF YOU."
>> AWESOME, THANK YOU.
>> HI, CASSIDY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> NOW, BELIEVE IT OR NOT, THIS
GAL IN FRONT OF YOU ONCE HAD NO
CONFIDENCE.
I REMEMBER I ONCE LOST OUT ON A
JOB I REALLY WANTED.
AND THEN I WAS LIKE, A JOB
DOESN'T DEFINE ME, I DEFINE ME.
AND THAT'S HOW I FOUND THE POWER
IN ME.
ANY QUESTIONS BEFORE WE START?
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU GET THE JOB?
>> SORRY?
>> THE JOB YOU WANTED.
WHY DIDN'T YOU GET IT?
>> JUST DIDN'T GO ANY WAY.
NOW, LET'S GET STARTED.
>> DID THEY JUST NOT LIKE YOU?
>> I JUST DIDN'T GET IT.
NOW, THE JOB STORY'S JUST PART
OF MY INTRO, SO LET'S --
>> DID YOU WEAR WHAT YOU'RE
WEARING NOW?
>> WHAT?
>> DID YOU WEAR THIS OUTFIT TO
THE INTERVIEW?
>> NO.
>> WELL, THERE YOU GO.
>> YOU KNOW, ONCE UPON A TIME,
THAT WOULD HAVE STUNG.
BUT NOW I HEAR IT, AND I DON'T
FEAR IT.
COME ON, YOU TRY.
>> WHAT DID YOU WEAR TO THE
INTERVIEW?
>> SOMETHING NICE.
LEATHER PANTS.
LET'S JUST --
>> LEATHER PANTS?
>> YES.
JUST A NICE PAIR OF LEATHER
PANTS AND LEATHER GLOVES.
JUST LET IT GO.
>> OKAY, WELL -- THAT'S WHY SHE
DIDN'T GET THE JOB.
>> OKAY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GET US BACK ON
TRACK.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS FIRST
IMPRESSIONS.
RULE NUMBER ONE.
SHOW THEM WHAT YOU'RE WORKING
WITH IT.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT A SAMPLE
RESUME.
>> I'M SORRY, IS THAT YOUR
>> YEAH.
WHAT DO WE NOTICE?
WHAT ARE WE SEEING HERE?
>> THAT YOU TAKE SELFIES LIKE AN
UBER DRIVER.
>> YEAH.
IT SAYS "DO VOICES AND PERSONAL
COMPUTER NO."
>> IT ALSO SAY FROM 2014 TO
2025, YOU WERE A DOLLY PARTON
IMPERSONATOR.
>> CAN WE SEE YOUR DOLLY PARTON?
>> OKAY, GUYS, I DON'T HAVE THE
BOOBS WITH ME RIGHT NOW, AND
THAT WAS MOST OF IT, OKAY?
>> I'M SORRY, WITH THAT RESUME,
WHAT JOB COULD YOU HAVE POSSIBLY
BEEN INTERVIEWING FOR?
>> OH, MY GOD, FINE.
SPEECHWRITER FOR MICHELLE OBAMA,
OKAY?
>> WORD!
>> NO.
>> OH, MY GOD, THERE'S A WRITING
SAMPLE AT THE BOTTOM.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
IT SAYS, WHEN THEY GO LOW, WE GO
HIGH.
AM I RIGHT?
SO WHERE'S EVERYBODY FROM?
YOU IN THE FRONT, ARE YOU TWO A
COUPLE?
THE GUY IN THE DORK-ASS HAT NEXT
TO THE GIRL WHO'S WAY OUT OF HIS
LEAGUE?
MICHELLE LAUGHS THEN AD LIBS THE
REST OF THE SPEECH.
>> YOU WROTE MICHELLE OBAMA
DOING CROWD WORK?
>> GUYS, DO YOU WANT CONFIDENCE
OR NOT?
>> I'M NOT REALLY SURE ANYMORE.
>> WELL, I'M SURE ABOUT THIS.
RULE NUMBER TWO.
CLOTHES TELL THE STORY.
>> OH, NO.
>> IS THAT YOUR BATHROOM?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU GUYS ARE
MISSING THE LESSONS.
LET'S SHAKE THIS OFF, HUH?
LET'S SHAKE THIS OFF.
RELATIONSHIPS.
WHEN I FOUND MY POWER, I FOUND A
LOVING BOYFRIEND WHO'S WAITING
OUTSIDE FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
>> HE'S OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW?
>> YES.
>> CAN YOU BRING HIM IN SO WE
CAN MEET HIM?
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO MEET HIM.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE OF HOW HE LOOKS.
>> HOW DOES HE LOOK?
>> NOT GOOD.
>> CAN YOU DESCRIBE HIM?
>> OH, MY GOD.
HE LOOKS LIKE IF A GOBLIN LIVED
IN NEW YORK.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU?
I'M JUST REALIZING YOU ACTUALLY
MADE ME FEEL WAY MORE CONFIDENT.
AFTER MEETING YOU, I REALLY FEEL
AMAZING ABOUT MYSELF.
>> YEAH.
>> ME TOO.
>> THEN MY JOB HERE IS DONE.
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE MY DOLLY
PARTON?
>> SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JOLENE!
>> YEAH!
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, GEESE!
¶ YOU CAN STAY WITH ME
BABY YOU CAN STAY WITH ME
AND NOBODY WOULD CARE ¶
¶ YOU CAN STAY WITH ME
YOU CAN STAY WITH ME
AND JUST PRETEND
I'M NOT THERE ¶
¶ LIKE A SAILOR
IN A BIG GREEN BOAT
LIKE A SAILOR
IN A BIG GREEN COAT ¶
¶ YOU CAN BE FREE
YOU CAN BE FREE
AND STILL COME HOME ¶
¶ IT'S ALL RIGHT
I'M ALL RIGHT
YOU CAN CHANGE
YOU CAN CHANGE ¶
¶ YOU CAN CHANGE
YOU CAN CHANGE
YOU CAN CHANGE ¶
¶ YOU CAN CHANGE
BABY YOU CAN CHANGE
AND STILL CHOOSE ME ¶
¶ LIKE A SAILOR
IN A BIG GREEN COAT
LIKE A SAILOR
IN A BIG GREEN BOAT ¶
¶ YOU CAN BE FREE
YOU CAN BE FREE
JUST COME HOME
PLEASE ¶
¶ PLEASE PLEASE
I'M ALL RIGHT
I'M ALL RI-I-IGHT
I'M FINE ¶
¶ WELL
I'M ALL RIGHT ¶
>> HEY!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE, THANK
YOU.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, DURING A PRESS CONFERENCE
CELEBRATING HIS FIRST YEAR IN
OFFICE, PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID
THAT GOD WAS VERY PROUD OF THE
JOB HE'S DOING AS PRESIDENT.
TRUMP ADDED THAT GOD WAS
PROBABLY LOOKING UP AT US RIGHT
NOW.
SMILING FROM HORN TO HOOF.
ALSO, REMEMBER WHEN PRESIDENT
TRUMP STRAIGHT-UP TOLD US HE WAS
GOING TO HELL?
>> I THINK -- I THINK I'M NOT
MAYBE HEAVEN-BOUND.
>> BUT HE THINKS THAT AFTER THIS
WEEK, GOD IS BACK ON BOARD.
>>> VICE PRESIDENT J.D. VANCE
CRITICIZED PROTESTERS
CONFRONTING I.C.E. OFFICERS,
SAYING THEY SHOULD INSTEAD WRITE
AN OP-ED OR ARGUE ABOUT IT ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
YOU KNOW, JUST LIKE THESE YOUNG
SCHOLARS DID ON JANUARY 6th.
I GET THAT I.C.E. AGENTS ARE
PEOPLE, ALLEGEDLY.
AND THEY HAVE A JOB TO DO.
BUT AT SOME POINT, WHILE YOU'RE
PEPPER SPRAYING OLD LADIES OR
SHOOTING AT A NURSE, DO YOU EVER
STOP AND ASK YOURSELF, ARE WE
DICKS?
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN
INVITING WORLD LEADERS TO JOIN
HIS BOARD OF PEACE, OR BE
CRUSHED BY HIS COUNCIL OF
DESTRUCTION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S BOARD OF PEACE
CONSISTS OF COUNTRIES SUCH AS
RUSSIA AND SAUDI ARABIA, WHICH
IS LIKE IF "LAW AND ORDER SVU"
STARRED DIDDY.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLED OFF
HIS PROPOSED TARIFFS ON EUROPEAN
COUNTRIES WHO OPPOSE HIS DESIRE
TO ACQUIRE GREENLAND.
TRUMP BACKED DOWN AFTER
CONSULTING HIS MOST TRUSTED
ADVISER, THE STOCKS APP.
>>> THE SINGING OF THE U.S.
NATIONAL ANTHEM AT A NBA GAME IN
LONDON WAS INTERRUPTED BY
PROTESTERS YELLING, "LEAVE GIVEN
LAND ALONE."
YOU KNOW WE'VE GONE TOO FAR WHEN
THE BRITISH ARE LIKE, EASY ON
THE COLONIZING, CHUMP.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BECOME
LIKE A GUY ON A DATING APP.
"HEY, GREENLAND, YOU LOOK SO"
GOOD."
GREENLAND'S LIKE, "THANKS."
TRUMP'S LIKE, "SERIOUSLY, I NEED
YOU.
I'D LITERALLY GIVE $700 BILLION
TO BE WITH YOU."
"LOOK, NOT TRYING TO BE MEAN BUT"
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
TRUMP'S LIKE, "I'LL KILL YOU,
YOU UGLY BITCH!"
JUST OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD.
>> YEAH, SURE.
>>> THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE ANNOUNCED THAT NEXT
MONTH, IT WILL DEPOSE GHISLAINE
MAXWELL AS PART OF ITS JEFFREY
EPSTEIN INVESTIGATION.
IN THE MEANTIME, THEY'VE TURNED
OFF THE CAMERAS TO GIVE HER
PRIVACY TO PLAY WITH HER NEW
CHAIR AND LONG ROPE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, TAKE HER SIDE.
>>> WITH GEN-Z TERPS LIKE COOKED
AND AURA GAINING POPULARITY,
OLDER PEOPLE ARE FEELING OUT OF
THE LOOP.
HERE TO ACT AS OUR GEN-Z
TRANSLATER, OUR VERY OWN
MARCELLO HERNANDEZ.
>> YEAH, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S UP, COLIN?
>> WHAT'S UP?
YOU ARE HERE TO TRANSLATE SOME
GEN-Z SLANG IN.
>> YES, I AM, TO HELP OUT OLDER
FOLKS LIKE YOU.
>> WE'RE BASICALLY THE SAME AGE.
>> HA HA, NEVER GIVE UP.
THE FIRST WORD I WANT TO HELP
TRANSLATE IS CHOPPED.
THIS ONE IS BIG.
YOU'VE PROBABLY HEARD IT BEFORE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW CHOPPED, IT'S
THE SHOW ON THE FOOD NETWORK.
>> HA HA, NEVER GIVE UP.
NO, CHOPPED IS AN ADJECTIVE USED
TO DESCRIBE SOMETHING THAT IS
VISUALLY UNAPPEALING.
FOR EXAMPLE, THIS PICTURE OF
COLIN FROM MIDDLE SCHOOL.
IS CHOPPED.
>> DID YOU GET IT FROM MY
PARENTS IN THE JOKE'S ON YOU,
THAT PICTURE IS ACTUALLY OF ME
FROM COLLEGE.
>> WORSE.
BUT THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE EXPERIENCED WHAT WE
CALL A GLO-UP.
YOU WENT FROM BUSTED TO, HEAR ME
OUT, THOUGH.
>> THANKS.
SO HOW ARE YOU NOT -- WHY ARE
YOU NOT TEACHING ANY OF THIS
STUFF TO CHE?
>> CHE KNOWS THIS STUFF BECAUSE
GEN-Z SLANG IS AFRICAN AMERICAN
SLANG.
BASICALLY, BLACK PEOPLE START
SAYING SOMETHING, YOUNG PEOPLE
THINK IT'S COOL SO THEY START
SAYING IT, THEN WHITE PEOPLE SAY
IT.
THEN ONCE ELON MUSK SAYS IT,
IT'S OVER.
>> OH NO, MAN.
THAT'S CAPPED.
¶ TAPS ]
WAIT, WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
>> "CAP" HAS OFFICIALLY PASSED
AWAY.
>> NO, NO!
>> R.I.P., CAP.
>> YOU'RE NOT TEACHING US
ANYTHING, BY THE WAY.
>> OKAY, BOOMER.
MAYBE IT WOULD HELP IF I USE
GEN-Z TERMS TO TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING YOU'RE INTO.
SO WHAT IS ONE OF YOUR
INTERESTS?
>> "REAL HOUSEWIVES OF SALT LAKE
CITY."
SALTY THROUGH AND THROUGH.
AND THEN, I DON'T KNOW, WORLD
WAR II?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO WORLD WAR II.
>> OKAY, SURE.
>> SO, OKAY.
WORLD WAR II, OKAY.
SO BASICALLY, AFTER WORLD WAR I,
GERMANY'S ECONOMY WAS IN A SLOT
ERA.
SO THEY STARTED MOVING OUT OF
POCKET THANKS TO HITLER, WHO WAS
A CERTIFIED CRASHOUT.
THEN HE BECAME THE WORLD'S OP,
SO HE GOT HIGH-KEY
OVERSTIMULATED AND THEN HE
LOW-KEY UNALIVED HIMSELF.
AND THEN EVERYBODY WAS LIKE,
FAH!
>> THAT WAS AWESOME, YEAH.
AND MADE TOTAL SENSE.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY HITLER WAS
CHOPPED.
¶ TAPS ¶
NO, NO, NOT AGAIN, NO.
>> R.I.P. CHOPPED.
>> OH, NO.
OH, GOD.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT, MAN?
STOP PLAYING IN MY FACE, OKAY?
BE SO FOR REAL.
YOU COME TO MY DESK TRYING TO
DRAG ME WHEN YOU'RE THE ONE
SIPPING THE DUMB BITCH JUICE?
OKAY, YOU MUST BE DELULU,
BOO-BOO, I'M ABOUT TO
CUMBERBATCH OUT RIGHT NOW.
FAH!
>> I THINK I SPEAK FOR ALL OF US
WHEN I SAY, THAT WAS REALLY GOOD
AND YOU DID YOUR BEST.
>> OH, THANKS, MAN.
>> BUT I HAVE BAD NEWS FOR YOU,
COLIN.
>> NO!
MARCELLO HERNANDEZ, EVERYONE!
>>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT
DISNEY WORLD'S UPCOMING
VILLAINSLAND WILL FEATURE ICONIC
DISNEY CHARACTERS SUCH AS
MALEFICENT FROM "SLEEPING
BEAUTY," "GASTON FROM "BEAUTY OF
THE BEAST," "JAFAR FROM
ALADDIN, AND MELANIA FROM "THE
INAUGURATION."
>>> A STUDY SHOWS MEN'S DESIRE
FOR SEX PEAKS FROM THEIR 30s TO
EARLY 40s, WHEREAS WOMEN'S
DESIRE FOR SEX PEAKS AFTER
WATCHING A FEW EPISODES OF GAY
HOCKEY.
>>> TAYLOR SWIFT HAS BECOME THE
SECOND-YOUNGEST PERSON INDUCTED
INTO THE SONGWRITERS HALL OF
FAME BEHIND STEVIE WONDER.
BUT THE DIFFERENCE WITH TAYLOR
IS THAT THEY CAN'T JUST SAY THEY
MADE HER A PLAQUE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THOUGHT YOU'D
LIKE THAT.
>>> ACCORDING TO A NEW REPORT,
CHINA'S BIRTH RATE HAS DROPPED
TO ITS LOWEST LEVEL SINCE 1949.
EXPERTS BELIEVE THE DECREASING
NUMBER OF CHINESE CHILDREN COULD
HAVE A DEVASTATING EFFECT ON MY
SNEAKER COLLECTION.
>> THAT GOT THEM BACK.
>>> SAFETY EXPERTS HAVE CREATED
A NEW FEMALE CRASH TEST DUMMY
THAT COULD HELP BETTER PROTECT
WOMEN IN CAR ACCIDENTS.
YOU CAN TELL THE DUMMY IS FEMALE
BECAUSE SOMETIMES IT JUST PUTS
THE CAR IN PARK AND CRIES A
LITTLE.
>>> AN EAGLE SCOUT IN MISSOURI
HAS EARNED 140 BADGES, WHICH IS
EVERY POSSIBLE MERIT BADGE.
HE ALSO SET THE RECORD FOR MOST
MOLESTED BOYS.
I'M KIDDING!
YOUR RECORD'S UNBREAKABLE,
COLIN.
>>> A SWISS COMPANY HAS
INTRODUCED A NEW SUICIDE POD
DESIGNED FOR COUPLES.
IT'S MUCH MORE AFFORDABLE THAN
THE SUICIDE POD FOR SINGLE MEN.
>>> A VIDEO HAS GONE VERTICAL OF
A MYSTERIOUS DOUGH RITO-SHAPED
AIRCRAFT FLYING OVER AREA 51.
IT'S CALLED A TRIANGLE, SAD-ASS!
>>> A MEMORIAL SERVICE WAS HELD
IN SAN FRANCISCO FOR CLAUDE, A
BELOVED ALBINOAL BAITER AT THE
COLORADO ACADEMY OF SCIENCES
THAT RECENTLY DIED, BUT HIS
MEMORY WILL LIVE ON IN MY
GORGEOUS NEW BOOTS.
>>> CHANNING TATUM ANNOUNCED
THAT A STAGE VERSION OF "MAGIC
MIKE" WILL BE OPENING SOON IN
NEW YORK CITY.
A US OPENING SOON, YOUR AUNT.
>>> A RECENT STUDY SHOWS THAT
MANY AMERICANS ARE AFRAID TO
VOICE THEIR OPINIONS IN FEAR OF
BACKLASH.
HERE TO SPEAK HIS MIND WITHOUT
HOLDING BACK IS MR. ON BLAST.
>> HELLO, COLLEEN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M MR. ON BLAST, AND I AIN'T
AFRAID OF SHARING AN OPINION OR
TWO.
SO GET READY, 'CAUSE NO ONE IS
SAFE FROM BEING PUT -- ON BLAST!
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, GO AHEAD.
DO YOUR WORST.
>> FIRST UP, BILLIONAIRES.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
YOU'RE RICH.
WE GET IT.
I MEAN, WHAT DOES THE "B" IN
BILLIONAIRE EVEN STAND FOR,
BIDIOT?
HEY, "B" WORDS, YOUR HEDGE FUND
IS HEDGE DUMB.
ON BLAST!
>> I'M SORRY -- HEDGE DUMB?
THAT WAS YOUR BEST TAKEDOWN OF
BILLIONAIRES?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T HOLD BACK.
>> AND BABY, WE'RE JUST GETTING
STARTED.
>> DON'T CALL ME BABY.
>> OKAY, OKAY BABY.
NEXT UP, BIG PHARMA.
IBUPROFEN?
MORE LIKE I BE PUTTING YOU ON
BLAST!
>> IBUPROFEN?
YOUR TAKEDOWN OF BIG PHARMA IS
IBUPROFEN?
>> OH, BABY COLLEEN, YOU WANT ME
TO DIG IN?
WELL, HOW ABOUT THIS?
NEXT UP, CHINESE MEN.
>> OH, GOD.
>> I SAW ON THE NEWS THAT
CHINA'S BIRTH RATE IS AT AN
ALL-TIME LOW.
WHAT, BOYS, YOU CAN'T GET IT UP?
HEY, CHINA, GIVE ME 20 MINUTES
ALONE WITH YOUR MEN, AND I'LL
SHOW THEM A THING OR TWO.
>> YOU WANT 20 MINUTES ALONE
WITH ALL THE MEN IN CHINA?
>> NO, NO, I MEAN LIKE -- I'M
TRYING TO SAY LIKE -- MEN, IF
YOU'RE HAVING SEXUAL PERFORMANCE
ISSUES, CLEAN YOUR CALENDARS
BECAUSE I WILL BLAST YOU UNTIL
YOU ARE HARD!
>> STOP!
STOP.
>> EXACTLY.
>> STOP ENABLING HIM.
THAT CANNOT POSSIBLY BE WHAT YOU
MEANT TO SAY.
>> COME ON, MAN, GIVE ME A
BREAK.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I ACTUALLY -- I BET IT IS HARD.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE OUT HERE
LOOKING LIKE A BLACKJACK DEALER
ON A DISNEY CRUISE.
ON BLAST!
>> THAT WAS -- THAT WAS REALLY
GOOD, MAN.
>> REALLY?
>> PSYCH, NO.
THAT WAS HEDGE DUMB.
ON BLAST!
>> ARE YOU -- ARE YOU DONE?
MR. BLAST, EVERYONE!
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I'M MIC
AND TO OUR NEW SON-IN-LAW,
KEITH.
FROM NOW ON, CALL ME DAD.
>> AND YOU CAN CONTINUE TO CALL
ME CAROL.
>> THANKS, DAD.
>> THANKS, CAROL.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL FOOD WILL BE
SERVED SHORTLY.
THE KITCHEN JUST NEEDS A FEW
MORE MINUTES TO MICROWAVE THE
STEAK.
IN THE MEANTIME, THE COUPLE
WANTS TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
>> THANK YOU ALL FOR JOINING US
ON OUR SPECIAL DAY, AND WE
WANTED TO GIVE SOMEONE A SPECIAL
SHOUT-OUT.
HE TURNED 87 LAST WEEK.
JUST HAD BOTH OF HIS KNEES
REPLACED, BUT HE CAME ALL THE
WAY FROM DETROIT.
KEITH'S GRANDPA JACKSON.
>> I WANT TO MEET THIS NEW GIRL.
>> WANT TO SEE YOU ON THE DANCE
FLOOR BUSTING A MOVE, GRANDPA.
>> MORE LIKELY TO BUST A HIP
THAN MOVE.
>> YEAH, MY DAD'S GOT JOKES,
HUH?
>> NOW LET'S DANCE!
>> OH-OH, WELL, YOU HEARD THE
BRIDE, FOLKS.
LET'S GET THINGS STARTED WITH A
LITTLE EARTH, WIND, AND FIRE!
>> OH, MAN.
HARD TO BELIEVE MY BOY'S ALL
GROWN UP, HUH, DAD?
>> THEY'RE PLAYING MY SONG.
>> WHAT?
THE GROOVE GOT ME!
EVERYBODY OUT OF THE GODDAMN
WAY!
>> WHOA, GRANDPA JACKSON'S ON
THE FLOOR!
>> GO, GRANDPA!
GO, GRANDPA!
>> OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, DADDY.
LET'S SIT BACK DOWN BEFORE YOU
GET HURT, NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, SON.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SON.
Y'ALL KIDS HAVE SOME FUN NOW.
GIVE ME A GLASS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HEY, Y'ALL.
LET'S KEEP THINGS GOING RIGHT
NOW.
HOW ABOUT WE GROOVE, HUH?
>> OH!
THIS MY SONG!
>> WAIT --
>> THIS MY SONG!
>> I THOUGHT THE LAST ONE WAS
YOUR SONG.
>> THEY GOT THE GROOVE IN ME.
>> OH-OH.
¶ LET'S GROOVE TONIGHT ¶
>> COME HERE, BRIDE!
>> OKAY.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> COME ON, CUPCAKE!
>> OKAY.
>> PUT YOUR HANDS ON ME.
THERE WE GO.
>> OKAY, GRANDPA.
YOU DONE HAVE SOME FUN.
>> GO AWAY.
>> COME ON.
>> HONESTLY, I DON'T MIND.
>> BUT I DO.
GRANDPA!
>> OKAY.
>> YES, THAT'S YOUR NEW
GRANDDAUGHTER THAT YOU'RE
FREAKING ON.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SON, YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAKING A FOOL OF MYSELF HERE.
Y'ALL KIDS HAVE FUN, Y'ALL.
>> ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE TIME FOR
GRANDPA JACKSON, Y'ALL.
HE'S WORKING HARD OUT THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHILE HE'S TAKING A BREAK, THE
REST OF US ARE GOING TO HEAD
DOWN TO A BOOGIE WONDERLAND.
>> HEY, STOP PLAYING EARTH, WIND
& FIRE!
>> IF ANYONE KNOWS A SONG THAT'S
NOT ONE OF GRANDPA'S SONGS, FEEL
FREE TO STOP BY THE BOOTH, LET
ME KNOW!
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
DADDY!
>> OH, OH, MY GOD!
DAD!
IS ANYBODY HERE A DOCTOR?
>> I AM.
KINDA.
OH, I'M AFRAID THIS MAN'S BONES
ARE ALL GONE.
THEY ALL BROKE AT ONCE AND
TURNED TO POWDER.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO FOR
HIM.
>> BUT MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING I
CAN DO.
>> CHEERS FOR GRANDPA JACKSON,
Y'ALL!
>> GO GRANDPA!
GO GRANDPA!
>>> YOU LOVE "SURVIVOR" SO GET
READY FOR ANGST'S NEW
COMPETITION SHOW, "BACKSTAB
ISLAND."
>> I'M HERE TO GET RICH, NOT
MAKE FRIENDS.
>> I'M A FOX, BUT I'LL SNAKE MY
WAY TO THE TOP OF THE ISLAND.
>> OUT HERE, MY GREATEST
ADVANTAGE IS MY PERSONALITY
DISORDER.
>> ISLANDERS CHEAT AND BETRAY TO
WIN THE BACKSTAB CROWN.
>> OUT HERE, I DON'T NEED
FRIENDS.
>> I AM NOT HERE TO MAKE
>> AND ME, I AM HERE TO MAKE
FRIENDS.
IT'S THE ONLY REASON I'M HERE.
I LOVE PEOPLE.
>> I'LL TAKE YOU DOWN.
I DON'T CARE WHO YOU ARE OR
WHERE YOU'RE FROM.
>> I DO CARE WHO YOU ARE, AND I
DO CARE WHERE YOU'RE FROM.
'CAUSE I WANT TO HANG OUT ONCE
THE SHOW IS OVER AND WE ALL GET
BACK HOME TO L.A.
>> ON THIS ISLAND, TRUST NO ONE.
>> I'M HERE TO BURN BRIDGES AND
SHOW MY BODY OFF ON TV.
>> AND I'M HERE BECAUSE MY
COLLEGE FRIENDS HAVE DRIFTED
APART, AND I'M VERY LONELY.
I'M LOOKING TO HANG OUT WITH YOU
GUYS BACK IN L.A.
>> I NEED THE PRIZE MONEY 'CAUSE
MY DAD IS SICK.
PSYCH!
MY DAD'S NOT SICK, AND I HATE
THAT BITCH!
>> I DON'T NEED THE MONEY.
I HAVE PLENTY AFTER THE THING
THAT I DID WHEN MY COLLEGE
FRIENDS STOPPED TALKING TO ME.
>> IF YOU THOUGHT THE GUAVA
JUICE WOULDN'T BE FLYING THIS
SEASON, THINK AGAIN.
>> YOU TOLD JEN ABOUT MY
IMMUNITY?
YOU BITCH.
>> I TRUSTED YOU TO KEEP MY
INKEYE A SECRET, YOU BITCH.
>> I'M NOT HANGING OUT WITH YOU,
YOU BITCH.
>> THEN WHY DID YOU THROW A
DRINK AT ME?
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> SKILLS WILL BE PUT TO THE
TEST.
>> I'M OFF MY MEDS AND ON MY
PERIOD.
MY STRENGTH?
I WILL LITERALLY BITE YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU PUSHED ME!
OR DID I PUSH HER?
>> AND MY STRENGTH, I CAN HOOK
UP WITH FRIENDS AND NOT EVEN BE
WEIRD ABOUT IT THE NEXT DAY.
I CAN JOKE ABOUT IT OR JUST BE
QUIET, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU TAKE THE LEAD, AND I'LL
FOLLOW.
>> THAT'S A LIE.
WE HOOKED UP, AND SHE WAS SUPER
WEIRD ABOUT IT THE NEXT DAY.
>> IT'S STAB OR BE STABBED, SO
TUNE IN TO FIND OUT WHO WINS.
>> I'M GONNA WIN.
>> NO, I'M GONNA WIN.
>> SORRY, BOYS THAT MONEY'S
MINE.
SERIOUSLY?
I'M GETTING A RASH!
>> IS THIS ONE OF THESE SHOWS
WHERE YOU WIN GAMES OR HAVE
SECOND WITH PEOPLE?
I'M DOING BOTH.
>> "BACKSTAB ISLAND."
WE WILL SHOW SHARK ATTACKS WHEN
THEY HAPPEN.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, GEESE!
¶ I TRIED
I TRIED
SO HARD ¶
¶ I TRIED
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶
¶ THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶
¶ WHEN I WENT DEAF
WHEN I WENT DEAF
I JUST I USED MY EYES ¶
¶ BUT THOSE BASTARDS
STOOD ME IN A LONG LONG LONG
LONG LONG LONG
GOVERNMENT LINE ¶
¶ TILL I WENT
COMPLETELY BLIND ¶
¶ GET IN
LET'S DRIVE
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶
¶ THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶
¶ ON AND ON AND ON AND ON
ON AND ON AND ON AND ON
ON AND ON AND ON
ON AND ON AND ON ¶
¶ YEAH
MY SON IS IN BED
MY DAUGHTERS ARE DEAD
MY WIFE'S IN THE SHED ¶
¶ MY HUSBAND'S LICKING
THE LEAD OF THE WALL
AND THE REST ARE FORCE-FED
OR ELSE BAKED INTO BREAD ¶
¶ AND NOTHING'S BEEN SAID
FOR FOUR AND A HALF DAYS ¶
¶ WHEN THAT LIGHT TURNS RED
I'M DRIVING AWAY
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR ¶¶
THERE'S A BOMB IN MY CAR
¶ OH HEY-EY-EY
THANK YOU ¶¶
BEYOND THE HEADLINES WHERE WE
GO INTO THIS WEEK'S NEWS AND GET
A LITTLE DEEPER.
I'M MICHELLE DIXON.
WITH ME FROM "THE GUARDIAN,"
CHRISTOPHER WILKINS.
FROM "THE ATLANTIC," JACKIE
DONNELLY.
AND CALVIN EMMANUEL FROM "THE
CHICAGO TRIBUNE."
>> GREAT TO BE WITH YOU,
MICHELLE.
>> WELL, LET'S START IN
MINNEAPOLIS WHERE I.C.E.
CONTINUES TO RAID HOMES AND
BUSINESSES IN WHAT SOME PEOPLE
ARE CALLING AN OCCUPATION.
CHRISTOPHER, YOUR TAKE ON THIS?
>> MICHELLE, THE FIRST WORD THAT
COMES TO MIND IS UNPRECEDENTED.
I MEAN, YOU'VE GOT FEDERAL
OFFICERS ROAMING THE STREETS
JUST PULLING PEOPLE OUT OF THEIR
CARS BASED ON HOW THEY LOOK.
I MEAN, THIS JUST DOESN'T HAPPEN
IN AMERICA.
>> HM.
>> YEAH, WELL -- I MEAN -- I
KNOW IT HAPPENS WITH SOME
POLICE.
THERE ARE CERTAINLY BAD COPS OUT
THERE, OF COURSE.
BUT THIS IS AN ENTIRE FEDERAL
FORCE WEAPONIZED AGAINST THE
PEOPLE IT'S SUPPOSED TO PROTECT.
IT'S INSANE.
>> HM.
>> OKAY, RIGHT, SURE.
OKAY.
BUT THE DIFFERENCE HERE IS THESE
OFFICERS ARE MARCHING THROUGH
NEIGHBORHOODS WITH THE EXPRESS
MISSION OF JUST STIRRING THINGS
UP SO THEY CAN VIOLENTLY ARREST
PEOPLE.
THAT'S NEW.
>> HM.
>> OKAY, I MEAN -- YOU GUYS KNOW
WHAT I MEAN, THOUGH.
CAN SOMEONE ELSE GO, PLEASE?
>> VERY WELL.
JACKIE, ON SUNDAY, ANTI-I.C.E.
PROTESTERS INTERRUPTED A CHURCH
SERVICE.
NOW THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
ARRESTED TWO PEOPLE.
ARE TACTICS LIKE THIS HURTING
THEIR CAUSE?
>> I MEAN, IT'S UNLIKELY.
THIS WAS AN ISOLATED INCIDENT
AND PROBABLY WON'T SLOW THE
MOVEMENT DOWN.
I MEAN, LET'S BE HONEST.
NOT A LOT OF DEMOCRATS GO TO
CHURCH ANYMORE.
>> HM.
>> I MEAN, OF COURSE DEMOCRATS
GO TO CHURCH.
BUT IT'S A COMMUNITY THING.
IT'S NOT JUST ALL ABOUT JESUS.
>> HM!
>> SHE SAID CHURCH AIN'T ABOUT
JESUS?
>> COLOR ME SURPRISED.
>> I KNOW IT'S ABOUT JESUS, IT'S
JUST LEFT-LEANING CHURCHES ARE
NOT, YOU KNOW, SO POLITICAL.
>> HM!
>> OKAY, STOP.
THAT'S NOT AT ALL WHAT I MEANT.
>> RIGHT, I MEAN, JACKIE KNOWS
VERY WELL THAT ALL KINDS OF
PEOPLE ATTEND CHURCH.
>> YES.
>> IF IT MATTERS, I'VE STARTED
GOING AGAIN.
>> REALLY?
GOOD FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
EVER SINCE THEY CHANGED IT SO
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DRESS UP
ANYMORE.
I MEAN, HOW NICE IS IT TO WEAR
JEANS TO CHURCH, RIGHT?
>> HM!
>> LET'S MOVE ON TO
INTERNATIONAL NEWS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
CONTINUES TO TRY AND TAKE OVER
GREENLAND DESPITE FORCED
OPPOSITION FROM EUROPE.
JACKIE, HOW DOES THIS END?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I DO KNOW,
IT'S LIKELY A VIOLATION OF
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
YOU CAN'T JUST POINT TO A
COUNTRY AND SAY, HEY, THAT'S
OURS NOW!
>> HM.
>> I MEAN, SOME COUNTRIES DO
THAT, BUT NOT AMERICA.
>> HM!
>> REALLY.
>> HAS SHE MET AMERICA?
>> OKAY, ENOUGH.
WILL YOU GUYS PLEASE STOP MAKING
THE NOISES?
>> NOISES?
WHO'S MAKING NOISES?
>> I'M SORRY, I DON'T HEAR A
PEEP.
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY MAKING
NOISES, AND IT'S DISTRACTING.
CAN I AT LEAST GET THROUGH MY
POINT WITHOUT THE NOISES?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
GO AHEAD, AND I PROMISE WE WON'T
SAY A WORD.
>> NOT A WORD.
>> THANK YOU.
ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT DONALD
TRUMP MAY WANT TO JUST TAKE
SOMEONE ELSE'S LAND THROUGH
GREED AND AGGRESSION, BUT THE
REST OF US DON'T.
WE'RE AMERICA.
THIS IS NOT WHO WE ARE.
>> HM!
>> OKAY.
I THINK THAT GUY JUST MADE A
NOISE.
>> SORRY, JACKIE, I'LL ASK OUR
CAMERAMAN DARIUS NOT TO
INTERRUPT.
>> I'M SORRY, AIN'T KNOW Y'ALL
WAS DOING THAT.
>> LET'S TAKE A BREAK TO THANK
OUR CORE BROUGHT SPONSORS.
WHEN WE RETURN, WE'LL TALK TO A
WOMAN WHOSE JOB WAS REPLACED BY
A.I.
NOT A COMPUTER, THE FORMER NBA
PLAYER ALLEN IVERSON.
CHARGED AS MEETING THE PARENTS.
>> GOD, I'M JUST SO NERVOUS.
>> DON'T BE NERVOUS, THEY'RE
GOING TO LOVE YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I JUST REALLY WANT TO MAKE A
GOOD IMPRESSION.
>> YOU WILL.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO GREAT.
THEY'RE GOING TO LOVE YOU.
JUST ONE THING.
MY DAD'S FROM THE SOUTH.
>> THE SOUTH?
>> YEAH, SO HE'S PRETTY
OLD-FASHIONED.
SO JUST DON'T TALK POLITICS,
OKAY?
>> NO POLITICS.
>> I CAN DO THAT.
>> MOM, DAD, WE'RE HOME!
>> OH!
>> AVA, THERE'S MY LITTLE GIRL.
>> AND THIS MUST BE THE GUY THAT
WE'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT.
I HOPE THE DRIVE WASN'T TOO BAD.
>> IT WASN'T.
>> Y'ALL MADE GREAT TIME COMING
UP HERE.
Y'ALL TAKE 87?
>> Y'ALL TAKE 87?
>> WELL, LET'S JUST MOVE ON.
>> FRESHERING A JAB RABBIT --
THAT'S LITERALLY HOW YOU TALK.
>> WE HAVE TO BREAK UP NOW.
>> BUT WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
BREAKING UP WAS MY GOAL HERE?
RELATIONSHIPS ARE HARD, AND MEN
ARE COWARDS.
SOMETIMES YOU WANT TO BREAK UP
BUT IT WOULD BE EASIER IF SHE
BROKE UP WITH YOU.
I'LL BE TEACHING YOU HOW TO BLOW
IT SO BAD, YOUR RELATIONSHIP
EXPLODES.
WITH METHODS FROM MY NEW BOOK,
"50 WAYS TO GET YOUR LOVER TO"
LEAVE YOU BECAUSE LEAVING YOUR
LOVER IS HARD BECAUSE YOU LOVE
YOUR LOVER SO WHY NOT GET YOUR
LOVER TO LEAVE NOW?
YOU WANT TO CAPITALIZE ON HIGHLY
CHARGED MOMENTS LIKE MEETING HER
PARENTS.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH
YOU?
>> OUT TO LUNCH, STILL AM NOT
FINE.
>> BUT ANOTHER HIGHLY CHARGED
MOMENT IS VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> BABE, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO.
>> OH, I DID.
I JUST -- I SAW IT, AND I
IMMEDIATELY THOUGHT OF YOU.
>> 100 TAMPONS?
>> A VERY CHARGED MOMENT IS A
FAMILY FUNERAL.
IF YOU WANT TO END YOUR
RELATIONSHIP, TRY SHOWING UP
DRESSED AS A MEMBER OF THE
LUMINEERS.
IF YOU'RE JUST STARTING THE DAY,
BLOWING IT CAN BE AS SIMPLE
AS WEARING SOMETHING THAT MAKES
YOU SEEM GROSS.
>> SHOULD WE DO A BOTTLE?
GOING TO HIT THE RESTROOM.
>> HERE'S ONE.
THE NEXT TIME SHE COMES TO YOU
FOR ADVICE ON A COMPLEX
EMOTIONAL PROBLEM, RESPOND
SIMPLY WITH AN IMPRESSION OF THE
SORTING HAT FROM HARRY POTTER.
>> SHE IS STILL MY GRANDMOTHER,
BUT SHE DOESN'T RECOGNIZE MY
FACE.
>> HEY, HEY.
>> REMEMBER, THESE SITUATIONS
COULD ALWAYS BE MADE WORSE WITH
A HARD PIVOT TO A SIMPLE
QUESTION.
>> GREAT TIME COMING UP HERE --
>> OH, BE IT NOW?
GRACE DAVIS, WOULD YOU BE OPEN
UP TO OPENING UP OUR
RELATIONSHIP?
>> WHAT IF AFTER THAT SHE STILL
HASN'T BOUNCED?
AFTER TRYING EVERY METHOD IN THE
BOOK --
>> DUDE, MY FORESKIN IS KILLING
ME.
>> AND YOU STILL WANT TO BREAK
UP WITH HER BECAUSE ONE TIME SHE
GAVE YOU THE ICK.
>> ME HUNGRY FOR NACHOS!
>> REMEMBER, THERE'S ALWAYS THE
LAST-MINUTE HAIL MARY.
SHOWING UP ON YOUR WEDDING DAY
WITH A BOTCHED CHIN IMPLANT.
>> WOW.
I ASKED FOR THE JON HAMM, AND I
GOT THE JAY LENO, BROTHER.