>>> OKAY, GANG.
IF ANYONE HAS TO USE THE
BATHROOM, DO IT NOW.
WE'VE GOT ANOTHER TWO HOURS
BEFORE WE GET TO GRANDMA'S.
I'M JUST GOING TO FILL UP THE
TANK.
>> FILL UP?
NOT ALL THE WAY THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> WE HAVE TO.
>> BUT IT'S $5 A GALLOP.
>> I SAID WE HAVE TO!
>> KIDS, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
LEAVE ONE OF YOU BEHIND.
>> WHAT?
WHY?
>> GAS PRICES, DARLING.
>> DAD, WHY DOES GAS COST SO
MUCH?
>> THE EPSTEIN FILES!
KIDDING.
BUT POSSIBLY NOT.
IT'S CALLED BUTTERFLY EFFECT,
RIGHT?
EPSTEIN WAS FIRST DOMINO.
EPSTEIN, BING BING, BONG BONG,
BING BING, BONG BONG, WAR!
ANYWAY, IT'S ME, DONALD TRUMP.
YOU MIGHT REMEMBER ME FROM SUCH
CAMPAIGN PROMISES AS,
LOWER GAS
PRICES.
AND, NO MORE WARS.
PSYCH!
WE LOVE TO MAKE PROMISES
BECAUSE A PROMISE IS JUST A LIE THAT
HASN'T HAPPENED YET.
PUT NOW IT HAS.
AND GAS COSTS LIKE A MILLION
BILLION DOLLARS A GALLON.
AND AS FOR THE STOCK MARKET, LET
ME PUT IT IN A WAY
THAT THE
HARRY STYLES FANS IN THE CROWD
TONIGHT WILL UNDERSTAND.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO LOVE THIS
ONE.
THE STOCK MARKET IS GOING IN ONE
DIRECTION.
DOWN!
DOWN, I SAID.
YOU DON'T KNOW YOU'RE BROKE AS
HELL.
SORRY, I'M NOT FAMILIAR WITH HIS
NEWER MUSIC.
I AM STRAIGHT.
ANYWAY.
WHAT WERE WE TALKING ABOUT?
OH, YES, GAS PRICES,
WHICH ARE
VERY HIGH BECAUSE OF WAR WITH
IRAN.
WHICH IS WHERE THEY MAKE GAS.
I WISH SOMEONE HAD TOLD ME THAT.
BUT WE WILL WIN THIS WAR BECAUSE
IRAN IS OLD AND NOBODY LIKES
THEM.
IRAN IS LIKE BALLET AND OPERA
AND WEIRD TIMMY CHALAMET.
WOW, WOW THEM DOWN, TIMMY.
WHICH IS FRANKLY THE BEST TIME
TO KICK.
LOOK AT THE GAS BACK THERE.
FROZEN IN ONE OF THESE.
LOOK AT MARCELLO.
HE'S STILL PLAYING KIDS.
SNL'S LITTLE CHIHUAHUA.
THAT SOUNDS RACIST, BUT IT IS.
I'M A RACIST GUY, A RACIST GUY.
HOW ABOUT ASHLEY PADILLA?
LAST NAME SOUNDS SPANISH,
BUT
TAKE A LOOK AT HER, FOLKS,
WHAT'S THE WHITEST WHITE.
HAIRCUT!
WE HAVE HAIRCUT!
POINT IS, I HAVE EVERYTHING
UNDER CONTROL, OKAY?
I'VE BEEN MEETING WITH THE
NATION'S TOP MINDS.
JAKE PAUL.
HE WAS BOOED VERY BADLY AT THE
MIKE TYSON FIGHT.
WE HATE TO HEAR BOOS.
>> DID SOMEONE SAY BOOZE?
I HAD A COUPLE OF ROAD SODAS,
CHILL.
>> PETE HEGSETH, AS I LIVE AND
STRUGGLE TO BREATHE.
>> BEFORE WE BEGIN,
I WANT TO THANK YOU SINCERELY FOR THE
BEAUTIFUL
SIZE 16 FLORSCHEIM
SHOES.
THEY FIT ME LIKE A GLOVE.
>> HAPPY TO DO IT.
>> A CLOWN'S GLOVE.
IF YOU'RE WONDERING WHY I WAS IN
THE BACK SEAT OF THIS RANDOM
FAMILY'S CAR, I'LL TELL YOU THE
SAME THING I SAY WHEN PEOPLE ASK
ABOUT OUR PLANS FOR IRAN.
I DON'T KNOW!
>> ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
WELL, I'M GOING TO WANDER
AROUND.
>> GREAT.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING, SIR.
THE PRESIDENT CALLED ME HERE
TODAY TO GIVE YOU NEWS ON THE
WAR, OKAY, SO LISTEN UP.
THE NEWS IS, WE WON.
#WINNING.
YOU CAN STOP ASKING ME ALL ABOUT
IT, OKAY?
DON'T EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
FUGGETABOUDIT.
THE REAL PROBLEM IS, ALL YOU
GAYBIES -- GAY BABIES,
COPYRIGHT --
ALL YOU GAYBIES IN THE MEDIA ARE
COMPLETELY UNPATRIOTIC.
THEY'RE USING WHAT I DO AND SAY
TO MAKE ME LOOK LIKE A FOOL.
>> BEEN THERE.
I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE, PARTNER.
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN THERE A
LOT.
YOU KNOW, THE PRESS SAYS WE
BOMBED A SCHOOL?
I JUST BLAME IT ON THE
AYATOLLAH.
ALSO ON ALCOHOL.
ALL YOU DWEEBS STOP SAYING THE
STRAIT OF HORMUZ IS CLOSED.
IT'S WIDE OPEN.
SURE, THERE'S A BUNCH OF LAND
MINES FLOATING IN THE WATER.
WATER MINES, I GUESS.
BUT IF YOU'RE AN OIL TANKER AND
YOU'RE DRIVING IT AND YOU SEE
ONE OF THE MINES, JUST DO WHAT I
USED TO DO AT EVERY DUI
CHECKPOINT, CLOSE YOUR EYES AND
GUN IT.
>> BACK TO THE GAS STATION
SCENE.
KIDDING, OF COURSE.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
>> Announcer: IT'S "SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE" WITH --
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- HARRY
STYLES!
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S SO GREAT TO BE BACK HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE FOR A
SECOND TIME.
I COULDN'T RESIST WHEN I HEARD
THEY BOOKED MY FAVORITE-EVER
MUSICAL GUEST.
I FINISHED MY LAST TOUR IN 2023,
AND AFTER THAT, I TOOK A BUNCH
OF TIME OFF.
I REALIZED I'D SPENT HALF MY
LIFE IN MUSIC.
TOURING, CREATING ALBUMS, AND
MAKING SONGS ABOUT FRUIT THAT
PEOPLE THINK WERE ABOUT SEX.
I JUST REALLY LIKE FRUIT, GUYS.
I LIKE SEX, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU'RE ON HOLIDAY,
IT'S LIKE 5:00 IN THE AFTERNOON,
YOU'RE ALL COVERED IN SAND, YOU
AND YOUR PARTNER ARE ALL SWEATY
AND HOT AND YOU STUMBLE BACK TO
THE ROOM.
YOU JUST WANT TO, MM, PAPAYA.
BACK THEN, PEOPLE SEEMED TO PAY
A LOT OF ATTENTION TO THE
CLOTHES I WAS WEARING.
AND SOME PEOPLE ACCUSED ME OF
SOMETHING CALLED QUEER BAITING.
BUT DID IT EVER OCCUR TO YOU
THAT MAYBE YOU DON'T KNOW
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME, DAD?
I RAN IT BY, HE WAS FINE WITH
IT.
I GET ASKED A LOT ABOUT WHAT
I'VE BEEN UP TO ON THIS BREAK.
HONESTLY, I LEARNED A LOT ABOUT
MYSELF.
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN I'M SOMEONE
WHO TALKS RATHER SLOWLY.
I'VE FOUND OUT IT'S NOT THAT.
I'M DIRECTLILY BORING.
I TOOK UP JOGGING.
THERE'S NOTHING INTERESTING
ABOUT THAT.
BUT BECAUSE I'M ME, PEOPLE
PRETEND TO FIND THAT
INTERESTING.
BUT I DON'T RUN TO BE
I DO IT FOR THE FEELING IT GIVES
ME.
THAT RUNNER'S HIGH.
JUST AMAZING.
WATERMELON SUGAR HIGH.
RUNNER'S HIGH.
AND IF THAT DOESN'T DO IT FOR
YOU, I ALSO LOVE ECSTASY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
AS A BRITISH MAN WHO'S SPENT A
LOT OF HIS LIFE IN THE PUBLIC
EYE, I CAN ASSURE YOU THERE'S
SOMETHING NICE ABOUT BEING
BORING.
BETTER THAN THE ALTERNATIVE.
DURING MY BREAK, I FOUND A NEW
HOME IN A SMALL OLD ITALIAN
VILLAGE.
IT HAS 11 FULL-TIME RESIDENTS,
WHICH IS REALLY FUN.
IT'S PRETTY COOL TO BE ABLE TO
SAY YOU'VE HAD SEX WITH 100% OF
THE PEOPLE IN YOUR TOWN.
BUT I'M VERY, VERY HAPPY TO BE
BACK AT WORK NOW.
I HAVE A NEW ALBUM OUT.
IT'S CALLED "KISS ALL THE TIME,
DISCO, OCCASIONALLY."
AND SOME PEOPLE HAVE ASKED ME
WHERE I GOT THAT TITLE FROM.
AND I'LL LET YOU GUYS BE THE
FIRST TO KNOW, I DID A PROMPT ON
CHATGPT THAT SAID, "GIVE ME THE
MOST ITALIAN PHRASE TO EVER
EXIST."
AND IT CAME BACK WITH --
AND I LOVED IT.
BECAUSE WHAT'S BETTER THAN
KISSING ALL THE TIME?
WHICH I DON'T REALLY DO.
I DON'T WANT TO KISS ALL THE
TIME.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES KISSING CAN BE
GREAT.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE REALLY GOOD
AT IT AND YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
OR IF YOU HAVE A TIGHT LITTLE
BUM.
>> HEY, BUD.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP HERE?
>> YOU SAID TIGHT LITTLE BUM.
WHERE'S MY KISS?
>> COME ON, THEN.
EVERYONE KNOWS THERE'S NOTHING
LITTLE ABOUT THAT THANG.
YOU'RE HAUL AGHDAM WAGON PACK
THERE.
>> FACT.
>> WHATEVER, COME HERE.
NOW, THAT'S QUEER BAITING.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
I'M HERE, AND I'M HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
DONOVAN.
IS THE PROSECUTION READY TO
PRESENT ITS CASE?
>> IT IS, YOUR HONOR.
AND LET ME JUST SAY, IT'S MY
HONOR TO BE HERE.
>> NO.
NO.
NONE OF THAT.
DON'T BE CUTE.
THIS IS A COURTROOM.
NOW OVER TO THE DEFENDANT.
MR. DONOVAN, SINCE YOU DID NOT
HAVE AN ATTORNEY, THE COURT HAS
APPOINTED YOU A PUBLIC DEFENDER.
>> THANK YOU, YOUR HONOR.
>> BUT BEFORE HE GETS HERE, I
SHOULD PROBABLY WARN YOU.
HE'S SEBASTIAN MANISCALCO.
>> THE WORLD-FAMOUS COMEDIAN?
>> YES, BUT I PROMISE HE'S
NOTHING LIKE WHAT YOU'VE SEEN ON
TV.
BAILIFF, PLEASE LET HIM IN.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA TO BELIEVE
THIS.
I'M A LAWYER NOW.
I WENT TO NIGHT SCHOOL, AND I
BASHED THE BEST.
I CANCELED A GIG TO BE HERE, AND
MY AGENT WAS LIKE, WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT?
>> HA HA HA!
SEBASTIAN, YOU ARE A CHARACTER.
NOW ON TO THE MUCH LESS
DELIGHTFUL PROSECUTOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M A LITTLE THROWN.
DIDN'T EXPECT THE PUBLIC
DEFENDER TO BE SEBASTIAN
MANISCALCO.
BUT YOUR HONOR, THE CASE IS
SIMPLE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> FEBRUARY 19th, MR. DONOVAN
WALKED INTO A DEPARTMENT
STORE --
>> ALLEGEDLY.
>> AND WALKED OUT CARRYING
$5,000 WORTH OF STOLEN
MERCHANDISE.
>> WHO KNOWS IF THAT'S TRUE.
>> INCLUDING A DESIGNER SUIT,
SHOES, AND A BELT.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING
ABOUT A BELT, OKAY?
WHEN I WAS A KID, THE BELT
WASN'T TO KEEP THE PANTS UP.
IT WAS TO KEEP THE VOLUME DOWN.
OKAY?
I NEVER SAW MY DAD PUT THE BELT
ON.
I ONLY SAW HIM TAKE IT OFF.
IN MY DAY, I DON'T KNOW IF YOUR
DAD DID THIS, I DON'T KNOW IF
YOUR DAD DID THIS, BUT MY DAD,
HE USED TO POP IT TWICE.
HE USED TO GO POP, POP!
AND THEN IT WAS BELT TO ASS!
>> YOUR HONOR, NONE OF THAT WAS
RELEVANT.
I KNOW THE JURY COULDN'T
POSSIBLY FOLLOW WHAT HE WAS
SAYING.
>> VERY WELL.
WOULD THE COURT STENOGRAPHER
READ IT BACK, PLEASE?
>> I NEVER SAW MY DAD PUT THE
BELT ON I ONLY SAW HIM TAKE IT
OFF AND MY DAD I DON'T KNOW IF
YOUR DAD DID THIS BUT MY DAD I
DON'T KNOW IF YOUR DAD DID THIS
BUT MY DAD I DON'T KNOW IF YOUR
DAD DID THIS BUT MY DAD HE WOULD
SNAP IT TWICE POP POP AND THEN
BELT TO ASS.
>> IS THE BABY HAPPY NOW?
>> WHAT?
>> YOUR HONOR, WOULD THE DEFENSE
ATTORNEY MIND NOT MOVING AROUND
SO MUCH?
I'M HAVING TROUBLE DRAWING HIM.
>> HEY, PICASSO, DO ME A FAVOR.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO PAINT ME, YOU
GOTTA TELL ME, MAMA, SO I CAN
GIVE YOU A POSE.
I WANT YOU TO PAINT ME LIKE
THIS.
OR WORST-CASE SCENARIO, GET ME
LIKE THAT.
>> YOUR HONOR, HE'S NOT EVEN
TRYING TO ARGUE THE CASE.
>> OH, YOU WANT ME TO ARGUE THE
CASE?
OH, I DIDN'T THAT'S WHAT YOU
WANTED.
I'LL TALK ABOUT THE CASE, YOUR
HONOR.
LISTEN TO ME.
FOR MY CLIENT TO GET OUT OF THAT
STORE, HE WOULD HAVE HAD TO JUKE
OUT A SECURITY GUARD.
BANG, THEY GOT THE LASERS
EVERYWHERE, SO MY CLIENT WOULD
HAVE HAD TO TOM CRUISE THAT.
OKAY?
AND THEN THEY GOT THE SENSORS.
YOU KNOW ABOUT THE SENSORS, YOUR
HONOR?
THEY'RE ABOUT THIS TALL, THE
SENSORS.
THEY TELL YOU YOU GOT SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO HAVE.
MY CLIENT WOULD HAVE HAD TO GRAB
THE SHOES AND THE BELT AND THE
JACKET AND HOLD IT ABOVE HIS
HEAD AND GO LIKE THAT.
SO EITHER MY CLIENT IS NOT
GUILTY, OR HE BELONGS IN THE
OLYMPICS.
THE DEFENSE RESTS.
>> I THINK I'VE HEARD ENOUGH TO
MAKE A DECISION.
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
YOU'RE ALL JUST CAPTIVATED BY
THE WAY SEBASTIAN MANISCALCO IS
TALKING.
WHAT IF I TALKED LIKE THAT?
YOUR HONOR.
THIS GUY TOOK THE CROSS AND HE
WALKED RIGHT OUT OF THE STORE.
WE'VE GOT THE SECURITY FOOTAGE.
AFTER WATCHING!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, I ASK, WHY
WOULD HE DO THAT?
>> ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S IT!
I FIND YOU IN CONTEMPT OF COURT!
>> OH, OH, OH --
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> MR. MANISCALCO.
I FINISHED THAT PAINTING YOU
WANTED.
>> OH, LET ME TAKE A LOOK AT IT,
HONEY.
OH, MY GOD.
HONEY, PUT THAT IN THE LOUVRE!
>>> WHAT DO WE GOT?
>> COLLAPSED AT A BIRTHDAY
PARTY, BARELY BREATHING, BLOOD
PRESSURE'S THROUGH THE ROOF.
>> FOR PEOPLE WHO LOVE "THE
PITT."
>> LIKELY IT'S TRUE.
>> BUT CAN'T STAND ITS PHONY
LIBERAL SCIENCE.
>> A NONE TOO DEFINITIVE
DIAGNOSIS.
>> FROM PRODUCER ROBERT F.
KENNEDY JR. AND THE TEAM WHO
WANT TO MAKE AMERICA HEALTHY
AGAIN.
>> WHAT SHE NEEDS IS A STEAK.
EAT PROTEIN, PEOPLE.
>> GET ME BEEF TALLOW AND SIX
RAW EGGS, STAT.
>> FROM PRODUCER JILLIAN
MICHAELS AND THE FACEBOOK GROUP,
BEAT MOMS AGAINST VACCINE
TYRANNY.
>> I NEED 60 CCs OF BULL SEMEN
NOW!
>> COMES A SHOW OF THE
HIGH-STAKES MEDICAL CRUCIBLE OF
ORANGE COUNTY, CALIFORNIA.
>> WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
>> CAR ACCIDENT.
FEMUR FRACTURE AND TRAUMA TO
RIBS 2 AND 5.
>> OH, MY RIBS!
>> HAVE YOU HAD YOUR VACCINE?
>> LOSER!
>> OKAY, MAYBE METHYLENE BLUE.
>> MIGHT WORK.
>> WHEY POWDER AND A PROBIOTIC
BATH?
>> NOT QUITE.
>> A COLD PLUNGE IN BLUE JEANS.
>> BINGO, GET ON IT.
>> OH, NO, HE'S IN SHOCK, HE'S
IN SHOCK!
>> I NEED ALL HANDS.
TANNER, POWER UP.
>> YEP, GOT IT.
CLEAR!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> I HOPE NEXT TIME YOU QUESTION
MY DIAGNOSIS, YOU'LL DO IT IN
PRIVATE.
>> I'M THE DOCTOR HERE.
>> EXCUSE ME?
I'M A CERTIFIED ENERGY HEALER.
MY INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT HAS OVER
3,000 FOLLOWERS SO DON'T YOU
DARE TRY TO TELL ME HOW TO DO MY
JOB.
>> I NEED SOME AIR.
I'M GOING OUTSIDE TO SUN MY
TAINT.
>> AT MAHA-HOSPITAL, EMOTIONS
RUB GUY.
>> YOU COULD BE ANYWHERE, WHY
ARE YOU IN MAHASPITAL?
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY I'M
HERE?
FINE.
MY PARENTS DIED FROM THE COVID
VACCINE.
>> OH, MY GOD, I'M SO SORRY.
>> YEAH.
FOUND OUT THEY GOT IT AND I SHOT
THEM.
I'M GOING TO LUNCH.
>> FIVE STARS.
>> MEASLES, COME ON, LET'S GO!
>> HOW'S SHE DOING?
>> SHE'S ON LIFE SUPPORT.
SHE WAS FAIRLY HEALTHY BEFORE
THE ACCIDENT.
THE ONLY THING IS, SHE'S A
VEGAN.
>> NOTHING WE CAN DO.
>> ARE YOU INSANE?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING, ARE
YOU CRAZY?
UH-HUH, NOT IN MY HOSPITAL!
>> IF YOUR FAVORITE CHARACTER
FROM "THE PITT" WAS THE GUY WHO
PUNCHED THE NURSE IN THE FACE?
YOU'LL LOVE MAHASPITAL.
>> COMING THROUGH!
>> WITH A SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY
RFK JR.
>> COME ON, HELP ME OUT HERE.
>> IS THAT A BEAR?
>> I HIT HIM WITH MY CAR ON THE
WAY OVER HERE.
PREP HIM.
>> FOR SURGERY?
>> FOR JERKY.
BEEN DEAD FOR A DAY BUT THE
MEAT'S STILL GOOD.
PREP HIM!
I'M PROUD OF EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN TOLD OVER AND OVER
YOU'RE CRAZY WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IS DANGEROUS AND IRRESPONSIBLE.
BUT YOU DID IT ANYWAY.
>> SHE NEEDS SOME MORE RAW MILK
NOW!
>> MAYBE IT'S THE BRAINWORM
TALKING, BUT I LOVE THIS TEAM.
NOW DROP AND GIVE ME 50.
BUTTS TO THE SKY.
>> MAHASPITAL.
COMING SOON TO THE DAILY WIRE.
>>> GUYS, DO YOU EVER JUST WANT
TO GET UP, STAND UP, GET OUT OF
THE HOUSE?
>> ENOUGH OF THIS REGULAR,
EVERYDAY LIFE, AM I RIGHT?
>> TIME TO SET SAIL UPON THE
WATER WITH A CRUISE.
>> SPARKLE OF THE SEA.
LET'S GO!
>> HELLO, I'M ALEXA.
>> AND I'M GUUS.
>> WE'RE HERE TO GIVE YOU A TOUR
OF OUR BIG, BEAUTIFUL FLOATING
POWER MACHINE.
>> WITH SO MUCH GREAT STUFF, A
GRAND CASINO, A GORGEOUS BAR,
AND A SEAFOOD BUFFET YOU CAN
SMELL FROM 50 METERS AWAY.
>> SO MANY GREAT SMELLS.
>> BUT WHAT SPARKLE OF THE SEA
IS MOST KNOWN FOR IS OUR
WORLD-CLASS ENTERTAINMENT.
>> AM I RIGHT?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> LET'S GO!
¶ HOT DOG HOT DOG ¶
¶ HOT DOG YO ¶
>> I FEEL IN DANGER OF ROCKING
TOO MUCH.
I NEED TO SLOW THIS PARTY TRAIN
DOWN BEFORE I GO CRAZY.
>> HEY, NO PROBLEM.
IF YOU WANT TO GET SUPER SEXUAL
DOWNTOWN, THEN GET READY FOR
SUPERSTAR SEXY MUELLER.
¶ OH YEAH NATURLICH ¶
>> WOW.
SO SEXUAL.
I WANT TO PUT HIM IN MY POCKET
AND CARRYING HIM AROUND TOWN.
>> HA HA HA, HE'S MUCH TOO BIG
FOR THAT.
BUT SPARKLE OF THE SEA IS MORE
THAN MUSIC.
WE ALSO HAVE VARIETY ACTS.
>> DO YOU LIKE MAGIC, WHERE
SOMETHING SEEMS ONE WAY, BUT IN
REALITY IT IS ANOTHER?
>> THEN YOU'LL LOVE FELIX THE
FLAWLESS MUSICIAN.
ONE HOUR, ONE TRICK, CONSTANT
FLOURISHES.
LET'S GO!
>> WOW.
I LOVE AN EDGY MAGICIAN.
HE TAKES YOU RIGHT TO THE BRINK.
HEY, GUYS.
HERE'S A QUESTION I'D LOVE THE
ANSWER TO.
ARE YOU READY TO LAUGH?
>> NO, I NEED A SECOND.
OKAY, I'M READY!
AND YOU'LL LAUGH MUCH TOO MUCH
AT COMEDIAN JEAN K. JEAN, LET'S
GO!
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING, LET
ME ASK Y'ALL A QUESTION.
Y'ALL REMEMBER WHEN YOUR MAMA
USED TO COOK YOU A CASSOULET?
WITH THE DUCK CONFIT?
MAN.
BROTHERS BE EATING SOME
CASSOULETS, BOY.
I COULD EAT ABOUT TREY ALL BY
MYSELF.
BUT THEY AIN'T THE SAME DEED.
MY WOMAN COOKED AM' CASSOULET
WITH SOMETHING THEY CALL
IMPOSSIBLE MEAT.
MAN, I ABOUT TOOK MY ASS ALL THE
WAY TO BRUSSELS.
I TURNED AROUND AND I SAID,
YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE MEAT, 'CAUSE
IMPOSSIBLE TO EAT IT.
>> HA HA HA!
>> WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE, AM I
RIGHT?
>> JA.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP THAT SMILE
UPON YOUR FACE, JOIN US IN THE
GRAND BALLROOM FOR A FRIDAY
NIGHT ROCK PARTY MIGHT JUST BLOW
YOUR ASS OFF.
>> THEY MAY NOT SPEAK ENGLISH,
BUT THEY SING IT PHONETICALLY.
IT'S CITY VOGUE MACHINE, LET'S
GO!
¶ LADEMELON SUGY ¶
>> TOTALLY NAILED IT.
WASN'T THAT AMAZING, GUUS?
>> HONESTLY, I DID NOT CARE TOO
MUCH FOR THAT ONE.
>> BUT WE KNOW YOU LOVE ALL THE
ENTERTAINMENT, BIG AND SPECIAL
EXTRAVAGANZAS ON SPARKLE OF THE
SEA GRAND COSMOPOLITAN CRUISE.
>> A CRUISE IS JUST LIKE BEING
IN A HOTEL, BUT YOU CAN DRUM.
SO COME ON, DRUM WITH US.
>> AND LEAVE THE ENTERTAINMENT
TO WHO?
TO US!
HA HA HA!
>> HA HA HA!
>>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THANKS FOR COMING IN EARLY.
I JUST WANTED TO GET THE TEAM
TOGETHER BEFORE THE STORE OPENS
TO DISCUSS SOME CHANGES TO THE
BEST BUY REWARDS PROGRAM.
>> POINTS, POINTS BABY!
DING DING DING DA DA DING DING!
>> THANK YOU, REBECCA.
ANYWAY, IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE.
STARTING TODAY, CUSTOMERS WHO
SIGN UP WILL BE GETTING DOUBLE
POINTS ON ALL APPLIANCES.
ANYONE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
>> YES.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
AM I IN TROUBLE?
>> NOPE.
WE'RE JUST HERE TO TALK ABOUT
THE REWARDS PROGRAM, MR. POOTY.
>> OKAY, BECAUSE I HAD HEARD
THAT THERE WAS SOME RUMORS BEING
SPREAD ABOUT ME.
LIKE MOVING SEXUALLY TOWARDS
SOME OF THE MENS IN THIS STORE.
I MEAN, IS THAT WHY YOU GATHERED
US?
LIKE, TO ARREST ME?
FOR THOSE RUMORS?
>> NOPE.
IT'S OUR STANDARD TUESDAY
MEETING, MR. POOTY.
NO ONE'S GETTING ARRESTED.
>> OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
BECAUSE WHAT THEY HAD SAID WAS
THAT I HAD MANIPULATED THE
NIPPLES OF SOME OF THE MENS OR
SOMETHING.
IS THAT TRUE?
COULD THAT BE CORRECT?
>> UH -- I AM NOT AWARE OF THAT.
ANYWAY, THIS CHANGE APPLIES TO
ANYTHING IN THE APPLIANCE
SECTION.
INCLUDING AIR FRYERS, GUYS.
OKAY?
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
>> TOTALLY.
>> YEP.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> MR. POOTY?
YOU CLEAR ON THE POINTS SYSTEM?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
BUT WHAT I CAN SAY IS, WHATEVER
I HAD SUPPOSEDLY DID WITH
CERTAIN MENS WAS PROBABLY
SOMETHING THAT I HAD ALWAYS
WANTED TO DO.
AND, LIKE, SOMETHING THAT THEY
HAD LIKED, MANIPULATING THESE
NIPPLES AND SO FORTH.
AND I'MA STAND TEN TOES ON THAT.
>> OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT TOTALLY TRYING
TO DIG INTO WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT, MR. POOTY.
BUT THERE HAVEN'T BEEN ANY
COMPLAINTS.
NO ONE IS IN TROUBLE.
>> OKAY.
BECAUSE IF SOMEONE WERE TO BE
ARRESTED, I WOULD NOMINATE
CHRISTOPHER.
>> WHAT DID I DO?
>> WELL, THIS MAN HERE HAS A
VERY STRONG BISEXUAL MAGNETISM.
AND EVERY DAY, HE HAS TRIED TO
ALLURE ME SEXUALLY AGAINST MY
WILLS.
INTO JEOPARDIZING MY JOB AND MY
REPUTATION.
>> WHOA.
I'VE NEVER TRIED TO SEDUCE MR.
POOTY.
>> A MAN THIS FINE --
HAS NO BUSINESS SELLING
STEREOPHONIC SOUND SYSTEMS.
LIKE YOU SENT LOSESIVE HIMSELF
TO AWAKEN A DEMON WITHIN ME.
DO YOU WANT TO WRITE THAT DOWN
FOR THE RECORD?
>> NO, TAKE THAT OFF THE RECORD.
>> THERE IS NO RECORD.
>> PUT THIS ON THE RECORD.
THE OTHER DAY, A CUSTOMER CAME
INTO THE PC AND COMPUTER AREA,
AND THEY WERE LOOKING FOR WHAT
ELSE, DONGLES.
CHRISTOPHER SAID, IT WOULD BE MY
PLEASURE TO TAKE YOU THROUGH MY
PC AREA AND SHOW YOU THE
DONGLES.
MAN, HE CAN'T BE SAYING STUFF
LIKE THAT AROUND ME.
I HAVE TO GO OUT FOR MY DAMN
SHIFT TO COOL OFF.
>> OKAY, I'M PRETTY GOOD AT MY
JOB.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT'S A BAD
THING.
>> OKAY, MR. POOTY, IT SOUNDS
LIKE YOU'RE JUST ATTRACTED TO
CHRISTOPHER.
AND UPSET THAT IT'S NOT
RECIPROCATED.
>> NOT REPISAPATED?
NO, CHRISTOPHER GOT UP INTO
THESE DRAWERS.
HE MANIPULATED MY NIPPLES ON MY
BIRTHDAY.
AND LET'S JUST SAY, MY CURRENT
WIFE WAS SERIOUSLY DISPLEASED.
>> I'M SORRY, CURRENT WIFE?
>> YES.
THAT IS CORRECT.
MY PREVIOUS WIFE PASSED AWAY IN
A FOUNTAIN THAT WAS LIKE TWO
INCHES DEEP.
I WAS LIKE, WHAT YOU DOING DOWN
THERE, BETH POOTY?
STAND UP!
IT WAS -- IT WAS SO BAD, Y'ALL.
ANYWAYS.
WHAT WAS THE QUESTION?
>> MR. POOTY, IF YOU CAN'T STOP
BEING DISRUPTIVE, I'LL HAVE TO
GIVE YOU A WRITE-UP.
>> HEY.
DON'T YOU DARE TALK TO MR. POOTY
THAT WAY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YEAH.
I'VE BEEN ATTRACTED TO POOTY
SINCE THE DAY I MET HIM.
>> I KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BUT I IMMEDIATELY TOLD HR
ABOUT IT, AND THEY SAID THEY
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE REALLY CUTE
AND I SHOULD GO FOR IT.
SO YES, I HAVE MANIPULATED THIS
MAN'S NIPPLES ON MULTIPLE
OCCASIONS.
>> AND WHOOP THAT IT IS.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
EDWARD DAINES POOTY, WOULD YOU
BE SO KIND AS TO ACCOMPANY ME ON
A DATE AT THE CHEESECAKE
FACTORY?
>> HM.
I HAVE A COUNTERPROPOSAL.
INSTEAD OF THE CHEESECAKE
FACTORY, HOW ABOUT THE HEADPHONE
AREA RIGHT NOW?
>> WHATEVER POOTY WANTS, POOTY
GETS.
>> I HEARD THAT.
>> OKAY.
WELL.
I GUESS THOSE GUYS ARE GOING TO
GO HOOK UP IN THE STORE.
THANKS, EVERYBODY.
MEETING'S OVER.
AND REBECCA, TAKE YOUR MEDS,
GIRL.
WE SHOULD BE HERE
I SEE NO WATER OR FRIENDS ¶
¶ BUT THE MUSIC
KEEPS HITTING ME
LIKE A TEN OUT OF TEN ¶
¶ SO I DON'T THINK
GOT SOMETHING TO SAY
NO I DON'T THINK
GOT SOMETHING TO SAY ¶
¶ CONVERSATION IS
HEARING YOU
GET IT ALL OFF YOUR CHEST ¶
¶ YOU CAN COME OVER HERE
TO TELL ME AGAIN AND AGAIN ¶
¶ WHAT YOU THINK
I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO SAY
NO I DON'T THINK ¶
¶ MOVE IT SIDE TO SIDE
WITH YOUR HANDS UP HIGH ¶
¶ KEEP YOUR
CUSTOMER SATISFIED
AND LIVE YOUR LIFE ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE
THEY SAID ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ WE WANNA DANCE WITH
ALL OUR FRIENDS
DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ IT'S FEELING
LIKE THE MUSIC
HAS BEEN HEAVEN SENT ¶
¶ AND THAT THERE'S
NO DIFFERENCE IN BETWEEN
THE TEARS AND THE SWEAT UH ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ THEY SAID DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE
NO MORE ¶
¶ MOVE IT SIDE TO SIDE
WITH YOUR HANDS UP HIGH ¶
¶ KEEP YOUR CUSTOMER
SATISFIED
AND LIVE YOUR LIFE ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE
THEY SAID ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ WE WANNA DANCE WITH
ALL OUR FRIENDS
DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ IT'S FEELING
LIKE THE MUSIC
HAS BEEN HEAVEN SENT ¶
¶ AND THAT THERE'S
NO DIFFERENCE IN BETWEEN
THE TEARS AND THE SWEAT UH ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ THEY SAID DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE
NO MORE ¶
¶ GET YOUR FEET WET
TEACH THEM ALL TO RESPECT
THEIR MOTHER ¶
¶ YOU GOTTA GET
YOUR FEET WET
RESPECT
RESPECT YOUR MOTHER ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE
THEY SAID ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ WE WANNA DANCE WITH
ALL OUR FRIENDS
DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ IT'S FEELING
LIKE THE MUSIC
HAS BEEN HEAVEN SENT ¶
¶ AND THAT THERE'S
NO DIFFERENCE IN BETWEEN
THE TEARS AND THE SWEAT UH ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE
THEY SAID ¶
¶ DEEJAYS DON'T DANCE NO MORE ¶
¶ YOU GOTTA GET
YOUR FEET WET
RESPECT
RESPECT YOUR MOTHER ¶
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> TODAY MARKS THE START OF THE
THIRD WEEK WITH THE WAR IN IRAN,
WHICH IS WEIRD BECAUSE SOMEONE
ALREADY TOLD ME WE WON IT ON THE
FIRST DAY.
USUALLY WHEN A TEAM WINS, THEY
DON'T THEN STAY ON THE FIELD FOR
THREE MORE WEEKS.
IT KIND OF SEEMS LIKE THE MAIN
THING WE'VE DONE SO FAR IS GET
RID OF AN 86-YEAR-OLD AYATOLLAH
AND REPLACED HIM WITH A
56-YEAR-OLD AYATOLLAH.
A YOUNGER, CRAZIER BAD GUY HELL
BENT ON REVENGE.
WE DID IT!
ALSO, IS IT WEIRD THAT I'M KIND
OF JEALOUS THAT IRAN NOW HAS A
LEADER UNDER 80 YEARS OLD?
GOD, REMEMBER HOW MUCH BETTER
OUR COUNTRY WAS DOING WHEN WE
HAD A YOUNG, MUSLIM LEADER?
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAUGHT THE
MUSLIM PART.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID IN AN
INTERVIEW THAT HE BELIEVES
IRAN'S AYATOLLAH MOJTAB KHAMENEI
IS DAMAGED BUT PROBABLY ALIVE IN
SOME FORM.
WHICH IS ALSO A PRETTY GREAT
DESCRIPTION OF TRUMP.
>>> KHAMENEI WAS CHOSEN BY
IRAN'S 88-MEMBER ASSEMBY OF
EXPERTS.
MAKE THAT 62 MEMBERS.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP POSTED A
MESSAGE ON TRUTH SOCIAL READING,
IRAN WILL HAVE A GREAT FUTURE,
MAKE IRAN GREAT AGAIN.
OR, MIGA AS IN, THIS MIGA CRAZY.
>> I WANTED TO DO THAT ONE.
>>> THE FBI HAS REPORTEDLY
WARNED POLICE DEPARTMENTS IN
CALIFORNIA THAT IRAN COULD
RETALIATE BY LAUNCHING DRONES AT
HIGH-PROFILE TARGETS ON THE WEST
COAST.
THE OSCARS, TOMORROW ON ABC!
>>> HEALTH SECRETARY ROBERT F.
KENNEDY JR., SEEN HERE PACK FROM
HIS MISSION TO THE SUN --
SAID HE'S RECOVERING FROM
ROTATOR CUFF SURGERY ON HIS
SHOULDER.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO NEEDS ME NOW, SAID
TYLENOL.
>>> A SCHOOL BOARD IN NEW JERSEY
IS CONSIDERING A PROPOSAL TO
RENAME AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP.
NAMED TRUMP ELEMENTARY, HOME OF
THE FIGHTING ALLEGATIONS.
>>> MAYBE YOU WILL LIKE THIS.
A STATUE HAS APPEARED ON THE
NATIONAL MALL THAT DEPICTS
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND JEFFREY
EPSTEIN IN THE FAMOUS POSE FROM
TITANIC.
BECAUSE AS THEY WANT THE
TITANIC, WOMEN AND CHILDREN
FIRST.
>>> NORTH KOREAN LEADER KIM
JONG-UN TOOK HIS TEENAGED
DAUGHTER TO A MUNITIONS FACTORY
WHERE THEY TEST-FIRED PISTOLS
TOGETHER.
GIRL DAD.
>>> A SPECIAL ELECTION WAS HELD
IN GEORGIA TO REPLACE MARJORIE
TAYLOR GREENE.
THE ELECTION WAS WON BYHE T
CANDIDATE MOST SIMILAR TO
GREENE, A CONFEDERATE HE-MAN
DOLL.
>>> INDUSTRY EXPERTS ARE SAYING
THAT THE BEST ACTOR AT TOMORROW
NIGHT'S OSCARS WILL GO TO EITHER
MICHAEL B. JORDAN, AN ACTOR WHO
EMBODIED TWO SEPARATE ROLES
EXPLORING THEMES OF RACE AND
ANCESTRAL TRAUMA, OR PING-PONG
GUY.
>>> WHILE MANY ARE EXCITED FOR
THE OSCARS TOMORROW, SOME PEOPLE
THINK LIBERAL POLITICS ARE
INFLUENCING THE AWARDS TOO MUCH.
HERE WITH HIS TAKE IS
CONSERVATIVE COMMENTATOR TUCKER
CARLSON.
>> COLIN, LET'S ALL GO TO THE
MOVIES.
HUH.
REALLY.
YES.
WHY DON'T WE GRAB SOME POPCORN
AND WATCH AMERICAN CULTURE
COLLAPSE.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> ALL RIGHT, COMING IN HOT.
WELL, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THIS
YEAR'S NOMINEES?
>> WHERE TO EVEN BEGIN.
OH.
I KNOW.
WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT
SINNERS.
THAT'S RIGHT, "SINNERS."
LEFTIST WOKE AMERICA'S FAVORITE
MOVIE THIS YEAR IS ABOUT
SINNING, HUH.
REALLY, WHY DOES THAT NOT
SURPRISE ME?
SORRY, KIDS, WE DON'T GO TO
CHURCH ANYBODY, WE GO TO
SINNERS.
THAT'S THE RULE.
THAT'S THE GOAL NOW.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU DIDN'T LIKE "SINNERS."
YOU DON'T LIKE "SINNERS."
WHAT ABOUT "HAMNET."
>> BECAUSE WE'RE NOT ALLOWED TO
SAY HAMLET ANYMORE.
>> NO, NO --
>> THEY TOOK THE "L" AND GAVE IT
TO THE GBTQ.
IT'S HAMNET NOW.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HAMNET.
A MOVIE ABOUT A BOY WHO SHOWS
INTEREST IN THEATER, DIES.
HA HA HA!
I REALLY LIKED THAT PART.
>> THAT'S THE PART YOU LIKED?
>> EXCUSE ME, HEY, EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME.
HEY, EXCUSE ME.
>> NO ONE IS INTERRUPTING YOU.
>> EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME.
MOVING ON TO "BEGONIA."
HUH, REALLY.
I GUESS HETEROSEXUAL WOMEN
AREN'T ALLOWED TO HAVE HAIR
ANYMORE.
THEY HAVE TO SHAVE THEIR HEADS
INSTEAD OF THEIR ARMPITS.
AND I'M SUPPOSED TO BE ATTRACTED
TO THAT?
NO.
OH!
DON'T LOOK AT MY BREASTS, LOOK
AT MY SCALP.
THAT'S THE RULE.
THAT'S THE GOAL NOW.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
>> ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT A GOAL?
WHAT GOAL?
>> COLIN, WHAT EVER HAPPENED TO
THE GREAT AMERICAN FILMS?
LIKE "GONE WITH THE WIND" OR THE
FIRST 20 MINUTES OF "FORREST
GUMP."
>> THE PART WHERE THEY'RE
BULLYING HIM?
>> I LOVE THAT PART.
HA HA HA!
>> MAN.
DUDE.
I GOT TO TELL YOU THAT LAUGH IS
JUST AWFUL.
>> THAT'S NOT MY LAUGH ACTION
THAT'S THE SOUL OF AN 18th
CENTURY MENTAL PATIENT TRYING TO
ESCAPE FROM THIS LOCKET.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE THAT?
>> AND FINALLY, "ONE BATTLE
AFTER ANOTHER."
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M GENUINELY ASKING, I DID NOT
SEE THAT MOVIE.
>> TUCKER CARLSON, EVERYONE.
>> HEY, EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME.
>>> DAN ADEBAYO OF THE MIAMI
HEAT SCORED 83 POINTS AGAINST
THE WIZARDS, UNFORTUNATELY THE
NIGHT THE WIZARDS STARTED FIVE
MAKE A WISH KIDS.
THESE JOKES ARE NOT REAL.
>>> TACO BELL HAS ANNOUNCED --
>> Gus: DO YOU WORK FOR TACO
BELL?
JUST A HUGE FAN?
EVERYBODY ELSE IS LIKE, HARRY
STYLES!
YOU'RE LIKE, TACO BELL!
TACO BELL'S ANNOUNCED NEW
ADDITIONS TO THEIR MENU,
INCLUDING DIABLO-DUSTED CHICKEN
NUGGETS AND MOUNTAIN DEW BAJA
MIDNIGHT PIE.
IN KEEPING WITH THEIR NEW
SLOGAN, TACO BELL, DEATH TO
AMERICA.
>> THAT ONE MIGHT BE REAL.
>>> FLORIDA POLICE HAVE ARRESTED
A WOMAN ON CHARGES THAT SHE LEFT
HER 12-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER AT
UNIVERSAL CITY WALK WHILE SHE
WENT TO A BAR.
SO APPARENTLY IT'S A CRIME TO
FIND THAT KID A FATHER.
>>> YOUTUBE --
>> THAT'S THE GOAL.
>> YOUTUBE HAS LAUNCHED A NEW
TOOL THAT WOULD ALLOW REPORTERS
TO FLAG VIDEOS THAT USE AI TO
RECREATE THEIR LIKENESS.
LIKE THESE COMPUTER-GENERATED
REPORTERS.
I THINK I WOULD KNOW IF THEY
WERE USING AI.
MY BREASTS LOOK INCREDIBLE.
>>> A NEW STUDY SUGGESTS THE
DIFFERENCE IN SIZE BETWEEN A
PERSON'S INDEX AND RING FINGERS
THAN REVEAL THEIR SEXUAL
ORIENTATION.
THE STUDY SAID IF YOUR INDEX
FINGER IS OVER AN INCH INSIDE OF
A FELLOW, YOU MIGHT BE GAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> GOOD TO KNOW.
>> A GOOD WAY TO KNOW.
>>> APPLE ANNOUNCED ICE ADDING
EIGHT NEW EMOJIS, INCLUDING A
TREASURE CHEST, A TROMBONE, AND
ME IN MIDDLE SCHOOL BREAKING MY
FATHER'S HEART.
>>> NETFLIX ANNOUNCED PLANS FOR
A SEQUEL TO THE HIT MOVIE "KPOP
DEMON HUNTERS."
AND THEY BETTER HAVE NEW SONGS
BECAUSE IF I HEAR A KID SING
GOLDEN ONE MORE TIME, I'M
GOING TO --
¶ BLOW MY BRAINS UP UP UP ¶
THE TACO BELL PERSON LIKED IT.
>>> THE WINNERS OF THE ANNUAL
WIFE-CARRYING CONTEST IN ENGLAND
WAS A COUPLE FROM FINLAND.
ONCE AGAIN, THE WINNER FROM THE
HUSBAND-CARRYING CONTEST WAS
SCARLETT.
>> WE BOTH PUT FOOD ON THE
TABLE.
DIFFERENT KINDS OF FOOD.
>>> APPLE IS RELEASING EIGHT NEW
EMOJIS THIS SPRING.
HERE TO COMMENT ARE, ACCORDING
TO THE LATEST DATA, THE NUMBER
ONE MOST-USED AND NUMBER ONE
LEAST-USED EMOJIS, RED HEART AND
AERIAL TRAMWAY.
>> RED HEART IN THE HOUSE!
Y'ALL KNOW ME.
>> AERIAL TRAMWAY!
AERIAL TRAMWAY!
>> YEAH.
WOW.
THANKS FOR BOTH BEING HERE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE
NEW EMOJIS?
>> THEY'RE ALL GOING TO BE MORE
POPULAR THAN THIS LOSER.
I'M NUMBER ONE BECAUSE I'M
USEFUL.
PEOPLE USE ME FOR EVERYTHING.
I MISS YOU, HEART.
HERE'S A PIC OF MY DOG, HEART.
HERE'S A PIC OF MY BARE ASS.
HEART, HEART, HEART, HEART,
HEART.
AERIAL TRAMWAY IS ONLY USED WHEN
TALKING ABOUT THAT SPECIFIC
CABLE-BASED TRANSPORTATION.
>> CAP, CAP, CAP, CAP, CAP!
>> IT'S NOT CAP.
WHEN WOULD SOMEONE UES EWE?
>> HEY, I'M GOING TO TAKE THE
AERIAL TRAMWAY!
HEY, I'M ON THE AERIAL TRAMWAY!
>> OKAY.
WHAT OTHER USES THAT AREN'T
ABOUT PHYSICALLY RIDING IT?
>> YO, MAN.
GIRL GOT ME ACTING LIKE AN
AERIAL TRAMWAY!
>> THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
>> IT MAKES ALL THE SENSE.
>> IT MAKES NO SENSE.
COLIN, YOU SHOULD SEE THIS GUY'S
CREW.
THEY'RE SUCH DORKS.
>> NOPE.
>> WAIT, HOLD ON, I DIDN'T
REALIZE EMOJIS HAVE FRIENDS?
>> YES, MAN.
MY CREW IS FIRE.
I ROLL IN CRYING TEARS FACE,
HE'S COOL AS HELL.
THUMBS UP, THAT'S MY OG,
ORIGINAL GANGSTER.
THE EYES LIKE THIS?
>> BOO.
>> THAT'S MY DOG, OKAY?
AND 100 WITH TWO LINES UNDER IT?
THAT'S MY DAY ONE.
>> NO.
MY CREW, ALL BANGERS.
I'M ROLLING WITH MY BOY ORANGE
SQUARE.
>> ORANGE SQUARE SUCKS.
>> NO, DUDE.
OF COURSE WE GOT DIVISION SIGN.
>> DOG WATER, HE SUCKS.
>> SNORKELING EQUIPMENT.
AND MY BOY THE GOAT, BUILDING
WITH A HORN ON IT.
BUILDING WITH A HORN ON IT.
>> WHAT EVEN IS THAT?
IS THAT LIKE A HORN STORE?
>> OR A HORN SCHOOL.
>> THAT'S JUST AS BAD.
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
>> YOU DON'T MAKE NO SENSE.
>> MUST HAVE --
>> AERIAL TRAMWAY!
AERIAL TRAMWAY!
>> MOST -- DUDE, IT SUCKS, DUDE.
MOST OF HIS --
MOST OF HIS -- MOST OF HIS CREW
IS RBS.
>> WHAT'S RBF?
>> RIGHT BEFORE THE FLAGS.
YOU KNOW HOW THE FLAGS ARE AT
THE END?
RIGHT?
THIS DUDE AND ALL HIS LOSER
FRIENDS --
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
AERIAL TRAMWAY!
>> THEY'RE RIGHT BEFORE THE
FLAGS, DUDE.
YOU KNOW HOW --
AND -- BECAUSE HE'S BACK THERE
WITH ALL THE FLAGS?
THAT'S WHY HE CAN'T GET A
FINE-ASS GIRL LIKE I CAN.
>> RED HEART, YOU GOT A
GIRLFRIEND?
>> YEAH, DUDE.
IT'S KIND OF NEW.
I DON'T WANT TO JINX IT.
I'VE KIND OF BEEN CHILLING WITH
THE LADY DANCER IN THE RED DRESS
WITH HER ARMS LIKE THIS.
>> UGLY!
UGLY!
MY GIRL?
SHOUT-OUT TO MY GIRL.
THE WORD "ON" WITH TWO ARROWS
ABOVE IT.
>> THAT IS SO SAD.
UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES WOULD
ANYONE EVER USE THAT EMOJI?
>> LET ME THINK.
IF SOMETHING TO BOTH THE LEFT
AND THE RIGHT IS ON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T EVEN BE HERE, I CAN'T BE
WITH THIS GUY.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME, I'VE GOT
TO GO HOME.
>> YOU'RE LEAVING?
HOW ARE YOU GETTING HOME?
>> SAY IT.
>> UM --
>> SAY IT!
>> I'M TAKING THE AERIAL
TRAMWAY.
>> RED HEART AND AERIAL TRAMWAY.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE, GOOD NIGH
MOTORCYCLE?
>> WHO, ME?
YEAH, I GOT THIS UNDER CONTROL,
MAN.
I NEVER DONE IT BEFORE, BUT I'LL
ONLY BE DRIVING DOWN THE
HIGHWAY.
SO TAKE CARE, MAN.
>> YOU FORGOT THE PART WHERE HE
PAYS.
AGAIN.
I KNOW YOU'RE THE HIGH SCHOOL
QUARTERBACK, BUT THIS JOB NEEDS
TO BE A PRIORITY FOR YOU, OKAY?
>> THIS JOB IS A PRIORITY FOR
ME.
IT GOES FOOTBALL, SCHOOL, MY
BOYS, MY BOYS, SNEAKERS, A FEW
OTHER THINGS I'M FORGETTING,
THEN THIS JOB.
>> LOOK ALIVE, ANOTHER ONE'S
PULLING UP.
>> HE'S HERE, STEVE'S WORKING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO ASK HIM
STRAIGHT UP.
STEVE, DO YOU WANT TO GO TO THE
DANCE?
>> AND HE'LL SAY, YES,
RESOUNDING YES.
>> WE GOT THIS.
WE'RE READY, WE GOT THIS.
>> GREAT.
>> HI, THERE.
THAT WILL BE $18.97.
ORDER 23, RIGHT?
WAIT, I KNOW YOU GUYS.
WE GO TO HIGH SCHOOL TOGETHER.
>> GOD BROKE THE MOLD WHEN HE
MADE YOU!
>> GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE!
>> STEVE, DID YOU NOT GIVE THOSE
PEOPLE THEIR BURGERS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> IT'S JUST THESE TWO GIRLS
FROM MY HIGH SCHOOL.
>> DO YOU KNOW THEM?
>> NO, BUT I KNOW THEY'RE THE
ONLY TWO MEMBERS OF THE SCHOOL'S
QUIDDITCH TEAM.
>> THAT WAS PERFECT!
>> AMAZING!
>> OH, MY GOSH, OH, MY GOSH,
THANK YOU.
>> WE HAVE HIM WRAPPED AROUND
OUR FINGERS.
>> HOW COULD HE SAY NO?
>> HE'S GETTING A BARGAIN.
HE'S A 10, WE'RE TWO 5s.
>> DEAL OF A LIFETIME.
WE SET THE BAIT, NOW LET'S REEL
HIM IN.
>> HEY.
YOU GUYS AGAIN.
YOU GUYS WANT YOUR BURGER?
>> WELL, STEVE, THE BURGERS ARE
GOOD BUT WHAT ABOUT THE BOYS?
THEY SAY I WOULD LIKE TO CRUNCH
YOU UP LIKE A BAG OF CHIPS,
OKAY?
SOUND LIKE A PLAN?
>> HOW ABOUT I USE YOUR ASS AS A
TABLE.
PUT MY ELBOWS ON IT.
DID I SAY ASS?
DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE!
>> STEVE, WHAT IS GOING ON?
THEY'RE RACING AROUND LIKE A
NASCAR TRACK.
>> NOT MY FAULT.
>> AM I ON "IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"
RIGHT NOW?
AM I BASICALLY IMPRACTICALLY
JOKED UPON?
I CANNOT LET THAT HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> AMAZING!
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT'S YOUR NEXT MOVE?
>> NEXT TIME WE SAY, HEY, DANCE?
SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> SIMPLE AS THAT, THAT'S
PERFECT, OKAY.
>> HELLO, STEVE.
SO DOES YOUR PENIS KNOW --
>> DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE, DRIVE,
DRIVE!
>> STEVE, THOSE GIRLS ARE DOING
FRICKIN' DOUGHNUTS OUT THERE.
>> MR. BURGER, STEVE.
>> HEY, DID YOU GUYS WANT YOUR
BURGER?
>> STEVE, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I
WANT.
TO RIDE YOU TO DEATH.
OF COURSE.
>> I'M A VIRGIN, BUT I HAVE A
BOOK THAT TELLS ME EXACTLY HOW
THE IT WORKS.
>> STEVE, AS WE WENT ALL THE
WAY, I WANT YOU TO KNOW I
WOULDN'T KEEP IT.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU
GUYS?
>> LOOK.
WE GOT NERVOUS.
BUT WE CAME HERE TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING.
WILL YOU GO THE DANCE WITH US?
>> I WOULD LOVE TO GO TO THE
DANCE WITH BOTH YOU GUYS.
IT'S THE DEAL OF A LIFETIME.
I'M A 10.
AND YOU GUYS ARE BOTH 6s.
TWO 6s ADD UP TO, LIKE, 11?
>> 6s!
OH, MY GOD, 6s!
>> HE THINKS WE'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> WELL, I'LL SEE YOU TWO AT THE
DANCE.
>> DANCING THE NIGHT AWAY WITH
YOU, STEVE.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
>> EXCUSE ME.
I CRASHED THE MOTORCYCLE.
COULD YOU TWO 7s TAKE ME TO THE
HOSPITAL?
>> YEAH, BABE!
I'VE TURNED BACK
THE CLOCKS
IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR ¶
¶ IF WE STAY THE COURSE
WE COULD GET IT RIGHT
BUT I'M NOT DEVOID
OF AN APPETITE ¶
¶ AND ALL OF IT SEEMS TO BE
BRINGING US CLOSER ¶
¶ JUST FOR TONIGHT
LET'S GO HANGOVER CHASING
AND I'LL TALK YOUR EAR OFF
ABOUT WHY IT'S SAFE ¶
¶ AS I FUMBLE MY WORDS
AND FALL FLAT ON MY FACE
THROUGH THE TRUTH ¶
¶ JUST SAY THE WORD AND
WE'LL TAKE UP THE TEST ¶
¶ WHERE WE FLIRT
WITH THE BAD ONES
AND SKIP ALL THE REST ¶
¶ BUT WE SEE OUT THE NIGHT
WITH YOUR HEAD ON MY CHEST
ME AND YOU
THERE'S ONLY ME AND YOU ¶
¶ NOW I SEE YOUR TEARS
ON ACCOUNT OF MY WANTS
AND NOW IT APPEARS ¶
¶ THAT I'M FEELING
GUILTY AND WORRIED DEAR
THAT YOU THINK THAT
I MIGHT NOT WANT YOU HERE ¶
¶ DOES ALL OF THIS SEEM
TO BE BRINGING US CLOSER ¶
¶ OR AM I BACK-SEATING
YOUR LIFE
JUDGING WHILE YOU DRIVE ¶
¶ JUST FOR TONIGHT
LET'S GO HANGOVER CHASING
AND I'LL TALK YOUR EAR OFF
ABOUT WHY IT'S SAFE ¶
¶ AS I FUMBLE MY WORDS
AND FALL FLAT ON MY FACE
THROUGH THE TRUTH ¶
¶ JUST SAY THE WORD AND
WE'LL TAKE UP THE TEST ¶
¶ WHERE WE FLIRT
WITH THE BAD ONES
AND SKIP ALL THE REST ¶
¶ BUT WE SEE OUT THE NIGHT
WITH YOUR HEAD ON MY CHEST
ME AND YOU
THERE'S ONLY ME AND YOU ¶
¶ THERE'S ONLY ME AND YOU ¶
¶ LA-LA-LA-LA-LA
LA-LA-LA-LA-LA
LA-LA-LA-LA-LA-LA
LA-LA-LA-LA-LA ¶
¶ LA-LA-LA-LA
LA ¶
¶ ME AND MY BOYS YA BUT I GOT A
GIRL NEXT TO ME ¶
¶ SHE'S A DANCER I'M A DANCER
THAT MEANS SHE'S A FREAK ¶
¶ WAIT TILL YOU SEE HER MOVES
GET READY MY KNEES GETTING
WEAK ¶
¶ SHE PUTS ME IN THE CHAIR WAIT
HERE IT'S ABOUT TO GET HOT ¶
¶ YEAH SHE'S A DANCER ¶
¶ BUT NOT THE KIND YOU THOUGHT ¶
GIRLS?
¶ YOU PUT YOUR HANDS ON YOUR
HIPS AND THEN YOU GO LIKE THIS ¶
TURNED ON YET, FELLAS?
¶ GOING BACK TO HER PLACE THINGS
ARE GETTING SPICY ¶
¶ SHE SAID I'LL TREAT YOU RIGHT
I THINK SHE MIGHT BE WIFEY ¶
¶ SHE HEADS INTO THE KITCHEN
WANTS TO MAKE A MEAL FOR ME ¶
¶ CAN'T WAIT TO TASTE HER
COOKING ¶
¶ I NEVER SAID WHAT KIND OF FOOD
IT WOULD BE ¶
GIRLS?
¶ WE'RE HAVING STEW AND CREAM OF
FISH ¶
>> EAT UP, FELLA.
>> I LIKE THAT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
CHEW.
>> YOU'RE SO SHINY, GIRL.
>> SORRY, I'M NOT GREAT WITH MY
WORDS.
BUT I'M EXTREMELY GOOD WITH MY
HANDS.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> WATCH THIS.
¶ THESE GIRLS ARE DIFFERENT THAN
I THOUGHT THEY'D BE ¶
¶ I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO MATCH
THEIR FREAK ¶
BOYS?
¶ YOU USE YOUR LEGS THE BEST YOU
CAN ¶
¶ IF YOU GO LIKE THIS AND YOU GO
LIKE THAT ¶
¶ THEN YOU PUT YOUR HANDS ON
YOUR HIPS AND YOU GO AFTER
THAT ¶
>> HAPPY ST. PADDY'S DAY.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE MY BELLY
BUTTON?
NAH, YOU DON'T DESERVE IT.
FOR YEARS, I'VE BEEN TURNING
HEADS WITH MY BOLD, CONFIDENT
STYLE.
AND I'VE BEEN APPROACHED BY
COUNTLESS WOMEN WHO SAY, MY
HUSBAND'S LOOK SO IS BORING, I
WISH HE'D DRESS MORE LIKE YOU.
NOW YOU CAN.
I'VE PARTNERED WITH TARGET TO
RECREATE SOME OF MY
EXTRAORDINARY LOOKS FOR THE
ORDINARY MAN.
AT A BRYCE HE CAN AFFORD.
HARRY FOR HIM BY HARRY STYLES.
I'VE PULLED THESE LOOKS OFF, NOW
YOU CAN TOO.
>> CAN I, THOUGH?
I'M NOT CONVINCED.
WHEN YOU SEE ME IN A SIDE BY
SIDE WITH HARRY, THE ANSWER IS
DEFINITELY NO.
BUT WHEN YOU SEE ME ALONE, THE
ANSWER IS ALSO NO.
>> LIAR, LIAR, PANTS ON FIRE.
AS WE SAY IN ENGLAND, A LIAR,
FOR SHAME, TROUSERS AFLAME!
YOU LOOK SEXY, MATE, SHOW ME
YOUR TUSHY.
ZOOM IN ON THAT THING.
MM, LOOK AT THOSE BISCUITS.
GOING FOR A MORE FORMAL LOOK?
WE'VE GOT YOUR COVERED.
>> MY WIFE LOVES HARRY STYLES.
SHE'D NEVER SAY THIS, BUT I KNOW
SHE'S SAD I'M NOT HIM.
I SURPRISED HER FOR OUR
ANNIVERSARYDINNER BY WEARING
THIS HARRY FOR HIM BLOUSE HARRY
WORE TO THE MET BALL.
MY WIFE SAID HE LOOKED LIKE THE
EMBODIMENT OF ELEGANT
MASCULINITY.
WHEN I WORE THIS, SHE SAID, YOU
LOOK LIKE A SERIAL KILLER
WEARING THE CLOTHES OF THE WOMAN
HE KILLED.
>> THERE ARE MORE CASUAL
OPTIONS.
>> IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
BUT ON HARRY THIS OUTFIT JUST
WORKS.
WHEN HE WORE THIS TO AN AWARDS
SHOW, HE RECEIVED GLOWING
REVIEWS.
AND WHEN I WORE THIS TO MY
12-YEAR-OLD SON'S BASKETBALL
GAME?
THE REVIEWS WERE MIXED.
SOME PEOPLE TOLD ME I LOOKED
TERRIBLE.
WHILE OTHERS TOLD ME TO GO HOME
AND CHANGE.
>> NEVER CHANGE, BOO, YOU LOOK
GORGEOUS.
>> STOP, HARRY.
WANTING SOMETHING MORE SUBTLE?
I HAVE THE LOOK FOR YOU.
>> ON THE RACK, I GOT TO BE
HONEST THIS KIND OF LOOKED LIKE
JUST A LITTLE GIRL'S DRESS.
BUT WHEN I PUT IT ON I SAID --
OH, THIS IS JUST A LITTLE GIRL'S
DRESS.
WHEN HARRY WORE THIS AT A
CONCERT, THE GIRLS WENT INSANE.
BUT WHEN I WORE THIS TO WORK, MY
BOSS SAID, "THIS IS NOT THE
PROPER ATTIRE FOR A WELLS FARGO
LOAN OFFICER."
>> IS YOUR BOSS MIND?
YOU HAVE THE PERFECT LEGS FOR
THIS DRESS AND THE PERFECT
TUSHY.
SHOW THE BUM, MATE.
>> OKAY, HARRY.
>> PUT SOME HONEY ON THAT
BISCUIT.
I GUARANTEE MY HARRY FOR HIM
LOOKS WILL HAVE YOU SAYING --
>> I HAD TO GET ALL THE WAY
NAKED TO USE THE URINAL.
>> AND THAT'S A PROMISE.
>> I ENCOURAGED MY HUSBAND TO
WEAR HARRY FOR HIM.
AND IT WORKS.
HE WORE A SPARKLY TURTLENECK
WITH NO PANTS TO OUR DIVORCE
HEARING.
AND THE JUDGE AWARDED ME FULL
CUSTODY.
THANKS, HARRY FOR HIM.
>> AT FIRST, I WAS NERVOUS ABOUT
WEARING THIS.
ESPECIALLY TO A FUNERAL.
BUT LOW-KEY, I'M JUST OUT RIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH.
VAST DEPARTURE FROM HOW I
NORMALLY DRESS, BUT LOW-KEY, I
FEEL CONFIDENT AS HELL RIGHT
NOW.
HIGH-KEY, I'M UNCOMFORTABLE.
AND HIGH-KEY, I'M SWEATING.
AND HIGH-KEY, I'M INSECURE.
BUT LOW-KEY, I'M LOOKING LIKE
HARRY STYLES.
BUT HIGH-KEY, I DON'T.
>> TO GET MY CLOTHES TODAY ON
YOU, WITH HARRY FOR HIM,
AVAILABLE AT TARGET.
SHOW THEM YOUR TUSHIES.
>> HARRY FOR HIM, AVAILABLE
EXCLUSIVELY AT TARGET
GOSLING, I'VE HAD AN AMAZING
WEEK.
THANK YOU TO THE CAST OF "SNL."
HAPPY ST. PATRICK'S DAY.
GOOD NIGHT.