>>> SHE'S TOUGH.
SHE'S BRASH.
SHE'S SHOCKED BY EVERY WORD THAT
COMES OUT OF OUR OWN MOUTH.
TOO SMALL FOR TV, TOO BIG FOR
RADIO.
JUST RIGHT FOR YOUTUBE.
IT'S "CRIME STORIES WITH NANCY
GRACE."
>> GOOD EVENING, AMERICA.
I'M NANCY GRACE.
OUR TOP STORY TONIGHT, THE
MASKED CEO SHOOTER HAS BEEN
UNMASKED, AND GUESS WHAT?
IT'S GAME OVER, LUIGI.
AND OF COURSE, EVERYONE ONLINE
CELEBRATED THE HARD WORK OF LAW
ENFORCEMENT IN APPREHENDING THIS
DANGEROUS CRIMINAL.
JUST KIDDING, Y'ALL MADE HIM A
SEX SYMBOL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE HEALTH CARE ASSASSIN, LUIGI
MANGIONE, HAS GOT WOMEN AND GAY
GUYS ALIKE ALL HOT AND BOTHERED.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY?
THIS GUY LOOKS LIKE DAVE FRANCO
WITH EUGENE LEVY'S EYEBROWS.
I MEAN, REALLY?
WHAT IS GOING ON IN THIS
COUNTRY?
Y'ALL, THIS MAN IS NOT A SEX
ICON, OKAY?
THIS MAN IS, AND I CANNOT SAY
THIS ANY CLEARER, A MURDERER!
AND YET FOLKS ONLINE ARE POSTING
THINGS LIKE -- AM I READING THIS
RIGHT?
LUIGI GOT THAT BDE?
REALLY?
I HAVE BDE STANDS FOR BEHAVIOR
THAT'S EVIL.
AND WHAT?
THE ASSASSIN'S A TWUNK?
WHAT'S A TWUNK?
LIKE A TWEE TWUNK?
OR HOW ABOUT THIS COMMENT?
ALL HIS PHOTOS.
ROW, NEXT QUESTION.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
WHO RAISED YOU?
I MEAN, WHAT IS HAPPENING IN
THIS COUNTRY, Y'ALL?
JOINING US NOW IS PSYCHOLOGICAL
ANALYST DR. BARBARA CRATSTON.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF ALL THIS?
>> NANCY, THERE'S A LOT TO
UNPACK HERE.
>> COULDN'T AGREE MORE, THANK
YOU FOR JOINING US.
I MEAN, THIS GUY IS DANGEROUS,
Y'ALL.
THEY'RE SAYING HE DID IT WITH A
GHOST GUN?
HELL, I CAN USE A GHOST GUN.
'CAUSE EVERY NIGHT I WAKE UP TO
JONBENET'S SPIRIT SCREAMING,
YOU USED ME!
SPEAKING OF TERRIBLE FRAUDS,
BECAUSE THIS IS YOUTUBE, WE
COULD BE INTERRUPTED AT ANY
SECOND BY AN INSANELY LOUD AD.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN, BUT I --
>> HEY!
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU YOU COULD
SHED BELLY FAT BY ONLY EATING
HAMBURGERS?
BRO, I'D BE LYING!
>> JOINING US NOW IS DONNEL
DAVIS, A MAN WHO WAS AT THE
McDONALDS WHEN THIS WENT DOWN.
DONNEL, WHAT WERE YOU DOING AT
THE McDONALD'S?
>> THE SAME THING THAT I'VE BEEN
DOING THIS EVERY DAY SINCE I GOT
LAID OFF NINE MONTHS AGO,
PRETENDING TO GO TO WORK SO MY
WIFE DOESN'T FIND OUT.
>> DONNEL, YOU WERE FACE-TO-FACE
WITH THIS I DIDN'T MEAN NATURAL.
CAN YOU BELIEVE PEOPLE ARE
ATTRACTED TO THIS SEXY SLAYER?
>> I MEAN -- YOU COULD LOOK AT
HIM AND TELL HE HAD HOS.
I MEAN, WOMEN LOVE BAD BOYS, YOU
KNOW?
BACK IN THE DAY, YOU CAN IMPRESS
YOUR OLD LADY WITH A LITTLE
POEM.
NOW YOU GOT TO WRITE A
MANIFESTO.
>> IT IS SICKENING.
DONNEL, SOME PEOPLE ARE CLAIMING
HEALTH CARE IN THIS COUNTRY IS
BAD, LIKE WHAT?
THEN HOW COME MY DENTIST GIVES
ME BREAST EXAMS FOR FREE?
NOW DONNEL, WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON
HEALTH CARE IN THIS COUNTRY?
>> WELL, NANCY, I BEEN EATING
MAC DOPDS EVERY DAY FOR THREE
YEARS.
I GOT TYPE 10 DIE XWITS.
BLUE CROSS?
BITCH, I GOT BLUE FOOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT MY HEALTH
INSURANCE PLAN IS CALLED?
HOPING IT GOES AWAY.
>> DONNEL, HAVE YOU EVER TRIED
ALTERNATIVE MEDICINE?
>> YEAH, WHEN TE TELL ME HOW
MUCH THE PROCEDURE COSTS, I GO,
WHAT'S THE ALTERNATIVE?
>> THANK YOU, DONNEL.
NOW, OUR NEXT GUEST IS SOMEONE
WHO HAS BEEN AFFECTED CLOSELY BY
THIS STORY.
A GUY WHO HAPPENS TO LOOK LIKE
LUIGI MANGIONE.
>> HEY, NANCY.
YEAH, THIS WHOLE THING'S KIND OF
ABOUT AN ROLLER COAST ARE FOR
ME.
ON THE ONE HAND, I KEEP GETTING
TACKLED BY BOUNTY HUNTERS.
ON THE OTHER HAND, I'VE GOTTEN
SOME OF THE HORNIEST DMS IN MY
LIFE.
I HAVEN'T PAID FOR A MEAL IN
BROOKLYN IN DAYS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE
HEALTH CARE SYSTEM IN THIS
COUNTRY?
>> NANCY, HONESTLY --
>> HEY, GUYS!
DO YOU WANT A LONGER DONG IN
UNDER SIX DAYS?
WELL, SO DO I!
>> WELL SAID.
WELL, Y'ALL, THIS HAS BEEN
CRIME STORIES WITH ME, NANCY
GRACE.
AM I READING THIS RIGHT?
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, CHRIS
ROCK!
THANK
YES!
WELCOME, "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
THIS IS THE 50th ANNIVERSARY.
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE BEEN
AROUND FOR 50 YEARS.
WANT TO CONGRATULATE LORNE MICHAELS
ON 25 GREAT YEARS --
OF "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"!
A LOT GOING ON IN THE NEWS, MY
GOD.
IT'S SO CRAZY OUT THERE.
IT'S SO HARD JUST GETTING IN THE
BUILDING TONIGHT.
SO MUCH SECURITY.
MY GOD.
I WALKED BY A BUNCH OF BABY
OIL-SNIFFING DOGS.
IT WAS INSANE.
EVERYBODY'S WORRIED.
I MEAN, WE GOT LUIGI.
WE GOT LUIGI, YOU KNOW, AND
THAT'S GOOD.
I REALLY FEEL SORRY FOR THE
FAMILY.
EVERYBODY'S FIXATED ON HOW
GOOD-LOOKING THIS GUY
LOOKS ARE
FOR YOU LOOK LIKE JONAH HILL, NO
ONE WOULD CARE.
THEY ALREADY GAVE HIM THE CHAIR
ALREADY, HE'D BE DEAD, OKAY?
BUT HE ACTUALLY KILLED A MAN.
A MAN.
A MAN WITH A FAMILY.
A FAMILY.
KIDS, MAN.
I MEAN, I HAVE CONDOLENCES.
I HAVE REAL CONDOLENCES FOR, YOU
KNOW, FOR THE HEALTH CARE CEO.
I MEAN, THIS IS A REAL PERSON,
YOU KNOW?
BUT YOU ALSO GOT TO GO, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES DRUG DEALERS GET
SHOT.
I MEAN, YOU SEEN "THE WIRE,"
RIGHT?
IT'S BEEN A BAD YEAR FOR MY
PEOPLE, BLACKS.
IT'S BEEN -- IT'S NOT BEEN A
GOOD YEAR.
KAMALA.
DIDDY.
JAKE PAUL.
BEATING MIKE TYSON.
WHAT THE HELL?
WHO IS THIS JAKE PAUL?
THIS 27-YEAR-OLD PUNCHING A
60-YEAR-OLD MAN IN THE FACE?
IS THIS WHAT THE WHITE MAN HAS
REDUCED HIMSELF TO?
STOP IT.
WHO'S HE GOING TO FIGHT NEXT,
MORGAN FREEMAN?
I HATE JAKE PAUL.
I GOT LANDLORD HATE FOR HIM.
I HATE HIM.
I HATE HIM LIKE COCAINE HATES
MONOGAMY.
THE BIG THING, BIG THING, TRUMP,
MAN, TRUMP.
TRUMP, MAN.
TRUMP HAD A GOOD YEAR, MAN.
TRUMP SURVIVED AN ASSASSINATION
ATTEMPT.
SURVIVED ASSASSINATION ATTEMPT.
WON THE PRESIDENCY AGAIN BY
WINNING THE POPULAR VOTE.
WAS JUST NAMED "TIME" MAN OF THE
YEAR.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO A NICER GUY.
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
SCARED.
LIKE, OH, MY GOD, HE'S GOING TO
BE SO UNDIGNIFIED.
WHEN I SAY A LOT OF PEOPLE, I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE NINE NEW YORK
THERE'S DIDN'T VOTE FOR HIM,
OKAY?
NO, NO, PEOPLE ARE LIKE, "HE'S
GOING TO BE SO UNDIGNIFIED,
IT'S
THE PRESIDENCY OF THE UNITED
STATES."
DUDE.
IT'S THE UNITED STATES.
IT'S NOT -- YOU KNOW, COME ON.
WE'VE HAD SOME PRESIDENTS IN THE
UNITED STATES, COME ON, MAN.
THIS IS NOT THE MOST DIGNIFIED
JOB IN THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW, WE'VE HAD PRESIDENTS
SHOW UP TO THE INAUGURATION
WITH
PREGNANT SLAVES, OKAY?
AND I'M JUST TALKING ABOUT BILL
CLINTON.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW WHAT COUNTRY WE
LIVE IN.
YOU KNOW THE HISTORY OF THIS
COUNTRY.
YOU KNOW HOW MANY RAPISTS ARE IN
MY WALLET RIGHT NOW?
A CUP OF COFFEE IN AMERICA COSTS
SEVEN RAPISTS!
TRUMP'S GOING TO GET IT DOWN TO
THREE.
THAT'S RIGHT, MAN.
IT'S CRAZY.
MENENDEZ BROTHERS GETTING OUT OF
JAIL.
MENENDEZ BROTHERS?
YEAH, GETTING OUT OF JAIL.
JUST IN TIME TO GET DEPORTED.
TRUMP IS GOING TO DEPORT THEIR
ASS, YOU MURDERING MEXICANS!
TRUMP IS NOT PLAYING, MAN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS TIME IT'S TOTALLY
DIFFERENT.
HE'S WORKING WITH THE NUMBER ONE
AFRICAN AMERICAN IN THE WORLD.
THE RICHEST AFRICAN AMERICAN IN
THE WORLD.
ELON MUSK.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE IS AFRICAN AMERICAN.
ELON GOT MORE KIDS THAN THE
CLEVELAND BROWNS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOBODY KNOWS HOW TO GET RID OF
PEOPLE LIKE A SOUTH AFRICAN.
OH, HE'S SERIOUS.
TRUMP IS NOT PLAYING.
HE GOT ELON.
THEY'RE GOING TO PUT THEM IN A
ROCKET SHIP.
CALL IT "SPACEMEX."
OH, YEAH.
J. LO'S GOING TO MARRY BEN AGAIN
JUST SO SHE CAN STAY IN THE
COUNTRY.
I KNOW SHE'S NOT MEXICAN.
BUT TRUMP DOESN'T KNOW THAT.
JUST A BIG OLD LATIN STEW.
TRYING TO KEEP IMMIGRANTS OUT,
MY GOD.
YOU KNOW, A LOT LESS IMMIGRANTS
WOULD COME INTO AMERICA IF YOU'D
STOP PAYING THEM $700 MILLION TO
PLAY BASEBALL.
STEVE COHEN BOUGHT ONE DOMINICAN
FOR $700 MILLION.
USED TO BE ABLE TO GET A WHOLE
BUSHEL FOR THAT MUCH.
I SAID BUSHEL!
IN THE BIG STORY THIS WEEK --
THAT'S RIGHT, MAN -- JOE BIDEN
PARDONED HIS SON, HUNTER BIDEN.
I GOT TO HAND IT TO JOE, MAN.
YOU KNOW, HE DON'T MOVE AS FAST
AS HE USED TO.
HE DON'T TALK AS FAST AS HE USED
TO.
YOU KNOW, BUT THAT MIDDLE FINGER
STILL WORKS, BOY.
THAT'S RIGHT, MAN.
PEOPLE ARE COMPLAINING.
GOT THE NERVE TO COMPLAIN.
LIKE, WHAT?
ONLY AN ANIMAL WOULD NOT PARDON
THEIR SON.
MY GOD.
IMAGINE GOING HOME TO YOUR WIFE
IF YOU DIDN'T PARDON YOUR SON.
EVERY PARENT IN THE WORLD WOULD
PARDON THEIR SON.
EXCEPT THE PARENTS OF THE
MENENDEZ BROTHERS.
AND WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
GRACIE ABRAMS IS HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK!
MEET SANTA?
>> OH, YOU'RE GOING TO REMEMBER
THIS DAY FOR A LONG TIME.
>> HO HO HO!
WELCOME TO SANTA'S VILLAGE.
IS EVERYONE READY TO GET THEIR
PICTURE TAKEN WITH THE BIG GUY?
>> YEP, IT'S CLARE'S FIRST TIME.
>> THIS YEAR, WE'RE DOING
SOMETHING A LITTLE SPECIAL.
THIS YEAR, WE HAVE TWO SANTAS TO
CHOOSE FROM.
>> HO HO HO!
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS!
>> OH.
COOL.
>> ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS TELL ME
WHICH SANTA YOU WANT TO GO TO.
>> I'M SORRY, WHAT?
>> WHICH SANTA DO YOU WANT YOUR
DAUGHTER TO GET A PICTURE WITH?
A PICTURE YOU'LL CHERISH FOR THE
REST OF YOUR LIFE.
SO, SANTA NUMBER ONE?
OR SANTA NUMBER TWO?
WHAT IS YOUR -- PREFERENCE?
>> UH, I GUESS -- I DON'T KNOW,
UH -- THE REGULAR ONE?
>> REGULAR?
REGULAR, AS OPPOSED TO -- EXTRA
CRISPY?
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED TO BE A
LITTLE MORE SPECIFIC THAN THAT.
>> UH -- THE WHITE ONE?
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
COULDN'T QUITE HEAR YOU.
>> WE WANT TO SEE THE WHITE
SANTA CLAUS, PLEASE.
>> OH, THAT IS SHOCKING.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
WHO'S NEXT?
>> HI, YEAH, I'M SORRY, WHY ARE
THERE TWO SANTAS?
>> WELL, IT'S THE BUSIEST TIME
OF YEAR.
AND THIS CUTS THE WAIT TIME IN
HALF.
AREN'T YOU HAPPY THERE'S TWO
SANTAS?
>> YEAH, NO, DEFINITELY.
>> MUCH MORE CONVENIENT, THANK
YOU FOR DOING THIS.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
TIME TO DECIDE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT GRANDMA TO DO
WITH THE PICTURE?
DO YOU WANT HER TO PUT IT ON THE
FRIDGE?
OR IN THE GARAGE?
>> UM -- WE --
>> SO WHICH SANTA IS IT GOING TO
BE?
>> WE JUST REMEMBERED THAT WE'RE
JEWISH.
COME ON, GANG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BIANCA AND A LOU WASSERMAN TO
YOU TOO.
>> HI, WE'RE HERE TO MEET SANTA.
>> WELL.
WE'VE GOT TWO EQUALLY QUALIFIED
SANTAS TO CHOOSE FROM.
TAKE YOUR PICK.
>> I DON'T KNOW, THEY BOTH SEEM
GREAT.
>> WELL, THEY'RE ONLY -- YOU
KNOW, THEY ARE.
BUT ONLY ONE SEEMS TO BE GETTING
ALL THE WORK.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ONE SANTA'S BEEN BUSY ALL DAY.
AND THE OTHER SANTA IS SO FREE,
HE'S ON A ZOOM MEETING.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO
INTERRUPT HIS MEETING, SO WE'LL
JUST WAIT FOR THE OTHER ONE.
>> OKAY, WELL, I JUST WANT TO
SAY I WILL BE CHOOSING THE BLACK
SANTA.
I SEE YOU, BLANTA.
>> BLANTA IS NOT A THING, PLEASE
DO NOT CALL ME THAT.
>> I AM JUST SO EMBARRASSED BY
THESE SMALL-MINDED PEOPLE WHO
CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE SANTA BEING
ANYTHING OTHER THAN A STRAIGHT
WHITE MAN.
IN FACT, IF THERE WAS A QUEER
FEMALE SANTA, I WOULD CHOOSE
THEM.
>> WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK.
'CAUSE THEY'RE HERE.
SAY HI TO SANTA NUMBER THREE.
>> HI.
HO HO HO.
>> BLACK.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
W WE'LL GO WITH THE BLACK ONE,
THANK YOU.
COME ON, LET'S GO SEE BLANTA.
>> I DON'T LIKE BLANTA AT ALL,
I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND TAKE
MY LUNCH, ACTUALLY.
>> OKAY, LOOKS LIKE SANTA IS
GOING ON A BREAK.
>> OH, YES!
>> DON'T CLAP YET, BECAUSE IT'S
TIME TO BRING OUT OUR BACKUP.
EVERYONE WELCOME ARAB SANTA.
LANGUAGE ]
>> AND HO HO HO!
>>> NEXT WEEK, MARTIN SHORT WITH
MARIJUANA NIPPLE PASTIES.
>> THOUGHT THEY WERE EARTH DAY
STICKERS.
>> TOTALLY.
THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, MY TURN.
LET'S SEE.
LET'S SEE WHAT MY SECRET SANTA
HAS DELIVERED -- OKAY.
WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
>> WELL, NOT TO OUT MYSELF AS
YOUR SECRET SANTA, BUT I MADE
YOU INTO A SIMPSONS CHARACTER.
>> YOU MADE ME INTO A SIMPSONS
CHARACTER?
SO I'M LIKE IN THE SHOW NOW?
>> WELL, NO.
I JUST MADE IT USE AN APP CALLED
SIMPSIFY.
YOU SENT IN A PHOTO, THEY MAKE
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE IN THE
SIMSOMES.
>> THAT'S HILARIOUS, THANK YOU,
TREVOR.
THIS IS THE BEST GIFT I'VE
GOTTEN IN MY LIFE, SERIOUSLY.
>> OKAY.
I GUESS I'LL GO NEXT.
LET'S SEE WHAT MY SECRET SANTA
GOT ME.
OH, A JUMP ROPE.
>> I PANICKED.
>> NO -- I LIKE IT.
I'M JUST NOT TOTALLY SURE THAT I
CAN USE IT FOR ANOTHER SEVEN
MONTHS.
>> AGAIN, I'M REALLY SORRY.
>> A QUESTION.
WHAT WOULD MY JOB IN
SPRINGFIELD?
CAROL?
>> MAYBE YOU'RE THE MEDICAL
DIRECTOR AT A TEACHING HOSPITAL,
LIKE YOU ARE IN REAL LIFE.
>> WRONG.
WHEELS?
>> MY NAME IS SUSAN.
>> IN HIS DEFENSE, YOUR NAME IS
SUSAN WHEELS.
>> YEAH, I JUST DON'T THINK HE
MEANT IT THAT WAY.
BUT MAYBE YOU WORK WITH MR.
BURNS.
>> NO.
I'M A DANCE TEACHER.
AT BART'S SCHOOL.
AND BART LIKES ME.
BECAUSE I SEE SOMETHING IN HIM.
>> COOL, MAN, YEAH.
THAT SEEMS FINE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE ENJOYING THE
GIFT.
>> OKAY, CAN I GET A GIFT NOW?
I HAVEN'T OPENED MINE YET.
OH, TAMPONS!
OH, MY GOD, I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
TRY THESE!
NOW I WON'T HAVE TO KEEP BUYING
NEW PANTS.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHO I'D LIKE TO
AVOID IN SPRINGFIELD.
HOMER.
HOMER'S NOT A GOOD GUY.
>> REALLY?
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK HE'S KIND
OF FUNNY.
>> SO IT'S FUNNY TO DRINK ALL
DAY AND STRANGLE YOUR SON AND
HIT YOUR WIFE?
>> I DON'T THINK HOMER HITS
MARGE.
>> IN MY EPISODE, HE DOES.
>> IN YOUR EPISODE OF "THE
SIMPSONS" HOMER HITS MARGE?
>> THAT'S PART OF IT.
WHAT ELSE HAPPENS?
AROUND, COME ON, LET'S GO
AROUND, WHAT ELSE HAPPENS IN MY
EPISODE?
>> MAYBE MILLHOUSE GETS A COOL
HAIRCUT AND BART GETS JEALOUS?
>> THAT'S GOOD, BUT NOT FOR MY
EPISODE.
SAVE IT FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK HAPPENS.
BART GOES TO MY DANCE CLASS, BUT
HE'S GOT TEARS IN HIS EYES.
SOMETHING'S WRONG AT HOME.
SO I GO SEE MARGE, AND I CAN
TELL.
SOMEBODY KICKED HER ASS.
>> YOU GOT TO TELL CHIEF WIGHAM!
>> CHIEF WIGHAM IS TOO STUPID
AND FAT.
NO, I TAKE MATTERS INTO MY OWN
HANDS.
SO I'D GO LOOKING FOR HOMER.
>> OH, HE'S PROBABLY AT MO'S.
>> HE IS.
BEEN DRINKING ALL NIGHT.
>> PROBABLY WITH HIS BUDDY
BARNEY.
>> YES, WHEELS.
YOU'RE ON A ROLL.
>> I DON'T LOVE THAT.
>> SO I WALK OVER TO HOMER AND I
SAY, "WHAT KIND OF MAN HITS A
WOMAN?"
AND HOMER TAKES A SWING AT ME.
BUT I SPIN AND KICK HIM IN THE
CHEST.
AND AS HE LIES DYING ON THE
FLOOR, HE UTTERS HIS FINAL
WORDS.
D'OH!
>> THEN MARGE COMES RUNNING IN.
SHE JUMPS INTO YOUR ARMS AND SHE
SAYS --
>> MY HERO!
YOU KILLED HOMIE!
>> AND BART'S THERE TOO.
HE HUGS YOU AND SAID, "THANKS,
DAD."
>> CUT TO NIGHTTIME, ME AND
MARGE ARE IN BED.
SHE SAYS, "READY TO GO TO ROUND
SIX?"
AND I SAY, "I GOT THE STAMINA."
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE A DANCER!
>> IT ALL COMES TOGETHER.
JUST LIKE ME AND MARGE.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS, EVERYONE!
SEEMS LIKE YOUR GRANDPA WAS A
SPECIAL GUY.
>> HE REALLY WAS.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME CLEAN OUT
HIS BARN, GUYS.
IT MEANS A LOT.
>> OF COURSE, BENNIE.
THAT'S WHAT NEIGHBORS ARE FOR.
WE KNOW HOW MUCH IT MEANS TO
YOU.
>> HE WAS THE GREATEST GUY I'VE
EVER MET.
I'LL MISS HIM EVERY DAY.
>> WE'RE HERE FOR YOU, BUD.
>> WHAT'S THE STORY HERE?
>> YEAH.
THAT'S GRANDPA'S OLD CAR.
HE GOT IT WHEN HE WAS A TEENAGER
IN THE '50s.
IT BROKE DOWN, BUT MAN, HE LOVED
THIS THING.
HE TALKED ABOUT IT LIKE IT WAS
ALIVE.
EVEN HAD A NAME FOR IT.
HE CALLED IT KIRBY.
>> DID THE CAR JUST START ON ITS
OWN?
>> I THINK IT JUST SMILED.
GRANDPA SAID IT WAS MAGIC, BUT I
THOUGHT HE WAS CRAZY.
>> I THINK HE WANTS US ALL TO
GET IN.
>> WHOA, WHOA!
>> INSANE!
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> THAT'S ODD.
MAYBE WE JUST GOT TO --
>> LOOKS LIKE KIBY DON'T WANT US
IN THERE.
>> I'M TRYING TO UNLOCK IT.
>> WHAT YEAR DID YOU SAY THIS
CAR WAS FROM AGAIN?
>> 1958.
>> WHY WON'T THE CAR DOOR OPEN?
>> LET ME TRY.
DID HE JUST SMACK MY BUTT?
¶ I LIKE BIG BUTTS AND I CANNOT
LIE ¶
>> KIRBY!
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT I
DIDN'T KNOW MY GRANDFATHER THAT
WELL.
>> I REMEMBER YOU SAYING HE WAS
THE GREATEST GUY YOU EVER MET.
>> HEY, WHY DON'T WE ALL LISTEN
TO SOME TUNES?
¶ SNOW IS FALLING WHITE ¶
¶ WE GOT THE POWER ¶
¶ WHITE
¶ POWER ¶
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD.
WELL, I'M OUT.
>> RICHELLE, JAMARI!
>> DON'T HAVE TO ASK ME AGAIN.
>> WE COMING.
>> FIRST THING TOMORROW, I'M
TAKING THIS THING TO THE
SCRAPYARD, HOW ABOUT THAT?
¶ I'M SORRY ¶
>> KIRBY IS SORRY?
>> HE KNOWS HE MESSED UP.
>> KIRBY, SO -- YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> YO, GUYS, WHERE HAVE YOU
BEEN?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER FOR
YOU.
STACY'S PARTY'S TONIGHT.
ARE YOU GUYS COMING OR WHAT?
>> I COULD REALLY USE A PARTY.
>> AND I COULD USE A DRINK.
>> ONLY PROBLEM IS, UBER WON'T
BE HERE FOR LIKE 25 MINUTES.
>> YOU THINKS THINKING WHAT I'M
THINKING?
>> AIN'T NO WAY I WAS GETTING IN
THAT CAR.
>> LYFT, WHEN UBER'S TAKING TOO
LONG AND YOUR GRANDPAPPY'S CAR
IS RACIST.
>>> OKAY, EVERYBODY, LET'S
HUDDLE UP, HUDDLE UP.
I THINK THINGS GOT PRETTY WILD
AT LAST FRIDAY'S HOLIDAY PARTY,
BUT WE WANT TO MAKE IT CLEAR
THAT WE AT INTERCORP HAVE A
ZERO-TOLERANCE FOR WORKPLACE
HARASSMENT.
NOW, THAT BEING SAID, CORPORATE
HAS DECIDED TO FIRE OUR VICE
PRESIDENT OF SALES, MARK
SANDERS.
>> ABOUT DAMN TIME.
>> NASTY BUZZARD.
>> AND ALSO OUR FRONT DESK GUY,
CHARLIE.
>> AWW!
>> NOT CHARLIE!
>> AND IF IT'S ONLY OKAY WITH
YOU, THEY'D LIKE TO BOTH
FORMALLY APOLOGIZE TO ALL OF
YOU.
COME ON OUT HERE, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, PHIL.
FIRST OF ALL, I JUST WANT TO
SAY, I OBVIOUSLY HAD TOO MUCH TO
DRINK AT THE HOLIDAY PARTY.
AND MY BEHAVIOR WAS INEXCUSABLE.
>> YEAH, MINE TOO, MY BAD.
>> SPECIFICALLY, I KNOW WHAT I
SAID, YOU KNOW -- WHEN I SAID
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU DRESSED
GIRLIE FOR ONCE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT I MEANT.
BUT I KNOW IT WAS HIGHLY
INAPPROPRIATE.
>> WELL, I THINK IT MEANT YOU'RE
A PIG AND THAT'S WHY THEY FIRED
YOUR ASS.
>> HEY, DONNA.
I SAW THAT DRESS TOO.
I BELIEVE I ALSO SAID SOMETHING
TO THE EFFECT OF, MM, MM, MM,
GIRL, YOU GOT 94 JUNK THAN A
YARD SALE, HOW MUCH FOR THAT
DIRTY OLD BOX?
THEN I SHOOK MY HEAD, I DID A
LITTLE DANCE, AND I SAID, DON'T
YOU HURT NOBODY WITH THAT THING.
THAT WAS WEIRD, MY BAD.
>> OH, CHARLIE, YOU'RE JUST TOO
MUCH.
>> CLASSIC CHARLIEISM.
>> YEAH, MICHELLE, I KNOW I
JOKINGLY SAID, IF YOU TOOK A
TEQUILA SHOT WITH ME AND DANCED,
I'D MAYBE GIVE YOU THAT
PROMOTION YOU ASKED FOR.
I GUESS THAT WAS OUT OF LINE.
>> OH, YOU GUESS?
SERIOUSLY?
GO TO HELL, MARK.
>> OKAY, LET'S TRY TO KEEP IT
CORDIAL HERE, GUYS.
>> MICHELLE MY BELLE, I KNOW I
BASICALLY SAID THE SAME THING,
EXCEPT I LAID ON THE FLOOR, PUT
A DOLLAR BILL IN MY MOUTH, AND I
SAID, MMM-MMM-MMM, TRY TO PICK
IT UP WITH NO HANDS, SHELLEY.
THEN I SHOOK MY HEAD, DID A
LITTLE DANCE, AND I SAID, DON'T
YOU HURT ME WITH THAT THING, I'M
COOL.
>> YOU STILL OWE ME ANOTHER TRY,
CHARLIE.
>> HOW IS THAT BASICALLY THE
SAME THING?
>> COME ON, PHIL, YOU CAN'T FIRE
CHARLIE, HE'S JUST BEING
CHARLIE.
>> THE DECISION CAME FROM
UPSTAIRS, THERE'S NOTHING I CAN
DO.
>> DAVID, I KNOW WHEN I MET YOUR
HUSBAND AT THE HOLIDAY PARTY,
YOU KNOW, WE KIND OF HAD A
AWKWARD EXCHANGE.
>> OH, YOU MEAN WHEN YOU ASKED
WHO THE GUY WAS IN OUR
RELATIONSHIP?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S A LITTLE MORE THAN
AWKWARD.
>> SERIOUSLY, MARK?
WHAT A DUMBASS.
>> I SAID IT, I WAS WRONG, I GET
IT NOW.
>> NOW, NOW, NOW.
I THINK I KNOW WHERE MARK IS
COMING FROM HERE, BECAUSE DAVID,
I REMEMBER TELLING YOU AND YOUR
HUSBAND SOMETHING LIKE, LOOK
HERE, OLD CHARLIE IS STRAIGHTER
THAN A CHOPSTICK.
BUT IF WE WAS IN THE JOINT?
MMM-MMM-MMM!
I SAW YOU AND YOUR HUSBAND
KNICK-KNACK AND PADDY-WHACK.
BECAUSE YOU'D BE GIVING THIS DOG
A BONE.
THEN I WOULD SHAKE MY HEAD, DO A
LITTLE DANCE, AND I WOULD SAY,
DON'T YOU HURT EACH OTHER WITH
THEM THINGS.
YOU GOT TO FORGIVE ME.
>> SERIOUSLY, CHARLIE, IT WOULD
BE AN HONOR TO SERVE WITH YOU.
>> YOU CANNOT FIRE CHARLIE.
CAN'T YOU JUST GIVE HIM MARK'S
JOB INSTEAD?
>> DON'T YOU THINK -- I ALREADY
TRIED THAT, GAIL.
>> YOU OFFERED THE DOOR GUY MY
JOB?
I'M THE VIP OF SALES.
HE'S BEEN DRINKING SINCE 6:00
A.M.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO STAY WET.
GAIL, DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT ME.
MAYBE I CAN LAND A JOB AS YOUR
CHRISTMAS TREE.
BECAUSE I'M ALREADY DECORATED.
I'VE GOT THREE BALLS AND
DING-A-LING-A-LING FOR THE WHOLE
FAMILY, MMM-MMM-MMM!
>> DON'T MAKE PROMISES YOU CAN'T
KEEP, CHARLIE.
>> HOW ARE YOU OKAY WITH THIS
GUY?
WHAT IF I SAID I WANTED TO SHAKE
MY DING-A-LING-A-LING?
>> OH!
>> OH, WHY DO YOU HAVE TO MAKE
EVERYTHING SEXUAL?
>> YEAH, HE'S JUST BEING A SWEET
OLD GUY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I KNOW WHY I'M BEING
FIRED, TOMMY.
YOU REMEMBER THE OTHER DAY WHEN
I CAUGHT YOU LEAVING THE COMPANY
GYM?
>> NO, CHARLIE, I DON'T.
>> WELL, YOU WAS WEARING THEM
GRAY SWEAT PANTS, AND I ACCUSED
YOU OF TRYING TO SMUGGLE OUT A
CAN OF TENNIS BALLS.
>> NOT RINGING A BELL.
>> YOU TOLD ME THAT WAS ALL YOU,
SO I POINTED AT IT AND I YELLED,
AIN'T NO WAY ITTY BITTY TOMMY IS
SLINGING WOOD LIKE THAT!
IT WAS REAL LOUD IN FRONT OF
EVERYBODY.
>> VAGUELY.
>> THEN I SHOOK MY HEAD, AND I
DID A LITTLE DANCE, AND I SAID,
DON'T YOU HURT NOBODY WITH THAT
THING, TOMMY!
>> OH, YEAH, NOW I REMEMBER,
YES, YES.
>> IS THAT WHY I'M GETTING
FIRED?
>> ACTUALLY, NO, CHARLIE.
YOU'RE BEING FIRED BECAUSE YOU
WERE CAUGHT ON CAMERA STEALING A
WHOLE VENDING MACHINE AND
REPORTING IT MISSING.
>> WELL, TECHNICALLY IT IS
MISSING.
>> PLUS YOU CHARGED THE CFO'S
CREDIT CARD WITH 32 DIFFERENT
ONLYFANS ACCOUNTS.
>> SO IT WENT THROUGH?
>> UH-HUH, AND YOUR URINE SAMPLE
HAD A MELTED BAGGY OF COCAINE IN
IT.
>> THAT'S WHERE I DROPPED IT.
>> YOUR NAME'S NOT CHARLIE, IT'S
RICKY LAMONT, YOU HAVE A WARRANT
FOR MAKING FAY FAKE E-BIKE
BATTERIES.
>> BECAUSE THEY CAUGHT ON FIRE?
THAT'S MY BAD, EVERYBODY.
¶ I COULD GO AND
READ YOUR MIND ¶
¶ I THINK ABOUT
YOUR DUMB FACE
ALL THE TIME ¶
¶ LIVING IN YOUR GLASS HOUSE
I'M OUTSIDE, OH ¶
¶ LOOKING INTO BIG BLUE EYES
HE DID IT JUST TO HURT ME
MAKE ME CRY ¶
¶ SMILING THROUGH IT ALL
YEAH, THAT'S MY LIFE ¶
¶ YOU'RE AN IDIOT
NOW I'M SURE
NOW I'M POSITIVE
I SHOULD GO AND WARN HER ¶
¶ OOH, BET YOU'RE THINKING
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ KICKING BACK ON YOUR COUCH
MAKING EYES FROM
ACROSS THE ROOM ¶
¶ WAIT, I THINK
I'VE BEEN THERE TOO ¶
¶ WHAT'D SHE DO TO
GET YOU OFF UH-HUH
TAKING DOWN HER HAIR LIKE
OH MY GOD ¶
¶ TAKING OFF YOUR SHIRT
I DID THAT ONCE
OR TWICE, UH ¶
¶ NO, I KNOW
I KNOW IT'S WRONG
BUT I THINK I LIKE HER
SHE'S SO FUN ¶
¶ WAIT, I THINK I HATE HER
I'M NOT THAT EVOLVED ¶
¶ I'M SORRY SHE'S MISSING IT
SAD, SAD BOY ¶
¶ NOT MY BUSINESS
BUT I HAD TO WARN YA ¶
¶ OOH, BET YOU'RE THINKING
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ KICKING BACK ON YOUR COUCH
MAKING EYES FROM
ACROSS THE ROOM ¶
¶ WAIT, I THINK
I'VE BEEN THERE TOO ¶
¶ OOH
YOU'VE GOT ME THINKING
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ BUT I KNOW WHAT I KNOW
AND YOU'RE JUST
ANOTHER DUDE
OOH, THAT'S SO TRUE ¶
¶ OH-OH, OH-OH ¶
¶
¶ MADE IT OUT ALIVE
BUT I THINK I LOST IT
SAID THAT I WAS FINE
SAID IT FROM THE COFFIN ¶
¶ REMEMBER HOW I DIED
WHEN YOU STARTED WALKING
THAT'S MY LIFE
THAT'S MY LIFE ¶
¶ I'LL PUT UP A FIGHT
TAKING OUT MY EARRINGS
DON'T YOU KNOW THE VIBE
DON'T YOU KNOW THE FEELING ¶
¶ YOU SHOULD SPEND THE NIGHT
CATCH ME ON YOUR CEILING
THAT'S YOUR PRIZE
THAT'S YOUR PRIZE ¶
¶ OOH
BET YOU'RE THINKING
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ KICKING BACK ON YOUR COUCH
MAKING EYES FROM
ACROSS THE ROOM ¶
¶ WAIT, I THINK
I'VE BEEN THERE TOO ¶
¶ OOH
YOU'VE GOT ME THINKING
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ BUT I KNOW WHAT I KNOW
AND YOU'RE JUST
ANOTHER DUDE ¶
¶ OOH, THAT'S SO TRUE
OH-OH
SHE'S SO COOL ¶
¶ KICKING BACK ON YOUR COUCH
MAKING EYES FROM
ACROSS THE ROOM ¶
¶ OOH, THAT'S SO TRUE
OH ¶¶
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU, GOOD EVENING,
EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THIS WEEK, AMERICA CONTINUED THE
DELICATE, SENSITIVE DEBATE OVER
WHO WILL PLAY THIS GUY IN THE
NETFLIX MINISERIES.
AFTER POLICE ARRESTED SUSPECTED
CEO SHOOTER LUIGI MANGIONE, THEY
FOUND A NOTE ON HIM EXPRESSING
ANGER AT CORPORATE AMERICA.
YET HE WENT TO STARBUCKS BEFORE
THE SHOOTING AND THEN WAS CAUGHT
AT McDONALD'S.
SO PERHAPS HIS GREATEST CRIME
WAS HYPOCRISY.
THE McDONALD'S WHERE THE SHOOTER
GOT CAUGHT HAS BEEN GETTING
ONE-STAR YELP REVIEWS TO PUNISH
THEM FOR SNITCHING.
FIRST OF ALL, WHO LOOKS AT YELP
REVIEWS OF McDONALD'S?
THE ONLY YELP REVIEW OF
McDONALD'S SHOULD BE, "WAS OPEN,
5 STARS."
EVERYONE WHO WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL
WITH THE ALLEGED SHOOTER SAID
THEY WERE SHOCKED THAT HE COULD
BECOME AN ASSASSIN, WHEREAS
EVERYONE I WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL
WITH WAS SHOCKED I DIDN'T.
>>> TENSIONS OVER MYSTERIOUS
DRONES FLYING ABOVE NEW JERSEY
CONTINUED TO RISE AFTER A DRONE
CRASHED INTO A PERSON'S
BACKYARD.
AT LEAST WE KNOW WHOEVER'S
FLYING THEM IS A FRIGGING WOMAN.
>>> DONALD TRUMP HAS BEEN NAMED
TIME'S PERSON OF THE YEAR.
BECAUSE NO PERSON ON EARTH HAS
TAKEN OUT MORE OF OUR GODDAMN
TIME.
>>> AMAZON IS PLANNING TO DONATE
$1 MILLION TO DONALD TRUMP'S
INAUGURATION.
IT MAKES SENSE BECAUSE AMAZON
AND TRUMP BOTH WANT TO SHIP
STUFF OUT AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.
IT'S THE '90s, GUYS.
>>> TRUMP ALSO SAID FRIDAY THAT
HE WOULD TRY TO PERMANENTLY END
DAYLIGHT SAVING TIME BY
CHALLENGING THE SUN TO A STARING
CONTEST.
>>> IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT MATT
GAETZ WILL HOST A NEW TALK SHOW
ON ONE AMERICA NEWS NETWORK
CALLED "THE MATT GAETZ SHOW."
HE'LL BE COVERING EVERYTHING
FROM QUINCEANERA TO PROM NIGHT
JITTERS.
>>> A LAWYER WORKING WITH ROBERT
F. KENNEDY JR. HAS PETITIONED
THE GOVERNMENT TO REVOKE
APPROVAL OF THE POLIO VACCINE,
BECAUSE IT AIN'T CHRISTMAS
WITHOUT SOME TINY TIMS.
>> ELON MUSK GAVE OVER $20
MILLION TO THE MYSTERIOUS RBG
PAC WHICH CLAIMED TRUMP AND RUTH
BADER GINSBURG AGREED ON THE
ISSUE OF ABORTION.
WOW, I NEVER EVEN KNEW TRUMP GOT
HER PREGNANT.
>>> SUPREME COURT JUSTICE
KETANJI BROWN JACKSON MADE HER
BROADWAY DEBUT IN A ONE-NIGHT
PERFORMANCE IN "N-JULIETTE"
WHILE JUSTICE THOMAS BLEW
EVERYONE AWAY IN "KINKY BOOTS."
>>> SENATOR MITCH McCONNELL,
SEEN HER WATCHING A GUST OF WIND
BLOW AWAY A HOMELESS GUY'S
LOTTERY TICKET --
HE SUFFERED MINOR INJURIES AFTER
HE FELL DURING A REPUBLICAN
LUNCH, BUT THANKFULLY HE LANDED
ON HIS HARDSHELL BACK.
>>> FOLLOWING A LENGTHY LEGAL
BATTLE, A PANEL OF JUDGES IN THE
UK RECENTLY PUBLISHED THEIR
RULING THAT CALLING A MAN BALD
IS A FORM OF HARASSMENT.
HERE TO COMMENT IS A BALD MAN.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME,
COLIN.
BY THE WAY, MY EYES ARE DOWN
HERE.
>> THANKS, MAN, YEAH.
I WASN'T LOOKING AT YOUR --
>> MY WIDDLE BALD HEAD?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
SAY?
>> OF COURSE NOT, NO.
>> YOU CAN'T MAKE FUN OF A MAN
FOR BEING BALD THANKS TO THREE
BRAVE JUDGES IN THE UK, WHOO!
>> OKAY, SO THEY'RE ALL BALD.
>> ARE THEY?
I DIDN'T NOTICE.
I DON'T SEE HAIR.
OR COLOR.
TO ME, EVERYONE IS BALD AND
BLACK.
HEY, MAYBE THAT'S JUST ME.
>> YEAH, IT'S DEFINITELY JUST
YOU.
SO I IMAGINE YOU'RE PRETTY HAPPY
ABOUT THIS RULING?
>> OF COURSE.
SICK AND TIRED OF ALL THE BALD
JOKES, COLIN.
AND YEAH, I'VE HEARD THEM ALL.
WHEN I TAKE A SHOWER, I GET
BRAINWASHED.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
WHITES SCREAM WHEN THEY SEE MY
HEAD?
GIVE ME A BREAK.
APPARENTLY WHEN I WEAR A RED
TURTLENECK, I LOOK LIKE OLD
SPICE DEODORANT BECAUSE OF HOW
MY LITTLE BALD HEAD POPS OUT.
SOMETHING FUNNY ABOUT THIS TO
YOU, COLIN?
>> WHY WOULD YOU BE WEARING IT
UP TO YOUR EYE BROWS?
>> SINCE MY EYES GET COLD.
YOU KNOW, I ONCE DID JURY DUTY
WITH 11 OTHER BALD MEN AND THE
DEFENDANT STOOD AND UP SAID WE
LOOKED LIKE A CARTON OF EGGS.
EVERYONE LAUGHED, AND THAT GUY
KILLED SOMEBODY.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT WE DECIDED.
>> JESUS, MAN.
>> YEAH.
DON'T MESS WITH THE BALD MAN,
COLIN, 'CAUSE WE GOT NOTHING TO
LOSE.
EXCEPT MAYBE OUR EYEBROWS.
PLEASE LAUGH.
>> NO ONE'S LAUGHING, I'M SORRY.
>> LOOK, COLIN.
THERE'S NOTHING FUNNY ABOUT
BEING BALD.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> LOTIONING MY HEAD BECAUSE
SOMETIMES IT GETS DRY AND IT
GETS CHAPPED.
WHAT IS FUNNY ABOUT THAT TO YOU,
COLIN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
KIND OF A COUPLE THINGS.
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY ONE OF THOSE
PEOPLE WHO MAKES INSENSITIVE
JOKES ASKS REALLY INSENSITIVE
QUESTIONS LIKE, DOES THE CARPET
MATCH THE DRAPES?
>> WELL, DO THEY?
>> NO.
IT'S ACTUALLY CRAZY HAIRY DOWN
THERE.
THE CARPET IS GROSS.
THAT WHAT YOU WANTED TO KNOW?
>> NO.
I'M ACTUALLY SORRY I ASKED.
>> YOU'RE A JERK.
>> I'M SORRY?
>> YOU'RE A JERK!
YOU'RE A JERK!
SORRY, SCREAMING GOT ME SWEATY.
GOT TO TOWEL OFF.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU THINK THIS IS FUNNY,
COLIN?
JUST BECAUSE MY HEAD IS WET?
>> IT'S SO LOUD.
>> I DARE YOU TO LAUGH.
LOVE TO SEE YOUR ASS IN COURT.
MY LITTLE HANDS ON SOME OF YOUR
WIFE'S MARVEL MONEY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
A BALD MAN, EVERYONE.
>> I'M ALSO IMPOTENT.
DON'T LAUGH!
>>> TODAY MARKS THE 250th
ANNIVERSARY OF ALABAMA BECOMING
A STATE.
TO FIND OUT WHAT LIFE WAS LIKE
IN ALABAMA 205 YEARS AGO, GO TO
MISSISSIPPI.
>>> THE GOLDEN GLOBE NOMINATIONS
WERE ANNOUNCED WITH THE MOST
GOING TO EMILIA PEREZ, WHICH IS
A MUSICAL ABOUT A MEXICAN CARTEL
LEADER WHO TRANCE TRANSITIONS
INTO A WOMAN.
THE MOVIE WAS WRITTEN WHEN I
ASKED CHATGPT TO MAKE MY
GRANDPA'S HEAD EXPLODE.
>>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT FOR
THE FIRST TIME EVER, MICHELOB
ULTRA IS THE MOST POPULAR DRAFT
BEER.
THANKS TO AN UNPRECEDENTED
INCREASE IN PUSSIES.
>> WE CAN DO THAT?
>>> KRISPY KREME REVEALED THAT
ITS ONLINE ORDERING SYSTEM WAS
BRIEFLY HACKED.
APPARENTLY, KRISPY KREME'S
CYBERSECURITY HAS A FEW HOLES.
SOMETHING WRONG WITH THIS MIC.
>>> EXPERTS ARE SAYING PARENTS
OF TEENAGERS SHOULD TEACH THEM
PORN LITERACY, PARTICULARLY
STEPMOTHERS.
>>> FOR THE FIRST TIME IN ALMOST
50 YEARS, WHALE MEAT WAS
AUCTIONED OFF IN JAPAN FOR
ALMOST $650 A POUND.
WOW, THAT'S CRAZY.
I GET IT FOR FREE JUST BY
SCRAPING IT OFF MY YACHT
PROPELLER.
DID SOMEONE CLAP?
>>> SABRINA CARPENTER JUST CAME
OUT WITH A NEW NETFLIX CHRISTMAS
SPECIAL WHEN HAS RECEIVED RAVE
REVIEWS.
HERE TO COMMENT IS NEW CAST
MEMBER JANE WICKLINE.
HELLO, JANE, WELCOME.
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE A NEW SONG
FOR US?
>> YES, WELL, I'M A HUGE SABRINA
CARPENTER FAN, SO I'M ACTUALLY
GOING TO SING A SONG AS HER.
>> OH, OKAY.
I LOVE THAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO A SABRINA
CARPENTER IMPRESSION?
>> NO.
I CAN'T LOOK OR SOUND LIKE HER.
SHE'S COMPLETELY PERFECT.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO SING A
SONG IN HER STYLE?
>> NO.
BUT FOR THE PURPOSE OF THIS
SONG, I AM HERE.
>> OKAY.
GREAT.
SO WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
>> WELL, A LOT OF PEOPLE ON THE
INTERNET LIKE TO START JUICY
RUMORS ABOUT WHETHER POP STARS
ARE GAY.
THIS IS A NEW SONG THAT I,
SABRINA CARPENTER, WROTE, CALLED
"WHEN WILL EVEN ONE PERSON DO"
THAT ABOUT ME?"
¶ TAYLOR SWIFT SINGS ABOUT A
CRUSH ON A BEST FRIEND ¶
¶ AND YOU ALL CRY LESBIAN
BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T PHRASE IT MY
BOY BEST FRIEND ¶
¶ IN A MUSIC VIDEO I MAKE OUT
WITH JENNA ORTEGA ¶
¶ NO ONE DOUBTS ME AT ALL WHEN I
SAY THIS IS A SONG FOR ¶
¶ ONE OF MY EX-BOYFRIENDS AND
THAT'S ALL IT WAS ¶
¶ BUT NO ONE EVEN WONDERED ¶
¶ ARIANA BREAK UP WITH YOUR
GIRLFRIEND EVERYONE'S PISSED ¶
¶ HARRY WEARS RAINBOW PANTS YOU
WRITE 50 ARTICLES ABOUT IT ¶
¶ I MAKE OUT WITH JENNA ORTEGA
PASSIONATELY AND EVERYONE'S LIKE
I HEARD A SONG ABOUT SHAWN
MENDES ¶
¶ HELP ME JUST TELL ME WHERE I'M
GOING WRONG ¶
¶ WHY AM I THE ONLY STRAIGHT POP
STAR TAKEN AT THEIR WORD ¶
¶ IT'S LONELY I DO GAY STUFF AND
YOU DON'T GET MAD ¶
¶ I JUST WANT THE SAME
TREATMENT ¶
¶ I WANT TO HAVE MYSTIQUE ¶
¶ WHY DON'T YOU THINK I'M EITHER
BI OR PRETENDING I MIGHT BE ¶
¶ I'M NOT BI OR PRETENDING BUT
WHY DOES NO ONE THINK I'M
LYING ¶
¶ I WANT YOU TO THINK I HAVE
SECRETS ¶
¶ I WANT YOU TO THINK I MIGHT
HAVE SECRETS ¶
>> SORRY.
DOES THIS HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE CHRISTMAS SPECIAL?
>> OH, I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT THE
CHRISTMAS SPECIAL UP, COLIN.
FOR THE ALBUM THAT IS CALLED
FRUITCAKE.
DOES THAT MAKE YOU THINK OF
ANYTHING?
>> I GUESS THE CAKE.
¶ PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT I'M DOING WRONG ¶
¶ I MADE OUT WITH A GIRL
ALIEN AT THE VMAs ¶
¶ NOTHING ¶
¶ I FEEL LEFT OUT WHY CAN'T YOU
SEE ME FOR WHO I ¶
¶ REALLY EASILY COULD BE IN
SECRET ¶
¶ SHOULD I COVER A SECOND ROUND
ON HOW MUCH CLEAR I CAN I GET ¶
¶ I LEAVE A TRAIL OF BREAD
CRUMBS THEN I LEAVE A TRAIL OF
LOAVES OF BREAD ¶
¶ I WANT YOU TO THINK I MIGHT
HAVE SECRETS ¶
¶ I MIGHT HAVE SECRETS COLIN I
MIGHT HAVE SECRETS ¶
¶ I JUST WANT YOU TO THINK I
¶ AND THAT'S ME AND MY SONG ¶
>> SABRINA CARPENTER, EVERYONE!
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
>>> NURSE, SCISSORS, PLEASE.
>> SCISSORS.
>> AND I NEED A BIT MORE
SUCTION.
>> SUCTION.
>> OKAY.
THE GALLBLADDER REMOVAL WAS
SUCCESSFUL.
AND THE PATIENT'S VITALS ARE
STATEMENT.
>> DOING GREAT, DOC.
>> ONCE YOU FINISH THE SUTURES,
WE'LL APPLY STERILE DRESSING.
>> DOCTOR, LOOKING AT THE
PATIENT'S MEDICAL CHART, IT SAYS
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO REMOVE HIS
APPENDIX, NOT HIS GALLBLADDER.
>> OH, MY GOD, WHAT?
THE PRE-OP INSTRUCTIONS SAID
GALLBLADDER REMOVAL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
OKAY, I'M JUST GOING TO OWN IT,
THAT WAS ME.
>> YEAH?
LESLIE MARKED THE WRONG ORGAN
FOR REMOVAL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WAIT, ARE YOU GUYS MAD AT ME?
>> NO TIME FOR THAT.
WE NEED TO REMOVE THE INFLAMED
APPENDIX RIGHT NOW BEFORE IT
BURSTS.
>> YES, DOCTOR.
>> WAIT, I FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS
REALLY HATE ME RIGHT NOW.
>> DOCTOR, HIS BLOOD PRESSURE IS
DROPPING FAST.
>> HEY, I'M FEELING REALLY
ANXIOUS.
CAN I GET A HUG?
>> NO, LESLIE, I DON'T WANT A
HUG FROM YOU RIGHT NOW.
>> STOP PICKING ON LESLIE, YOU
GUYS ARE BEING RUDE AT HELL.
>> YOU'RE JEALOUS BECAUSE LESLIE
IS THE HOTTEST GIRL IN NORTH
AMERICA.
>> DOCTOR, I'M LOOKING AT THE
X-RAY.
THERE'S A FOREIGN OBJECT IN THE
PATIENT'S ABDOMEN.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN AIRPOD.
>> OH, MY GOD, OKAY.
I'M JUST GOING TO OWN IT, IT WAS
ME.
>> WHAT?
LESLIE!
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
>> DON'T MAKE LESLIE CRY!
WHEN SHE CRIES, SHE SOUNDS LIKE
A VICTORIAN GHOST.
>> OOHHHHHH!
>> DOC, THE PATIENT IS STIRRING!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> OH, OH, OH!
>> HE'S AWAKE!
>> I AM AWAKE.
OF COURSE I'M AWAKE, BECAUSE I
WASN'T GIVEN ENOUGH ANESTHESIA.
>> THAT ACTUALLY WASN'T ME.
>> WE ALL KNOW IT WAS YOU,
LESLIE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, I'LL OWN THAT.
>> YEAH, AND I HEARD THE WAY YOU
GUYS WERE TALKING TO HER, AND
IT'S NOT OKAY.
ALL RIGHT?
>> I THINK YOU PUNCTURED AN
ARTERY WHEN YOU SAT UP.
>> SHH, I'M NOT DONE.
IF LESLIE WAS A GUY, WOULD I
PUNCH HER IN THE FACE?
YES.
IF I WERE A WOMAN, WOULD I PUNCH
HER IN THE FACE?
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
BUT EVERY WORKPLACE NEEDS A
LESLIE.
YEAH.
EVERYONE NEEDS -- EVERYONE NEEDS
A LESLIE.
EVERY WORKPLACE NEEDS A LESLIE.
ONE ANNOYING CO-WORKER TO RAG
ON.
IF IT WASN'T HER, IT WOULD BE
YOU, NURSE MICHELLE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> YES.
OW YORE, UNNAMED MALE NURSE.
>> I HAVE A NAME.
IT'S ALOUSIOUS COOTER.
>> THAT'S YOUR NAME THAT SUCKS.
AND YOU, NOT SURE WHAT YOUR ROLE
IN THIS SKIT IS.
BUT WHO HAPPY YOU'RE GETTING AIR
TIME, GOOD LUCK.
HOPE YOUR PARENTS ARE PROUD OF
YOU.
>> OH, THANK GOD HE SKIPPED ME.
>> NO, NO, NO.
I WAS JUST GETTING TO YOU.
>> HOW MUCH BLOOD YOU GOT?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, APPARENTLY A
LOT.
BUT MAYBE, MAYBE I'LL STOP
BLEEDING IF YOU OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
>> WHY WOULD I OPEN MY MOUTH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME JUST TRY IT.
OPEN IT!
HA HA HA!
YOU GUYS, YOU HAVE BEEN SO, SO
GOOD TO ME.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING IN
RETURN.
IF SOMETHING WAS TO GO WRONG, I
HAVE A STACK OF MONEY BURIED --
AT THIS ADDRESS -- 184 -- OH
GOD.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO, LESLIE?
>> I'M JUST GOING TO OWN IT.
I NEEDED TO CHARGE MY AIRPODS.
ARE YOU GUYS MAD AT ME?
¶ TWO AUGUSTS AGO
I TOLD THE TRUTH, OH
BUT YOU DIDN'T LIKE IT
YOU WENT HOME ¶
¶ YOU'RE IN YOUR BENZ
I'M BY THE GATE ¶
¶ NOW YOU GO ALONE
CHARM ALL THE PEOPLE
YOU TRAIN FOR
YOU MEAN WELL BUT AIM LOW ¶
¶ AND I'LL MAKE IT KNOWN
LIKE I'M GETTING PAID ¶
¶ THAT'S JUST
THE WAY LIFE GOES
I LIKE TO
SLAM DOORS CLOSED ¶
¶ TRUST ME
I KNOW IT'S
ALWAYS ABOUT ME
I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ¶
¶ TWO SUMMERS FROM NOW
WE'LL HAVE BEEN TALKING
BUT NOT ALL THAT OFTEN
WE'RE COOL NOW ¶
¶ I'LL BE ON A BOAT
YOU'RE ON A PLANE
GOING SOMEWHERE, SAME ¶
¶ AND I'LL HAVE A DRINK
WISTFULLY LEAN
OUT MY WINDOW ¶
¶ AND WATCH THE SUN SET
ON THE LAKE ¶
¶ I MIGHT NOT FEEL REAL
BUT IT'S OKAY, OH ¶
¶ 'CAUSE THAT'S JUST
THE WAY LIFE GOES
I PUSH MY LUCK, IT SHOWS ¶
¶ THANKFUL YOU DON'T
SEND SOMEONE TO KILL ME
I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ¶
¶ YOU WERE THE BEST
BUT YOU WERE THE WORST
AS SICK AS IT SOUNDS
I LOVED YOU FIRST ¶
¶ I WAS A DICK
IT IS WHAT IT IS
A HABIT TO KICK
THE AGE-OLD CURSE ¶
¶ I TEND TO LAUGH
WHENEVER I'M SAD
I STARE AT THE CRASH
IT ACTUALLY WORKS ¶
¶ MAKING AMENDS
THIS NEVER ENDS
I'M WRONG AGAIN
WRONG AGAIN ¶
¶ THE WAY
JOYRIDING DOWN OUR ROAD ¶
¶ LAY ON THE HORN
TO PROVE THAT IT HAUNTS ME
I LOVE YOU
I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ¶
¶ THE WAY LIFE GOES
I WANNA SPEAK IN CODE
HOPE THAT I DON'T
WON'T MAKE IT ABOUT ME ¶
¶ I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ¶¶
YEAR.
YOU'VE EARNED SOME TIME OFF.
BUT FIRST --
>> THE MOST INSANE EVENT OF THE
YEAR!
YOUR OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY!
60 EMPLOYEES.
SEVEN INTERNS.
ALL GOING HARD IN THE SAME SPACE
THEY WERE WORKING IN 50 MINUTES
AGO.
IT ALL KICKS OFF AT 5:45 P.M.
WHEN YOUR DRAB, BORING OFFICE IS
UTTERLY TRANSFORMED INTO YOUR
SAME DRAB, BORING OFFICE BUT
WITH A FEW LIGHTS TURNED OFF.
WITH MUSIC BY JASON'S LAPTOP.
AS SOON AS HE CAN FIGURE OUT HOW
TO PAIR A SPEAKER WITH IT.
>> IT SAYS IT'S ON, IT SAYS
BLUETOOTH IS ON.
>> WITH APPEARANCES BY THE SHY
GIRL FROM MARKETING WHO HAS ONE
DRINK AND REVEALS TOO MUCH ABOUT
HERSELF.
>> I ACTUALLY MAKE MORE ON
ONLYFANS THAN I DO HERE.
>> THE GUY WHO BROUGHT HIS KID.
>> IT'S DADDY'S WORK!
>> AND IMMEDIATELY REGRETS IT.
>> I WANNA GO HOME!
>> ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
>> THIRSTY?
HEAD OVER TO THE KITCHEN FOR AN
ICE WARM BEER.
HUNGRY?
ENJOY A GENEROUS SPREAD OF THE
SOGGIEST FOOD YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
>> SO WET.
>> BUCKLE UP, BECAUSE JUST WHEN
YOU THOUGHT THINGS COULDN'T GET
WILDER, THE ACTION IS BROUGHT TO
A SCREECHING HALT BY DANA FROM
SALES, RECORDING HER FIVE MINUTE
LONG SECRET SANTA.
>> WHO GOT THE DUNKIN' GIFT
CARD?
JASON DID, YEAH, THANK YOU,
JASON.
YOU GET TO COME ON UP.
GUYS, WE'RE ALMOST DONE SO DON'T
LEAVE.
>> THEN A TWIST NO ONE SAW
COMING.
THE CUTE GIRL FROM ACCOUNTING
HAS A FAT, QUIET BOYFRIEND.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> THIS IS KYLE.
WE MET AT CHURCH.
>> DING DING DING!
MYSTERY SOLVED.
EVERYONE WILL BE BUZZED.
EXCEPT FOR NICK, WHO DIDN'T
FINISH HIS WORK IN TIME.
AND WATCH THE DRAMA UNFOLD WHEN
WORK WIVES AND REAL WIVES
COLLIDE.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOUR HUSBAND IS
SUCH A CHARACTER, FUNNY.
I'M GOING TO GET A DRINK.
EXCUSE ME, GUYS.
>> SHE'S SO PRETTY.
I WANT TO SEE YOUR PHONE.
>> YOU'RE NOT SEEING MY PHONE.
>> IF YOU HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE,
I'M SEEING YOUR PHONE.
LET ME SEE --
>> GO, GO, GO, GO.
>> DON'T FORGET OFFICE JOKERS
WHO HAVE THE STAFF IN STITCHES
WHEN THEY DANCE ON A DESK.
THEN HAVE THE WHOLE STAFF SILENT
WHEN ONE OF THEM FALLS.
>> I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
NO BIG DEAL.
>> AND YOU'LL KNOW THE PARTY'S
LIT IF THE CLEANING STAFF LOOKS
SUPER PISSED OFF.
DRINKS WILL BE DRUNK.
H.R. COMPLAINTS WILL BE CREATED.
AND SOMEONE HERE IS GETTING A
DUI.
BUT IT'S NOT WHO YOU THINK.
JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT THE PARTY
COULDN'T RAGE ANY LONGER, IT
DOESN'T.
BECAUSE IT'S TUESDAY NIGHT, AND
ALL Y'ALL GOT WORK TOMORROW.
YOUR OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY.
>> YES, SO FANCY, I HOPE I DON'T
USE THE WRONG FORK.
>> ARE WE DINING SOLO TONIGHT?
>> NO, I'M HERE FOR A BLIND
DATE.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS, ACTUALLY.
I'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE
THIS BEFORE.
>> WELL, THAT GENTLEMAN OVER
THERE HAS BEEN STARING AT YOU
EVER SINCE YOU ARRIVED.
>> MY -- MY GOODNESS.
>> I'LL BE BACK WITH A MENU WHEN
I FEEL LIKE IT.
>> HELLO, LOVELY LADY.
I HOPE I'M NOT BOTHERING YOU.
>> WHY WOULD YOU BE BOTHERING
ME?
AREN'T YOU MY BLIND DATE?
HENRY McADAMS?
>> YEP.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
YOU SAID THAT WEIRD.
>> NO, I'M HIM.
HARRY McRIB.
>> OH, OKAY, I THOUGHT IT WAS
HENRY, AND YOU SAID I'D
RECOGNIZE YOU BECAUSE YOU'D BE
WEARING A ROSE.
>> OH, RIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT FELL IN THE TOILET.
DO YOU WANT ME TO GO GET IT?
>> NO.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST -- NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND MY SISTER SAID YOU'RE 28?
>> I WAS.
>> FUNNY.
I'M GLAD WE'RE DOING THIS.
>> HEY, I HAVE AN IDEA.
THIS PLACE IS SO STUFFY.
WHY DON'T YOU AND I GO HAVE SEX
IN MY CAR?
>> OH -- NO.
WHY DON'T WE JUST GET SOMETHING
TO EAT AND GET TO KNOW EACH
OTHER?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT BEING MUCH OF A
GENTLEMAN.
DO YOU LIKE STEAK?
>> OH, GOSH, I LOVE IT.
>> DIG IN.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
TELL ME MORE ABOUT YOURSELF.
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE KIDS?
>> TO DO WHAT?
>> OH, NEVER MIND.
I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE YOU'RE
WEARING A WEDDING RING.
>> OH, IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S TOTALLY DEAD.
>> OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I MEAN, I WISH IT WAS A MORE
INTERESTING STORY.
BUT SHE'S JUST REALLY BAD AT
TAKING SELFIES.
>> WHAT IS -- I'M SO SORRY --
>> SHE FELL OFF THE EIFFEL
TOWER.
>> I SHOULDN'T HAVE BROUGHT THAT
UP.
YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> NO, NO, DON'T APOLOGIZE.
I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN OUT WITH AN
INTERESTING, GORGEOUS WOMAN IN A
LONG TIME.
>> AWW, THAT'S ACTUALLY REALLY
SWEET.
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE TO
ASK ME?
>> YEAH.
HERE'S A QUESTION.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HAVE SEX IN MY
CAR?
>> AGAIN, I'M GOING TO SAY NO.
>> I MEAN, WHAT IF I PULL UP
RIGHT TO THE DOOR?
I GOT HEATED SEATS.
>> NO, I'M SORRY.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
I HATE TO SAY THIS, BUT PERHAPS
THIS WASN'T MEANT TO BE.
>> PERHAPS NOT.
GOOD NIGHT, HARRY OR HENRY OR
WHOEVER YOU ARE.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
AND MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> OH, WELL.
>> EXCUSE -- ARE YOU TIFFANY?
I'M HENRY, SORRY I'M LATE, SO
RUDE OF ME.
>> NO, THAT'S OKAY, SIT DOWN.
IT'S GREAT TO MEET YOU.
>> YOU TOO.
AND DON'T WORRY, I CAN AFFORD
THIS RESTAURANT.
I WORK IN FINANCE.
HOW OLD ARE YOU ANYWAY?
MY SISTER SAID YOU WERE KIND OF
OVER 30?
NOT THAT THAT'S BAD.
IT'S JUST DIFFERENT.
IN A BAD WAY.
TIFFANY, ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING?
>> OKAY, WHAT THE HELL.
PULL THE CAR AROUND.
>> ACTUALLY, IT'S MORE OF A
PEDICAB IF THAT'S OKAY.
>> YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
ABRAMS, ADAM SANDLER, THE WHOLE
CAST.
THANKS, EVERYBODY.
IT WAS THE BEST WEEK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!