A-Span
Disappear
C-Span
-We now go live
to the White House,
where press secretary
Karoline Leavitt
is
four or five seconds from
wildin'.
-Thank you.
Thank you, members of the press.
Could we hold the work
on the ballroom, please?
I'm delighted to be here today.
As some of you know, I'm
about to go on maternity leave.
That's when you tell President
Trump about your maternity
and he says leave.
But before I go,
I'd like to introduce a man
who just finished
absolutely owning the Dems
in his congressional testimony.
The man, the myth,
the liability.
Pete Hegseth.
-Alright, cut the track! Cut it!
And yeah, this is a scotch.
I said I'd have just one.
Here you go.
For the baby.
-Okay.
-Alright, now listen up,
dingbats. Okay?
As you might have seen
on our sick-ass TikTok,
we've been bombing stuff,
doing sick air raids.
This war has been a movie.
Specifically
"The NeverEnding Story."
We've hit Iran with everything we've got --
missiles,
bombs, drones, and twins!
But now we're in a cease-fire,
wink.
Which is why I have time
to come talk
to you butt-munches.
So, alright, dumb questions,
go.
-Uh, yeah. When you recited that
Bible verse from "Pulp Fiction"
about vengeance
and furious anger,
um, did you know it was fake and
it wasn't really in the Bible?
-Yeah!
But also, I do believe
that someday it will be.
In Bible 2: Electric Bible-aloo.
Now, I'm not going to apologize
because I wear my religion
on my sleeve literally.
I have a tattoo on my forearm of
Jesus choking out Jimmy Kimmel.
Next.
-Yeah. Is it true that
you've already spent 25 billion
in taxpayer dollars?
-Is it true you suck?
-I'm just trying
to get an estimate
of what you think the total cost
of this war will be.
-Huh. I don't know.
I guess I could put it
in terms
like a theater kid
like you would understand.
♪ 525,000,
600 billion ♪
Ruff, ruff.
You just got dog-walked.
Next.
-What about reports that U.S.
military facilities
have been badly damaged?
Exactly how many bases
have been hit?
-More bases
than you've ever hit, virgin.
And you want to see a base
that's been badly damaged?
Check out your mom after
she's done riding Pete's dragon.
In summary, war is awesome.
Okay?
Everyone's always asking me
when's this war gonna be over?
That's like asking,
when is sex gonna be over.
Answer -- When the man is done.
Yeah, you.
-But President Trump himself
just declared
that the war is over.
-Okay. Yeah.
When he says it, it's cool.
And to quote another thing,
he says, you're fired.
-I don't work for you.
-You know what? You're right.
You're actually
not working for me.
Too brunette, not enough filler.
And what are those, B cups?
-One is. Yeah.
-Now, look, I'd love to stay
here
and keep dunking
on your weak asses,
but someone else
wants to come say hello
before he's
almost certainly fired.
Director of the FBI,
Mr. Kash Patel.
-What up? What up?
It's K-dot,
a.k.a. Kash with a K,
a.k.a. the most effective
FBI director
this country's ever had.
Kash Patel.
Now, after
the attempted assassination
of President Trump --
another one --
we conducted an investigation
that could not have been
more thorough.
We dotted every T
and bulged every eye.
And for those of you saying I'm
doing a bad job running the FBI,
well, what if I told you
this agency is
only six weeks away
from pinpointing the exact
location of Osama bin Laden?
You guys should not be reporting
the lies and the gossip.
You should be reporting
on the historic nature
of my appointment.
I am a trailblazer.
I'm the first Indian person
to suck at their job.
Everyone says Indian
people are smart, hardworking,
incredibly intelligent.
I've proved,
without a shadow of a doubt,
that we can be just as incapable
and incompetent as the whites.
Okay. Questions?
Yeah, you, little shorty.
-Are you nervous about reports
that Trump is angry with you?
-Hell no!
President Trump loves me.
Everybody loves me.
Even the Correspondents
Dinner shooter said,
"Kill everyone but Mr. Patel."
You get a shout-out like that
in a psycho's manifesto,
you must be doing something
right.
-Okay. Is it true that you,
the director of the FBI,
was locked out
of your own e-mail account?
-That's just more lies.
I've always been able to log
into my e-mail,
except for a brief
36-hour period of time
when I forgot I had changed my
password to KashMeOutside69.
-And can I ask about
your drinking?
-What about it?
-I was actually talking to
Mr. Patel.
-Oh. Awesome.
-Let me be clear.
This FBI director has never been
drunk or hungover on the job.
This FBI director has never
filled a 40-ounce travel mug
with ice-cold gin
and a swirl of dry vermouth
and six lemon peels,
and called it a Kashtini.
This FBI director
has never used taxpayer dollars
to take a private jet to fly him
and his girlfriend
to three different
Buffalo Wild Wings locations
across the country
to see if
they could taste the difference.
And this FBI director
has definitely not stood
on top of a couch
at the VIP room
of TAO Nightclub
and Asian Bistro
and shouted,
"Who wants the nuclear codes?!
J.K.! I ain't got 'em!"
And beyond that, I just
have one more thing to say.
-Live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Olivia Rodrigo!
-Thank you, thank you,
thank you so much.
It is seriously a dream
to be hosting tonight.
I grew up watching this show
and they say your
favorite "SNL" cast is the one
you watched as a teenager,
so mine is Mikey Day, Sarah Sherman,
Kenan Thompson,
and Chloe Fineman,
and they all came back
this week just to cheer me on.
How sweet is that?
Anyway, I have a new album
out next month.
Thank you.
My last two albums
were called "Sour" and "Guts,"
and this new one is called
"You Seem Pretty Sad
for a Girl So In Love."
So I learned more words, guys!
And you may not know this,
but before I was Olivia Rodrigo
the singer,
I was actually Olivia Rodrigo
the child actor.
When I was six,
I had my first ever acting job
in an Old Navy commercial.
Can we show the clip?
-Summer sizzling
cabana dresses, $15.
-Yeah.
Pretty sweet, pretty sweet.
They cut my line, though.
I'm not sure why.
But I managed to get
the full footage.
-Summer sizzling
cabana dresses, $15.
-Hey, that's not my real mom.
I want to go to The Gap.
I'm not sure why they cut that.
Then when I was 13,
I was on a Disney show
called "Bizaardvark" and --
We had an incredible cast
which included
acting legend Jake Paul.
And we'd always talk about
our futures, me and Jake.
I'd say, "I really
want to create music
that explores the complexities
of girls my age,"
and he'd say, "Well,
one day I really want to
beat up old guys on Netflix."
And we both did it. Hooray!
These last few years
I've been touring my albums,
which has been so incredible.
There are so many highs on tour,
connecting with fans,
visiting new cities.
And there was one, uh,
notable low.
Oh, my God, that was fun.
I'm okay.
That wasn't fun.
And I wasn't okay.
You know,
a lot has changed for me
since my first single
"drivers license,"
which was about
the biggest event in my life
when I was a teenager,
and now that I'm older,
I decided to write a new song
about the most recent big event
in my adult life, and
I really hope it speaks to you.
♪ I got my REAL ID last week ♪
♪ Showed up at the DMV ♪
♪ I sat there waiting
14 hours
with nine forms
To prove it's me ♪
♪ They finally called
my number ♪
♪ G-107632 ♪
♪ And I approached the lady ♪
♪ She says I don't have
what I need ♪
♪ She said my ID isn't real ♪
♪ Well, then
why did you give it to me? ♪
♪ The lady said,
"You need a pay stub" ♪
♪ I said, "What the hell
is that? ♪
♪ I'm 23" ♪
♪ And I know I'm not perfect ♪
♪ But I've never been so mad
at someone ♪
♪ This lady wants my passport,
my W-2 ♪
♪ And my firstborn son ♪
♪ My gas bill, my body count,
bra size ♪
♪ How long will this be? ♪
♪ And she said forever ♪
♪ So I'll just use my old
fake ID ♪
We have got a great show
for you tonight.
I'm here,
so stick around.
We'll be right back.
-You're watching Pluto TV,
home of your favorite
classic shows.
Now it's the 1983 nighttime
drama "Edge of Destiny."
-Marguerite, what on earth
are you doing here?
You weren't invited
to the champagne ball.
-Oh, but of course I was, Diana.
Your son asked me himself.
-Ah! And that's what I wanted to
talk to you about.
Marguerite, you're not to see
Reuben anymore.
Not today, not ever.
You see, I don't want
my son interacting with trash.
- Excuse me?
After everything
I've done for this family.
Why you!
-Oh! Stop it! Oh, stay back.
-Diana!
No!
-Marguerite, what in heaven's
name did you do?
-Reuben,
I don't know what happened.
Your mother was telling me
these --
these lies when she --
-Lies?
What did she say?
-Oh, dear.
She said you were calling off
the engagement.
It was lies, wasn't it, Reuben?
-I'm sorry, Marguerite.
I'd lose the house,
my inheritance.
-You'd throw me away for --
for money?
You bastard!
-Reuben! Not the stairs!
-Now, Miss Stapleton,
begging your pardon, ma'am,
may I have a word with you?
-Oh, yes.
But let's step away
from the stairs.
-Oh, I'm sorry, miss,
there's no time.
I'm Jonas, the family attorney.
We're prepared to make
you a generous offer of $500
to leave the premises and never
speak to young Reuben again.
But you must sign here now.
-No, I'll never sign
such a thing.
Not now, not ever.
-Whoa, whoa. Now be careful.
My legs are a bit uneasy.
And I'm standing
in front of these stairs.
-Oh, no.
-Marguerite, did
you just push that dapper
old dandy down the stairs?
-And why is there a pile
of bodies down there?
-I have no idea what you're
talking about, Stacia, Randall.
What are you doing here?
-We're taking Leopold to the
terrace for his afternoon wee.
-No one informed us
there would be a collection of
trash by the stairway.
- How dare you?
I should --
-Excuse me, ma'am.
I have this tower of
champagne flutes.
Where do you think
I should put -- Whoa! Oh!
Oh, my goodness!
-Clarence! No!
Oh, look. I stopped myself.
-Oh! Thank goodness, Clarence.
-Are you alright, Clarence?
You just fell down
so many stairs.
-Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Oh, no. Wait, no, I'm not!
-I'm on to you, Stacia.
It was you who told Reuben
about my past.
It was you who asked
Diana to end the engagement.
-You're mad. I would never.
-Confess.
Confess or Leopold gets it.
-No! Leopold!
You wouldn't dare!
-Try me.
-No! Leopold!
-Ha! Who's the trash now?
Well, well, well,
I suppose there's no one left
to inherit the house after all.
Now, who has the last laugh?
-I do, bitch!
My room
-♪ I've got the perfect
bedroom ♪
♪ I've got the perfect bed ♪
♪ I've got a purple phone
with the curly cord ♪
♪ Right beside my head ♪
♪ I've got a lava lamp and
boy-band posters on the wall ♪
♪ I've got a beanbag chair
and I've got a disco ball ♪
♪ I've got my glow in the dark
stars on the ceiling ♪
♪ Got my mood ring
that tells me how I'm feeling ♪
♪ I've got a TV, built-in VHS,
I love my bedroom ♪
♪ It's the best,
the only problem is ♪
♪ I'm in a zoo on the bug people
planet ♪
♪ Zoo on the bug people planet ♪
♪ Every day when the sun
comes up ♪
♪ The bug people come and look
at me ♪
♪ They let the zoo members
come in first ♪
♪ And the older bugs get in
for free ♪
♪ They watch me
through my boy band posters ♪
♪ Beady eyes all in a row ♪
♪ And they sit on bleachers
while I use the toilet ♪
♪ When I flush, they clap
like it's the dolphin show ♪
♪ I love my perfect bedroom ♪
♪ And I know it's an artificial
human habit-habit-habitat ♪
♪ In a cave on the bug people
planet, planet, planet ♪
♪ That little room for me ♪
♪ I never felt so free ♪
♪ There's a bug
who always protests ♪
♪ I can tell he's got
a big heart ♪
♪ Once a baby fell in my room ♪
♪ And they shot me
with a tranquilizer dart ♪
♪ Now, I don't have a lot
of movies ♪
♪ "A League of Their Own"
is the only one ♪
♪ And they couldn't get
a real copy ♪
♪ So they had to make
a bug people one ♪
-There's no crying
in Earth ball.
-I think they did
a really good job.
♪ Every night
when the bugs go home ♪
♪ I'm left in my room
and I'm all alone ♪
♪ I stare at the stars
and think of my fate ♪
♪ And that's when they bring
me a potential mate ♪
Hi. I'm Alan.
Not quite sure
how I got here, but I, uh...
I think they want us
to reproduce.
-No.
-Totally. I'm not ready either.
Uh, we'll get to know each other
first, then reproduce.
-Not interested.
-Makes sense.
Well, uh,
it was nice meeting you.
Oh, here comes the claw.
Well, we tried, buddy.
What now?
A life of luxury
in the royal palace?
-♪ I love my perfect bedroom ♪
♪ I know it's an artificial
human habit-habit-habitat ♪
♪ In a cave on the bug people
planet, planet, planet ♪
♪ That little room for me ♪
♪ I never felt so free ♪
-'Cause you're silly.
-No, that is not the truth.
-Hi, y'all. Rhett and Bev
here live on ShopTV.
Bev got some good news
during the break.
-Okay.
-The judge denied
her daughter's petition
to be legally emancipated.
Kiss my ass, Kayla.
I got you for two more years.
You lost, punkin. You lost.
-I say this -- When she
found out, she was moonwalking
like Michael Jackson.
Do your moonwalk.
There you go. Okay.
Oh, your life is a hoot.
-I know.
-Alright, coming up,
the most talented man
in Christianity returns.
-Oh!
-Tim Tucker Neeb's here
selling his Christian Y.A.
book series, "Nazareth High."
-Oh, okay! Hunk alert!
-Ooh!
-The son of God's greatest
miracle passing geometry.
-Oh!
-Okay!
-Tim Tucker Neeb.
-Is he a stand-up comedian?
Okay.
-He's a riot.
-Well, I wish y'all
were here in the studio
'cause it smells so dang good
in here.
What?
-It does.
That is thanks
to our first seller,
owner of Daisy's Custom Cakes.
It's Daisy Rae Rutledge.
-Well, aren't you
just the cutest thing?
-Oh, my grand grandma
will be so happy you said that.
She always says
ugly girls die alone.
-Ooh. That's sad.
-That's a little intense.
Uh, so what you got for us
today, Daisy?
-I am selling my
famous lava cake
that comes in a reusable tin.
-Reusable? No.
And you get the cake
and the tin for the
ShopTV price of just $19.95.
-That's it? Okay, you stop.
-I know, right?
Daisy, go ahead
and show the shoppers at home
what's smelling so good.
-Oh, boy.
I'm drooling already.
-I know.
-Look at me.
-Don't eat the whole thing, Bev.
-Oh, boy. Okay, okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay, okay.
-Come on.
Y'all ever seen anything
like that?
-Uh, just my wife's once
and my cat's every day.
Um, Daisy, why does --
why does your cake got a little
starfish in the middle there?
-Oh, baby, that's a fudge hole.
-Oh, no.
No, that can't be
what it's called.
-Oh, it is.
It's from the fudge
filling inside in the oven.
The steam needs somewhere
to escape
so it pops a cute little hole
in the top.
-Oh, I wouldn't call it cute,
though.
-That steam's what forms
all these pretty crust creases
and flavor wrinkles
around the little fudge hole
here.
-Oh, do you -- do you have to
rim it like that?
-Oh.
-Get off the close-up, Odell.
-How about we see who's
on the shop line?
Caller, you're on ShopTV.
What do you think of this cake?
-I think it looked like
a big old butthole.
-Hang up, Odell!
-Shame on you.
-What?
-So rude. Now, Daisy, tell me.
You know, why in the heck
do they call it a lava cake?
I don't know diddly about
baking, so you got to tell me.
-That's right. That's right.
-Well, my gram-gram
always says with some patience,
anyone can bake,
even ugly people.
-Okay, how about no
more quotes from gram-gram.
-So, why is it called
a lava cake?
-Oh, because of
the liquid fudge inside, silly.
Bev, stick your nose in the
fudge hole and take a big whiff.
-Oh, that was an awful sentence,
so I think I'm gonna pass.
Pass on that.
-Bev, come on.
It smells amazing.
-Okay, okay,
I'll do a quick one.
Okay.
-Oh, dear. Oh, Bev.
You got kids.
-Okay, okay, okay.
That's great.
I'm glad I did that
right on camera.
That's -- Alright. That's great.
-Now, how about a taste?
Rhett, stick your little finger
in there.
-Oh, no, no, I don't want to
mess up the pretty cake.
-Oh, the cake will be fine.
Just go slow.
-Oh, don't --
Don't say that, sweetheart.
Okay. Here you go. Here we go.
Alright, I'm gonna stick
my finger in here.
-Alright, okay.
Rhett, why are you using
your pinkie?
-I don't know.
-Pinkie.
-It seemed more polite.
Okay? Okay. Here you go.
I'll do it there.
Oh, I don't -- Oh, my lord.
Oh, nice.
There you go. Oh. Oh.
And there's something.
It's --
-Oh.
And it's peanut butter flavor.
Taste it.
-Oh, I know. Okay.
-Okay.
Okay.
-I mean, it tastes good
despite how bad that looked,
y'all.
Can I get something
to wipe my hand off, please?
Not toilet paper.
Lynette, use your head.
Daisy, can you tell everybody at
home about the special bunghole?
Bundle. Bundle.
Not bunghole. Bundle.
-Uh, for the next 10 minutes,
if you order two cakes,
you get two more free.
How about that?
-Wow, okay, that's a deal.
Let's take another caller.
Hi there. You're on ShopTV.
-Yeah.
Do these cakes come in
different flavors?
-Oh, sure do.
What's your favorite?
-Asian.
-Oh, hang up, Odell!
-Okay. Yuck.
-I don't understand
the question.
-Good.
-Don't think about it ever
again.
-Disgusting!
-Don't think about it.
-Well, speaking of reheating,
I understand you got a
little demo with a vanilla cake.
-Oh, yes, yes, yes.
-Okay.
-Alright. If you stick your cake
in the microwave for 90 seconds,
it does something super neat.
-Okay. Oh.
-Steam starts
coming out the fudge hole.
-Okay.
-Tilt it the camera.
Tilt it to camera.
-Oh, no.
I think they can see
it just fine.
Okay. Oh, no, don't cut to
the dang overhead, Odell.
That's obscene. Blur that.
-Blur it.
-Blur. Oh!
-Well, don't --
Don't blur everything
but the hole, Odell.
Odell.
Well, Daisy,
we got a packed show.
I wish we could chat more,
but time's a little tight.
-Tight like that cake.
-Odell!
-We told you to hang up on him.
-Okay, more ShopTV after this.
And, Odell,
if you keep messing with us,
I'm gonna stop sleeping
with you.
-Whoa, Bev!
-Hey, Brianna, thanks so much
for coming to my birthday party.
-Oh, of course.
-And I'm so sorry
that I invited Duncan.
Uh, it was
before you guys broke up.
-Huh. It's okay.
It's like three whole weeks ago.
I mean, obviously, I've
been thinking about him a lot
and just,
like, crying every night.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's my birthday, so...
-Sorry. I overheard.
And I just want to say
that's rough.
I'm sorry.
I'm Kevin, by the way.
-Oh. I'm Brianna.
Hey, this is gonna sound crazy,
but could you, like,
pretend to be my date tonight?
Maybe make my ex
a little jealous?
-Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, I could do that.
-Oh. Oh, my God.
-Sorry? What was that?
-Oh, sorry. No, my ex is here.
It looks like she's already
with another guy.
-Oh, man.
-Yeah.
Hey, I know we don't know each
other, and this might be crazy,
but would you, like, pretend
to be my date tonight?
Acting. Okay.
Um, that could be great.
I mean, um, does it matter
that I had a baby before or...?
-No. Why would that --
-Oh, okay.
Just because I'm a little older,
but --
Oh, but we're acting.
Okay. So, um...
Officer, I'm 18. I swear.
-Actually, I'm okay. Thank you.
-No, I really -- No, I want to
do it, I want to do it, I want
to do it, I want to do it,
I want to do it.
-Shh-shh. Chill, chill.
-Okay, chill, chill.
-Just look at them.
Look at them.
-Okay.
-And that is why
I never went skiing again.
-You're so funny.
-Oh, no.
He's making her laugh.
Damn it. Okay, um,
pretend I just told you a joke.
-Okay. Got it.
A gay joke?!
Hey, buddy, my sister's gay!
-No. Why that? No.
Laugh like you like it.
-Okay.
What a great gay joke!
-Oh, my God.
-Fun fact -- My sister's gay.
-What are you doing?
-Oh, my God.
He's with someone,
and they're having so much fun.
-Um, well,
then we need to have more fun.
Boop!
No, no, no.
-You're bad.
-Oh!
-You're so bad.
-Come on,
how are we gonna top that?
-Oh, you're bad!
-Aah!
-Oh! Oh, you're bad!
Oh! It's what they're doing.
Come on, lick it off.
-This is not what they're doing.
-Come on.
Do you want her back or not?
Lick it off.
Oh, yeah! Oh, that's the stuff.
Now giggle.
-Giggle?
-Yes.
Is she looking?
-Yeah,
but, like, not in a good way.
-Wow.
They're so, like, physical.
Their sexual chemistry is
off the charts.
-Uh, okay. Here, I got you.
-Oh, you're such a gentleman.
-Oh, quick,
give me your jacket.
-No!
-What?
-What are you doing?
-I'm taking your jacket.
Oh, you have nipples like
my son.
Look at that.
-Hey!
-You do.
-That's my shirt.
-His are like boing-boing.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Here.
-Boing-boing?
-Take mine. Take mine.
Take mine. Take mine.
-Okay.
-Stop it! Sit still!
-Oh, my God.
They're all over each other.
Oh, quick, give me a massage.
He'll hate that.
-Alright, you got it.
-Oh, my God.
Okay, well,
can I give you a massage?
-Oh, are you kidding?
I live for those things.
-Okay, perfect.
-What?!
-What are you doing?
You said you love massages.
I thought they were
something different.
What was that?!
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God!
-Alright, watch this.
Hey, everyone.
I just wanted to say
happy birthday to Marcus.
And the only thing better
than having friends
you've known your whole life
is meeting someone
you feel
like you've known forever.
-Oh, I feel the same way.
-Okay. Watch this.
-No. Do not. Do not.
-Watch this.
Let me say something.
Stop!
Ting ting ting ting!
Thank you for having
this birthday party!
-For I have met a man tonight.
We made love in the bathroom
so hard that it got in the food.
His name is Heinrich.
-It's Duncan.
He goes by Duncan.
We are to be wed at midnight!
-No. No, we're not.
-Under the clock tower.
-Jesus Christ.
-Now, let us pray.
-Duncan, wait.
I have to say something.
Duncan, I made a mistake.
I'm not over you.
And I was trying
to make you jealous tonight
by flirting
with some random nobody.
-Whoa.
-But...
I did it because I love you.
Please don't marry her.
-Too late, bitch!
I'm pregnant.
No, you're not.
-Yes, I am.
-No, she's not.
-I'm pregnant!
-Ma'am, stop.
Stop.
I want her.
I choose her.
Come on, babe,
let's get out of here.
-Alright.
You want to take my car or --
-Not you!
-I didn't know.
-Good night, ma'am.
Good night to you, I say.
-You put on quite
a show tonight, Beverly.
-Would you like
some more potatoes?
-Yes, please.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Olivia Rodrigo.
-♪ I know that the bar closes
at 11 ♪
♪ I hope you never finish
that beer ♪
♪ You know all the words to
"Just Like Heaven" ♪
♪ And I know why he wrote them ♪
♪ Now that you're standing
right here ♪
♪ One night I was bored in bed ♪
♪ And stalked you on
the Internet ♪
♪ Feminine intuition ♪
♪ Always had a vision
of us standing like this ♪
♪ Pressed up in the bathroom
line ♪
♪ Looking like an angel
on the walls of Versailles ♪
♪ The most alive I've ever
been ♪
♪ Kiss me and I might
drop dead ♪
♪ And I feel like I might
throw up ♪
♪ Left hook, right punch to
the gut ♪
♪ You're so, so pretty, boy ♪
♪ I'm paranoid I made you up ♪
♪ Yeah, I'd love it if you
walked me home ♪
♪ If you promised we could go
real slow ♪
♪ 'Cause I got chewing gum ♪
♪ And a bunch of stuff I'd like
to know ♪
♪ Like, have you ever been to
Japan? ♪
♪ Or taken that Eurostar to
France? ♪
♪ I've been dropping hints
all night ♪
♪ That I'd love it if you held
my hand, God damn ♪
♪ And then maybe we could
make-makeout ♪
♪ Clothes off and fall to
the ground ♪
♪ Let's go steady,
let's go out ♪
♪ And tell the whole damn
world ♪
♪ One night I was bored in bed ♪
♪ And stalked you on
the Internet ♪
♪ Feminine intuition ♪
♪ I always had a vision
of us standing like this ♪
♪ Pressed up in the bathroom
line ♪
♪ Looking like an angel
on the walls of Versailles ♪
♪ The most alive I've ever
been ♪
♪ But kiss me and I might ♪
♪ Pisces and a Gemini ♪
♪ But I think we might go
really nice together ♪
♪ If you let me stay the night ♪
♪ Well, I think I might just
have to stay forever ♪
♪ Pisces and a Gemini ♪
♪ But I think we might go
really nice together ♪
♪ If you let me stay the night ♪
♪ I might just have
to stay forever ♪
♪ One night I was bored in bed ♪
♪ And stalked you on
the Internet ♪
♪ It's feminine intuition ♪
♪ I always had a vision
of us standing like this ♪
♪ Pressed up in the bathroom
line ♪
♪ You're looking like an angel
on the walls of Versailles ♪
♪ The most alive I've ever
been ♪
♪ Kiss me and I might ♪
♪ Kiss me and I might
drop dead ♪