Martin's
-Alright, alright.
Here you are, ma'am.
Here you are.
Here is your Washington Redskin.
That's a shot of Campari
in an empty potato skin.
-Thank you.
To world peace.
-Yeah, it should be any day now.
-Alright. Alright.
Incoming.
Alright, cut.
Cut the jukebox. Cut it!
My man.
Drug boat!
-Secretary Hegseth,
can I get you your usual --
a shot of beer
with a, uh, pint of whiskey
dropped into it?
-That's right --
a reverse Irish car bomb, yes.
It's just nice
to have my sneaky bar here,
where I'm not going to
run into anyone from work
'cause none of Trump's people
like drinking as much as I do.
-Wrong!
-What?!
-Come on!
-Brett Kavanaugh!
-What is up?
Order!
Order in the court!
Yes. Order.
I find in favor
of six Bud Lights
and three shots of Jame-O.
-Yes!
-Come on!
-Yeah, a 6-3 decision.
Coming right up, Your Honor.
-Ah, Pistol Pete.
I kind of figured I was going to
find you here.
-Oh, did I include you
on a Signal chat by accident?
-No. No.
I just saw all the women
covering their drinks.
-Oh! Come on!
That could be you, too, buddy!
-I like that. I like that.
I like that.
-Ah, it's just great
that we share that.
-Yeah, it is fun. It is.
It's fun we share that.
Hey, can I just say we are both
kicking ass right now?
-Right?
Dude, can you believe
I just, like, started a war?
-Can you believe
I ended abortion?
Hey, your body, my choice.
-You knew I'd do it!
You knew I'd do it!
-Ah!
-Oh, how is the war going,
by the way?
-Oh, it's totally chill.
It's, uh -- It's totally chill,
or at this point --
It's like me
at a DWI checkpoint --
it completely blew over.
-Oh? Oh, really?
I-I thought I read we were, uh,
we were still bombing stuff.
-Ah, no, just like a few
every now and then.
We can stop whenever we want to.
-Oh, that's cool.
Check this out.
-What -- What is this?
What have you been up to?
-Well, it's a new, uh...
voting district
that I approved in Tennessee.
-Oh, wow. That's --
-Oh, wait. Actually, no.
That's a --
That's a field sobriety test.
They told me to draw a circle.
-Dude, you were really close.
-Thanks, Kemosabe.
-Yeah, you knew --
you knew it was a shape.
-Yeah.
Appreciate that.
-Can I be honest with you, man?
-Sure.
-It's just I -- I worked so hard
on this Iran War,
and I'm just worried
it's gonna end.
you know? It's kind of like I took
a bunch of BlueChew
and then didn't bang anyone.
Like, okay, I guess I'll just
watch "Seinfeld" bricked up.
-Well, thank God
we got each other, right?
-Yeah.
-You know
what the real war is right now?
The real war?
It's the war against...
...male loneliness.
I used to have all my buddies
to hang out with.
P.J., Tobin.
Squee.
Gangbang Greg.
-Yeah.
-Dr. William Cosby.
Just wish there were more
people in this administration
who could really hang.
-Yeah.
-Does this bar take "Kaaaash"?!
-Kash, what's up?
Ka-ching!
-Let's go!
-So, what's up? Are we
wilding out tonight or what?
-Yeah, we always wild,
KPop Demon Hunter.
-Yeah,
I got nothing to do tomorrow,
you know, 'cause of the...
"Ceasefire!"
Guys, check this out.
I made my own FBI bourbon
with my name on it.
-What?!
-Yes!
Somehow, this is a real thing
that I, the FBI director,
had made.
This is real.
-I bring my own alcohol to bars
because sometimes they think
I'm a kid with the fake ID.
They say, "Oh, no adult
would make this face
in official photos."
But, seriously, we're
all living the American dream.
I'm the first person
in my family to go to college...
parties,
many years after graduating.
-Hey K-9, is that rumor true
that you make everybody
in the FBI take a polygraph?
-No. I told them
to make a graph
of everyone in the FBI
who's poly.
My girlfriend wants to open up
our relationship.
-Oh, sick!
-Dude, come on!
-Yeah, she went --
She said she wants
to bring other dudes
into the bedroom
and for me to stay
in the living room.
-Hey, since we're opening up,
can I tell you guys
something top secret?
-Brother,
everything's a secret
when you're blacked out.
-Right.
Alright.
We're going to let Trump
do a third term.
-Nooo!
-Whaaat?!
-Come on!
I thought that was
unconstitutional.
Yeah, it was.
But Trump found
the original Constitution,
and at the end,
he wrote "Psych!"
We're gonna live forever!
-Yes!
-Alright, sorry, gentlemen.
It's your least favorite words
in the entire world --
last call.
-Oh, boo!
-Come on! Come on!
-So, what's it gonna be?
-Well, I guess...
I'll drink a whiskey drink.
-I'll drink a vodka drink.
-I'll drink a lager drink.
-I'll drink a cider drink.
-♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Matt Damon!
-Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm so happy to be here.
Guys, this is my third time
hosting.
Which seems a little low, right?
I mean, just considering I've
been around for like 30 years.
But that's okay.
I'm -- I'm here now.
I'm really excited because
I have a new movie coming out.
It's called "The Odyssey."
And it is in theaters --
not this weekend,
not next weekend,
but nine weekends from now.
Mid-July, baby!
So ...
we have more good news.
It is Mother's Day tomorrow.
Yes.
And I know normally
"SNL" flies all the cast moms in
for the show --
first class, no expense spared.
Apparently, that was
going to happen again this year,
but then Spirit Airlines
shut down.
So for all of you
waiting to see the cast moms,
I'm sorry --
it ain't happening tonight.
-Sorry. You said the cast moms
aren't coming tonight.
-Yeah, that's right, sir.
Uh, no cast moms this year.
-Oh, okay.
But Marcello's mom is here,
right?
-No, she's not here.
I'm sorry.
That wasn't in the cards.
-Well,
I'd really like to meet her.
-Buddy,
I don't know what to tell you.
We got to move on.
In about 15 minutes,
it is going to be Mother's Day.
And I realize for a lot of you,
you're probably freaking out
because you didn't get
your mother a gift.
Don't worry.
I thought about this.
I got you guys covered.
Just send her this.
Hey, there.
It's me -- Matt Damon.
I bet you thought
your kid forgot
to get you a Mother's Day gift.
No, this is your gift --
a personal message from me.
But wait.
I'm confused.
Your kid asked me
to make a video for their mom.
But you're their sister, right?
What?!
Shut up! No way.
'Cause you don't look
a day over --
You're kidding me.
I would have guessed
like 28, 29.
How old am I?
Old enough to know
what I'm doing.
Young enough to do it well.
Listen, I gotta go.
But you deserve a night out.
You tell your partner
to take you out on a date.
Not this weekend,
not next weekend,
but nine weekends from now.
There's a movie I think
you're really gonna like.
Happy Mother's Day.
So...
Just clip that and send it to
your mom -- you're all set.
-Hey, dumbass,
Marcello's mom is here.
-Hi, Matt Damon.
-Okay, Mom,
get away from this weirdo, okay?
-Bye, Matt Damon.
-We got a great show.
Noah Kahan is here --
so is Marcello's mom.
Stick around.
We'll be right back!
-You're watching
The Monster Channel.
Real
We now return to...
Godzilla
Dawn
-Admiral on deck!
-At ease.
I just got to sleep.
This better be good.
-Admiral, we're tracking
a sizable anomaly
in the Pacific Ocean,
heading west towards the
Northern California coastline.
-You woke me up for a Russian
reconnaissance sub?
-This is no sub, sir.
-Uh, Admiral, you might want to
take a look at this.
The USS Indiana just sent
a sonar scan of the location.
Whatever this thing is, it's
as tall as the ocean is deep.
-What's the depth there?
-Uh...2,500 feet.
-What?!
There's something the size
of two Empire State Buildings
swimming in our ocean?
-Admiral, you might want to
take a look at this.
It's making impact tremors
on the ocean floor.
It's not swimming, sir --
it's walking.
-Walking?!
What the hell is this thing?
-Admiral, um, you might want to
take a look at this.
-Jesus! What now?
The stress is drying me out.
Can I get, like, the thick,
green juice that I like?
-Here you are, sir!
-Thank you.
-What have we got, Officer?
Do you want to --
Do you want to finish the sip
that's in your mouth, sir?
-You like to savor the taste?
Okay.
Um, well, I'm looking
at the thermal imaging --
-Is there pineapple in this?
-No, sir,
just greens and apples.
-Oh, it tasted like pineapple
for a second. Sorry.
-Oh, Admiral, we just lost
contact with our submarine.
-All their comms are offline.
-Yeah, the data is showing
it suffered total hull failure.
I'll try and get the video
from its FLIR cam.
-Lock in, people.
We're gonna be here for a while.
I should eat something.
Can I get some of that runny,
lumpy yogurt that I like?
-I-I accessed the video, sir.
-Let me see it.
-Oh, my God!
-Jesus, Officer Harris!
I just saw that thing
grab a nuclear submarine
and crush it
like an empty soda can.
That cannot be possible!
So I need you to look me
in the eyes right now
and tell me
that video is authentic.
-Your yogurt, sir!
-Thank you.
-Putting so much
in your mouth, sir.
The video is authentic.
-Ah!
Well, I lost my appetite.
Can I get a huge,
ice-cold water, please?
-Here you go, sir!
-Thank you.
-Admiral, I'm getting
a transmission from Okinawa,
but it's in Japanese.
-Um, I know Japanese.
-You speak Japanese?
-Yes. Yes. I do.
I-I dated a girl from Japan,
and I lived there
for three years, sir.
-Was she hot?
-Um, don't know
why that matters.
Not really.
-Sorry to hear that.
Now go translate that message.
-Of course.
Excuse me.
Okay. Um.
All right. Um.
There's a lot of static.
-Hey, guys,
it's really important
that everybody stays hydrated.
This is a high-stress
situation.
I need everybody drinking
a lot of water.
Thank you.
-Thank you, Admiral.
-Um. Okay. Okay.
They're saying, uh,
"Monster
destroyed Okinawa base...
with laser from mouth"?
-My God!
-Oh, my God.
-They're --
They're calling it --
They're calling it "Godzilla."
--No, no, no, no.
Sir, please don't --
-Did you just say "Godzilla"?!
-Everyone, please stop!
I'm so wet!
I'm so wet.
I know a lot of high-stakes
information is being revealed,
but, please, if you can,
just try and spit away from me,
please.
-Sorry.
I didn't get to do it yet.
-Oh, God! He's here!
-Coming this Mother's Day, a
movie especially made for mom...
-Kids!
What are you doing here?!
-Mom, you know
we wouldn't miss Mother's Day.
-Oh, come in, come in!
-...with all the things
she loves in movies
and none of the things
she doesn't.
-Actually, we have some news.
We're gonna move back home.
-What?! Ahh!
-Introducing "Mom The Movie"...
the only movie completely devoid
of conflict, suspense,
and dramatic tension.
Just things
that work out for Mom.
-Oh, no.
Mom, is the big pickleball
tournament
at the same time
as my baby shower?
-No. They're on different days.
-Great!
-Yes!
-'Cause moms have enough stress.
So why not let them feel good
for a day, with dialogue like...
-Mom...
you're a really good mom.
-...and...
-It's twins.
-Oh! That's two!
-...and...
-That is a great story, Mom.
And I love that you told me the
race of all the people involved.
-Moms are the hardest-working
people in the world.
They deserve a movie
where the house is clean,
the kids are home,
and the husband is
straight up Matt Damon.
-I just love being married
to you, Matt Damon.
-I feel the same way, Rhonda.
Rhonda Damon.
-Remind me again how we met?
-Well, I was giving
a talk-back after a movie I did,
and I noticed your
massive necklace from the stage.
Now...you want to go upstairs?
-To make love?
-No.
To do a fashion show
with everything in your closet.
-Okay!
-Yes, yes!
-Yes!
-A story by moms for moms.
-Hey, is that the pink puffy
purse I bought you
with the big old gold chain?
-You're right.
It goes with everything.
-"Mom The Movie" is a hit,
and audiences are raving.
-I liked when the kids all
needed their birth certificates
and she had them.
-And it's designed
with the understanding
that most moms will fall
asleep after 23 minutes.
-So after that point,
the characters just
move things around and smile.
-I loved when the entire
family watched a full episode
of "House Hunters."
-It was helpful when
the characters put on name tags
so the audience could track
who was who.
It was a nice touch.
-How about that Mark Damon?
-Oh!
-And rest assured,
if something bad happens,
it'll be to someone
you don't like.
-Mom, did you hear?
Your friend is sick.
-Oh! Which one?
-Judith.
The one who said
your porch pillars were ugly.
How sad.
-So treat your mom to a movie
so tailor-made to her,
she'll wonder
if she wrote it herself.
-You mind
if I slip into something
a little more comfortable?
-Rhonda Damon.
-Jason Flippin' Bourne.
-"Mom The Movie" --
streaming now on HomeGoods+.
-Hey, there you go, sweetheart.
Enjoy that.
-Oh, that's nice.
-Enjoy that, sweetheart.
-That's nice for you.
-Hey. Sorry to bother.
Do you guys think
you could keep it down?
-Hey, get the hell out of here.
-Go back to Wall Street!
-What's wrong with this guy,
huh?
Pushing in here like that.
-You know what it is --
everybody thinks
they're a tough guy these days.
-Hey, that's true.
That's true.
Hey. Hey, speaking
of tough guys, huh,
listen to this.
The other day, this guy's
smoking a cigarette
right outside my house.
He flicks his cigarette
right onto my lawn.
So I go, "Hey, pick it up!"
This guy looks me in the eye.
He goes, "Make me."
-Oh!
-Oh, boy!
So then what happened?
-I'll tell you what happened.
He kicked my ass.
And then he made me
pick up the cigarette.
I did.
I picked it up with my mouth.
-Yeah. Everybody thinks they're
a tough guy these days.
-Yeah.
I had a run-in myself recently.
-Oh, yeah?
-I see this tough guy
at the grocery store.
He's yelling
at the checkout girl.
I go, "Hey, jackass, your mother
ever teach you manners?
'Cause if not, I'm gonna teach
you some right now."
-Oh, boy!
Oho!
-So what did he say to that?
-Nothing.
He just kicked my ass.
Right away.
He wheeled his chair over to me
and laid me out flat.
-Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
He was in a wheelchair?
-Yeah, the guy
was like 100 years old.
Of course he was.
-Yeah, of course.
-Anyway, he's rolling away,
and I go, "That all you got?"
-There we go. There we go.
-Oh, man.
-Big mistake on my part.
-Oh.
-He came right back, took his
little oxygen tube off his face.
He stuck it right up my ass.
And he cranked it to full.
This guy -- he blows me up
like I'm a friggin' balloon.
-Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
That's a unique punishment.
-It sure was.
-Man, that's what I'm saying,
you know?
Everybody's got to be
a tough guy these days.
-Hey, tell me about it.
I'm at church a few weeks back.
I turn to the guy behind me,
and I say, "Peace be with you."
He kicks my ass.
- What?
-I say, "Father, how dare you?"
-Oh, my God!
-"You're ruining
my daughter's wedding."
-Oh. It was --
It was the priest?
-Yes!
You know the phrase,
"He put his foot in my ass"?
-Oh, he didn't do that, did he?
-No, no, no.
He put my foot in my ass.
Both of them.
-Oh, my God.
Not your feets.
That's terrible.
But other than that,
it was a beautiful ceremony.
-It was a beautiful ceremony.
-I will say that.
-It was beautiful. Cheers.
-I'll tell you, even the kids
think they're tough guys now.
The other day, I asked my son
what he wants for breakfast,
right?
So he kicks my ass.
-Unbelievable.
-I look at my wife. I go,
"What's wrong with this kid?"
And she kicks my ass.
-That's insane.
-Some of the tough guys
are girls.
-Absolutely, absolutely.
-You know, life used to be
a little more civilized.
A few years back, I had words
with this tough guy,
but we didn't fight.
Instead, he picked up
a dirty quarter off the ground,
and he said I had to
keep it in my mouth forever.
And if he ever saw me, he was
going to yell, "Quarter check!"
And if it weren't in there,
he was going to kick my ass.
-Oh. That's tough.
-Those days are long gone, man.
Listen to this.
Christmas Eve, right?
I'm at a bar and I go,
"Hey, everybody,
this next round is on me,"
right?
And this tough guy goes,
"I don't need no charity,
you a-hole."
-And then he kicked your ass?
-I wish.
He captured me.
-What do you mean
he captured you?
-He captured me. I-I don't know
how else to say it.
That guy captured me.
He puts me in a dog cage
in his basement.
Right?
He's giving me a gummy bear
every eight hours.
Every eight hours,
I get one gummy bear --
a yellow one, too,
not even a red one --
a yellow gummy bear, right?
And at first, I'm pissed off.
But a few weeks go by,
and I realize -- I go --
I'm actually excited to see him,
you know?
When he comes home,
I'm pumped up
because he's finally going to
give me my little gummy bear.
-I'm waiting for my gummy bear.
You know, I want it bad.
And he's training me
is what he's doing.
I'm like his dog, you know?
And -- And he even -- one day,
he leaves the cage unlocked.
But I don't run away.
-Oh, 'cause you're a good boy.
-Exactly.
-I'm a good boy now, you know?
I'm learning tricks.
I'm not having accidents
no more.
I'm peeing
where I'm supposed to go.
I'm doing what I got to do,
you know?
And sometimes,
I think about leaving, you know,
but then I say to myself,
"Don't be a moron.
If you leave, you're not gonna
get your gummy bear."
-That's right. That's right.
-And besides, by now,
I'm dedicated to this guy.
You know what I mean?
I love him.
He's my whole world.
I tell him -- I go to him --
I go, "I belong to you.
I'm your creature now.
I would die for you."
-So then what happened?
-Well, then he kicked my ass.
-Okay.
-He waited until I loved him,
and then he kicked my ass.
I'm like, "What in the hell's
going on with you?"
-Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Watch out.
Tough guy, 3 o'clock.
-Oh, no.
-Hey, quarter check!
-Oh!
Uh, it's right here, boss.
It's still in there.
-Good.
-Yeah, everybody's a tough guy
these days.
-Ain't that the truth?
-I think
we should take some classes.
-Ever wish you knew
how your cat was feeling?
-Yes!
-Every dang day.
-Well, now you can.
-How?
-With Tidy Care Kitty Litter!
-Tidy Care Kitty Litter...
...provides
color changing crystals
for your cat's
health monitoring.
With new Tidy Care technology,
our kitty litter crystals
turn orange
at the first sign
of a health issue
and green when your little
fur baby is healthy as can be.
-That's incredible.
-Thanks, Tidy Care.
-Oh. What does blue mean?
-Don't, uh --
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
-Great.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi.
-It's blue again.
-It is?
-Yeah.
Well, is the guy still here?
-Oh, I don't --
-I'm here.
-Oh, hi.
-Uh, what does blue mean?
-You don't want to know.
-Yes, we do.
-No, we really do.
-Okay, but, uh...
Okay.
Our color changing crystals
change
to a bright aquamarine blue
at the first sign
of human urine.
-What?
-The litter turns blue
when people pee on it.
-But why?
-I don't know.
It just -- It just does.
-So that means
someone in this house...
-Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
-You don't think our son --
-No.
-I do.
-Jesus Christ!
-Why are you still here?
-Come on, don't you want to
know who made it blue?
-It's the cat.
-Brother, blue ain't no cat.
-Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
-Night!
-Good night.
-Well, we all know
where he's going --
- Stop!
-Dammit.
-There goes your cat theory,
dumbass.
-Danny! Danny, get in here!
-Yeah, Dad?
-Are you peeing
in the litter box?
-W-What?
-Are you peeing
in the litter box?
-No!
-Don't lie to me!
-I'm not!
I hate you!
I hate this house!
-That's a weird kid.
-Why would you ask him
something like that, Dennis?
He's 16!
-The crystals were blue, Meghan.
They were blue.
-Do you hear yourself
right now?!
It was the cat!
-She's just as dumb as the son.
-Would you stay out of this?
-He doesn't do anything wrong.
He's a good kid.
I mean, he plays cello,
for Christ's sake.
-And pees in the litter box.
-Shut up!
-Well, then you tell me
what's going on, Meghan.
'Cause it sure as hell
wasn't me.
And if it wasn't him, then...
...you.
- Dennis!
-Oh, my God, it was you.
-How? How?!
I am a woman!
I would have to squat so low!
-It all makes sense.
I haven't seen you pee for days.
-You've never seen me pee.
-Exactly.
-You're nuts!
-I'm nuts?! I'm nuts?!
Then what's this, huh?!
This entire litter box is blue!
You made the whole thing blue!
-It was the cat!
-Blue ain't no cat!
-Hey, guys.
-What?!
-Is that your dog?
-Yeah.
-My bad.
Blue can also mean dog.
-Oh, come on.
-Why wouldn't you say that?
-Tidy Care Kitty Litter.
It's usually the son.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Noah Kahan.
The Great Divide
-♪ I can't recall the last time
that we talked ♪
♪ About anything
but lookin' out for cops ♪
♪ We got cigarette burns
on the same side of our hands ♪
♪ But we ain't friends ♪
♪ We're just morons
who
broke skin in the same spot ♪
♪ You know
I think about you all the time ♪
♪ And my deep misunderstanding
of your life ♪
♪ And how bad it must have
been for you back then ♪
♪ And how hard it was
to keep it all inside ♪
♪ I hope you settle down ♪
♪ I hope you marry rich ♪
♪ I hope you're scared
of only ordinariness ♪
♪ Like murderers and ghosts
and cancer on your skin ♪
♪ And not your soul
and what he might do with it ♪
♪ You inched yourself
across the great divide ♪
♪ We drove aimlessly
along the Twin State line ♪
♪ I heard nothin' but the bass ♪
♪ In every ballad
that you'd play ♪
♪ While you swore to God
the singer read your mind ♪
♪ But the world is scared
of hesitatin' things ♪
♪ Yeah, they only shoot
the birds who cannot sing ♪
♪ And I'm finally aware
of how petty and unfair ♪
♪ It was to stare ahead
like everything was fine ♪
♪ You know I think about you
all the time ♪
-♪ And my deep misunderstanding
of your life ♪
♪ And how bad it must have
been for you back then ♪
♪ And how hard it was
to keep it all inside ♪
♪ I hope you settle down ♪
♪ I hope you marry rich ♪
-♪ I hope you're scared
of only ordinariness ♪
♪ Like murderers and ghosts
and cancer on your skin ♪
♪ And not your soul and
what he might do with it ♪
♪ Rage, in small ways ♪
♪ Did you wish
that I could know ♪
♪ You'd fade... ♪
♪ ...to some place ♪
♪ I wasn't brave enough to go? ♪
♪ I hope you settle down ♪
♪ I hope you marry rich ♪
♪ I hope you're scared
of only ordinariness ♪
♪ Like murderers and ghosts
and cancer on your skin ♪
♪ And not your soul
and what he might do with it ♪
-♪ I hope you threw a brick
right into that stained glass ♪
♪ I hope you're with someone
who isn't scared to ask ♪
♪ I hope that you're not
losing sleep about what's next ♪
♪ Or about your soul
and what he might do with it ♪
-It's "Weekend Update"
with Colin Jost and Michael Che.
-Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone.
-Welcome to "Weekend Update."
I'm Michael Che.
-I'm Colin Jost.
Well, this week
Secretary of State Marco R--
-Rubio!
-Marco Rubio traveled to Italy
to meet with Pope Leo
in an attempt to repair the U.S.
relationship with the Vatican
after the Pope requested
anyone but J.D. Vance.
During their meeting,
Marco...
-Rubio!
-...also presented the Pope with
a gift of an egg-shaped crystal,
which he bought on his
favorite religious website,
AdamAndEve.com.
-The Pentagon on Friday
released never-before-seen files
on UFOs,
but don't worry.
The most dangerous
flying objects have
already been eliminated.
Spirit
The Supreme Court temporarily
restored mail-order access
to abortion pills,
citing prom season.
-World health authorities
are tracking down
dozens of passengers
who left a cruise ship
where there was
a deadly outbreak of hantavirus,
which is typically caused
by exposure to rodent droppings.
Damn it.
That better not be you, Mickey.
-That's dumb.
-It's dumb.
Officials around the world
are tracking passengers
potentially infected
with the virus,
which sounds scary,
but let the president calm
your fears.
-Briefed
-Have
Under
-Oh, my God,
that's...that's such great news.
But why?
Why does that sound familiar?
-Are there worries
about a pandemic at this point?
-No, we're not at all.
And we have it
totally under control.
It's one person coming in
from China,
and we have it under control.
It's going to be just fine.
-And it was.
So...
-It didn't need the thumbs.
President Trump dismissed
weapons fire between the U.S.
and Iran as a "love tap."
He also called gas prices
"gentle sodomy."
FBI Director Kash P--
-Patel!
-Well-played.
FBI Director Kash Patel has
reportedly been
giving out
bottles
of his personalized whiskey
to FBI staff.
Kash Patel Whiskey --
so strong you won't be able
to see straight.
-Jeffrey...
-Even I have limits.
-Jeffrey Epstein's alleged
suicide note was released
and contains the phrase
"What you want me to do?
Bust out crying?"
Which is apparently
referencing a line
from a "Little Rascals" movie,
and I think this note is real
because Little Rascals were
Epstein's type.
-Health Secretary
RFK Jr. posted a picture
of himself holding a bird
he caught at Dulles Airport
and then a second picture
of himself burping feathers.
-The FDA has authorized its
first fruit-flavored e-cigarette
intended for adults.
Okay, but if it's for adults,
then why is this the commercial?
-This week, President Trump
met at the White House
with the president of Brazil,
a parrot with a BBL.
I really wanted that one
to work.
Kamala Harris
has reportedly told donors
that she wants the DNC
to release its autopsy
of what went wrong
in the 2024 campaign.
Autopsy? Come on. He's not dead.
Parrot
-The Met Gala took place
in New York this week.
Here to give his thoughts
on fashion's biggest night
is conservative political
commentator Tucker Carlson.
-Thank you, Colin.
The Met Gala, a night
of fashion and fun -- huh!
Really? Yes.
Come on, everybody.
Let's all prance around
in our $100,000 clown outfits
and watch
the American empire crumble.
What are we doing?
What's going on?
-So, you didn't like
this year's Met Gala?
-Oh, no, I loved it
because when I go to a museum,
I don't want to talk
about history.
No, I want to look at the Rock
in a skirt.
Do you smell what
the Rock is cooking?
'Cause I do.
It's gender confusion.
That's the rule.
That's the goal now.
-I don't think that's the goal.
I think it's just,
like, meant to be fun.
-Okay, well,
what about Madonna?
She named herself
after the Virgin Mary.
And you want to know
my favorite thing
about the mother
of Jesus Christ?
Oh, I know.
The big pirate ship on her head.
And I have to be attracted
to this?
-You don't have to
be attracted to any of it.
I mean, weren't there
any outfits you liked?
I mean, Heidi Klum's was fun,
right?
-Oh, yes.
The left has finally gotten
what they've always wanted.
They put the Statue of Liberty
in a burka.
-You know
that's not what she was doing.
-Oh, what's next?
Does the Chrysler Building
become the Anti-Chrysler
building?
What are we doing?
What's going on?
Is this the New York
we want to live in, Colin?
-Don't you live in, like, Maine?
-Yes.
And let's talk about Maine.
M-a-i-n...e?
Huh! Really?
The "e" is silent.
But who silenced it and why?
-What the hell are
you talking about?
You're talking about
the silent "e" in Maine now?
-I'm glad you brought it up,
Colin.
-I didn't.
-And what does that "e"
stand for?
Oh, I know. "Euphoria."
-No.
-Oh, yes. "Euphoria."
And no, I'm not talking
about the feeling I get
when I press one for English.
-Come on, man.
-Oh, and look who's next
coming down the runway.
It's Jaafar Jackson,
who had the gall to show up
after starring
in the Michael Jackson movie.
-Oh, yeah, some people were very
upset about that movie, yeah.
-And they should be.
The movie ends in 1988,
so obviously they avoided
something serious
that needs to be acknowledged,
the part
of Michael Jackson's life
no one wants to talk about
anymore.
Of course I'm talking about the
part when he was a white man.
-Okay.
-No! Sorry, kids.
Michael Jackson
doesn't get to live
a beautiful white life anymore.
Huh!
Who does that remind me of?
Oh, that's right...all of us.
That's the rule.
That's the goal now.
"Shamona"?
Yeah, more like "shame on ya."
-Oh, Jesus, dude,
that's just awful.
-And now, a word
from our sponsor.
Round bananas.
You want to eat bananas
without looking gay?
Try round bananas.
-No, you can't do
ad reads on the show.
-Now, let's talk about
A$AP Rocky's outfit.
He was on the red carpet wearing
my least-favorite color...
African-American.
-No!
Tucker Carlson, everyone.
Tucker Carlson.
-Shame on ya.
What are we doing?
-Tina Charles
Tina Charles, the WNBA's
all-time-leading rebounder,
announced that she is retiring.
Charles credits
her rebounding success
to WNBA players missing a lot.
This week was
Teacher Appreciation Week,
so thank you...
Teacher Appreciation Week.
So, thank you to the greatest
teacher of all time...
Dad's belt.
Want to take back
the applause?
-Kyle Rittenhouse,
who opened fire
at a 2020 civil rights' rally,
was being treated after being
bitten by a venomous spider
and posted this picture
from the hospital.
And you can see where the
spider bite left two fat lumps.
-A woman in Florida
was arrested
after she allegedly kicked a boy
at a youth football game.
But on the bright side,
it's good!
-It's so dumb.
-This week, military officials
would not officially confirm
or deny reports
of the U.S.
using kamikaze dolphins
with mines
strapped to their bodies
against Iranian battleships.
Here to end the debate
are two kamikaze dolphins.
-We're ready
to die for your country,
and that's all you got for us?!
-On your feet!
On your feet, New York!
-Yeah. All right, all right.
-On your feet!
-Okay.
I got to say, I'm shocked
you guys are real.
How do you even become
a kamikaze dolphin?
-Oh, dude, the same way
everybody goes to Army.
Recruiter came by our reef, and
he said he had an opportunity.
And, frankly, Colin, I had hit
reef bottom at this point,
and my life had no "porpoise."
-Wow.
So, you guys...
you guys are cool
just like swimming into a boat
and blowing yourselves up?
-Yeah, man!
I mean, there's not a lot
of options for dolphins, Colin.
I mean, what,
we go to Sea World?
I'd rather die
than live in Orlando, man.
Plus, if a dolphin dies
an honorable death,
in heaven, you're rewarded
with 72...sturgeons.
-Oh, you loved "porpoise"?!
You went crazy for "porpoise"!
-It's a good pun.
"Sturgeons"
instead of "virgins."
-Look at my tail, Colin, huh?
-Look at mine.
Look at our tails.
Look at what we can do.
Do you see what we do?
-What are you doing while
you're waiting to be deployed?
Can I ask?
-What else, man?
Having sex as much as possible.
-Right.
-Regular dolphins are
already mad-horny.
But dolphins who know
they're gonna die soon?
Oh, yeah, we're a problem.
-Yeah, dude.
I got a deep-ocean kink.
You know what I'm saying, Colin?
I've been swimming
down to the dark zone,
smashing some freaky fuglies.
Anglerfish with a light on it?
Blew its back out last night!
-Oh, no.
-You know that light?
Che, you'll love this.
I put that light on its head
in my mouth.
-And I watched.
I watched it.
Yeah, but me personally,
I like a thick bitch.
I swam my ass up to a big,
ol' honey the other day.
-Let's just say I turned that
blue whale into a sperm whale.
-Let's switch gears.
How do you know which boat
to even swim into?
Can I ask?
-We don't.
We're dolphins, man.
-We have no idea.
-We're just swimming
with this stuff, man.
But if you have fish,
we work for you.
That's kind of how it is.
-So, if I have fish,
you'll work for me?
-Yeah.
-Yep.
-And you guys can sink
any type of boat?
Like, let's say a ferry
that's a huge...
a huge
financial drain on its owner.
-Yep! Yep!
-If you got fish, we'll do it.
-Well, then, fellas,
I think I've got a job for you.
-Yeah, fish. Fish!
-Oh! Oh!
-Kamikaze dolphins, everyone.
-Get the hell out of here.
Get the hell out of here!
Doris Fisher,
the co-founder of The Gap,
has died at the age of 94.
She is survived by her Gap Kids.
-A group of middle-school
students in Mississippi
kept their bus from crashing
after the driver passed out
behind the wheel.
The town says the kids are
heroes who acted quickly,
while the bus driver says,
"The kids robbed me of the death
I have long begged for."
-A DoorDash driver in New York
has been indicted on charges
that she recorded a passed-out,
naked customer
and posted it on TikTok.
And even worse, she
didn't even get my good side.
It's not a very good side.
-Police in New Jersey
are investigating a construction
site
after a porta-potty
mysteriously exploded,
though in New Jersey,
that's just the sound
of an angel getting its wings.
-That's beautiful.
-A recent study found
that people
who are chronically late
are more likely
to be viewed by their peers
as unpleasant.
Here to comment on this
is Jane Wickline.
-Hi.
Hello. And I'm so sorry again
about being late today.
-Oh, yeah.
You know, just don't take this
the wrong way.
I just don't understand
how you can be late for a job
that starts at 11:30 p.m.
-Right. Yeah, I know.
I have a really hard time
being on time places,
but I know the effects
my lateness has on others,
so I really --
I want to make things right.
-I think that's good of you,
Jane.
-This song is dedicated
to everyone I've ever made
wait for me.
And it comes from the bottom
of my heart.
♪ Everyone's asking my ETA ♪
♪ Everyone has to get off
my ass ♪
♪ No one needs to know
if I'm on my way ♪
♪ Calm the "f" down
and focus on you ♪
♪ I am late ♪
♪ What are you gonna do? ♪
♪ Nothing ♪
♪ I thought so ♪
♪ I am late,
and I'm not gonna text you ♪
♪ I'm not even rushing ♪
♪ Maybe I'll walk ♪
-I thought
you wanted to make things right.
-Oh, I am.
♪ Someone texted the chat ♪
♪ They're running
three minutes behind ♪
♪ It must be a holiday
where we say useless stuff ♪
♪ Dan says this theater
doesn't have previews ♪
♪ Take a Klonopin, Dan ♪
♪ You're stressing me out ♪
♪ You want to know
if I'm on my way ♪
♪ Guess what, bitch? ♪
♪ I'm gonna show up 40 minutes
late with an ice-cream cone ♪
♪ Forty minutes late
with an ice-cream cone ♪
♪ I'll look you straight
in the eye ♪
♪ Say the trains were slow ♪
♪ With ice cream dripping
all down my hand ♪
♪ Forty minutes late,
with an ice-cream cone ♪
-It seems like you're not
respecting other people's time.
-Well,
it's more complicated than that.
♪ It's not
that I don't respect your time ♪
♪ It's just that
looking at my phone ♪
♪ Matters more
than our friendship ♪
♪ People should build
their schedules around me ♪
♪ And generally treat me
like I am God ♪
Introducing our lovely backup
dancers, Lola and Rebecca!
Yeah, give it up for them.
-Sorry. Where are they?
-Um, they're late,
as is their right.
♪ If I were early,
then I would have to wait ♪
♪ And I would rather it be you ♪
♪ So, I'm going to show up
40 minutes late ♪
♪ With an ice-cream cone ♪
♪ I'm 40 minutes late,
and I'm on my phone ♪
♪ Forty minutes late ♪
♪ Six melting scoops ♪
♪ I tried, like,
a hundred samples ♪
♪ Forty minutes late ♪
♪ And I picked vanilla ♪
♪ There was a huge line,
and I paid with a check ♪
♪ I was born late,
and I will die never ♪
♪ I will get there
when I get there ♪
♪ If I get there ♪
♪ I am late,
and that won't kill you ♪
♪ You can all go to hell ♪
♪ You can go to hell ♪
♪ I'm late ♪
-Jane Wickline, everyone.
- Thank you.
-Oh, the dancers are here.
-They're here now?
For "Weekend Update,"
I'm Colin Jost.
-I'm Michael Che. Good night.
You had one duty!
-So, again,
those are some of the key
elements of the Roaring '20s.
And Mr. Connelly
will go into greater detail
when he's feeling better
and he's back in class,
hopefully tomorrow.
Any questions?
Okay.
Well, we're almost out of time.
Um, just before I go,
I just want to say
that it has been an honor
and a privilege
to be your substitute teacher
these past few days,
and you've all been so attentive
and respectful,
and that's not always the case,
I can tell you.
Um, so since you've
been so well-behaved,
I just have a little treat.
Um...I thought maybe
for the last few minutes,
uh, I'd give everyone a chance
just to kind of let loose,
uh, get out of your seats and,
you know, dance a little bit.
All right?
All right, here we go.
Let's do it, guys.
Here we go. That's it.
We're just gonna let loose.
Just come on up and dance.
Here we go.
We don't get to do
this every day. I know.
Come on. Here we go.
We're gonna get the wiggles out,
you know?
Let's just get into our bodies
a little bit,
and we're gonna kind of
feel that.
It just feels,
feels good to be in your body.
David, I see you.
You're ready to let loose.
Come on up.
Come on, buddy. Don't be afraid
to dance with your teacher.
It's okay. Come on, David.
Come on.
We can get up here.
Wait. Isabel, wait! Isabel!
Hang on, hang on.
Izzie?
I know. Look. I know you're shy.
You're shy. Okay.
But on the dance floor,
I have a feeling you're going
to be like Shakira.
Come on.
Let's do some of that.
Hey, Sammy.
Sammy, we all know
you can dance.
Come on, Sammy. Come on up here.
Show us what you got.
Wait, wait.
I see Franklin's about --
he's about ready
to jump in here.
Franklin? Come on.
Come take over my spot.
You want to take my territory?
Let's go. Move over, Teach.
You know, let's see.
Wait. Franklin's feeling it.
Come on.
Wait, wait. Jesse! Hold on. Wait.
Is Jesse gonna...
Jesse's gonna beat Franklin
up here?
Uh-oh.
We got a battle coming, guys!
Girl, get up here!
Come on, girl.
Don't play me, girl.
Come on. Let's...
Come on, let's -- wait.
Daphne knows what I'm
talking about. Right, Daphne?
Daphne's about to break out some
of those bat mitzvah moves.
Right, Daphne? Come on.
We vibing now.
And Amber. Uh-oh!
I see Amber about
to make a move.
Oh! Look out!
It's an Amber alert.
It's an Amber alert, y'all!
Go, Amber! Go, Amber.
Go, Amber!
Whoo! We are feeling it now.
Rick's feeling it, too.
Rick. Right, Rick?
Come on. Let's go.
Rick and Franklin
are about to tag-team up here.
Oh, here we go.
Now it's about to kick off.
Franklin, Rick. Franklin, Rick.
Franklin, Rick.
Come on. Uh-oh!
I'm about to catch a taxi.
I'm on a fishing expedition.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, let's pull her in.
Let's pull her in.
Wait.
She's putting up a fight,
but she's about to flop
on this dance floor.
Come on. Let's get
those wiggles out, Daphne.
Come on! Let's do it.
Come, let's shake your booty
with the substitute-y.
Come on.
Let's get some of that, right?
You can't touch this.
Can't touch this, right?
We know this one.
Can't touch this.
I'm bringing you back
to my days.
Come on. Everybody up.
Let's go! Everybody!
Everybody down.
Everybody up. Everybody down.
Everybody! Hi, champ!
Everybody down. Everybody up.
Everybody up!
Now scream!
All right, all right.
Well, that was fun.
That was, uh, a lot of fun.
Um, a lot of fun.
Really fun. Wow.
Really a lot of fun.
I might actually, uh, head out
a little before you guys,
um, maybe take the boom box and,
uh, just kind of get in my car,
maybe leave, um,
just before you guys, maybe.
Just head home,
stay home, you know,
maybe move,
maybe a different country.
Um, but yeah, it's all good.
Feeling good for the summer!
What?! Hard to complain
when it's almost summer!
So. Yeah. Yeah, that was fun.
That was really, really, really,
really, really, really fun.
Um...okay. Thanks.
-Did...did that happen?
-I prefer to pretend
that it didn't happen.
-Hey, guys. I can see him.
He's in the parking lot.
He's just kind of standing there
with his head against a tree.
-Hey, Rick, isn't that your dad?
-Yeah.
Yeah, that's, uh, that's my dad.
-Hey, I'm -- I'm sorry, bro.
These next few weeks gonna
be really, really bad for you.
-Yeah, they really are, huh?
-Once again, Noah Kahan.
Doors
-♪ I grew up pretending sticks
were little guns ♪
♪ I would point 'em
at my dad ♪
♪ And he'd get mad ♪
♪ 'Cause God forbid
I hurt someone ♪
♪ I'd hurt anyone I could ♪
♪ Anyone who got too close ♪
♪ Anyone who wouldn't look ♪
♪ I was born
into a 100-year storm ♪
♪ Foot of ice across Vermont ♪
♪ And in that dark
and in that frost ♪
♪ A heart was formed ♪
♪ Malcontented and unwarm ♪
♪ You were unsuspecting ♪
♪ Not unwarned ♪
♪ That I'm the trouble ahead ♪
♪ That I scream in my sleep ♪
♪ You're putting money on red ♪
♪ I'm a sure bet
at a losing streak ♪
♪ I keep showing you doors ♪
♪ But you can't open them up ♪
♪ 'Cause it gets harder
to see me ♪
♪ The closer you try to look ♪
♪ I just live here, babe ♪
♪ But you're the one
who decided to knock ♪
♪ You knocked ♪
♪ Have you ever stared
directly at the sun? ♪
♪ Have you ever shared
some closeness so exposed ♪
♪ To have it spit back
by someone? ♪
♪ So forgive me if I jump
at the rattle of your keys ♪
♪ Oh, are you leaving? ♪
♪ No, babe, I'm just waking up ♪
♪ And now what? ♪
♪ I'm left staring
at the ceiling ♪
♪ Listing reasons you should
pack all your things up ♪
♪ That I'm the trouble ahead ♪
♪ That I scream in my sleep ♪
♪ You're putting money on red ♪
♪ I'm a sure bet
at a losing streak ♪
♪ I keep showing you doors ♪
♪ But you can't open them up ♪
♪ 'Cause it gets harder
to see me ♪
♪ The closer you try to look ♪
♪ I just live here, babe ♪
♪ But you're the one
who decided to knock ♪
♪ You knocked ♪
"SNL"!
♪ I'll be gone so long
before the anger comes ♪
♪ I'll be only what you've
known of me till now ♪
♪ Oh, how I hope
you're moving on ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the trouble ahead ♪
♪ I still scream in my sleep ♪
♪ You're putting money on red ♪
♪ I'm a sure bet
at a losing streak ♪
♪ I keep showing you doors ♪
♪ But you can't open them up ♪
♪ 'Cause it gets harder
to see me ♪
♪ The closer you try to look ♪
♪ I just live here, babe ♪
♪ But you're the one ♪
New York!
Thank you!
-And now a scene from...
Of two
-I'm home, honey bunny,
honey bunny, honey bunny.
Can I get a smile?
Can I get a hi?
Can I get a hello, honey bunny?
Can I get a hug?
Honey bunny, honey bunny.
-Well, look who comes
crawling home late as sin.
Where have you been, been,
been, been, been, been,
been, been, been,
been, been, been, been, been?
I've been waiting here for two,
two, two, three, three, three.
Do I hear a four, four, four,
five, five, five, five,
for five, five hours.
You said you'd be home
by 8:00, 8:15, 8:30,
8:35 with traffic.
Now it's 11:45, 11:50.
Do I hear 11:55, 55, 55, 55, 55,
midnight?
Bold,
coming from the man
past his prime in a cowboy hat.
-I can explain, darling.
It was bumper to bumper
to bumper to bumper
to bumper to bumper.
I took I-10, I-10, I-10.
Can I get an I-10?
I took I-10 to I-20, I-20, I-20,
I-20, I-30, I-30, I-30.
I got off at exit 40
and went straight through
the Whataburger drive-through
and got a honey-butter chicken
biscuit and took my time.
-Meanwhile you got
a woman waiting for you at home!
Now, folks,
this is a fine woman.
This woman is lean
and mean and weaned.
She weighs not 80 pounds,
not 90, not 91, not 92.
Not 92 1/2...
-Higher!
-...not 92 3/4, not 92 7/8...
-...not 92 8/9...
-Higher!
-...not 92--
-Much higher.
Higher, higher, higher
every single day
since the day we were wed.
-How dare you?!
-Meanwhile, folks,
I can smell it.
I can smell it from here.
You've been drinking.
Was it one glass?
Two glass, three glasses,
four glasses?
Can I hear a bottle?
One bottle, two bottle,
three bottle, four bottle.
How many bottles?
-Oh, that's rich coming from you
when you reek of perfume!
And you got lip gloss
on your collar.
I know you're with them
sinful girls.
I know you're with Bella,
Bailey,
Bobbi, Bambi, Bertie,
Bulla, Buggy,
Betsy, Betty, Bonnie,
Brenda...
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
-...and Jewish Samantha!
-Maybe.
You were with Betty Botter,
and I bet you bought her butter.
-I would never buy her butter,
'cause I know your butter's
better.
-I know you like her butter
better
'cause I bet her butter's hot.
-Now, how can you blame me,
folks,
when how many times have
we had sex in the last year?
Was it 20 times?
20 times? Can I get at 20?
20.
Was it ten?
Was it ten? Was it ten?
Was it five? Was it four?
No, the winner is zero sex
in the last calendar year.
-Well, folks,
there's a reason for that,
reasons I will illuminate
presently.
I had a headache.
I had a backache.
I had a toothache.
I was cold.
I had a bad day.
I had a long night.
I had a big lunch.
I was tired.
I had a phone call
with my sister.
with my mother.
I had a fight on a phone call
with my sister and mother.
And I had a headache.
I had a migraine.
And most importantly, I'm old!
And, honey bunny, the thought
of your naked Whataburger body
literally disgusts me.
-I want a divorce!
-You do?
Well, maybe that'd be
for the best.
-Well, folks,
it has come to this.
It looks as if
this marriage is...
going once, going twice.
Last chance,
folks, and this marriage is --
-Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Mama! Mama! Mama! Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad!
-Do I hear you're getting
a divorce,
splitting up,
conscious uncoupling,
amicably parting?
Is it my fault?
-Is it my fault, my fault,
my fault, my fault, my fault?
-I blame all four of you.
I just said the quiet part
out loud.
But don't worry, boys.
We have a special offer today.
Who wants Daddy on weekends,
Daddy on weekends,
Daddy on weekends?
Can I get Daddy on weekends?
Nobody? Nobody?
Okay.
Who wants Daddy on Christmas?
Daddy on Christmas?
Anybody want?
-Yup!
-We got one taker.
Now, remember, folks.
This is Dad on Christmas.
We're talking dirt bikes, PS5s,
and pizza, pizza, pizza.
-Yup!
-So, the vibes would be worse
at Daddy's house,
but there will be more TV
and a lot more rules.
Less rules.
-All right. Yup.
I heard y'all yelling next door.
And I'd like to make
an offer on that little lady
who is no longer spoken for.
-Neighbor Frank bidding
on little, old me?
-Yes, ma'am.
I am a freak in the bedroom.
We can do it upside down,
on all fours,
from the front,
from the back, from the side,
doggy-style,
piggy-style, and country-fried.
-Oh, hearing you all
fancy my wife
has caused me to re-enter
the bidding.
Can I get a second chance?
Second chance, second chance,
second chance?
How about a third chance?
How about a fourth chance?
Can I get any kind of chance
at all,
because, to me,
you are priceless?
That's right, baby doll.
You are priceless.
-Sold to me, the happiest,
little lady on earth.
-Yup!
Kahan
Aziz
Cast and crew
Mothers
We love you.