>>> WELL, SENATOR, REPUBLICANS
FACE AN UPHILL BATTLE ON
TUESDAY.
I KNOW.
OBAMA WAS JUST IN GEORGIA
CAMPAIGNING FOR THE OTHER GUY.
DID YOU SEE IT?
IT WAS LIKE A COMEDY CENTRAL
ROAST UP THERE.
I FIGURE I COULD USE SOME
HELP.
SEND HIM IN.
HERSCHEL WALKER.
HEY, THERE.
MS. McDONALD.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
I WAS HAVING TOO MUCH FUN
IN
THAT FREE MERRY GO ROUND YOU
HAVE OUT FRONT.
THAT'S A REVOLVING DOOR.
- WELL, GREAT JOB ON YOUR
CAMPAIGN, HER SHELL.
- YES, EXCELLENT.
YOU REMEMBER JON CORNYN.
NO.
AND OF COURSE MARSHA
BLACKBURN, SENATOR FROM TENNESSEE.
OH, YOUR HEINESS.
WELL, THE MIDTERMS WASN'T THE
RED WAVE WE WERE HOPING FOR,
BUT
WE WERE HOPING YOU COULD WIN
THIS TUESDAY.
YEAH.
PRIORITY
YOU GOT THIS BIG PRIMARY COMING UP.
KNOW.
WELL, MY EX-WIFE SAID ALL I
DO IS RUN OFF.
NO, HERSCHEL, THE GEORGIA RUNOFF.
IT'S CLOSE.
- HOW CLOSE?
- SO CLOSE.
WARNOCK IS POLLING AT 59.4%.
YOU ARE POLLING AT 49.1.
WELL, THE FIRST PRIORITY IS
TO FIGURE OUT WHICH IS BIGGER.
WELL, THE ELECTION IS TUESDAY.
THEY HAVE ALREADY STARTED
COUNTING THE VOTES MY MAIL.
YOU GOT TO REMEMBER.
THEY STILL GOT TO COUNT THE
VOTES BY FEMALE.
SURE.
WE WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
BECAUSE
THIS RUNOFF IS REALLY IMPORTANT.
WE COULD REALLY USE THE WIN
RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
ASS
GUM
I'M ALL OUT OF BUBBLE GUM.
THREE DAYS
WE WANT TO BE REALLY CAREFUL,
AND YOU'VE HAD SOME SCHEDULES ALREADY.
IS THERE ANYTHING WE SHOULD KNOW
IN THE FINAL STRETCH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MAYBE BAD THINGS FROM YOUR
PAST THAT MAYBE PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW YET.
YES.
DEFINITELY.
SO MANY.
WELL, I HATE TO ASK, BUT CAN
YOU TELL US SOME OF THEM?
LET ME SEE.
WHERE DO I START.
SO THERE'S THIS PRETTY LADY THAT
WORKS AT THE McDONALD'S, RIGHT?
SO I WENT DOWN THERE--
ANYWAY,
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO KEEP IT
SO I
DROVE HER DOWN TO THE PLANNED
PARENT TRAP.
WOW.
THAT'S A LOT.
THIS MIGHT BE TOUGH.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M FEELING VERY CONFIDENT ABOUT
THIS ERECTION.
DON'T YOU MEAN ELECTION?
I DO NOT.
MAYBE IN THE FINAL PUSH,
LET'S LAY LOW AND FOCUS ON THE MESSAGE.
EXACTLY.
JUST LIKE KANYE.
NO, NO, NO.
ON THE ISSUES PEOPLE CARE ABOUT,
INFLATION, CRIME--
VAMPIRES, WEREWOLF,
SCARY GECKO
WE GOING
TO BE LOOKING INTO ALL THAT.
RIGHT. SO MAYBE NONE OF THAT.
REALLY?
BECAUSE THAT'S LIKE 90% OF MY
NEXT SPEECH.
RIGHT.
COULD WE HAVE A MOMENT ALONE?
OH, SURE.
YOU CAN TOSS A BLANKET RIGHT
OVER MEE, AND I'LL FALL ASLEEP.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
NIGHT NIGHT.
WELL DONE.
JUST TO BE CLEAR,
LAST HOPE TO WIN THIS YEAR IS HERSCHEL
WALKER?
YEAH.
SO PLAN B?
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
EXCUSE ME.
COME ON, GIRL.
DON'T TRADE THAT IN FOR NO BIG
MAC.
I'M SORRY.
- CAN I SHOW YOU SOMETHING VERY
EXCITING?
- OH, YEAH, SURE.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A LOOK IN
THERE.
OH, WOW.
LOOK IT'S A LITTLE ROOM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
USED TO BE MY PANIC ROOM.
NOW IT'S ALL YOURS, JUST UNTIL
ELECTION DAY.
WHY AM I ALREADY IN THERE?
THAT'S A MIRROR.
GO ON AHEAD.
YOU GOT EVERYTHING YOU NEED IN THERE.
GET IN THERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
THEY GOT LUNCHABLES IN THERE AND
EVERYTHING.
IT'S ONLY FOR A FEW DAYS,
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
IT'S "SATURDAY
NIGHT
KEKE PALMER.
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE IN NEW YORK.
IT'S CHRISTMAS TIME, THE TREE IS LIT,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, IT'S
SAGITTARIUS SEASON.
AND THAT'S GOOD FOR ME BECAUSE I'M
I'M VERY INTO ASTROLOGY.
AND I KNOW SOME ARE GOING TO SAY IT'S NOT REAL,
BUT TO THAT I
SAY, HOW'S THAT CRYPTO GOING.
THIS HAS BEEN AN AWESOME YEAR
FOR ME.
NOPE
I WAS NOMINATED FOR AN ACADEMY
AWARD!
THAT PART'S NOT TRUE.
BUT IT'S NOT LYING IF
THAT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS YOU
JUST LEARN TO DO IN THIS BUSINESS.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, HONEY.
I HAVE BEEN ACTING SINCE I WAS
NINE YEARS OLD.
THE FIRST ROLE I DID WAS IN A
MOVIE.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN,
EXCEPT FOR
WHEN I GOT YELLED AT BY LAWRENCE
FINCHBURG.
DRAMATIC
I STARTED LAUGHING AT HIM.
I HAD A GOOD REASON.
I'M A LITTLE KID WATCHING A
40-YEAR-OLD MAN CRY TO ME ABOUT
WINNING A NATIONAL SPELLING BEE.
HIST
BUT WHEN I STARTED LAUGHING,
HE WAS LIKE, YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
THIS IS NOT WHAT REAL ACTORS DO.
AND MY MAMA WENT OFF ON HIM,
Y'ALL.
SHE'S SO CHICAGO, SHE STARTED
SCREAMING
I DON'T CARE IF YOU
WAS IN THE MATRIX.
THIS IS GOOD TIMES.
AND I HONESTLY DO APPRECIATE
THAT HE DID.
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS INTENSE,
HE TAUGHT ME HOW TO BE A
PROFESSIONAL IN REAL TIME, YOU KNOW.
AND I'VE TAKEN LESSONS FROM
EVERYONE I'VE WORKED WITH.
I RECENTLY GOT SOME GOOD ADVICE
ON BEING ON SNL.
HE WAS LIKE, KEKE, GET UP ON
STAGE, YOU'RE FUNNY.
YOU'RE FUNNIER THAN ME.
HE DIDN'T EXACTLY SAY THAT,
BUT THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
DELUSIONAL QUEEN.
I'M ESPECIALLY GLAD TO BE HERE, THOUGH,
BECAUSE THERE'S SOME
RUMORS GOING AROUND.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN IN MY COMMENTS
SAYING KEKE'S HAVING A BABY, KEKE'S PREGNANT,
AND I WANT TO
SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
I AM!
I GOT TO SAY,
THOUGH, IT IS BAD WHEN PEOPLE ON
THE INTERNET SPREAD RUMORS ABOUT YOU,
BUT IT'S EVEN WORSE WHEN
THEY'RE CORRECT.
I WAS TRYING SO HARD TO KEEP IT
ON THE DOWN LOW
BECAUSE I GOT A
LOT OF STUFF GOING ON.
PEOPLE KEPT COMING UP TO ME, CONGRATULATIONS.
I'M LIKE, S HAD, H, CAN Y'ALL
STOP?
I GOT A LIQUOR SPONSORSHIP ON
THE LINE.
ONCE THE CHECK CLEARS, WE CAN
GET TO THE BAILEY BI.
BUT HONESTLY, THIS HAS BEEN THE
BIGGEST BLESSING.
I'M GOING TO BE A MOM.
EVEN THOUGH SOME PEOPLE FEEL A
LITTLE WEIRD ABOUT ME HAVING A BABY
BECAUSE I WAS A CHILD ACTOR.
I'M 29, I'M GROWN,
I HAVE SEX, A OWN A HOME,
I STORMED THE CAPITOL ON JANUARY 6th,
YOU KNOW, THINGS ADULTS DO.
Y'ALL KNOW I'M THE SAME PERSON
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN, AND I'M PROUD
OF THAT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, WHEN I
FIRST GOT INTO COMEDY
AND I
DREAMED OF STANDING ON THIS STAGE,
I ASKED MYSELF, KEKE, WHO
WILL YOU BE?
WILL YOU BE LIKE A MYA RUDOLPH, EDDIE MURPHY,
A CRYSTAL WIG
TYPE?
AND NOW THAT I'M HERE, I CAN
TELL YOU EXACTLY WHO I AM.
I'M KEKE PALMER.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW TONIGHT!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING THE SOAP CHANNEL.
WE NOW RETURN TO A CLASSIC 1984
EPISODE, FORCINGTON'S RIDGE.
>>> EVERYONE, I HOPE YOU'RE ALL
ENJOYING THE CHAMPAGNE.
IT'S MADE RIGHT HERE AT
FORCINGTON VINEYARDS, AND IF
YOU'RE LUCKY, I'LL GIVE YOU THE
RECIPE.
OH, ALEXIA, YOUR JOKES LIKE
YOUR BRAVE HAR DOS ALWAYS WORK.
SOMEONE'S TRYING TO BUTTER ME
UP BEFORE I JUDGE THE POLO HORSE
RACE CONTEST THIS AFTERNOON.
OH, I DON'T NEED LUCK.
MY HORSE IS HUGE, REALLY BIG.
IS IT NOW?
I GUESS IT'S MY JOB AS THE JUDGE
TO BE THE JUDGE OF THAT BIG HORSE.
NOW, PLEASE, EVERYONE MAKE YOUR
WAY TO THE GARDEN FOR SOME KAYNATES.
AM I SAWING THAT RIGHT?
LEAD THE WAY, MY DEAR.
NO, I THINK I'LL HANG BACK
FOR A MOMENT.
I NEED TO ADJUST MY BREASTS IN
THIS BIG MIRROR.
THEY'RE PERFECT.
HELLO, ALEXIA.
WELL, SANDRINE, YOU WAITED
FOR MY MIRROR SHOT.
WELL, WITH YOUR VANITY AND
WANDERING BREASTS, I KNEW JUST
WHERE TO FIND YOU.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU HAD AN INVITE.
MAYBE YOU FORGOT TO SEND IT
LIKE YOU DIDN'T FORGET NOT TO
FALACIATE MY HUSBAND EVERY DAY.
WELL, YOU SAID THAT WRONG,
BUT I DID DO IT, AND I'LL DO IT
EVERY DAY.
WELL, MY MOUTH IS EXIT ONLY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE IN MY
HOME?
OH, YOUR HOME?
YOU DIDN'T HEAR?
I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOUR SECRET
PROPOSAL, AND I FOUND SOME PLACE
TO GO TO WHEN I HAVE GUESTS OVER.
YOU BITCH.
TAKES ONE TO BE ONE.
YOU'RE GOING TO REGRET THAT!
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW I REALLY FEEL.
YOU ALMOST SMEARED MY LIPSTICK.
YES.
WHAT IS THAT SHADE CALLED
ANYWAY?
DESPERATE HAG?
WHEN I GET OVER THERE, I'M
GONNA--
LET ME DOWN!
WITH PLEASURE.
RIGHT OVER THERE.
OH, THAT ALMOST HURT.
HOW DELIGHTED WHEN YOUR FACE
HIT MY TABLE.
IT'S MY TABLE NOW.
REMEMBER?
SO I LOVED IT AS MUCH AS YOU'RE
GOING TO LOVE THE TASTE OF MY FISTS. OH.
OUCH.
ALEXIA, SANDRINE, MY GOD, I
CERTAINLY HOPE THIS VIOLENCE
ISN'T ABOUT WHO'S FALACIATING ME.
BY THE WAY, TIKTOK.
NO, DARLING, THIS IS ABOUT
SOMETHING MUCH, MUCH BIGGER. OKAY.
I FEEL LIKE THAT'S A DIG AT ME.
YOU TWO HAVE BEEN FRIENDS FOR 50 YEAR.
15.
YEAH, SURE.
BUT HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
THIS IS NO WAY FOR TWO FRIENDS
TO BEHAVE.
FRIENDS?
WE'RE NOT FRIENDS.
BUSINESS PARTNERS THEN?
BUSINESS PARTNERS.
WITH MY FINANCIAL ABILITIES
AND YOUR CHAMPAGNE RECIPE, WE
WOULD BE UNSTOP ZBLBL THAT MIGHT
BE THE BEST THING I'VE HEARD ALL DAY.
SHALL WE TALK THROUGH THE
DETAILS OVER LUNCH?
YES, WE SHOULD.
YOU COMING
WHEN I HAVE A RIDE, Y'ALL,
TEMPERATURES DROPPING.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
SEASON
IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR WE
FIND A MAN TO KEEP US WARM
THROUGH THESE COLD MONTHS.
BUT NOT JUST ANY MAN WILL DO.
WE OUT HERE LOOKING FOR SOME--
BIG BOYS.
SEASON
IT'S A REASON
TO GET A BIG BOY, I NEED A BIG BOY.
GIVE ME A BIG BOY ♪
SEASON
♪ IT'S ALL THE GIRLS ARE LEAVING
TO GET A BIG BOY ♪
♪ I NEED A BIG BOY
WANNA
WITH POLAR
BEAR ARMS,
KEEPS ME SNOW IN THE
WINTER SNOWSTORM ♪
WIND CHILL
♪ HE BRING IN MY GROCERIES IN
JUST ONE TRIP ♪
♪ WHEN THE SUN COMES BACK, I
NEED A BIG BOY HOTTY,
MAKES HIS
OWN HEAT WITH A BIG BOY BODY ♪
THREE
SIX PACK
♪ BIG BOY WITH A BIG OLD BACK,
A CALIFORNIA KING, REFRIGERATOR
STACKED ♪
STAKES
♪ BUTTER BACON, CHEESE, AND
LASAGNA IN THE TRAY ♪
NORMAL MAN
WITH NORMAL
SNACK
♪ AND I HOPE HE ASKS ME TO BE
HIS WINTER WIFE
BECAUSE MESSING
WITH A BIG BOY WILL CHANGE YOUR
LIFE ♪
♪ IT'S CUPPING SEASON
IT'S ALL
THE GIRLS NEED
A BIG BOY, I WANT A BIG BOY,
GIMME A BIG BOY ♪
♪ I NEED A BIG BOY BODY LIKE A BOUNCER,
BIG MOUTH BREATHER AND
LEGS LIKE A MONSTER ♪
♪ GET IN THE BED AND HE GOING TO
DO ME RIGHT,
HE SNORE ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ AND THEN HE STOPS ♪
BABE?
DID THIS MAN JUST DIE?
♪ ANYTHING I NEED, MY BIG BOY
GOT IT ♪
♪ IF I NEED A SNACK, HE GOT
SNICKERS IN HIS POCKET ♪
♪ BIG BOYHOODDY, YOU KNOW I'M
GOING TO ROCK IT ♪
♪ AND IF WE TRAVEL, YOU KNOW WE GOING
IN FIRST CLASS
BECAUSE HE
DON'T FIT IN THE BACK ♪
♪ HEY, BIG BOYS, GO BIG BOYS,
I LIKE THE BIG BOYS ♪
♪ WHAT ABOUT GIRLS?
I LIKE GIRLS, BUT THEY CAN'T
KEEP ME WARM.
WANNA SOMETIMES
LIKE THIS
WHOLE YEAR
TRASH
♪ ALL I DO IS WORK AND STRESS
AND I COULD USE A BIG BOY SO I
COULD JUST RELAX ♪
♪ HE CAN HAVE THEM LOVE HANDLES
IN THE FRONT AND IN THE BACK ♪
THREE
♪ IF WE TALKING GIRLS, I LIKE MY
WOMEN BIG ♪
NO MATTER
♪ IT'S CUPPING SEASON,
IT'S NOW WE GOT A REASON
TO GET A BIG BOY, I WANT A BIG BOY,
GIMME A BIG BOY.
WE OUT HERE LADIES.
WE THE REASON FOR THE SEASON.
THESE BEARS DON'T HIBERNATE IN
THE WINTER.
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND US.
WE'LL BE SHOVELING SNOW IN
SHORTS.
♪ BIG-BA-BIG BOYS ♪
HAVE YOU EVER DATED THE
RAPPER DRAKE?
HAVE YOU EVER MET DRAKE AT A
PARTY, TALKED ON INSTAGRAM?
OR EVEN MADE FLIRTY EYE
CONTACT WITH HIM AT A
RESTAURANT.
IF THE ANSWER IS YES, YOU ARE
NOT ALONE.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF US.
AND YOU MAY BE ENTITLED TO BENEFITS.
FOR TOO LONG, WE HAVE
WITNESSED AUBREY DRAKE GRAHAM
WRITE HIT AFTER HIT ABOUT WOMEN
WHO HAVE WRONGED HIM ONLY TO
EARN MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
WELL, TODAY, HER LOSS IS OUR
GAIN.
BECAUSE WE, THE THOUSANDS OF
DRAKE'S EXES AND SHAWTYS HAVE
VOTED TO JOIN FORCES.
AND OFFICIALLY UNIONIZE AS
THE UNITED TINGS OF AUBREY.
IT IS TIME WE STAND UP AND
FIGHT FOR OUR RIGHTS AS TINGS IN
A UNITED FRONT.
MY NAME IS COURTNEY.
I LEFT DRAKE A VOICE MAIL ONCE
ABOUT AN OVERDUE CAR PAYMENT,
AND NOW I'M AN INTERLUDE ON AN ALBUM.
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
I SERVED DRAKE SOME LETTUCE
WRAPS IN '09, AND APPARENTLY I'M
HIS EX NOW.
DRAKE HIM HIT ON ME DAVE AND
BUSTERS ONCE, I TOLD HIM I WAS A
LESBIAN, AND HE SAID ME TOO.
MY NAME IS KEKE PALMER, AND
THAT KEKE DO YOU LOVE ME SONG
RUINED MY LIFE.
EVERYONE WAS ASKING, ARE YOU
THAT KEKE?
YES, I'M THE KEKE, NOT THAT
KEKE.
DRAKE SENT ME A BOBBY HILL
GIFT ON INSTAGRAM ONCE.
I SAID, WHO IS THAT.
NEXT THING I KNOW, I'M THAT
GOOFY SHAWTY THAT CURVED HIM.
WE MAY HAVE STARTED FROM THE
BOTTOM, BUT WE STILL HERE.
TO BE CLEAR, A UNION
MEMBERSHIP IS NOT DEPENDENT ON
DATING DRAKE.
YOU MAY QUALIFY AS ONE OF
AUBREY'S TINGS IF YOU MET DRAKE
AT A BASKETBALL GAME, MET DRAKE
AT A CLUB, SAW DRAKE AT A CLUB,
BEEN TO A CLUB AT ALL.
HAVE DINED AT THE FOLLOWING
RESTAURANTS, RUTH'S CHRIS STEAK
HOUSE.
NOBU, NOBU, NOBU.
BUT HERE, AT UNITED TINGS OF
AUBREY, WE BELIEVE IN A BRIGHTER FUTURE.
ONE WHERE TINGS CAN BE LEFT
ALONE.
AND YOUR NAME STAYS OUT OF
DRAKE'S MOUTH.
♪ 525,600 TINGS ♪
♪ LIKE WOMEN WHO LIVE IN
MEMPHIS ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU'VE
MET HIM AT ALL ♪
♪ BECAUSE YOU ♪
UNITED TINGS OF AUBREY.
HERE AT NEW YORK CITY'S
FIRST-EVER HELLO KITTY STORE.
WHO'S EXCITED?
LET'S DO IT.
I LOVE HELLO KITTY.
ME TOO.
DREAM JOB ALERT.
NOW, AS EMPLOYEES, YOU HAVE
TO BE PREPARED TO ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS ABOUT SAN RIO'S
OFFICIAL HELLO KITTY STORY.
SO IF YOU OPEN UP TO PAGE
FIVE, YOU'LL SEE A LIST OF FACTS
ABOUT HELLO KITTY.
SHE LOVES TO BAKE COOKIES, SHE
LOVES TO GO TO SCHOOL, AND SHE'S
NOT A CAT, SHE'S A HUMAN LITTLE GIRL.
OH, INTERESTING.
I NEVER KNEW THAT. NO.
YEAH.
IT'S A FUN FACT, RIGHT?
ISN'T THIS A SWEET ONE.
HELLO KITTY'S FAVORITE FOOD IS
MAMA'S APPLE PIE.
WHY DID YOU SAY HELLO KITTY
IS A LITTLE GIRL?
BECAUSE ACCORDING TO THE
CREATORS, IT WAS A HUMAN LITTLE
GIRL.
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME IF YOU
HAD A BABY COMING OUT LOOKING
LIKE HELLO KITTY, YOU WOULD
THINK THAT WAS A REAL BABY?
I WOULD TELL THE DOCTOR TO
THROW IT AWAY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD MOVE ON.
HELLO KITTY IS IN THE THIRD
GRADE, AND FUN FACT, SHE LIVES
IN LONDON.
WICKED, ISN'T IT?
CHEERIO.
OH, GOOD.
SHE ALSO HAS A BOYFRIEND, DEAR
DANIEL, AND UNLIKE HELLO KITTY,
HE ACTUALLY IS A CAT.
SO THE GIRL IS A PERSON, BUT
THE ONE IN THE SUIT AND TIE IS A
CAT?
YEAH.
YES.
OKAY.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK FOR ME.
AND THEY'RE DATING, SO YOU'RE
TELLING US THESE ARE BARE BACKS?
WE DON'T TALK THAT WAY IN SAN
RIO.
I'M SORRY.
SH S THIS NOT CRAZY TO YOU GUYS?
I GUESS IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD,
BUT I DON'T CARE ABOUT THIS JOB.
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE AN INSANE
PLACE TO GET HIGH.
HELLO KITTY LOVES CANDY.
SHE WEIGHS FIVE DOLLS, THREE
APPLES.
SHE'S MEASURED IN APPLES?
SHE'S ALSO IN 3rd GRADE.
SHE WAS BORN IN 1974.
YOU'RE TELLING ME SHE'S A
48-YEAR-OLD THIRD GRADER WHO'S
FLAPPING CHEEKS WITH THE CAT NO
JIMMY?
NO.
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT CLAPPING
CHEEKS AT SAN RIO.
SHE LOVES MILK.
HER FAVORITE SHOES ARE SANDALS.
WHAT'S HER RACE?
WHAT?
WHAT'S HELLO KITTY'S RACE?
SHE DOESN'T HAVE ONE.
OH!
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO TOUCH THAT
ONE?
SHE HAS AN AGE, HEIGHT, PET, AND
RELATIONSHIP, BUT SHE'S
RACELESS?
IF SHE CAN BE ANYTHING, SAY
SHE'S BLACK.
I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME?
SAY THAT LITTLE WHITE GIRL IS BLACK.
NO, WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO
THAT.
DO YOU LIKE THIS?
CONFUSING US WITH YOUR LIES
ABOUT HELLO KITTY HAVING SEX AND
HOW BIG APPLES ARE?
BECAUSE WE ONLY RECOGNIZE ONE
BIG APPLE, NEW YORK, THE BEST
CITY IN THE WORLD, AND WE'RE NOT
GOING TO LET YOU RUIN IT.
WHO'S WITH US?
I AM.
I AM TOO.
BECAUSE I AM NEW YORK.
AND I AM NEW YORK.
AND IF YOU MESS WITH HELLO
KITTY, YOU MESS WITH NEW YORK.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, HELLO
KITTY?
YEAH.
JUST TELL US THE TRUTH, LADY.
NATASHA LEON, WHAT DO YOU
WANT?
THIS IS NEW YORK, SO SAY THAT
HELLO KITTY ISN'T A LITTLE HUMAN GIRL.
SAY SHE'S A CAT.
OKAY.
FINE.
SHE'S A CAT.
YEA!
YEAH!
NOW, COME ON, EVERYBODY.
I GOT US ALL TICKETS TO SEE THE
YANKEES ON BROADWAY AT MADISON
SQUARE GARDEN.
HELLO KITTY THE HUMAN?
FORGET ABOUT IT.
HOW
FAST
ONE WEEK AGO
OH, KENAN THOMPSON, THE
LEGEND, MAN.
KEKE, YOU HAVING FUN?
- YES.
I'M WORKING WITH MY IDOL.
- STOP IT.
NO, NO, I GREW UP WATCHING
YOU AS A KID.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO WORK WITH
YOU.
I ACTUALLY HAVE AN IDEA FOR A
PROJECT I WOULD LOVE TO TALK TO
YOU ABOUT LATER.
ANYTHING WITH KEKE PALMER,
I'M THERE, NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
REALLY?
BECAUSE I GOT THIS IDEA FOR A REBOOT
OF WHAT?
♪ SIT DOWN ON THE COUCH AND LOOK
ON THAT TELLY ♪
♪ KENAN AND KELLY
COOL
GON BREAK ALL
THE RULES ♪
KENAN AND KELLY
ASK
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE
A STREAMING THEORY.
I WOULD HAVE SAID YES TO KENAN
AND KEL, BUT NOW IT'S JUST KELLY.
SOLD BEFORE
I TOLD THE PRODUCERS WE WROTE
IT TOGETHER.
RIGBY NOW
HAS FAT SUSHI.
MAYBE TOO FRESH.
KELLY, I THINK THAT SALMON
YOU CAUGHT
MIGHT BE A PIRANNA.
here come the bus
KEL'S FAVORITE CATCH PHRASE
WAS UH-OH, HERE IT GOES.
BUS
NO BUS
YOU CAN'T KEEP TAKING ORANGE SODAS.
JUST PUT IT ON MY TAB.
I'M GOOD FOR IT.
OKAY.
$5,000 WORTH OF ORANGE SODAS, KELLY.
DON'T YELL AT ME BECAUSE
GUESS WHAT?
I'M PREGNANT WITH YOUR CHILD.
KEKE WAS GUNNING FOR AN EMMY
AWARD.
SO SHE WANTED TO BRING DRAMATIC
MOMENTS IN.
I THOUGHT, THAT WON'T WORK, AND
I WAS RIGHT.
KELLY, DID YOU FIX THE SLUSH
MACHINE?
YEP.
TRY IT OUT, KENAN.
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
I HAVE BEEN CRAVING ONE FOR
WEEKS NOW.
THAT'S ODD.
KELLY!
WHY WOULD YOU TELL ME IT IS
FIXED?
YOU ARE SUCH AN--
WHAT?
AN IDIOT?
GO AHEAD.
SAY IT.
IT AIN'T LIKE I HAVEN'T HEARD IT BEFORE.
MY MAMA USED TO GET DRUNK EVERY
DAY AND CALL ME AN IDIOT.
CHIRAQ
MY UNCLE TOLD HER TO BLAME ME
FOR MY DADDY LEAVING.
ME.
HOW YOU GOING TO BLAME A LITTLE
GIRL FOR THAT MAN BEING A
COWARD?
HOW?
UH-OH, HERE COMES THE BUS.
IT JUST STARTED, AND I THINK
WE HAVE A TONE ISSUE.
BUT PEOPLE SEEM EXCITED ABOUT
IT, I GUESS.
HEY, KENAN.
- HEY, DEVON, GOOD JOB ON THE
SONG, MAN.
THANK YOU.
I CAN DO OTHER STUFF TOO, THOUGH.
CHECK THIS OUT.
STUFF
THANK YOU.
I THINK WE ALREADY FOUND SOMEONE.
HEY, EVERYBODY!
KEL
OH, I MISSED YOU.
OH, MAN, I MISSED YOU TOO!
WHO LOVES ORANGE SODA?
KEL LOVES ORANGE SODA.
OH, SWEET BABY.
KEL, IT'S BEEN SO LONG, MAN.
WHAT YOU BEEN UP TO?
HANDS UP, EVERYBODY, THIS IS
A ROBBERY.
GIVE ME ALL THE MONEY IN THE REGISTER.
YOU NOT STEALING A DIME,
MR. ROBBER.
YOU BEEN WONDERING WHERE I BEEN.
I BEEN LEARNING THE ARTS OF
KARATE.
FOOL
KEL!
OH, DON'T DIE ON ME, KEL.
NO.
DON'T GO INTO THE LIGHT.
MY BABY NEEDS HIS FATHER.
YOU HEARD THAT RIGHT, KENAN.
KEL'S THE FATHER.
I SLEPT WITH HIM JUST TO HURT
YOU.
WHY DO I HURT THE ONES I LOVE
THE MOST?
BUS
HERE IT COMES.
NO!
THE SHOW IS NOT GOOD.
BUT JORDAN PEEL CALLED
AND WANTS
US TO DO A SEQUEL CALLED YEP.
YEP
THE AR BEE'S FIVE FOR TEN.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU GET FIVE
ARBY'S SANDWICHES FOR $5.
THAT'S FIVE STACKED SANDWICHES
FOR JUST TEN BUCKS.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY ABOUT
THAT?
I GUESS ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS
HOW?
YEAH.
THAT SEEMS LIKE A LOT OF ROAST
BEEF SANDWICHES FOR $10.
IT'S FIVE HEAPING PILES OF
TENDER ROAST BEEF FOR ONLY TEN
MEASLY DOLLARS.
CAN YOU EVEN BELIEVE IT?
HONESTLY, NO. YEAH.
WE'RE STRUGGLING TO UNDERSTAND
THE PHYSICS OF HOW THIS MUCH
ROAST BEEF IS $10.
BECAUSE ISN'T ONE ROAST BEEF
SANDWICH NORMALLY AT LEAST $5?
I BET YOU NEVER THOUGHT $10
COULD GET YOU FIVE MOUNTAINS OF
ROAST BEEF.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE
SAYING.
WE DON'T THINK IT'S POSSIBLE.
I JUST GOOGLED ROAST BEEF
PRICES AT THE GROCERY STORE, AND
IT SELLS FOR $11 A POUND, BUT
YOU'RE SAYING--
WE'RE GIVING YOU POUND AFTER
POUND OF ROAST BEEF FOR JUST
$10.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
I KNOW BREAD IS SUPER CHEAP, BUT
IT'S NOT NEGATIVE DOLLARS.
ARBY'S IS A FOR-PROFIT
BUSINESS, RIGHT?
LIKE YOUR GOAL IS TO MAKE MONEY.
I COULDN'T MAKE FIVE ROAST BEEF
SANDWICHES AT HOME FOR $10.
I GUESS WE'RE WONDERING, WHERE
ARE YOU GETTING ALL THIS ROAST
BEEF?
ARBY'S, WE HAVE THE MEATS!
NO, NO, NO.
THAT DON'T ANSWER HIS QUESTIONS.
WE KNOW YOU HAVE THE MEATS, BUT
WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THE MEATS.
ALSO, WHAT KIND OF MEATS.
OVER AT TACO BELL, DON'T MISS
THE NEW $5 BOX.
WAIT, WHAT?
YOU GET A CHILUPA SUPREME, A
BEEFY FIVE-LAYER BURRITO,
CINNAMON TWISTS, CHIPS, AND A
FOUR OUNCE SODA FOR ONLY $5.
IS THAT REAL?
LOOK IT UP.
IT'S THE $5 BOX ON AT TACO BELL.
OKAY.
I DON'T LIKE YOU CHANGED THE
SUBJECT TO TACO BELL.
NOW I'M WORRIED ABOUT THIS BOX TOO.
WELL, ARBY'S IS LOOKING--
YEAH, YOU GET MULTIPLE
BURRITOS AND CINNAMON STICKS AND
A GIANT SODA FOR $5?
HOW CAN THAT PHYSICALLY HAPPEN.
THAT MEANS EACH FULL BURRITO IS
LIKE 70 CENTS.
SO ARBY'S IS LOOKING PRETTY
GOOD BY COMPARISON, RIGHT?
NO.
THIS ALL SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
I THOUGHT THE FOUR FOR FOUR MENU
AT WENDY'S WAS INSANE.
WHAT'S THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOUNDS SUSPICIOUS.
YOU DO THE VOICEOVER IN THE
STORE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M PHYSICALLY PRESENT AT EVERY
ARBY'S LOCATION.
AND YOU THINK THE WENDY'S
DEAL SOUNDS SUSPICIOUS?
YOU'RE THE ONES OFFERING FIVE
GIANT--
TOWERS.-- OF ROAST BEEF FOR $10.
HOW MANY SANDWICHES DO YOU GET
FROM ONE COW?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
A MILLION.
WE WOULD HONESTLY RATHER PAY
MORE AND GET LESS ROAST BEEF SO
WE WOULDN'T BE WORRIED ABOUT
WHERE IT'S COMING FROM. OKAY.
SO HOW MUCH FOR HOW MUCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS TWO ROAST BEEF
SANDWICHES FOR $15.
I WOULD SAY THREE.
YOU'RE GOING TO EAT THREE
SANDWICHES?
YOU DO NOT SHAME ME!
NOT IN MY DEBUT ARBY'S
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, SZA.
♪
♪ KISS ME DANGEROUS ♪
♪ BEEN SO LOST WITHOUT
YOU ALL AROUND ME
GET ANXIOUS ♪
♪ LEAD ME
DON'T LOOK BACK
IT'S ALL ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW
FEELING LOST
BUT I LIKE IT ♪
♪ COMFORT IN MY SINS
IT'S ALL ABOUT
ALL I GOT RIGHT NOW
FEEL THE TASTE ♪
♪ OF RESENTMENT
SIMMER IN MY SKIN
IT'S ALL ABOUT
BLOOD STAIN ON MY SHIRT ♪
♪ NEW CHICK ON MY NERVES
OLD BUDDY GOT CURVED
GOING BACK ON MY WORD
DAMN CHICK ♪
♪ YOU SO THIRSTY
STILL DON'T KNOW MY WORTH
STILL STRESSING PERFECTION
LET YOU ALL IN MY MENTAL ♪
♪ GOT ME LOOKING TOO DESPERATE DAMN
YOU AIN'T DESERVE ♪
♪ BROAD DAY SUNSHINE
I'LL FIND A WAY TO ♪
♪ MESS IT UP STILL
CAN'T CRY ABOUT THE THING
THAT I CAN'T CHANGE
JUST MY MIND ♪
♪ GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE
TOUGH CROWD I HATE IT
CAN'T STAY
IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ FEELING LOST
BUT I LIKE IT
COMFORT IN MY SINS ♪
♪ IT'S ALL ABOUT
ALL I GOT RIGHT NOW
FEEL THE TASTE ♪
♪ OF RESENTMENT
SIMMER IN MY SKIN
IT'S ALL ABOUT ♪
♪ BLOOD STAIN ON MY SHIRT
NEW CHICK ON MY NERVES
OLD BUDDY GOT CURVED
GOING BACK ON MY WORD ♪
♪ DAMN CHICK YOU SO THIRSTY
STILL DON'T KNOW MY WORTH
STILL STRESSING PERFECTION
LET YOU ALL IN MY MENTAL ♪
♪ GOT ME LOOKING
TOO DESPERATE DAMN
IT'S WHAT YOU SAY ♪
♪ AND HOW YOU DO ME
HOW I'M 'POSED TO TRUST
BABY ♪
♪ 'POSED TO LOVE
IT AIN'T 'POSED
TO HURT THIS WAY ♪
♪ ALL I NEED
IS THE BEST OF YOU
HOW I GOT TO SAY IT ♪
♪ GIVE ME ALL OF YOU
IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW
FEELING LOST BUT I LIKE IT
COMFORT IN MY SINS ♪
♪ IT'S ALL ABOUT ME
ALL I GOT RIGHT NOW
FEEL THE TASTE
OF RESENTMENT ♪
♪ SIMMER IN MY SKIN
IT'S ALL ABOUT
BLOOD STAIN ON MY SHIRT ♪
♪ NEW CHICK ON MY NERVES
OLD BUDDY GOT CURVED
GOING BACK ON MY WORD
DAMN CHICK YOU SO THIRSTY ♪
♪ STILL DON'T KNOW MY WORTH
STILL STRESSING PERFECTION
LET YOU ALL IN MY MENTAL ♪
♪ GOT ME LOOKING TOO DESPERATE
DAMN YOU AIN'T DESERVE ♪
♪
WEEKEND
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, YOU GUYS ARE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS,
BUT ALEX JONES AND
KANYE WEST GOT TOGETHER THIS WEEK,
AND IT DIDN'T GO GREAT.
KANYE WEST MADE ANTI-SEMITIC
JOKES AND SAID, I LIKE HITLER,
WHICH IS ALSO THE PASS WORD HE
USED TO GET INTO MAR-A-LAGO.
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T THINK
KANYE IS OFF HIS MEDS SO MUCH AS
HE'S IMMUNE TO THEM.
WE'RE BASICALLY DEALING WITH THE
OMICRON VARIANT OF KANYE.
WE THOUGHT HE WOULD FADE AWAY,
BUT NOW WE REALIZE WE MAY HAVE
TO LIVE WITH THE BRAIN FOG OF
LONG HAUL KANYE.
STUFF
IF JEWS DO CONTROL THE MEDIA,
HOW ARE WE STILL SEEING A NEW
INTERVIEW WITH KANYE EVERY DAY.
ALSO IF THEY CONTROL THE MEDIA,
EXPLAIN THE 80 FOOT CHRISTMAS
TREE OUTSIDE OF NBC.
>>> PRESIDENT BIDEN SIGNED A MEASURE
THAT WOULD FORCE RAILWAY
WORKERS TO AVERT A STRIKE,
BUT
DOES NOT GET SICK LEAVE.
HOW DO YOU EXPECT BIDEN TO CARE
ABOUT SICK LEAVE
WHEN HE SHOWS
UP TO WORK EVERY DAY WITH FULL
BLOWN CTE.
ACT
IT SOLIDIFIES MARRIAGE
PROTECTION FOR INTERRACIAL
MARRIAGES.
BUT IF I MARRY A WHITE LADY,
WHO'S GOING TO PROTECT ME FROM
MY MOTHER?
THE GEORGIA SENATE RUNOFF SET
RECORDS FOR EARLY VOTING.
HERSCHEL WALKER HAS ALWAYS
ENCOURAGED HIS SUPPORTERS TO
TAKE CARE OF VOTING EARLY
BEFORE
IT BECOMES A PROBLEM.
OH, MAN.
PRESIDENT BIDEN HAS RECOMMENDED
THAT SOUTH CAROLINA
BECOME THE
FIRST STATE TO VOTE IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARIES
TO GIVE
BLACK VOTERS MORE OF A VOICE IN
SELECTING THE 2024 CANDIDATE.
NOT TO BE OUTDONE, DONALD TRUMP
ALSO PLANS TO GIVE VOTERS A VOICE
WITH THIS BLACK PUPPET.
THERE IS GROWING SUPPORT TO
MOVE THE FIRST DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARY FROM IOWA SO SOUTH CAROLINA,
BUT WHY MOVE IT TO
ANOTHER BORING STATE?
START THE PRIMARIES WITH A BANG
IN FLORIDA.
RIGHT?
INSTEAD OF WATCHING A POLITICIAN
EAT A CORN DOG AT THE IOWA STATE FAIR,
IMAGINE SMOKING METH,
SHIRTLESS AT GATOR LAND
AS HE BATTLES FOR THE STATE'S KEY
DEMOGRAPHIC, GRANDMAS UNDER 30.
RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
FLORIDA MAY NOT GIVE US FDR OR JFK,
BUT IT WILL DEFINITELY GIVE
US HPV.
A FEDERAL JURY HAS FOUND THE
OATH KEEPERS LEADER
GUILTY OF
SEDITIOUS CONSPIRACY.
HE PLANS TO APPEAL THE VERDICT
BECAUSE HE FEELS THAT THE TRIAL
LIKE HIS VISION
WAS VERY
ONE-SIDED.
QUESTIONS ARE BEING RAISED
ABOUT VLADIMIR PUTIN'S HEALTH
AFTER HE FELL DOWN THE STAIRS AT
HIS HOME AND SOILED HIMSELF.
QUESTIONS LIKE IS THERE A VIDEO?
AN APPLE FACTORY IN CHINA IS
EXPECTED TO CUT iPHONES BY 6 MILLION
IN RESPONSE TO WORKER
PROTESTS.
THEIR MAIN DEMAND IS MORE PLAY TIME.
I'M SHOCKED TOO.
IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT KIM
KARDASHIAN AND KANYE WEST HAVE
REACHED A SETTLEMENT IN THEIR DIVORCE,
AND I'M GOING TO GO OUT
ON A LIMB AND SUGGEST THAT SHE
HAD AN EASIER TIME
FINDING A
A GOOD LAWYER.
IT'S THE HOLIDAY SEASON, WHICH
CAN BE ESPECIALLY TOUGH FOR
CHILDREN OF DIVORCE.
HERE TO COMMENT IS CHILD OF
DIVORCE MICHAEL LONGFELLOW.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS, EVERYONE.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS, MICHAEL.
SO YOUR PARENTS ARE DIVORCED.
IS THAT HARD FOR SNU. NO.
I WAS A TINY BABY.
I HAVE NO MEMORY OF THEM BEING TOGETHER.
UNTIL I GOT OLDER, I WASN'T SURE
THEY KNEW EACH OTHER.
I HAD A CHILD TELL ME, YOU KNOW
YOUR PARENTS HAD SEX TO HAVE
YOU, AND I WAS LIKE, I DON'T
KNOW THAT THEY'VE MET, SO THAT'S
STUPID.
WELL, SURELY YOU WERE AWARE
AT SOME POINT THEY MET.
I WASN'T, AND DON'T CALL ME
SHIRLEY.
IT'S NOT SNAKES ON A PLANE.
I HONESTLY, THE HOLIDAYS MUST
HAVE BEEN MORE DIFFICULT WITH
DIVORCED PARENTS.
I DISAGREE.
THERE ARE PERKS TO HAVING
PARENTS ALWAYS GETTING MARRIED
AND DIVORCED AND MARRIED AGAIN.
YOU EVER ASK FOR A BROTHER FOR
CHRISTMAS AND ACTUALLY GET ONE?
I HAVE AND I DIDN'T HAVE TO WAIT
FOR HIM TO GROW UP.
WE CAME OFF THE SHELF READY TO GO.
WE WERE PLAYING CATCH THAT DAY.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN NICE.
IT WAS.
AND BROTHERS IS NOT THE ONLY
THING DIVORCE HAS GIVEN ME.
IT'S GIVEN ME SISTERS, BROTHERS,
DADS, AND YOU GOT MY NEWEST DAD
KERRY WHO'S A SEMINUDIST I'VE
SEEN NAKED 43 TIMES.
WHEN YOU SEE YOUR MOM'S
BOYFRIEND NAKED, YOU THINK A LOT
OF THINGS, BUT YOU DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN 42 MORE TIMES.
WELL, I AT LEAST HOPE HE HAS
A NICE BODY.
WHY?
YOU KNOW WHAT, I DON'T KNOW.
NEVER MIND.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU'RE THEN
PRO-DIVORCE?
WELL, MY DAD IS A DIVORCE
ATTORNEY, SO PUT FOOD ON MY TABLE.
SO YOUR FATHER IS A DIVORCED
ATTORNEY WHO'S ALSO BEEN
DIVORCED?
MULTIPLE TIMES.
I MEAN, THIS GUY WALKS THE WALK.
IS HE A BAD HUSBAND OR A
WORKAHOLIC?
HE'S AN ARTIST.
BUT HE WAS STILL A GREAT DAY.
HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING A KID
SHOULD KNOW, BRUSH YOUR TEETH,
DO YOUR HOMEWORK, IF INFIDELITY
CAN'T BE PROVEN, THEY'RE ONLY
ENTITLED TO 30%.
AND IT'S NOT EASY TO PROVE IN A
COURT OF LAW.
TEXT MESSAGES AREN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
GOOD TO KNOW.
SO IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR DAD
ENJOYS HIS WORK.
ABSOLUTELY.
IN FACT, HE MET HIS CURRENT WIFE
BECAUSE HE HANDLED HER DIVORCE.
SOME SAY THAT'S A CONFLICT OF INTEREST.
I JUST SAY HE'S GOT THAT
DOG HIM.
MICHAEL LONGFELLOW, EVERYONE.
AND DON'T CALL ME SHIRLEY.
>>> DALLAS COWBOYS OWNER JERRY
JONES IS UNDER FIRE OVER A
PICTURE OF HIM FROM 1967 WHERE
HE LOOKS AS BLACK STUDENTS ARE
STOPPED SOMEWHERING THE SCHOOL.
WOULD A RACIST OWN A TEAM THAT
HAS THE STRONGEST BLACK MEN HE
CAN FIND TO WORK ON HIS FIELD?
HAWAII'S LARGEST ACTIVE
VOLCANO BEGAN ERUPTING FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE 1984.
ALSO ERUPTING FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE 1984, YOUR AUNT WATCHING
YELLOW STONE.
THIS WEEK MARKS THE 40th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE CLASSIC
MICHAEL JACKSON ALBUM, THRILLER.
AND SAY WHAT YOU WILL ABOUT
MICHAEL JACKSON, BUT HE
DEFINITELY HAD A HUGE EFFECT ON
A LOT OF PEOPLE'S CHILDHOODS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS LIKE ANYMORE.
THE WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION
IS CHANGING THE NAME OF
MONKEYPOX TO M POX DUE TO THE
CONCERN THAT THE ORIGINAL COULD
BE RACIST, WHICH I DIDN'T THINK
WAS AN ISSUE.
BUT NOW I'M WONDERING, WHAT'S
THE N IN I-95?
MERIAM WEBSTER ANNOUNCED ITS
WORD OF THE YEAR IS GASLIGHTING.
IT'S A WORD MY EX MADE UP TO
MAGICALLY WIN ARGUMENTS SHE WAS LOSING.
LAW ENFORCEMENT DEPARTMENTS
IN SIX EUROPEAN COUNTRIES
ARRESTED NEARLY 50 DRUG
TRAFFICKERS RUNNING A COCAINE
SUPER CARTEL.
YOU KNOW WHAT MADE THE CARTEL
REALLY SUPER?
FRIENDSHIP.
A POLICE OFFICER IN NEW
YORK--
A POLICE OFFICER IN NEW YORK
STATE IS BEING CALLED THE BABY
WHISPERER AFTER HE HELPED
DELIVER HIS FIFTH BABY IN NINE
YEARS.
ONLY FIVE BABIES IN NINE YEARS,
SAID NICK CANNON.
OKAY.
THERE YOU ARE. OKAY.
A WOMAN IN ATLANTA GAVE BIRTH TO
HER BABY IN A McDONALD'S.
SO CAUTION, WET FLOOR.
IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT KIDS
CARTOON PEPPA PIG WILL INTRODUCE
A SAME-SEX COUPLE TO ITS CAST OF
CHARACTERS.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS A VERY
UPSET PRESIDENT OF THE FAN CLUB,
TRISH DALE.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME. YES.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE PRETTY UPSET
ABOUT THIS NEW ADDITION TO THE SHOW.
I'M MORE THAN UPSET.
I'M MAD AS H-E-C-CAN K.
WOW, YOU SPELL OUT HECK.
OKAY.
MICHAEL, YOU MAY THINK I'M
OVERREACTING, BUT PARENTS WHO
LOVE PEPPA PIG SHOULD GET TO
CHOOSE WHAT KINDS OF THINGS
THEIR KIDS SEE.
WHAT ARE THE CHARACTERS LIKE?
IT'S A POLAR BEAR GIRL WITH
TWO DADDIES, AND ONE'S A DOCTOR,
AND ONE STAYS HOME AND MAKES SPA GUESSTY.
I THINK THAT SOUNDS CUTE.
YEAH, IT IS.
IT IS CUTE.
UNTIL THEY ANALLY ENTER EACH
OTHER.
WHAT?
COME ON, MICHAEL.
SURE.
IN THE FIRST EPISODE, THEY MAKE SPAGHETTI.
BUT YOU KNOW AS SOON AS THOSE
PLATES ARE CLEARED, THEY'RE
ANALLY ENTERING EACH OTHER, AND
ONE IS A DOCTOR, SO HE KNOWS
JUST WHERE IT GOES.
TRISH, I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN ON THE SHOW.
OH, I KNOW.
IT WILL BE SOMETHING INNOCENT
LIKE TEACH PEPPA HOW TO RIDE A BIKE.
THAT'S NICE.
AND ONCE PEPPA HAS THE HANG
OF IT, THEY'LL SAY, YOU GOT
THIS, GIRL, AND THEN THEY GO
BEHIND A BUSH AND ANALLY ENTER
EACH OTHER.
I THINK THIS SHOW IS
REFLECTING THAT GAY PEOPLE EXIST
AND IT'S JUST A PART OF LIFE.
IT'S NOT A PART OF LIFE.
IT HURTS.
WHAT DOES?
I TRIED IT.
IT HURTS, AND IT HURTS.
AND THEY'RE POLAR BEARS, SO YOU
KNOW IT'S LIKE THIS BIG.
IMAGINE THAT IN YOU.
TRISH, I THINK YOU NEED TO
CALM DOWN.
I CAN'T.
I'VE TRIED EVERYTHING.
I'VE TRIED MEDITATION, POPPERS,
IT STILL HURTS.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER EPISODE
WHERE--
OH, TRISH, PLEASE.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER EPISODE
WHERE PEPPA IS HAVING TROUBLE
WITH HER MATH HOMEWORK, SO THE
BIGGER POLAR BEAR, THE MORE
MASCULINE ONE, SAYS LET'S GO
UPSTAIRS AND GET OUR CALCULATOR,
BUT THEY NEVER COME BACK.
AND YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT THEY
WERE DOING UP THERE?
ANALLY ENTERING EACH OTHER. SHOWERING.
OH, OKAY.
TO GET READY TO ANALLY ENTER
EACH OTHER BECAUSE IT'S A
PROCESS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
I GOOGLED IT.
IT'S SICK.
THEN DON'T LET YOUR KIDS WATCH.
I DON'T HAVE KIDS. ANYMORE.
ANYMORE?
THEY GREW UP, AND I DON'T
KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
TRISH, THIS IS ALL IN YOUR
HEAD.
THE SHOW WILL NEVER SHOW ANY OF THAT.
THAT'S WHY I ANIMATED MY OWN,
SO EVERYONE CAN SEE EXACTLY WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
WELL, THE BIG ONE IS THE BOTTOM.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S THE TWIST.
I'M SORRY.
I HATE TO INTERRUPT.
WHO ARE YOU?
IT'S OKAY.
I ACTUALLY WATCH THIS SHOW, AND
IT'S TWO POLAR BEAR MOMMYS, NOT
TWO DADDIES.
WHAT?
NOW I HAVE TO GOOGLE THAT?
NO, NO.
IT'S LIKE--
UH-HUH.
OH, SO IT'S JUST MASHING AND
MUSHING?
THAT'S FINE.
I'VE DONE THAT.
TRISH DALE, EVERYBODY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY, THE
12th MONTH OF PREGNANCY IS
ALWAYS THE HARDEST.
WELL, WE JUST WANT TO DO ONE
LAST ULTRASOUND TO MAKE SURE THE
TWINS ARE IN THE RIGHT POSITION.
SOUNDS GOOD, DOC.
HIT ME WITH THE COLD ASS JELLY. OKAY.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK HERE.
THERE THEY ARE, YOUR BEAUTIFUL BABIES.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M CRYING.
LOOK HOW CUTE THEY ARE.
OKAY, Y'ALL, THAT IMAGE IS CRISP.
I'LL WATCH THE SUPER BOWL ON
THAT THING.
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE KICKING.
NOW, WOULD YOU SAY THIS IS A
TYPICAL AMOUNT OF MOVEMENT?
WELL, I DID HAVE THREE
MONSTER ENERGY DRINKS THIS
MORNING.
WELL, THAT'S NOT RECOMMENDED,
BUT IT DOES EXPLAIN THE BREAK
DANCING.
COME ON NOW.
GET IT.
DOES THAT HURT?
WELL, I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT YOU
GET WHEN YOUR SPERM DONORS WAS
ONE OF THE JABBER WALKERS?
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT?
YEAH.
THE SPERM BANK HAD ATHLETES, IVY LEAGUES.
WELL, FOR FUTURE REFERENCE,
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO WATCH
YOUR CAFFEINE INTAKE.
NO SMOKING, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S A NO.
WHAT IF THE BABIES ARE
SMOKING.
WHAT?
MY DAD BAD.
THIS THING IS LIKE AN EXHAUST
PIPE LATELY.
SLOW DOWN, Y'ALL.
SLOW DOWN.
WHY DOCTOR R THEY SMOKING
CIGARETTES?
BECAUSE IT LOOKS COOL.
NOW, DOCTOR, MEDICALLY SPEAKING,
WHAT ARE THEY DOING WITH THE
UMBILICAL CORD?
WELL, THEY APPEAR TO BE
JUMPING ROPE.
SORRY.
I HAVE BEEN CRAVING FLAMING HOT
CHEETOS LATELY.
DAMN, THESE THINGS ARE HOT.
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TAKE IT EASY
ON THE SPICY FOODS.
YOU KNOW, DOC, I WASN'T EVEN
SURE I WANTED TO GET PREGNANT.
BUT THEN I LOST TWO IUDs IN A
ROW, AND I TOOK IT AS A SIGN.
WELL, I THINK I FOUND THEM.
OH, COME IN. HI.
I HAVE A DELIVERY.
I THINK YOU HAVE THE WRONG
ROOM, SIR.
NOBODY HERE ORDERED McDONALD'S.
WAIT.
I THINK THE BABIES DID.
THEY HAVE A PHONE?
I'M NOT ONE OF THOSE PARENTS
WHO'S GOING TO LIMIT SCREEN TIME
LIKE A LOSER.
OH, THEY'RE MOVING.
OH, WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT YOU WAITING FOR?
GIVE THE KIDS THEY FISH.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
LOVE YOU, BABY.
OH, DON'T FORGET YOUR TIP, BRO.
COME ON.
THERE YOU GO.
NO, I'M GOOD.
LOOK AT HOW HAPPY THEY ARE.
MAN, THEY REALLY CHOWING THAT
THING DOWN, AIN'T THEY?
EXCUSE YOU.
WELL, I HAVE TO SAY, I DON'T
THINK BABIES SHOULD BE EATING
FILLET O FISH SANDWICHES IN THE
WOMB.
WAIT A SECOND.
WHERE ARE THEY?
WHERE DID THEY GO?
OH, MY GOD.
NO!
>>> OKAY, GIRLS,LET GET STARTED
WITH OH, HOLY NIGHT.
AND A ONE AND A TO TWO AND A--
♪ OH, HOLY NIGHT, WHERE STARS
ARE BRIGHTLY SHINING ♪
♪ IT IS THE NIGHT OF OUR DEAR
SAVIOR'S BIRTH ♪
♪ FALL ON YOUR KNEES, OH, HEAR
THE ANGEL'S VOICES, OH, NIGHT,
DIVINE, OH, NIGHT DIVINE ♪
YES.
I FELT LIKE I WAS THERE.
MR. DAVID, WHY DO DEDE AND
DANA GET TO DO ALL THE SOLOS?
BECAUSE ART IS NOT FAIR.
AND MAYBE IF YOU PUT YOUR
WHOLE P WORD IN IT, YOU WOULD
GET A SOLO.
YEAH, WE PUT OUR WHOLE P WORD
IN IT.
OH, I FORGOT, WE HAVE A NEW
STUDENT TRANSFERRING.
EVERYONE, THIS IS KAYLA. HELLO.
WELCOME TO CHRIST MOON HIGH.
I'VE NEVER GONE AN ALL GIRLS
SCHOOL BEFORE.
WE'RE ALL IS SISTERS HERE.
WE'RE ALL SINKED UP, SO
THAT'S PRETTY COOL TOO.
FOCUS UP.
KAYLA, HOW ABOUT YOU SING A
LITTLE OH HOLY NIGHT FOR US.
I HAVEN'T PRACTICED.
♪ FALL ON YOUR KNEES, OH, HEAR
THE ANGELS VOICES, OH NIGHT
DIVINE, OH, NIGHT DIVINE ♪
HELLO.
I'LL TELL HER.
THAT WAS BROADWAY.
YOU'RE THE NEW FUNNY GIRL.
WHERE DID YOU TRANSFER FROM?
HEAVEN?
DEDE, SNAP OUT OF IT.
SHE'S OUR COMPETITION.
WE CAN'T LET HER STEAL OUR SOLO. RIGHT.
WHAT WAS HER--
MR. DAVID, WE'RE GOING TO RUN
IT BACK, AND A ONE.
♪ FALL ON YOUR KNEES ♪
SING ALONG!
♪ OH, NIGHT WHEN CHRIST WAS
BORN.
BECAUSE CHRIST WAS BORN IN
THE CITY!
♪ OH, NIGHT DIVINE ♪
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE MADE MY DECISION, AND I'VE
CONSULTED WITH THE GODS, PLURAL.
WE GO TO CATHOLIC SCHOOL.
GROW UP!
THE SOLO GOES TO KAYLA!
SEEMS FAIR TO ME.
WAIT, WAIT.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
CHRISTMAS IS A SEASON OF TOGETHERNESS.
SO WHY DON'T WE ALL DO THE SOLO
TOGETHER?
US TOO?
EVEN ME?
ALL OF US.
AND LET'S PUT OUR WHOLE P WORDS
INTO IT.
I LOVE THIS WOMAN!
♪ FALL ON YOUR KNEES, OH HEAR
THE ANGEL VOICES, OH NIGHT
DIVINE, OH NIGHT DIVINE ♪
SZA.
♪
♪ PEOPLE WANT ME ♪
♪ TO GET RATCHET
PEOPLE WANT ME
TO ATTACK IT ♪
♪ PUT THE HOOD ON
NOW THEY CALLIN'
ME CASSIUS ♪
♪ RAUNCHY LIKE BOB SAGET
GREEDY I CAN'T PASS IT
EATIN' EVERYTHING ♪
♪ I'M DOING
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
YOU KNEW ME ♪
♪ IN THE PAST TENSE
I AIN'T NO JULIA STILES
THIS AIN'T NO LAST DANCE
WAY PAST IT ♪
♪ WAY
ROLLIN' ON MY EX
'CAUSE HE VALIDATE ME
OPEN UP A CHECK ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT NO RECEIPT
MIND KEEP POSSESSED
LET MY SPIRIT SPEAK FREELY
HEY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE MY PAST
CAN'T ESCAPE ME
MY-- PRECEDES ME ♪
♪ MY MY
HOW THE TIMES CHANGE
YOU STILL PLAYIN'
THE VICTIM ♪
♪ AND I'M STILL PLAYIN'
THE PICK-ME
IT'S SO EMBARRASSING ♪
♪ ALL OF THE THINGS I NEED
LIVING INSIDE OF ME
I CAN'T SEE IT
IT'S SO EMBARRASSING ♪
♪ ALL OF THE LOVE I SEEK
LIVING INSIDE OF ME
I CAN'T SEE ♪
♪ I'M BLIND
BLIND BLIND BLIND BLIND
BLIND BLIND ♪
♪ YOU AIN'T GETTING
YOUR CHICK BACK
CALM DOWN IF YOU
WOULD NEVER SAY THAT ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT TO PLAY
I'D RATHER GET PAYBACK
MOMMA TOLD ME NEVER
PAY FOR YOUR MAN ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT TO
BREAK THIS
I HURT TOO MUCH
I LOST TOO MUCH ♪
♪ I LOVE TOO MUCH
IN MY PASSION GROWN
HEARD THEY POP OUT THE ZONE ♪
♪ I LIKE IT WHEN YOU
PULL UP AT THE RED LIGHT
I LIKE ALL THE VIOLENCE
GIVE ME THAT FUNCTION ♪
♪ I LIKE WHEN YOU CALL
AND WE COULD GO ALL NIGHT
BETTER WHEN YOU HIGH
NEVER TELL ME I'M BONKERS ♪
♪ MY PAST CAN'T ESCAPE ME
MY COOCHIE CAN BEAT ME
MY MY HOW THE TIMES CHANGE ♪
♪ YOU STILL TALKIN'
'BOUT BABIES
AND I'M STILL TAKIN'
THE PLAN B ♪
♪ IT'S SO EMBARRASSING
ALL OF THE LOVE I SEEK
LIVING INSIDE OF ME
I CAN'T SEE IT ♪
♪ IT'S SO EMBARRASSING
ALL OF THE LOVE I SEEK
SAID I CAN'T SEE
I'M BLIND ♪
♪ BLIND BLIND BLIND BLIND
BLIND BLIND BLIND BLIND
BLIND BLIND ♪
DECK.
WE WANT TO THANK YOU AGAIN FOR
FLYING WITH US.
SHOULD BE A SMOOTH RIDE TO HAWAII.
I'M GOING TO ASK THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANTS TO DIM THE CABIN
LIGHTS AND LET YOU FOLKS GET
SOME REST.
THAT'S REAL CUTE, BUT THESE
LIGHTS GOING TO GO AHEAD AND
STAY ON.
WAKE Y'ALL AS UP, BECAUSE
THIS IS A BIG MOMENT FOR CHERYL
AND I NOW.
DRUM ROLL, PLEASE.
WHAT YOU JUST WITNESSED IS
DENISE AND I LOGGING OUR
MILLIONth MILE AS FLIGHT ATTENDANTS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
FA-LA-LA-LA-BONUS.
THIS PLANE IS ALSO
CELEBRATING A VERY SPECIAL
OCCASION TONIGHT.
THIS PLANE HAS NOW FLOWN 10
MILLION MILES.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
10 MILLION MILES.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT.
OH, IT'S NOT JUST A LOT.
IT'S ILLEGAL.
UH-HUH.
BUT DON'T TELL NOBODY BECAUSE
WE MADE SOME GOOD MEMORIES ON
THIS PLANE HERE.
OKAY.
REMEMBER THAT LITTLE BITTY PLANE
CRASH WE GOT INTO?
YES, GIRL.
REMEMBER THAT BIG PLANE CRASH,
THOUGH?
THIS PLANE HAS BEEN IN MORE
THAN ONE CRASH?
MA'AM, THIS PLANE BEEN IN A
BUNCH OF CRASHES.
GIRL, YOU ARE ON A ROLL TONIGHT.
I FEEL GOOD.
WE JUST FLEW A MILLEY, A MILLEY,
A MILLEY.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M FLYING TO MY GRANDMOTHER'S
FUNERAL, AND I DO NOT NEED THIS
RIGHT NOW.
YOU BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
MA'AM, NOT TO WORRY.
YOU GROW THROUGH WHAT YOU GO
THROUGH, JUST LIKE THIS PLANE.
THIS PLANE HERE IS OLD, Y'ALL.
OLD AS HELL, Y'ALL.
THIS PLANE LIVED THROUGH SEGREGATION.
LOOK AT THE SIGN ON THE BATHROOM.
WHITES ONLY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
UH-HUH.
THAT'S VERY UPSETTING.
EVERYTHING YOU'RE SAYING IS.
OKAY?
CAN YOU STOP TALKING SO I CAN
WATCH A MOVIE?
WELL, I WAS ABOUT TO TELL YOU
HOW THE ENGINE WASN'T STARTING
EARLIER, BUT LET ME NOT BECAUSE
YOU'RE TRYING TO WATCH PORN.
THE ENGINE ISN'T STARTING?
NOPE.
AND I FOUND THIS HERE SCREW
UNDER THE PLANE BEFORE WE TOOK
OFF.
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE IT'S FROM OR
WHERE IT GOES.
AND THAT'S A LONG-ASS SCREW,
SO YOU KNOW IT'S ESSENTIAL.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOSH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
DID THE PLANE JUST LIKE TURN
OFF?
SIR, IT'S 1:00 A.M., THE
ENGINE'S JUST TAKING A LITTLE NAP.
Y'ALL DON'T NEED TO DO ALL
THAT.
GIRL, GO GET THE CABLE.
SEE THAT THERE.
WASN'T NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
HEY, FOLKS, JUST HAD A LITTLE
HICCUP WITH THE ENGINE THERE.
SHOULD BE FINE NOW.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IT'S PAST MIDNIGHT.
THAT MEANS IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
HAPPY 90th BIRTHDAY, CAPTAIN!
90th?
OKAY, Y'ALL.
WE GOING TO GO AHEAD AND DIM THE
CABIN LIGHTS SO Y'ALL CAN GET
Y'ALL SOME REST.
WELL, NOBODY'S GOING TO BE
ABLE TO SLEEP NOW.
IT'S BECAUSE YOU EXCITED,
RIGHT?
THAT'S GOOD.
BECAUSE TO LAND, WE'RE GOING TO
NEED EVERYONE TO RUN TO THE
FRONT OF THE PLANE TO HELP US
POINT DOWN.
WE ARE TALKING FLOOR IT.
WE GOT TO WORK TOGETHER,
Y'ALL.
INCREDIBLE CAST FOR LETTING ME A
PART OF THEIR TEAM.
Y'ALL HAVE A GOOD NIGHT!