>>> SENATOR RICH, MIND IF I JOIN
YOU?
>> SENATOR RUBIO, OF COURSE,
HAVE A SEAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> DECEMBER WE BETTER TOAST TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THAT WAS A BIG VICTORY TONIGHT.
21 POINTS.
>> YES, SIR.
WELL, THERE WAS NEVER ANY DOUBT.
I GUESS TRUMP OWNS THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY NOW.
>> YEAH.
I GOT TO ADMIT, THOUGH.
SOMETIMES I DO NOT KNOW WHAT MY
PARTY IS DOING.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN PUSHING FOR
UKRAINE FUNDING FOR THE PAST SIX
MONTHS.
IT'S ESSENTIAL TO AMERICAN
SECURITY.
AND TRUMP JUST KILLED IT WITH
ONE PHONE CALL.
THE MAN DOESN'T CARE ABOUT THIS
COUNTRY ONE IOTA.
SOMETIMES I THINK HE'S DOWNRIGHT
DANGEROUS.
>> HM.
AND YOU JUST ENDORSED HIM,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, BIG-TIME,
HE'S GREAT.
>> SO GREAT.
>> HE IS INCREDIBLE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> NOW, TRUMP GAVE YOU THE NAME
LITTLE MARCO.
RIGHT?
>> UH, YEAH, YEAH.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO SHAKE
IT.
PEOPLE STILL YELL IT AT ME IN
AIRPORTS.
HE KIND OF MADE MY LIFE HELL.
>> AND YOU ENDORSED HIM, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> BIG-TIME.
THAT GUY'S JUST THE BEST.
THE BEST.
HE'S AMAZING, AMAZING.
>> SOUTH CAROLINA IN THE HOUSE.
>> WELL, WELL.
SENATOR GRAHAM.
SENATOR SCOTT.
GET IN HERE, JOIN US, GET YOUR
BUTTS IN HERE.
>> WITH PLEASURE, WITH PLEASURE.
>> Y'ALL TALKING ABOUT TRUMP?
>> UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW WE ARE.
YES, SIR.
>> OH, HEY TIM, I SAW YOU WITH
TRUMP ON THAT LAURA INGRAHAM
TOWN HALL LAST WEEK.
KIND OF ROUGH, RIGHT?
YOU WERE SITTING RIGHT THERE,
HE
SAID TO THE CROWD THAT YOU'VE
BEEN A MUCH BETTER CANDIDATE FOR HIM
THAN YOU EVER WERE FOR
YOURSELF.
>> YEAH, HE'S SO FUNNY.
>> HE'S HILARIOUS.
>> SUPER FUNNY.
>> A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO HE MADE
YOU STAND IN FRONT OF A CROWD
ASK SAY YOU HATE NIKKI HALEY.
ISN'T SHE THE ONE WHO APPOINTED
YOU IN THE SENATE?
>> NO, NO, HE DIDN'T MAKE ME SAY
THAT I HATE HER.
HE SAID, "YOU MUST REALLY HATE
HER."
BUT Y'ALL SAW WHAT I DID.
I STEPPED RIGHT UP TO THE MIC
AND I SAID, "NO, I JUST LOVE
YOU."
>> WOW.
YOU SHOWED HIM.
VERY COOL.
>> YEAH, I DO LOVE HIM, THOUGH,
HE'S GREAT, HE'S GREAT.
>> HE IS SO GREAT.
>> I ADORE THE MAN.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY OF THESE?
>> CAN I NIBBLE OFF YOURS?
>> PIGS IN BLANKETS ARE GOOD.
>> UH-HUH, SURE ARE.
>> YOU KNOW, HE ONCE DOXED ME?
>> HE DOXED YOU?
>> NO!
>> NO, REALLY?
>> BACK IN 2015.
HE GAVE OUT MY PERSONAL CELL
PHONE NUMBER IN A SPEECH TO ALL
HIS SUPPORTERS.
HAD THOUSANDS OF HIS PEOPLE CALL
ME UP TO YELL AT ME.
>> THREATENING MY LIFE.
HAD TO GET A NEW PHONE.
>> MM -- YOU OKAY?
>> OH, GOSH.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> SWITCHED TO VERIZON.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I STILL THINK HE'S THE GREATEST
PRESIDENT SINCE REAGAN.
>> OH, HE IS GREATER THAN
REAGAN.
>> OH, HE'S GREATER THAN
LINCOLN.
>> OH, YEAH, RIGHT?
>> SO DARN HANDSOME, IT MAKES ME
JEALOUS.
YOU KNOW TRUMP ONCE SAID I SWEAT
MORE THAN ANYONE HE'S EVER SEEN?
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEP, YEP.
HE SAID MY SWEAT WAS DECEMBER GUSTING
AND WE NEED SOMEONE IN
THE WHITE HOUSE WHO DOESN'T HAVE
WHATEVER MARCO'S GOT.
BUT THAT'S FINE, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
HE DOES WHAT IT TAKES TO WIN.
>> HE DOES.
- HE'S TOOL AND HE IS TALL AND I
LIKE HIM.
THESE TATER TOTS ARE NICE.
>> THEY'RE NOT SOGGY OR
ANYTHING.
>> SEASONED.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW -- I'VE
NEVER REALLY TALKED ABOUT THIS.
BUT ONE OF THE JANUARY 6th RIOTERS --
I'M SORRY, ONE OF THE
JANUARY 6th TOURISTS.
>> RIGHT.
>> POOPED ON THE FLOOR IN MY
OFFICE.
>> OH, COME ON!
>> LOOK IT UP.
I SWEAR, LOOK IT UP.
SENATOR RICH, "POOP IN OFFICE,"
LOOK IT UP.
TRASHED MY DESK.
TOOK A BIG OLD DEUCE RIGHT ON
THE FLOOR.
LOOK, THAT'S NOT TRUMP'S FAULT,
RIGHT?
TRUMP CALLED THE GUY WHO DID IT
AN INNOCENT PATRIOT.
BUT HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY DO IT.
SO WE ALL AGREE, TRUMP IS GREAT,
RIGHT?
>> HE'S WONDERFUL.
>> AS PERFECT A MAN AS THE GOOD
LORD EVER MADE.
>> WHAT I LOVE ABOUT HIM
PERSONALLY IS HE DOESN'T HAVE A
RACIST BONE IN HIS BODY.
I LIKE THAT.
>> REALLY?
DID YOU SEE HIM LAST NIGHT AT
THAT SPEECH IN SOUTH CAROLINA
WHEN HE TOLD THAT CROWD THAT
BLACK PEOPLE LIKE HIM BETTER NOW
BECAUSE HE HAS A MUGSHOT?
>> YEAH, MY MAN GOT STREET CRED!
YOU KNOW.
BUT LOOK, UNDERNEATH IT ALL,
HE'S A GOOD MAN
AND I LOVE HIM,
I DO.
>> HEY, TIM.
>> YEAH?
>> WHATEVER HE DID TO YOU, IT'S
NOT YOUR FAULT.
>> BUT NO, NO, HE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING TO ME.
I'M FINE.
>> I MEAN, ARE YOU REALLY?
REMEMBER, HE'S NOT GOING TO BE
AROUND FOREVER.
WELL, HE MIGHT BE, RIGHT?
>> SOMETIMES I THINK HIS ASS IS
GOING TO LIVE A THOUSAND YEARS.
BUT TIM?
HONEY?
DON'T LET HIM TURN YOU INTO
SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> GUYS.
I AM A U.S. SENATOR.
AND I WILL NEVER, EVER
COMPROMISE MY INTEGRITY FOR
DONALD TRUMP.
BUT I MIGHT IF HE MADE ME VICE
PRESIDENT, HEY!
>> AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- SHANE
GILLIS!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S -- YEAH.
I'M HERE.
I -- MOST OF YOU PROBABLY HAVE
NO IDEA WHO I AM.
I WAS ACTUALLY -- I WAS FIRED
FROM THIS SHOW.
AWHILE AGO.
BUT, YOU KNOW.
DON'T LOOK THAT UP, PLEASE.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHO I AM,
PLEASE DON'T GOOGLE THAT.
IT'S FINE, DON'T EVEN WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS -- I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
BE UP HERE, HONESTLY.
I SHOULD BE HOME.
I SHOULD BE -- I SHOULD BE A
HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL COACH.
THAT'S WHAT I SHOULD BE.
LIKE, GOD MOLDED ME PERFECTLY TO
BE A HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL COACH.
SLASH NINTH GRADE SEX EDUCATION
TEACHER.
BUT THAT IS WHAT I WANT TO BE.
THAT IS, YOU KNOW -- I CAN FEEL
IT.
IT'S LIKE MY TRUE CALLING.
YOU KNOW.
I CAN FEEL IT, YOU KNOW, GETTING
OLDER, IT'S PASSING ME BY.
YOU KNOW, MY BIOLOGICAL CLOCK IS
TICKING ON THIS STREAM.
YOU KNOW HOW LIKE WHEN A WOMAN'S
BIOLOGICAL CLOCK IS TICKING, SHE
SEES A BABY IN A STROLLER AND IS
LIKE, "OH MY GOD."
THAT'S HOW I AM IF A SEE A BIG
15-YEAR-OLD.
"OH MY GOD, LOOK AT THE SIZE OF"
THAT KID."
"WITH THE RIGHT COACHING, THAT"
KID COULD BE SOMETHING SPECIAL,
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW.
I COME FROM A LONG LINE OF
COACHES IN MY FAMILY.
MY FATHER'S ACTUALLY A VOLUNTEER
ASSISTANT GIRLS HIGH SCHOOL
BASKETBALL COACH.
HE'S ACTUALLY HERE RIGHT NOW.
YOU GET HIM ON THERE?
YEAH.
THERE HE IS.
THERE'S MY DAD.
THE VOLUNTEER ASSISTANT GIRLS
HIGH SCHOOL BASKETBALL COACH.
I DON'T KNOW, IT'S FUNNY, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T THINK THAT'S FUNNY, TO
BRING MY DAD HERE TO MAKE FUN OF
HIM FOR BEING A GIRLS HIGH
SCHOOL BASKETBALL COACH?
ALL RIGHT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GREAT.
NEVER MIND.
THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING TO BE A
BIG HIT HERE.
MY MOM'S UP THERE WITH HIM.
MY MOM -- I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE
FUN OF YOU.
MY MOM ASKED ME THIS A LOT.
IT'S KIND OF AN INTENSE
QUESTION.
"WHEN DID WE STOP BEING BEST"
FRIENDS?"
AND SHE'S RIGHT.
WE USED TO BE BEST FRIENDS.
YOU REMEMBER THAT, WHEN YOU WERE
A LITTLE BOY, YOU LOVED YOUR
MOM, YOU TO THE SHE WAS THE
COOLEST -- YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU
WERE GAY?
YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE JUST
A GAY LITTLE BOY?
EVERY LITTLE BOY IS JUST THEIR
MOM'S GAY BEST FRIEND, THERE'S
ZER ROW DIFFERENCE.
I WAS GAY FOR MY MOM.
SHE WOULD PICK ME UP FROM
SCHOOL, HOP IN THE VAN, "GIRL,
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DAY."
I THOUGHT SHE WAS COOL.
I WOULD LISTEN TO HER MUSIC.
♪ BAM BAM BAM ♪
LET'S GO, GIRLS!
I WOULD DANCE FOR HER.
SHE'D BE LIKE, "LOOK AT MY
LITTLE DANCER!"
BUT -- MY MOM ASKED ME WHEN WE
STOPPED BEING BEST FRIENDS, AND
I DON'T HAVE THE HEART TO TELL
HER.
BECAUSE LIKE MOST MEN, I KNOW
EXACTLY WHEN ME AND MY MOM
STOPPED BEING FRIENDS.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME I WHACKED
OFF.
RIGHT?
BEFORE THAT, YOU'RE LIKE,
"WHERE'S MY MOM, I LOVE MY MOM,"
SHE'S TO COOL."
ONE NIGHT, "WHEN'S THAT BITCH
GOING TO LEAVE THE HOUSE?
I HAVE SO MUCH BUSINESS TO
ATTEND TO."
ALL RIGHT, I HOPE I CAN SAY
THOSE WORDS ON TV.
ANYWAY, MY WHOLE FAMILY'S HERE,
SO I'LL TALK ABOUT THEM INSTEAD
OF ANYTHING ELSE.
TALK ABOUT MY FAMILY.
I'LL TELL YOU THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN TELL BY
LOOKING AT ME, BUT I DO HAVE
FAMILY MEMBERS WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
IT ALMOST GOT ME.
I DODGED IT, BUT IT NICKED ME.
IT NICKED ME.
IT'S FUNNY.
LOOK, I DON'T HAVE ANY MATERIAL
THAT CAN BE ON TV, ALL RIGHT?
I'M TRYING MY BEST.
ALSO, THIS PLACE IS EXTREMELY
WELL-LIT.
I CAN SEE EVERYONE NOT ENJOYING
IT.
YOU KNOW.
JUST THE MOST NERVOUS I'VE EVER
BEEN.
DON'T CLAP NOW, SHUT UP.
NO, I TALK ABOUT DOWN SYNDROME.
YOU CAN TELL WHO'S NEVER BEEN
AROUND DOWN SYNDROME.
"I HAVE FAMILY MEMBERS WITH DOWN"
SYNDROME."
PEOPLE WHO HAVE NEVER BEEN
AROUND IT ARE ALWAYS LIKE, "OH."
LIKE IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD.
ARE THEY OKAY?
THEY'RE DOING BETTER THAN
EVERYBODY I KNOW.
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES HAVING A
GOOD TIME PRETTY CONSISTENTLY.
THEY'RE NOT WORRIED ABOUT THE
ELECTION.
THEY'RE HAVING A GOOD TIME.
MY NIECE -- MY NIECE HAS DOWN
SYNDROME.
AND I THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING TO
GET A BIGGER LAUGH.
I THOUGHT WE WERE ALLOWED TO
HAVE FUN HERE.
NO, MY NIECE HAS DOWN SYNDROME.
IT'S A FUNNY THING THAT HAPPENS
WHEN SOMEONE IN YOUR FAMILY HAS
DOWN SYNDROME.
MY SISTER WAS PREGNANT.
EVERYONE WAS VERY, VERY SCARED.
THEY COME INTO YOUR LIFE, YOU
REALIZE THEY'RE THE ONLY GOOD
MEMBER OF YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY.
IT'S CRAZY.
YOUR FAMILY GETS TOO PROUD.
MY FAMILY'S GROUP TEXT, IT'S
PICTURES OF MY NIECE.
EVERY DAY, SOMEBODY ELSE
COMMENTS "SHE LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
UNCLE SHANE."
YEAH, I SEE IT A LITTLE.
THERE'S NO DENYING SHE LOOKS
LIKE ME WITH BANGS.
JUST HAPPY, JUST -- BUT MY
SISTER, MY NIECE'S MOTHER, SHE
DIDN'T KNOW SHE COULD GET
PREGNANT.
SHE FOSTERED THEN ADOPTED THREE
BLACK KIDS.
THEN SHE FINALLY GOT PREGNANT.
NOW SHE HAS A KID WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
HER HUSBAND IS FROM EGYPT, HE'S
AN ARAB GUY.
YOU GO TO THE HOUSE, IT'S LIKE
GETTING INTO THE CRAZIEST UBER
POOL YOU'VE BEEN IN.
IT'S CRAZY.
LIKE, HOW DID YOU GUYS MEET?
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING, I DON'T
KNOW -- MY NIECE, ONE DAY -- I'M
NOT SAYING IT'S SOMETHING I'M
LOOKING FORWARD TO, BUT I THINK
IT WILL BE A NICE THING FOR THE
WHOLE COUNTRY.
I WOULD SAY WHEN MY NIECE IS
PROBABLY IN FIFTH, SIXTH GRADE,
OUT AT RECESS, SOME WHITE KIDS
OUT THERE, "HEY, YOU'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO PLAY WITH US, YOU'RE
RETARDED."
THEN THREE BLACK KIDS COME
FLYING OUT OF NOWHERE.
START WHALING ON THAT CRACKER.
EVERYONE'S GOING TO BE BE LIKE,
OH!
IT'S A NICE MOMENT.
YEAH, I SAID CRACKER.
NO WE -- MY FAMILY AND I, BY
OPENED A COFFEE SHOP IN MY
HOMETOWN FOR PEOPLE WITH DOWN
SYNDROME TO WORK AT.
DON'T CLAP.
I DIDN'T DO IT FOR THE CLAPS.
IT'S GOING EXACTLY HOW YOU WOULD
THINK IT WOULD GO.
IT'S DOING WELL.
LINE AROUND THE CORNER EVERY
DAY.
NOT BECAUSE THERE'S A TON OF
PEOPLE GOING, BUT SERVICE IS --
EVERYONE'S GETTING APPLE JUICE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW TO FIX THAT
PROBLEM.
THERE'S ONE THING -- THERE'S ONE
THING YOU NOTICE, THOUGH, WHEN
YOU WORK WITH THESE GUYS.
IT'S FUNNY.
LITERALLY THERE'S ZERO
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US AND THEM.
ESPECIALLY AT WORK.
THERE'S NO DIFFERENCE.
EVERY DAY THESE DUDES SHOW UP TO
WORK JUST --
YOU'RE LIKE, "WHAT'S YOUR
PROBLEM, DUDE?"
I HATE THIS JOB.
ALL RIGHT, HEY.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
21 SAVAGE IS HERE, SO
>>> DAD, DID YOU HAVE TO DRAG US
TO CHURCH WHILE WE'RE ON
VACATION?
>> CAN'T WE SKIP ONE SUNDAY?
>> HEY.
WE'RE CATHOLIC, OKAY?
I DON'T CARE WHERE WE ARE ON
SUNDAYS, WE GO TO CHURCH.
WHAT DID WE DO SUNDAY WHEN WE
VISITED IRELAND?
>> WE WENT TO CHURCH.
>> BINGO.
WHY SHOULD JAMAICA BE ANY
DIFFERENT?
>> ALL RIGHT, WELCOME, BROTHERS
AND SISTERS.
LET'S REMEMBER THAT AFTER THE
SERVICE, WE'RE GOING TO BE
HOLDING A HOMEGOING SERVICE FOR
SISTER CHARLENE, GOD REST HER
SOUL.
>> SEE, GUYS?
CHURCH IS CHURCH, NO MATTER
WHERE YOU ARE IN THE WORLD.
>> AND NOW A MESSAGE FROM FATHER
LAWRENCE.
♪♪
♪ UDNA DE BLOOD ♪
♪ UNDA DE BLOOD ♪
♪ IN THE MORNING WHEN ME WAKE
UP ♪
♪ RUB BLOOD OF JESUS ON ME FACE
LIKE MAKEUP ♪
♪ UNDA DE BLOOD ♪
♪ UNDA DEBLOOD ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, ME BROTHER
LAWRENCE, AND YES, YOU WILL COME
TO THE 6:30 A.M. IN THE MORNING
MASS.
ME SAY GOOD MORNING AND MANY
BLESSINGS TO THE CONGREGATION.
>> BRUH!
>> HA HA, WHOO!
>> WHY DID YOU MAKE US WEAR
DRESS SHOES WHEN FATHER LAWRENCE
HAS ON ADEES DAS SLIDES NO
SOCKS?
>> HE'S A PRIEST, HE CAN WEAR
WHAT HE WANTS, PAY ATTENTION.
>> ALL RIGHT, LISTEN UP, YOU
HEAR?
I'M GONE THAT HURRY UP AND
DELIVER THE WORD.
SISTER COOKED UP A NICE CURRY
GOAT WITH PEA.
WE HAVE TO GET BACK TO IT QUICK.
WE DON'T WANT NO STALE RICE AND
PEA.
IF YOU HEAR ME, SAY AMEN.
>> HONEY, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> HUSH NOW CHILD, ME TRYING TO
HEAR THE GOOD WORD.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME WORSHIP.
>> NOW, BEFORE ME READ FROM THE
BOOK, ME WANT TO ASK THE
CONGREGATION IF WE HAVE ANYBODY
NEW JOINING US FOR TODAY, ANY
GUESTS, ANY VISITORS, ANYTHING
LIKE THAT?
WE HAVE ANYBODY NEW TODAY?
>> YOU CAUGHT US.
WE'RE ACTUALLY IN FROM OHIO.
>> AMAZING.
THIS FORMER LINEBACKER COME HERE
ALL THE WAY FROM OHIO.
ENOUGH OF THAT NOW.
YOU WANT TO SIT AND HEAR ABOUT
OHIO?
OR YOU WANT TO HEAR ABOUT JESUS,
THE BLOOD, THE SAVIOR?
>> ME WANT TO HEAR ABOUT JESUS,
FATHER LAWRENCE.
>> ME NOT CARE ABOUT ANY OHIO.
>> WE WANT TO HEAR ABOUT JESUS,
FATHER LAWRENCE!
>> VERY GOOD.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT JESUS AND
WHERE YOU CAN FIND HIM.
♪ PON DE MANGER PON DE CROSS ♪
♪ THREE DAYS LATER OH MY GOD ♪
♪ HIM NOT THERE WHERE HIM GO
UP IN HEAVEN DAT I KNOW ♪
♪ ON THE PROMISE ON DE BLOOD ON
DE BLOOD ♪
♪ UNDA DE BLOOD ♪
>> SEE?
CHURCH IS CHURCH.
FATHER IS RIGHT.
JESUS WAS PON THE CROSS, DIED
FOR OUR SINS, TREE DAYS LATER
GONNA RAISE UP INTO HEAVEN.
>> RICKY.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
>> ALL RIGHT, ME GETTING LONELY
UP HERE, WE NEED SOME SUPPORT.
YOU WITH THE ROOTS.
>> WHO, ME?
>> YES, YEAH.
YOU, THE ONE WITH THE ROOTS,
COME ON.
>> ROOTS, HONEY, GO.
BE RESPECTFUL.
MAKE US PROUD.
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE BIBLE
VERSE?
>> I GUESS THE ONE WE READ AT
OUR WEDDING.
I CORINTHIANS 13.
>> THAT ONE SUCH A BEAUTIFUL
ONE, THAT ONE.
ME GO AND FIND, READ IT NOW.
LOVE BE PATIENT.
LOVE BE KIND.
♪ LOVE WID DE BACKUP THAT BIG
ROUND BEHIND WIND UP HER ♪
♪ AND SHE PUT IT ON MINE ♪
♪ UNDA DE BLOOD UNDE DE BLOOD ♪
EVERYBODY NOW!
♪ UNDER THE BLOOD ME SAY UNDER
THE BLOOD ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, JUST YOU!
♪ UNDA DE BLOOD ME SAY UNDA DE
BLOOD ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, DAD!
>> BIG UPS TO THE FATHER
LAWRENCE!
>>> THE THRILL OF VICTORY.
>> THE SATISFACTION OF PLACING A
BET AND WATCHING IT HIT BIG.
>> THE EXHILARATION OF AN UPSET
ONLY YOU SAW COMING.
>> WITH BETTING APPS RIGHT ON
YOUR PHONE, IT'S EASIER THAN
EVER TO TURN YOUR PASSION FOR
SPORTS INTO COLD, HARD CASH.
>> WITH SO MANY GAMES TO BET ON,
YOU ALMOST CAN'T LOSE.
>> BUT THERE'S A DARK SIDE, AS
WELL.
>> WE ALL KNOW A FRIEND WHO
STRUGGLES WITH ONLINE GAMBLING.
>> A FRIEND WHO'S ON THE VERGE
OF LOSING EVERYTHING.
HIS HOUSE, HIS FAMILY, HIS
ENTIRE LIFE.
>> NOW YOU CAN BET ON EXACTLY
HOW HE'LL LOSE IT ALL WITH ROCK
BOTTOM KINGS.
IT'S THE ONLY APP THAT LETS YOU
TAKE PROP BETS ABOUT HOW YOUR
DEGENERATE GAMBLER FRIEND IS
FINALLY GOING TO HIT ROCK
BOTTOM.
>> WILL IT BE, GOES DOUBLE OR
NOTHING ON A RANDOM WNBA GAME?
OR BETS HIS CHILD COLLEGE FUND
ON THE COIN TOSS?
>> WHEN YOUR FRIEND IS DESPERATE
FOR CASH, YOU CAN BET ON WHAT
HIS LOWEST MOMENTS WILL BE.
TAKE OUT A LIFE INSURANCE POLICY
ON HIS OWN MOTHER?
WILL HE SET UP A FAKE GOFUNDME
THAT SAYS HE HAS LEUKEMIA?
WHAT WILL HE SELL FIRST?
HIS PS5 OR HIS KIDNEY?
>> YOU CAN BUILD A PARLAY ABOUT
EVERYTHING THAT COULD HAPPEN TO
HIM.
DIVORCE.
MARRIES RICH OLD WIDOW.
ARRESTED FOR ELDER FRAUD.
FACES HIS OWN DEATH BUT IS
IMMEDIATELY CAUGHT WHEN HE USES
AN APP TO GAMBLE.
>> WITH ROCK BOTTOM KINGS,
YOU'LL FEEL YOU'RE IN THE GAME.
THE GAME OF YOUR FRIEND VERSUS
HIS HORRIBLE DEMONS.
>> BUT AGAIN, ADDICTION IS A
REAL PROBLEM.
>> WE TAKE IT VERY SERIOUSLY.
>> THAT'S WHY ALL THESE GAMBLING
ADS ARE FULL OF CASH, GOLD,
FIREWORKS, AND FLAMES EXPLODING
EVERYWHERE.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT A LOSER.
YOUR FRIEND IS.
>> THEY SAY THE HOUSE ALWAYS
WINS.
WELL, NOW YOU'RE THE HOUSE, AND
YOUR FRIEND IS PROBABLY GOING TO
LOSE HIS.
>> DOES IT SEEM A LITTLE CRUEL
TO BET ON YOUR FRIEND'S
DEVASTATING ADDICTION?
SURE.
BUT IT'S ALSO HILARIOUS.
>> SO HOWEVER YOUR FRIEND
BOTTOMS OUT, MAKE SURE YOU CASH
OUT AT ROCK BOTTOM KINGS.
>> DOWNLOAD ROCK BOTTOM KINGS
TODAY.
BECAUSE GAMBLING IS SERIOUS.
SERIOUSLY AWESOME.
>> ROCK BOTTOM KINGS.
HE'S THE ONE WITH THE PROBLEM.
ENGINE NEXT
MEETING.
>> LET'S MAKE SOME NOISE!
>> OKAY.
LET'S START WITH WORKPLACE
RELATIONSHIPS.
GENERALLY, WE DISCOURAGE IT.
BUT OF COURSE, IT HAPPENS.
SO WE HAVE A FEW RULES.
>> YOU CAN ASK A CO-WORKER OUT
ONCE, BUT IF THEY SAY NO, YOU
CANNOT ASK THEM AGAIN.
>> SO WAIT, QUESTION.
I CAN ASK ANYONE OUT ONE TIME?
>> I GUESS TECHNICALLY, YES.
>> SWEET.
LAUREL, WILL YOU GO OUT WITH ME?
>> NO.
>> SO THAT'S IT, THEN?
LIKE, THAT DOOR IS CLOSED UNTIL
IT RESETS AT THE END OF THE
YEAR?
>> NO.
IT DOESN'T RESET.
>> OKAY.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
I CAN'T ASK LAUREL OUT AGAIN,
WHICH MEANS I HAVE TO MOVE ON TO
MY SECOND CHOICE, CARLEY.
WILL YOU GO OUT WITH ME?
>> DON'T LOVE THAT YOU CALLED ME
YOUR SECOND CHOICE, BUT SURE.
>> SEE, THIS IS INTERESTING.
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO GO OUT
WITH CARLEY.
SO CAN I TAKE THAT YES, BANK IT,
AND USE IT ON LAUREL?
>> THERE'S NO BANKING IT.
IT'S NOT A GAME SHOW.
>> EXCUSE ME.
I HAVE A QUERY.
>> OKAY, ERIC, WHAT IS IT?
>> ARE WE ALLOWED TO ASK WOMEN
IF THEY ARE TICKLISH?
>> NO.
>> OH, SO YOU SAID I CAN JUST GO
AHEAD AND TRY?
TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE!
>> ERIC, CUT YOUR NAILS.
>> NO!
>> ANOTHER QUESTION.
SO WE ALL KNOW CLARK IS GAY,
RIGHT?
>> NO, ONLY TOLD YOU.
>> NOW THAT WE ALL KNOW CLARK IS
GAY --
WHICH I'M PERSONALLY FINE WITH.
BUT SINCE CLARK IS NEVER GOING
TO ASK A WOMAN OUT DUE TO HIS
CONDITION --
DOES THAT MEAN I CAN BUY CLARK'S
ASKS?
>> SURE, 20 BUCKS A POP.
>> GREAT.
HERE'S -- IT'S LIKE $1,500.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE SO MUCH CASH
ON YOU?
>> I GO TO THE STRIP CLUB AT
LUNCH.
>> THAT'S WHERE I KNOW YOU FROM.
>> YOU GUYS WORK TOGETHER.
>> LAUREL, I LOVE YOU, I THINK
YOU'RE SMOKING HOT, WOULD YOU GO
OUT WITH ME?
>> STILL, NO.
>> BACK TO SILVER.
CARLEY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS, BUT YES.
>> SEE, THAT'S WHAT I DON'T LIKE
ABOUT YOU.
YOU WANT IT TOO MUCH.
OKAY.
I'M JUST GOING TO BANK CARLEY'S
YES, IS THAT COOL WITH
EVERYBODY?
>> YEAH.
>> WORKS FOR ME.
>> NO.
NO BANKING YESES.
>> WE HAVE A QUERY.
>> WHY ARE YOU ALL USING THE
WORD "QUERY"?
>> ME AND ROBERT HAVE BEEN
SECRETLY HOOKING UP FOR FIVE
MONTHS.
IS IT BAD THAT I'M HIS DIRECT
SUPERIOR?
>> YES, THAT'S OBVIOUSLY BAD.
>> UH-HUH, DOES IT HELP THAT I'M
JUST DOING IT TO GET A RAISE?
>> THAT DOES NOT HELP, NO.
>> OKAY, WE'RE JUST GOING TO GO
AHEAD AND WRAP THIS UP.
>> WAIT.
CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
I LEARNED SOMETHING IMPORTANT
TODAY.
AN OFFICE IS A SACRED PLACE.
AND OFFICE RELATIONSHIPS ARE
TOUGH.
BUT YOU CAN ONLY ASK SOMEONE OUT
ONCE.
IF THEY SAY NO, THAT'S IT.
>> THAT'S LITERALLY THE ONLY
THING WE'VE COVERED TODAY.
>> HERE'S SOMETHING YOU DIDN'T
COVER.
YOU CAN BANK YESES, AND THEY
ROLL OVER EVERY YEAR.
>> AND OVER TIME, THEY ACCRUE
INTEREST.
>> AND YOU CAN TRADE IN YOUR
CHRISTMAS BONUS FOR 20 NEW ASKS.
>> AND BOOTY KHAKIS ARE OKAY.
>> NO, THEY ARE NOT.
>> THAT WAS NEVER OKAY.
>> NEVER.
>>> 30-YEAR-OLD GORDON DWYER
JUST COULDN'T CATCH A BREAK.
NOT AT WORK.
>> DWYER!
>> NOT IN LOVE.
AND ESPECIALLY NOT ON THE COURT.
>> GORDON FOR THREE!
>> NICE SHOT, IDIOT.
>> WHY AM I SUCH A LOSER?
>> BUT THAT'S ALL ABOUT TO
CHANGE.
>> GORDON, THOUGHT YOU COULD USE
THESE.
DONALD J. TRUMP?
WHOA!
TRUMP "NEVER SURRENDER"
SNEAKERS?
AWESOME!
I'M OPEN.
>> AND GORDON DWYER'S ABOUT TO
FIND OUT THAT WINNING --
>> COME ON, MAN, HOW'D YOU MISS
THAT?
>> IS A STATE OF MIND.
>> I DIDN'T MISS.
IT WENT IN.
>> OH.
ALL RIGHT.
>> FROM NEWSMAX STUDIOS AND THE
WRITER OF "LIKE MIKE" COMES
ANOTHER MOON CALL SNEAKER MOVIE
FOR WHITE PEOPLE.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THESE TRUMP
SHOES MADE YOU GOOD AT
BASKETBALL?
>> NO.
THEY GAVE ME THE POWER TO SAY
I'M GOOD AT BASKETBALL.
THEN DOUBLE DOWN ON THAT UNTIL
PEOPLE ACTUALLY START TO BELIEVE
IT.
>> NOW HE GETS WHATEVER HE
WANTS.
>> MR. MITCHELL.
EVERYBODY'S SAYING I SHOULD HAVE
YOUR OFFICE BECAUSE MY CUBICLE'S
A DISASTER RIGHT NOW.
>> CAN I HAVE A MINUTE TO GATHER
MY THINGS?
>> BYE-BYE.
>> HE GETS WHOEVER HE WANTS.
>> WOW.
THAT WAS THE MOST FANTASTIC
LOVE-MAKING YOU'VE EVER HAD.
>> NOT REALLY, IT ONLY LASTED --
>> TWO HOURS, THAT WAS A
TWO-HOUR LOVE SESSION, YOU HAD A
BIG "O," YOU HAD A VERY BIG "O"
THERE.
>> I DID?
WANT TO GO AGAIN?
>> I'D LOVE TO BUT YOU'RE TOO
TIRED.
>> HE IS WHATEVER HE SAYS HE IS.
>> EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME.
IT'S 170.
>> NOW HE'S A BRAND-NEW MAN.
AND PEOPLE ARE NOTICING.
>> NICE SHOES.
BUT YOU KNOW, IN MANY WAYS, THE
REAL MAGIC HAS BEEN INSIDE OF
YOU ALL ALONG.
>> WRONG.
IT COMES FROM THE SHOES, AND
YOU'RE COMING OFF AS VERY
STUPID, AND FRANKLY, QUITE RUDE,
WALKING IN HERE LIKE THIS.
>> MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
IN TERMS OF BASKETBALL MOVIE
PASTICHE, AND WITH REGARD TO
SHOES I THINK WE'VE DONE A
WONDERFUL --
>> WHITE MEN CAN TRUMP.
>> OH, YOU GOT NEW SHOES TOO?
>> YEAH.
AIR BIDENS.
NOW PASS ME THE ROCK.
HERE WE GO.
OH-OH!
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING FOX.
AT 9, IT'S THE NEWS.
AT 10, THE SCARY NEWS.
FIRST, IT'S "THE FLOOR" HOSTED
BY ROB LOWE.
>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M ROB LOWE, AND WELCOME TO
THE FLOOR.
TONIGHT, CONTESTANTS WILL TRY TO
ELIMINATE THEIR COMPETITORS AND
EXPAND THEIR TERRITORY ON THE
FLOOR BY IDENTIFYING AS MANY
PHOTOS AS THEY CAN BEFORE TIME
RUNS OUT.
BEFORE THE BREAK, DEFENDING
CHAMPION DAVID --
>> WHAT UP?
>> WAS CHALLENGED BY NEWCOMER
ALLEN --
>> PUMPED TO BE HERE.
>> WELCOME, ALLEN.
THE FIRST CATEGORY TONIGHT IS
DRINKS.
I'LL SHOW YOU A PICTURE OF A
DRINK, YOU TELL ME WHAT IT IS.
>> NO SWEAT.
>> EASY.
>> WELL, ALLEN, IT'S YOUR FIRST
TIME UP HERE.
WHEN THAT CLOCK STARTS TICKING,
PEOPLE SOMETIMES LOSE THEIR
COOL.
>> NO, NO, I WORKED IN
RESTAURANTS MY WHOLE LIFE.
I KNOW PRESSURE, AND I KNOW
DRINKS.
I GOT THIS.
>> WE'LL SEE.
DAVID, HOW ARE YOU AT DRINKS?
>> WELL, MY WIFE IS PREGNANT, SO
I HAVE BEEN DRINKING FOR TWO.
>> OKAY.
THEN LET'S DUEL!
>> ORANGE JUICE.
>> OH -- WHITE WATER.
ORANGE JUICE BUT WHITE.
BIG GLASS OF PAINT.
CLAM CHOWDER NO CLAM.
BOOB WATER.
LIQUID TEETH.
PAPER JUICE.
TITTY WATER.
MAN MAYONNAISE.
I KNOW WHAT THIS IS, IT COMES
OUT OF A COW.
LIQUID COCAINE.
>> DUDE.
>> IT'S MERCK, FINAL ANSWER
MERCK.
>> GREAT TRY, ALLEN, BUT YOU RAN
OUT OF TIME.
WHAT WENT WRONG?
>> I DON'T KNOW, THE CLOCK
STARTED AND I JUST FROZE LIKE A
GLASS OF MILK.
OH.
THAT'S WHAT THAT WAS.
THANK YOU.
>> DAVID.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN YOU SAW
ORANGE JUICE?
>> I THOUGHT, THAT'S ORANGE
JUICE.
>> INCREDIBLE.
WELL, IT'S TIME FOR A NEW
CHALLENGER, AND THAT'S SUSAN
FROM KINGSTON.
>> READY TO PLAY.
>> THIS CATEGORY IS "FAMOUS
FIGURES."
THESE ARE INFLUENTIAL PEOPLE
LIVING OR DEAD.
>> OKAY, BIT OF A HISTORY BUFF,
SO FEELING PRETTY GOOD.
>> WELL, WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
OH -- ABRAHAM LINCOLN.
>> THAT'S FDR.
>> MARGARET THATCHER.
>> PASS.
UH, PASS.
OH -- I LOVE HER -- PASS.
I'M SORRY, I KNOW THEM, I'M
NERVOUS.
PASS.
I KNOW THEM ALL.
MY BRAIN'S NOT -- PASS.
HUGE FAN.
PASS.
GO, WARRIORS.
PASS ON THAT.
UH --
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHO OPRAH IS?
>> OF COURSE I KNOW WHO OPRAH
IS, I'M JUST AFRAID TO GET IT
WRONG ON TV.
PASS.
CLEVELAND.
>> WAIT.
CLEVELAND IS A HISTORICAL
FIGURE?
>> YES.
HE WAS THE FIRST AFRICAN
AMERICAN CAST MEMBER ON "FAMILY
GUY."
DAVID, YOU ONLY GOT ONE RIGHT
BUT IT WAS MY FAVORITE.
WE'RE SAYING GOOD-BYE TO SUSAN
AND HELLO TO OLIVIA.
>> HELLO.
>> OH, HI.
DID YOU SEE THAT LAST ROUND?
>> I SAW ALL OF THAT, YES.
>> I KNEW THE PEOPLE, I JUST --
DIDN'T WANT TO LOOK STUPID.
>> WELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE NEXT CATEGORY IS A TOUGH
ONE.
IT'S "FAMOUS ART OR ARTISTS."
OLIVIA SAYS YOU'RE AN ART
HISTORIAN?
>> I AM.
>> DAVID, HOW ARE YOU WITH ART?
>> I DID KNOW THE PEOPLE ON
THERE.
>> OKAY.
YOU'LL SEE A PAINTING, TELL US
THE TITLE.
>> WE GONNA DIE!
PASS.
HO ON A HALF SHELL.
SHE FARTED.
PASS.
GAY STUFF.
>> SEE?
IT'S HARD.
>> BE QUIET.
PASS.
I DON'T KNOW.
COVID HOOKUP?
PASS.
J.K. SIMMONS AND CYNTHIA NIXON.
OH -- OH -- THE MERCK MAID,
SHE'S SPILLING ALL HER MERCK.
PASS.
MR. PENIS.
DR. PENIS.
PASS.
>> OH, I KNOW HIM, THAT IS
BASQUIAT.
THE ARTIST.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> HEY!
>> NO, NO, THAT'S THE WEEKND.
>> OH, SURE, YEAH, IT WAS THE
WEEKND FOR SURE, I GOT THAT
WRONG.
♪♪
♪ WOAH WOAH WOAH
WANT IT ALL
I WON'T LEAVE A BREADCRUMB ♪
♪ WHAT I THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING
THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ ALL WE KNOW IS
RIDIN' IN THE BACK
IT'S A MAY'
IT'S A MAY' ♪
♪ 32 SHOTS IN THE K
IN THE K ♪
♪ MARATHON
I REALLY RUN THE A
RUN THE A ♪
♪ YOU SAY YOU TOUCHED ME
HOW SWAY?
HOW SWAY? ♪
♪ GRAVEYARD THAT'S WHERE
THEM BOYS STAY
ALL STAY
♪ HYPNOTIZE
THEY DO WHAT I SAY
WHAT I SAY ♪
♪ 21 BOY DON'T PLAY
DON'T PLAY ♪
♪ MY GLOCK GEN5 SAID HEY
SAID HEY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHOPPER EVERYWHERE
THAT'S BAE
THAT'S BAE ♪
♪ GET THAT BOY
UP OUT THE CAR
YOU'RE GIVIN' TRADE
GIVING TRADE ♪
♪ WE BEEN SPINNIN'
THROUGH THEY HOOD ALL DAY
ALL DAY ♪
♪ IF SAY THEY OUTSIDE
OKAY OKAY
I CAN'T LET A GIRL PLAY ME
NO WAY NO WAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE A DUCK
IF YOU BELIEVE WHAT GIRLS SAY
WHAT GIRLS SAY ♪
♪ SHE GOT WAY MORE BODIES
THAN MY OLD K OLD K ♪
MY LIL' BROTHER
BEAT HIS BODY OJ OJ ♪
♪ TALKIN' 'BOUT THEY LIT
ON THE FLAME
THAT LIL' BOY A MASCOT
HE AIN'T GANG ♪
♪ WATCH A HALF A MILLION
DOLLARS AND IT'S PLAIN ♪
♪ I DON'T GO THROUGH TSA
TO GET ON PLANES ♪
♪ YOU GET -- WITHOUT --
THEN YOU LAME
SHE KNEW I WAS LEAVIN'
'FORE I EVEN CAME ♪
♪ TWO REVOLVERS ON MY WAIST
JOHN WAYNE
SMACK BOYS THEN I GET ON LIVE
AND SING YEAH ♪
♪ WANT IT ALL
I WON'T LEAVE A BREADCRUMB ♪
♪ WHAT I THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING
THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ ALL WE KNOW IS
HOW MANY GOT THE BELT?
A LOT ♪
♪ CATCH 'EM AT THE LIGHT
HE GET NAILED POP
911 SOMEBODY HELP ♪
♪ SUB-TWEETING
BAD FOR YOUR HEALTH ♪
♪ I'M A GANGSTER
I AIN'T TAKIN' NOTHIN' BACK
I'LL NEVER DO NO SONG
WITH NO RAT ♪
♪ PUT A LEGO IN A STICK
IT RAT-A-TAT
I DON'T WANNA TALK
GO AND CATCH A HAT ♪
♪ BIG DRACO COME UP
OUT THAT SCAT 21
HE STOOD ON BUSINESS
NOW HE LAYIN' ON HIS BACK ♪
♪ ASK AROUND I BE RAPPIN'
NOTHIN' BUT FACTS ♪
♪ WE THE REASON
ALL THESE BOYS
RUNNIN' TRACK ♪
♪ YOU AIN'T NEVER STEPPED
YOU CAN'T TELL ME A THING
I GOT BIG KAHUNAS
AND I'M LETTIN' 'EM HANG ♪
♪ KEEP MY MOUTH CLOSED
AND THAT'S NEVER
GONNA CHANGE ♪
♪ YOU GET IN THE JAM
AND GO TO POINTIN'
AND BLAME ♪
♪ I AIN'T LET IT SLIDE
I WAS SHARPENIN' AIM
SMOKING ON MY BROTHERS GOT HIS
LEFT SLAIN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW IT'S SMOKE
'CAUSE THEY AIN'T EVEN
TAKE OFF HIS CHAIN ♪
♪ SAY IT'S UP WITH ME
YOUR ASS MUST DO COCAINE ♪
♪ WANT IT ALL
I WON'T LEAVE A BREADCRUMB ♪
♪ WHAT I THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING
THOUGHT SOMEBODY
SAID SOMETHING ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ G BLOCK
ALL WE KNOW IS REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM
REDRUM REDRUM ♪
♪ YEAH ALL WE KNOW IS ♪♪
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> JUST HOURS AGO, DONALD TRUMP
WON THE SOUTH CAROLINA PRIMARY,
WHICH MEANS THAT TRUMP IS NOW
UNDEFEATED.
EVERYWHERE EXCEPT COURT.
TRUMP HAS BASICALLY LOCKED UP
THE NOMINATION AND HE'S CLEARLY
ALREADY PIVOTING TO THE GENERAL
ELECTION WITH A MORE MODERATE,
UNIFYING TONE.
>> NOVEMBER 5th WILL BE OUR NEW
LIBERATION DAY BUT WITH THE
LIARS AND CHEATERS AND
FRAUDSTERS AND CENSORS AND
IMPOSTERS WHO HAVE COMMANDEERED
OUR GOVERNMENT, IT WILL BE THEIR
JUDGMENT DAY.
THEIR JUDGMENT DAY.
>> NOW, WHERE DID I HEAR THAT
BEFORE?
OH, RIGHT.
>>> POLITICAL EXPERTS SAY THAT
NIKKI HALEY COULD HAVE BEEN
HELPED BY BLACK VOTERS IN SOUTH
CAROLINA, BUT THEY HAVE LONG
DISLIKED HER.
THIS MOSTLY DUE TO A PHENOMENON
KNOWN AS "BITCH TOO SKINNY."
NIKKI HALEY INSISTED THAT SHE'S
NOT STAYING IN THE RACE TO BE
DONALD TRUMP'S RUNNING MATE,
SAYING, "I FEEL NO NEED TO KISS
THE RING."
WHILE TIM SCOTT SAID HE'LL SUCK
THAT RING RIGHT OFF TRUMP'S
FINGER.
>>> THE ALABAMA SUPREME COURT
RULED THAT EMBRYOS CREATED
THROUGH IVF ARE CHILDREN AND
THAT BLACK EMBRYOS CAN BE TRIED
AS ADULTS.
>> COLIN.
>> IT'S CRAZY THAT THEY'RE
SAYING EMBRYOS ARE THE SAME AS
CHILDREN.
IF YOU THINK AN EMBRYO IS THE
SAME AS A BABY, TRY TELLING YOUR
WIFE, "HEY, HONEY, I LEFT OUR
BABY IN THE FREEZER."
EVEN DONALD TRUMP THINKS THIS
DECISION GOES TOO FAR.
HE CAME OUT STRONGLY IN FAVOR OF
IVF, SAYING THIS.
>> I STRONGLY SUPPORT THE
AVAILABILITY OF IVF FOR COUPLES
WHO ARE TRYING TO HAVE A
PRECIOUS LITTLE BEAUTIFUL BABY.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, HE HAD ME RIGHT UNTIL
THE END WHEN HE SAID "LITTLE
BABY" LIKE HE WAS
RUMPELSTILTSKIN.
"I MUST HAVE THEIR BEAUTIFUL,"
LITTLE, DELICIOUS BABIES."
TRUMP'S ALSO LIKE
RUMPELSTILTSKIN IS IN THAT HE
CLEARLY WOVE HIS OWN HAIR OUT OF
STRAW.
>> DONALD TRUMP ANNOUNCED HE IS
SELLING LIMITED-EDITION GOLD
SNEAKERS FOR $400.
YOU CAN CHECK THEM OUT ON THE
FEET OF THE GUY GETTING DRAGGED
OFF YOUR FLIGHT.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT
PRESIDENT BIDEN'S CAMPAIGN ENDED
ITS JANUARY FUND-RAISING WITH
$56 MILLION IN THE BANK.
NOW, IF HE CAN ONLY REMEMBER HIS
ATM CODE.
>>> WHILE BOARDING AIR FORCE ONE
THIS WEEK, BIDEN NARROWLY
AVOIDED TRIPPING AND FALLING ON
THE STAIRS AGAIN AND INSTEAD DID
A FORWARD ROLL BEFORE INVITING
EVERYONE INSIDE THE CHOCOLATE
FACTORY.
>>> THIS WEEK THE ALABAMA
SUPREME COURT RULED A FROZEN
EMBRYO IS A HUMAN BEING.
HERE TO COMMENT IS A FROZEN
EMBRYO FROM ALABAMA.
>> HI, THERE, COLIN.
SO FUN TO BE HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY.
>> WOW.
YOUR ACCENT'S KIND OF ALL OVER
THE PLACE, MAN.
>> YEAH, I GUESS I NEVER TALKED
BEFORE, BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A
MOUTH OR THROAT OR LUNGS.
>> RIGHT.
DO YOU KNOW WHO YOUR PARENTS
ARE?
>> NO, COLIN.
BUT BASED ON MY ACCENT AND SIZE,
I'M GOING TO GUESS SOFIA VERGARA
AND AN OOMPA LOOMPA.
>> YEAH.
WELL, I HAVE TO ASK.
AS AN EMBRYO, DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE A FULL HUMAN LIFE?
>> DOES THIS LOOK LIKE A LIFE TO
YOU, COLIN?
I'M LIVING AT NEGATIVE 200
DEGREES IN LIQUID NITROGEN,
FREEZING MY NONEXISTENT NUTS
NIPPLES OFF.
I DON'T GOT A BRAIN, I DON'T GOT
A HEART.
I'M LIKE TOM SANDOVAL.
>> SO YOU WATCH "VANDERPUMP
RULES"?
>> OF COURSE NOT.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE EYES.
EVEN WITHOUT EYES I CAN SEE
TOM'S A PURE NARCISSIST.
I'M JUST HAPPY TO BE OUT THE
FREEZER, COLIN.
THE FREEZER'S LIKE PRISON.
NO NAMES, ONLY NUMBERS.
ONCE I SAW THEM PUT MY BEST
FRIEND INTO SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT.
>> WOW, LIKE A JAIL CELL?
>> A WOMB.
NINE MONTHS THEY HAD HIM IN
THERE EATING OUT OF A TUBE.
THEN THEY TRANSFERRED HIM TO
REAL JAIL, ALABAMA.
GETS ME UPSET JUST THINKING
ABOUT IT, I'M SORRY, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO -- I NEED THAT.
>> DID YOU JUST POP A ZIN IN
YOUR MOUTH?
>> I DON'T HAVE A MOUTH, COLIN.
BUT YES, I'VE BEEN DOING A
COUPLE OF ZINS A DAY.
MAYBE 20 MAX.
ALL THE EMBRYOS ARE DOING IT.
SURE, IT MIGHT BE BAD FOR ME.
BUT WHEN THAT ZIN HITS --
>> YOU FEEL LIKE A GOD, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
LOOK, COLIN.
I DON'T KNOW WHY SOCIETY'S
TRYING TO MAKE ME GROW UP SO
FAST.
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE A HUMAN?
CAN'T I JUST BE AN EMBRYO FOR A
WHILE?
THERE'S SO MUCH I STILL WANT TO
DO.
LIKE MAYBE I'LL DIVIDE IN TWO
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED A TWIN.
I THINK HE'D BE DELICIOUS.
>> SO YOU THINK THE
ALABAMA SUPREME COURT WENT TOO
FAR?
>> I'M SURPRISED THEY STOPPED AT
EMBRYOS.
WHY NOT SAY SPERM ARE PEOPLE
TOO?
PUT SOME CAUTION TAPE AROUND THE
WASHCLOTH IN MICHAEL CHE'S
DRESSING ROOM.
THAT'S A CRIME SCENE, BROTHER,
>> I DON'T USE A WASHCLOTH, I
USE A DISHRAG.
>> EWW.
IT USED TO BE A DISHRAG.
NOW YOU CAN CUT A LOAF OF STALE
BREAD WITH IT.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING, I'M
NOT FULLY FORMED.
I'M JUST LIKE YOU, MAN.
I'M A PERSON WITH NO DISCERNIBLE
TALENTS, JUST A GENERIC WHITE
BLOB.
>> AND JUST LIKE YOU, COLIN, I
DON'T FEEL ANYTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL.
WATCH.
SLAP ME, COLIN.
>> I'M NOT SLAPPING YOU.
>> SLAP ME.
OH!
THERE'S A MONSTER WITHIN YOU,
AND NOW EVERYONE HAS SEEN IT.
THIS JUST IN.
COLIN JOST ASSAULTS AN EMBRYO.
JUST WAIT TILL ALABAMA HEARS
ABOUT THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU NEED TO LEAVE,
FROZEN EMBRYO.
BY THE WAY, HOW DID YOU EVEN GET
TO NEW YORK?
>> THE WAY ALL BODILY FLUIDS
TRAVEL.
SOAKED INTO THE SEATS OF A MEGA
BUS.
>> A FROZEN EMBRYO, EVERYONE.
>> ROLL TIDE, BABY!
>>> SCIENTISTS ARE CONCERNED
THAT ZOMBIE DEER DISEASE COULD
SPREAD TO HUMANS, SO PLEASE WEAR
A CONDOM.
MORE OF A WARNING THAN A JOKE.
>>> BOEING ANNOUNCED THAT THE
HEAD OF THEIR TROUBLED 737 MAX
PROGRAM IS LEAVING THE COMPANY
AFTER HE WAS SUCKED OUT OF AN
EMERGENCY EXIT.
>>> NEXT THURSDAY IS LEAP DAY,
WHICH MEANS WE'VE GOT TO WAIT
TILL FRIDAY FOR IT TO FINALLY BE
OVER.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT WOMEN
BENEFIT FROM REGULAR EXERCISE AT
TWICE THE RATE OF MEN.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, JARS.
>>> THE STARS OF THE 1968
VERSION OF "ROMEO AND JULIET"
ARE SUING PARAMOUNT TO STOP THE
DIGITAL RELEASE OF THEIR MOVIE,
WHICH INCLUDES NUDE SHOTS OF
THEM AS TEENAGERS.
PARAMOUNT HAS AGREED TO LOCK IT
AWAY WHERE NO ONE WILL EVER SEE
IT.
PARAMOUNT PLUS.
>>> RED LOBSTER IS CELEBRATING
ITS ANNUAL LOBSTER FEST BY
OFFERING 150 PEOPLE A TWO-HOUR
ENDLESS LOBSTER EXPERIENCE WHERE
YOU CAN TAKE A LOBSTER INTO A
PRIVATE ROOM AND DO ANYTHING YOU
WANT TO IT.
>>> AN 84-YEAR-OLD WOMAN FROM
CANADA IS ATTEMPTING TO JOIN THE
WNBA, AND EARLY SCOUTING REPORTS
SAY SHE CAN REALLY MOP THE COURT
WITH HER LONG-ASS TITTIES.
>>> NEW YORK CITY POLICE ARE
TRYING TO DETERMINE THE OWNER OF
A HUMAN LEG FOUND ABANDONED ON A
BRONX SUBWAY TRACK.
THE TOP THEORY SO FAR BEING THE
GUY YELLING "AAHHH!"
>> REALLY GOOD ACTOR.
>> THANKS.
>>> NEXT WEEK MARKS THE
BEGINNING OF WOMEN'S HISTORY
MONTH.
HERE TO COMMENT IS LEGENDARY
WRITER, TRUMAN CAPOTE.
>> WELL, ISN'T THIS NICE.
>> HI, TRUMAN.
IT'S AN HONOR TO HAVE YOU.
I'M SURPRISED YOU'RE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT WOMEN'S HISTORY
MONTH.
>> WHY?
I LOVE WOMEN.
THEY'RE WHAT DOLLS ARE BASED ON.
>> RIGHT, YEAH.
I'M WATCHING THE NEW SEASON OF
FEUD ABOUT HOW YOU BETRAYED
YOUR FEMALE FRIENDS BY WRITING
MEAN THINGS ABOUT THEM.
>> I DIDN'T BETRAY THEM, I
SIMPLY PUBLISHED WHAT THEY TOLD
ME IN CONFIDENCE.
WE WERE FRIENDS.
I CALLED THEM MY SWANS.
>> RIGHT, YEAH.
WHY DID YOU CALL THEM YOUR
SWANS?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL,
MEAN, AND HELLA WHITE.
>> RIGHT.
>> ANYWAY, I'M HERE TO TALK
ABOUT SOME OF MY FAVORITE WOMEN
FROM HISTORY.
WILL YOU LET ME DO THAT, COLIN?
>> SURE, TRUMAN, OF COURSE.
>> THANK YOU.
STARTING WITH AMELIA EARHART.
THE GREAT BUTCH OF THE SKY.
TRUE, LOOK AT THAT HAT.
YOU KNOW, SHE WAS SO BRAVE.
SUCH AN INNOVATOR.
TERRIBLE WHAT HAPPENED TO HER.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S THE REASON WHY
WE DON'T HAVE FEMALE PILOTS.
>> WAIT, WE DO HAVE FEMALE
PILOTS.
>> WELL, WE SHOULDN'T.
NEXT IS BETSY ROSS.
HM, BETSY, LOOK AT THAT HAT.
SHE'S SUCH AN IMPORTANT PART OF
THE COUNTRY.
POOR THING.
THERE WERE ONLY 13 STAR STARS ON
THE FLAG BECAUSE THAT'S AS HIGH
AS SHE COULD COUNT.
>> TRUMAN.
>> SHE WAS DRUNK THE WHOLE TIME.
SHE WAS TRYING TO MAKE A HAT.
>> YOU SAID YOU LIKE WOMEN.
>> OF COURSE I DO.
THERE IS NOTHING MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN A WOMAN.
EXCEPT THE ASS OF A MAN.
>> RIGHT.
>> CHE AGREES.
>> YEAH.
>> NEXT!
FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE.
FLORENCE, LOOK AT THAT HAT.
I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT SHE'S THE REASON EVERY NURSE
IS A WOMAN.
>> NOT ALL NURSES ARE WOMEN.
>> THEY SHOULD BE.
>> TRUMAN, YOU'RE JUST LYING.
>> AREN'T I ALLOWED TO SPIN A
YARD FROM TIME TO TIME, COLIN?
LIKE THE FRENCH SAY.
>> SORRY, WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> I SAID, WOMEN ARE LIKE
KOMBUCHA.
THEY'RE FULL OF LEAST, AND
THEY'RE TECHNICALLY ALIVE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, COLIN, I LOVE
WOMEN BUT THEY DON'T LOVE ME
BACK, AWW.
>> MAYBE BECAUSE IT'S YOU SAY
MEAN THINGS TO THEM.
>> THEY'RE THE ONES WHO ARE MEAN
TO ME.
ONE WOMAN CALLED ME A NASTY HOMO
THE OTHER DAY.
>> OH MY GOD, THAT'S AWFUL.
>> ALL BECAUSE I CALLED HER A
BITCH WHILE I WAS BJ'ing HER
HUSBAND.
>> OKAY -- WELL, THERE YOU GO.
I MEAN --
>> LET'S DO ANOTHER WOMAN,
COLIN.
ELEANOR ROOSEVELT.
SHE PUSHED FDR DOWN THE STAIRS.
KICKED HIM WITH HER BIG LESBIAN
FEET.
>> TRUMAN, STOP.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT SACAGAWEA?
SHE LIED TO THOSE GUYS.
SHE KNEW WHERE THE GOLD WAS.
>> GOLD, WHAT GOLD?
YOU'RE JUST MAKING UP THESE
TERRIBLE STORIES.
DO YOU LIKE WOMEN AT ALL?
>> OH, PLEASE, COLIN.
NO ONE LOVES WOMEN LIKE A GAY
MAN -- WHO HATES WOMEN.
I'VE HAD FUN.
AREN'T YOU GLORIA VANDERBILT'S
SON?
>> NO, THAT'S ANDERSON COOPER.
>> OH.
WHY THE HELL AM I HERE?
>> TRUMAN CAPOTE, EVERYONE.
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT HAT.
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M
COLIN JOST.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE.
GOOD NIGHT.
WHETHER OR NOT!
OH, AND LOOK WHO JUST WALKED IN.
MR. POPULAR HIMSELF, RICKY
MONROE.
>> YEP, THE KING IS BACK IN THE
CASTLE.
FASHIONABLY LATE AS EVER.
>> REUNION AWARDS ARE COMING UP,
SO STICK AROUND, Y'ALL.
>> RICKY FREAKING MONROE.
>> OH, NO, IS THAT CALEB AND
RANDLE?
GET OVER HERE, BOYS.
BABE, I PLAYED FOOTBALL WITH
THESE GUYS.
>> HA HA HA!
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> DON'T MATTER.
>> HOW THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
I HEARD YOU MOVED TO THE BIG
CITY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
TALLAHASSEE, FLORIDA.
LEFT THE DAY AFTER GRADUATION
AND NEVER LOOKED BACK.
I OWN THE THIRD-BEST NIGHTCLUB
THERE.
AS YOU CAN SEE BY THE THREADS,
BUSINESS IS GOOD.
WAIT, NO WAY.
IS THAT FORREST GUMP?
WONDER WHAT THAT IDIOT'S BEEN UP
TO SINCE HIGH SCHOOL.
>> FORREST GUMP?
HONESTLY, KIND OF A LOT.
>> YEAH.
LEARNING TO TIE HIS SHOES?
GODDAMN, HE WAS DUMB.
YOU GUYS REMEMBER WE USED TO
CHASE HIM AROUND IN MY TRUCK AND
THROW ROCKS AT HIM?
THOSE ARE SOME OF MY BEST
MEMORIES.
>> REALLY?
KIND OF ASHAMED OF THAT.
>> WHY?
I BET THAT GUY STILL LIVES AT
HOME WITH HIS MAMA.
REMEMBER HE WAS ALWAYS SAYING
THAT?
"MAMA SAYS LIFE IS A CHOCOLATE"
BAR," WHATEVER.
>> YOU SERIOUSLY HAVEN'T HEARD
ABOUT ALL HIS ADVENTURES?
>> ADVENTURES?
IF ANYONE FROM THIS TOWN HAS HAD
ADVENTURES, IT'S ME.
ONE NIGHT AT MY CLUB, I DID
COCAINE WITH DANNY DEVITO.
>> ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL, LET'S GIVE
OUT SOME REUNION AWARDS.
THE AWARD FOR MOST STYLISH GOES
TO -- RICKY MONROE.
>> HEY!
HEY!
BOOM, BABY!
LET'S BE HONEST, I HAD THIS ONE
IN THE BAG.
THANKS, Y'ALL.
>> AND OUR NEXT AWARD IS MOST
SUCCESSFUL.
>> OH-OH.
LOOKS LIKE IT MIGHT BE A CLEAN
TONIGHT FOR ME.
>> THE WINNER, OF COURSE, IS
FORREST GUMP.
>> THANKS, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> MOST SUCCESSFUL?
NO, THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
>> CONGRATS, FORREST, ON
EVERYTHING YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED,
FROM YOUR PURPLE HEART, YOUR
PING-PONG CAREER, OF COURSE
BUBBA GUMP SHRIMP WHICH HAS MADE
YOU GREENBOW'S FIRST BILLIONAIRE
ALUMNI.
>> DID YOU SAY BILLIONAIRE?
>> I DID.
>> GUMP, YOU HAVE A BILLION
DOLLARS?
>> I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
MONEY, BUT THAT NICE MAN AT THE
BANK SAID I'M PROBABLY WORTH
MORE LIKE 1.3.
>> THAT'S COOL.
I HAVE TWO JET SKIS, WHATEVER.
>> SO FORREST, DO YOU WANT TO
SAY ANYTHING?
>> YEAH.
I'D LIKE TO DEDICATE THIS AWARD
TO MAMA.
>> WHO'S ALSO HIS DATE, HA HA!
>> MAMA'S IN HEAVEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, SORRY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> I ALSO WANT TO DEDICATE THIS
TO MY VERY BEST FRIEND IN THE
WHOLE WORLD, BUBBA.
>> WHO COULDN'T BE HERE TONIGHT
BECAUSE HE'S IMAGINARY.
HA HA!
>> NO, HE COULDN'T BE HERE
BECAUSE HE DIED IN VIETNAM.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I DIDN'T -- WELL -- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR HIS SERVICE.
>> AND OF COURSE, MY VERY BEST
GIRL, JENNY.
>> NO.
HOT JENNY?
YOU LOCKED THAT DOWN?
OH, I GOT TO GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THAT.
HOT JENNY, GIRL, WHERE YOU AT?
>> SHE'S IN HEAVEN WITH MAMA.
>> SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS.
DO YOU HAVE ANY FRIENDS THAT
AREN'T DEAD?
>> LIEUTENANT DAN!
>> WHERE'S HE AT?
STAND UP, MAN.
>> HE CAN'T.
HE AIN'T GOT NO LEGS.
>> GODDAMMIT.
WHATEVER.
YOU WON, GUMP.
>> OKAY, THANK YOU, FORREST.
AND FIND ME LATER BECAUSE I WANT
TO HEAR ALL ABOUT THE TIME YOU
MET JOHN LENNON.
>> I DID COCAINE WITH DANNY
DEVITO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AWESOME.
OKAY.
RICKY, DON'T GO ANYWHERE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE WON AGAIN.
OUR LAST TROPHY, THE "PEAKED IN
HIGH SCHOOL" AWARD.
>> HEY, HEY!
PEAKED IN HIGH SCHOOL AND STILL
GOING UP, YAH!
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT "PEAKED"
MEANS.
>> DOESN'T MATTER.
WAIT, GUMP, WHAT THE HELL YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
>> ME AND YOUR WIFE IS LIKE PEAS
AND CARROTS.
YOU COME HOME, GO ONLINE, ORDER
A SEX DOLL.
WHEN SHE SHOWS UP YOU'RE LIKE,
WHOA, SHE'S WAY OUT OF MY
LEAGUE.
THAT'S WHY I GOT FUGLIANA.
>> FUGLIANA.
>> INTRODUCING FUGLIANA, THE
AVERAGE-LOOKING SEX DOLL FOR
BELOW-AVERAGE-LOOKING MEN.
SHE MAY NOT BE THE DOLL YOU
WANT, BUT HONEY, SHE'S THE DOLL
YOU DESERVE.
>> IT'S TRUE.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
I'M 36 BUT LOOK 52.
MY OLD SEX DOLL WAS MUCH HOTTER
THAN ME.
I'D GET NERVOUS AND COULDN'T
PERFORM.
IN THE BEDROOM.
BUT THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM WITH
FUGLIANA.
LOOK AT HER.
SHE'S NOT INTIMIDATING.
SHE'S GOT THE PAUL GIAMATTI EYE
THING FROM "THE HOLDOVERS."
>> FUGLIANA.
>> SHE CAN DO A VARIETY OF
POSITIONS IN THE BEDROOM.
LIKE MISSIONARY.
MISSIONARY.
AND MISSIONARY.
DON'T WORRY, GUYS.
SHE'S FLEXIBLE.
CHECK IT OUT.
SHE COULD ALMOST PUT HER LEG
BEHIND HER HEAD.
ALL RIGHT, CLOSE ENOUGH.
FUGLIANA COMES IN ALL DIFFERENT
STYLES.
LET'S GET THAT LEG DOWN.
DON'T TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
WHY DON'T WE HEAR FROM SOME OF
OUR OTHER SATISFIED CUSTOMERS?
>> MY OLD SEX DOLL LOOKED LIKE A
WOMAN YOU'D HAVE TO WINE AND
DINE.
BUT FUGLIANA IS THE KIND OF GIRL
THAT WILL "S" YOUR "D" FOR AIR
FRYER DINO NUGGETS AND SOME
LIMEADE IN A SHREK CUP.
THANK YOU, FUGLIANA.
>> WHEN I TOOK MY OLD SEX -- NOT
RIGHT NOW, FUGLIANA.
WHEN I TOOK MY OLD SEX DOLL TO A
RESTAURANT, PEOPLE WOULD STARE.
NOW PEOPLE STILL STARE.
BECAUSE I'M HAVING DINNER WITH A
PLASTIC WOMAN.
>> HER FACE CAN MAKE OVER 200
EXPRESSIONS BASED ON MY ACTIONS.
WHEN I TELL HER MY IDEA FOR A
PODCAST.
WHEN I SHOW HER MY PENIS.
PLUS SHE COMES FULLY LOADED WITH
INGROWN HAIRS.
LOOSE ASPIRIN.
SLEEP APNEA.
AND BAD BREATH.
LET'S CLOSE THAT MOUTH UP.
FUGLIANA EVEN TALKS.
PULL THIS CORD AND HEAR HER SAY
ONE OF HER EXTREMELY REALISTIC
CATCHPHRASES.
>> LET'S MAKE THIS QUICK, THAT
SUSHI IS ABOUT TO MAKE ME PAINT
YOUR TANK.
>> SHE EVEN DOES DIRTY TALK LIKE
JODIE FOSTER FROM "TRUE
DETECTIVE."
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S THE SPOT.
WE FOUND 'EM, BOYS.
CASE CLOSED.
>> OH, FUGLIANA, GIRL, YOU'RE
TRIPPING.
LET'S HEAR ANOTHER GLOWING
CUSTOMER REVIEW.
>> WHAT I LOVE ABOUT FUGLIANA IS
I CAN IMAGINE HER ACTUALLY BEING
INTO ME.
A GUY WHO RECENTLY GOT FIRED
FROM CHIPOTLE FOR PLAYING WITH
THE GUAC LIKE IT'S SLIME.
>> FUGLIANA.
>> GET YOURSELF A FUGLIANA
TODAY.
SHE'S NOT JUST A SEX DOLL, SHE'S
MY BEST FRIEND.
>> DUDE, THAT'S PATHETIC.
>> AHH!
>> FUGLIANA.
THE SEX DOLL YOU DESERVE.
CUZ YOU BUSTED.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, 21 SAVAGE.
♪♪
♪ LACE FRONT MESSED UP
YOU SHOULD'VE
WORE YOUR BONNET ♪
♪ RUNNIN' FROM ME
RUNNIN' FROM ME
RUNNIN' FROM ME ♪
♪ DROP THE LO' I'M COMIN'
I ALREADY KNOW
IT'S RUNNIN' FOR ME ♪
♪ GIRL IT'S TRULY A BLESSIN'
YOU CAN MAKE ALL THE MESS
THAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ AND THAT'S ALL THAT I WANT
IS FOR YOU TO RUN
RUNNIN' LIKE A FAUCET ♪
♪♪
♪ I'M POURIN' UP WOCKY
IN GREECE
I CAME A LONG WAY
FROM THE EAST ♪
♪ SHE LEAVIN' HER --
ON THE SHEETS
MY BROTHER SAY
HE WANTS A NIECE ♪
♪ WHEN I'M WITH YOU
IT'S A SAFE SPACE
BABY YOU'RE BRINGIN' ME
PEACE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW HOW IT GETS
IN THE STREETS
AIN'T NONE OF IT SHALLOW
IT'S DEEP ♪
♪ YEAH I WANNA CUDDLE
FOR WEEKS ♪
♪ YOUR MAMA'N 'EM
THINK THAT YOU INNOCENT
I KNOW YOU TURN
INTO A FREAK ♪
♪ DON'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT YOUR EXES ♪
♪ WHATEVER IT IS
IT COULD BE
THEY'RE PLAYIN'
I'M MAKING 'EM SEE ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU SWINGIN'
ON THEM LIKE THE D ♪
♪ I HAD TO COMB OUT
THE DREADS
SHE FELL IN LOVE
WITH THE BRAIDS ♪
♪ GUTTER GIRL
SHE COOK AND CLEAN
AND SHE'LL LOAD UP THE Ks ♪
♪ YOUR BODY GOT ME IN A DAZE
IT DON'T MATTER THE LOOK
YOU GET SLAYED ♪
♪ HER FACE CARD
NEVER DECLINE
FORGET ALL THAT MAKEUP
YOU FINE ♪
♪ BETTER TELL ALL THEM BOYS
YOU MINE
SHE A DOLLAR
WAY MORE THAN A DIME ♪
♪ WHEN I'M WITH YOU
I GET NERVOUS
IT GOTTA BE LOVE
IT'S A SIGN ♪
♪ YEAH I DON'T CARE
WHERE WE'RE GOIN'
I'M RIDIN' ♪
♪ FORGET WHAT YOU
BRING TO THE TABLE
'CAUSE BAE YOU'RE THE TABLE
I'M EATIN' LET'S DINE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU'RE MY BABY
YOU KNOW YOU'RE MY TWIN ♪
♪ IF THEY DISRESPECT ME
THEN IT'S COMIN' TO AN END
IF THEY TRY TO PLAY WITH ME
WE KNOW THAT YOU GON' SIN ♪
♪ BABY IF ONLY YOU KNEW
HOW MUCH I DO LOVE YOU
HOW MUCH I DO TRUST YOU ♪
♪ I PRAY THESE --
DON'T MAKE ME
HAVE TO PROVE IT ♪
♪ YOU NEED SOMEBODY
TO MOLD YOU
YOU NEED SOMEBODY
TO HOLD YOU
♪ HE A LIL' BOY
AND I TOLD YOU ♪
♪ WHY YOU KEEP LOOKIN'
FOR CLOSURE?
HIT ELIANTTE AND FROZE HER ♪
♪ NOW YOU A BEAR POLAR
PLAY WITH HER CAT DOJA
THROW THAT -- BACK
LIKE YOU 'POSED TO ♪
♪ TRUST ME
I'M TAKIN' IT EASY ♪
I REALLY WANNA GET NEEKY ♪
♪ YOU ACTIN' SHY
BUT YOU FREAKY ♪
I WANT A PIECE NO REESE
♪ SHE SAYIN'
BAE COME MEET ME
AT THE SALON
I'M ON PEACHTREE ♪
♪ SHE KNOW I'M PULLIN' UP BP
TEN PRESIDENTIALS NO D.C
SHE LOVE LOUIS AND CC
NO 2K I GOT VC ♪
♪ GRAB ON THAT --
WHEN SHE GREET ME
I HEARD OF YOUR MAN
HE SWEET TEA ♪
♪ YOU CUFFED ME
DON'T EVER RELEASE ME ♪
♪ TALK ABOUT ME
IN YOUR STORIES
BAE SUB-TWEET ME ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU'RE MY BABY
YOU KNOW YOU'RE MY TWIN ♪
♪ IF THEY DISRESPECT ME
THEN IT'S COMIN' TO AN END
IF THEY TRY TO PLAY WITH ME
WE KNOW THAT YOU GON' SIN ♪
♪ BABY IF ONLY YOU KNEW
HOW MUCH I DO LOVE YOU
HOW MUCH I DO TRUST YOU ♪
♪ I PRAY THESE --
DON'T MAKE ME
HAVE TO PROVE IT ♪
♪ YOU ARE
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
I DEDICATE
I DEDICATE IT ALL TO YOU ♪
>> COOL, BUT WHAT DO YOU USE FOR
MUSIC?
>> USE MY ALEXA.
I ASK IT TO PLAY STUFF AND IT
SOUNDS GREAT.
>> OH MY GOD, YOU HAVE AN ALEXA?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
IT LISTENS TO EVERYTHING YOU
SAY.
>> OH, DUDE, FOR REAL?
>> YEAH, YOU THINK THAT THING'S
OFF BUT IT'S ALWAYS ON.
NOTHING IS PRIVATE.
>> OH, COME ON, IT'S NOT
LISTENING.
>> IT TOTALLY IS.
I SWEAR.
EVEN IF IT'S NOT, YOUR PHONE IS
LISTENING.
YOUR TV.
ANYTHING THAT'S ONLINE.
>> YEP, IT'S TRUE.
I HAD AN APPLE HOME POD.
WHEN ME AND TERESA WERE TALKING
ABOUT A TRIP TO THE CAYMAN
ISLANDS, MY COMPUTER STARTED
SENDING ME EMAILS FOR HOTELS
THERE.
IT WAS FREAKY.
>> EVERYONE GETS HOTELS' EMAILS.
>> OKAY, FINE.
LET'S TRY SOMETHING.
KENNY, LOOK AT YOUR GMAIL.
SAID AD IN THE LITTLE CORNER ON
THE RIGHT?
>> YEAH, IT SAYS -- IT'S AN AD
FOR A FORD F-150 ELECTRIC TRUCK.
THAT'S JUST -- OH MY GOD.
>> WAIT, WHAT?
>> MY GIRLFRIEND AND I WERE
TALKING ABOUT THIS YESTERDAY.
I TOLD HER I MIGHT WANT TO GET
ONE.
>> OH, WHOA.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> SEE?
>> THAT'S A COINCIDENCE.
EVERYONE GETS TRUCK ADS.
>> FINE, BRENT.
WHY DON'T YOU CHECK YOUR GMAIL?
>> MAYBE I WILL.
OKAY.
SEE, THIS IS DUMB.
THESE THINGS ARE ALWAYS WRONG.
LISTEN TO THIS.
WHY IS THERE AN AD HERE FOR A
GREEN BAY PACKERS BUTT PLUG?
WHAT EVEN IS THAT?
"SHOW YOUR PACKERS PRIDE WITH"
THIS 10-SPEED ANAL PLUG FOR
THE ADVENTUROUS CHEESEHEAD IN
YOUR LIFE.
THIS IS SO STUPID.
WHY WOULD IT SEND ME THIS?
>> BRENT, YOU'RE WEARING A GREEN
BAY PACKERS SHIRT.
>> YEAH, SO?
I'M FROM WISCONSIN.
LOOK AT THIS THING.
"INDUSTRIAL STRENGTH AND"
WATERPROOF."
WATERPROOF?
LIKE I'M GOING TO USE IT IN MY
JACUZZI?
>> YOU DO HAVE A HOT TUB, RIGHT?
>> I HAVE A JACUZZI.
BUT WHY WOULD I USE IT IN THERE?
SO I CAN SQUAT BACK AGAINST THE
SIDE AND LET THE JETS VIBRATE
AGAINST IT?
WHO DOES THAT?
GUYS, I SWEAR I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THIS IS.
>> COME ON, BRENT.
YOU MUST HAVE AT LEAST JOKED
ABOUT IT.
>> NO, NEVER.
WHY I WOULD JOKE ABOUT SOME
GREEN BAY PACKERS BUTT PLUG THAT
PLAYS THE PACKERS FIGHT SONG
WHILE IT'S INSIDE YOU?
THEN WHEN YOU OPEN YOUR MOUTH,
IT SUDDENLY GETS LOUDER?
WHAT'S EVEN FUNNY ABOUT THAT?
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> IT GETS A LITTLE LOUDER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THIS THING JUST POPPED UP.
I MEAN, MAYBE MY WIFE WAS USING
MY PHONE.
SHE STEALS IT ALL THE TIME TO
PLAY WORDLE.
MAYBE SHE HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THIS.
>> YOUR WIFE, JENNIFER, THE
METHODIST MINISTER, WAS TALKING
ABOUT GREEN BAY PACKERS SEX
TOYS?
>> YEAH, AS A GOOF.
MAYBE SHE WANTED TO WALK INTO
OUR BEDROOM ONE NIGHT WITH A
LITTLE SMILE ON HER FACE AND I'D
BE LIKE, THAT'S WEIRD, DO YOU
HEAR "GO, PACK, GO" PLAYING?
THEN SHE WOULD OPEN HER MOUTH,
AND IT WOULD SUDDENLY GET
LOUDER.
WE WOULD LAUGH SO DAMN HARD.
THEN WE'D GET IN THE JACUZZI --
>> WAIT, SHE WANTED TO DO THAT?
>> THAT IS SUCH A SPECIFIC
SCENARIO.
>> I DON'T KNOW, LOOK.
IT'S JUST ONE STUPID AD ON MY
PHONE.
THERE'S PLENTY OF OTHERS.
SEE, ALL OF THIS HAS NONE TO DO
WITH ME.
LOOK AT THAT.
HAIR RESTORATION.
"CONSTANCE WU AUTOGRAPH"
MEMORABILIA.
BELLY FAT SUPERBURNER.
"GREEN BAY PACKERS PACK-ON"
STRAP-ON.
"CONSTANCE WU PUBLIC APPEARANCE"
CALENDAR."
IT'S A BUDGE OF RANDOM CRAP.
>> WAIT, WHAT IS THAT
WEIRD-LOOKING APP ON YOUR PHONE?
>> DON'T PRESS THAT ONE,
DON'T --
♪♪
>> WAIT.
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
>> THAT'S "GO, PACK, GO," RIGHT?
BRENT, DO YOU HEAR THAT?
BRENT?
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
>> BRENT.
OPEN YOUR MOUTH, BRENT.
OPEN MOUTH.
♪♪
>> PACKERS PRIDE!
THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
THIS MEANS A LOT TO ME TO BE
HERE, I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.