-All right, are you listening?
Okay.
-I think I'll start
with "Open the effing Strait,
you crazy bastards,
or you'll be living in hell."
And then at the end,
maybe throw in
"Praise be to Allah."
-You think I should type,
"Praise be to Allah"?
And that's from...
that's from you,
the president of
the United States?
-Yes, yes, Allah.
They say, "Allah."
It's a sarcastic attack on
the world's largest religion.
They famously have a great sense
of humor
about that kind of stuff.
-As your press secretary,
this puts me
in a tough position, sir.
-Oh, don't worry
about that, Karoline.
Like I said to Pam Bondi
and Kristi Noem right
before I fired them,
"You're doing a terrific job!"
-Thank you, sir.
I love you, too.
-All three of those
were played by Ashley.
It's an interesting detail.
There are a lot
of important things
happening
in the world right now,
and I have to make some
urgent phone calls.
-Hello?
-Tiger? It's Donald.
What's going on, buddy?
Are you playing in the Masters
this weekend?
-Uh, no, sir.
I don't know if you'll
remember,
but I, uh,
flipped my car and got a DUI.
-Oh, right, a "Dewey,"
as in "Do he drive on pills?
Yes, he do."
-That's a good one,
Mr. President.
-You should have
told the cops we were friends.
He would have let you off.
-Well, I did, and they didn't.
-Ah! If only
there was something
I could have done to help.
Oh, well!
Want to play some golf?
-I'm actually
at a rehab facility
in Switzerland at the moment.
-Oh, and how's
the course there?
-Oh, well, actually,
there's no golf.
You see,
I don't know why...
-Okay. Who else?
Oh, wait. Who is this?
I don't recognize the number.
Hello?
-Hello, Donald.
-Melania? You're calling me?
That's not a good sign.
-Listen.
I decided I should do
a big, random speech
completely out of nowhere
and say I am not Epstein victim.
Is that good?
-Uh, darling, I gotta admit,
that sounds a little insane.
Who are you? Me?
-Well, it's not just Epstein.
I thought I could also say
I, Melania Trump,
in no way helped out the Gilgo Beach
serial killer.
That way, no one is suspicious.
-Darling, I think
that's gonna make
everyone way more suspicious.
-Okay, okay.
What if I announce
I barely
partied with Diddy?
Would that help?
-You know, Melania,
I'd really love to talk more,
but I have a meeting
with, uh, Ronald Reagan.
Let's see.
Anything else I'm forgetting?
There's gotta be something.
Oh, right. The war.
-What?!
-Pete, it's President Trump.
Wassup?!
-Wassup?!
Remember that in the '90s?
-Sorry, Mr. President.
I didn't know it was you.
It just said unknown caller.
So I figured I'd just answer and
say a couple military secrets.
-That's wonderful.
That's great.
So, what's the latest
on that whole thing
we're doing in Iran?
-Well, rest assured, sir,
Iran is as obliterated
as me
every Saturday night,
allegedly.
We destroyed everything.
We wet their willies,
tapped their sacs, and purpled
every single nurple.
You also probably heard that I
want to start a draft again,
which is a great sign
for the ceasefire.
Yeah, except this time we're
fighting millennial cringe
by letting 40-year-olds
join the military.
Yeah, put that finger mustache
to work pulling a trigger.
-Really good. Really good.
That's great. That one
for sure hits with me.
-But, sir, you know,
I gotta ask.
Is it true what I heard?
Are you actually negotiating
with these Herbs?
-You know what? Don't worry
about the negotiations.
I just heard they're
going really, really bad.
I sent in my secret weapon,
J.D. Vance.
After those Iranians spent
20 hours talking to J.D.,
they said, "Please, sir,
just go back to bombing us."
-Yeah. Very good, sir.
Even hearing about
someone getting bombed
just got me hard as hell.
-That's great. That's great.
I'm bricked, as well.
All right, well, keep up
the good work, Pete.
And hey, if you think
of a good reason why
we went to war,
could you let me know?
-Well, you know, honestly,
sir, if I were you,
I'd probably just tell them,
"We did it all for the nookie."
-What?
-The nookie!
-Come on.
-So we can take that oil
and stick it in our cars.
Stick it in our cars!
-Cars!
$7 a gallon. Hegseth, out.
-And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Colman Domingo.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much.
I am so excited to be here
hosting "Saturday Night Live."
Now, I have been
an actor since the '90s,
so you may be sitting
here thinking,
"Where do I know him from?"
And it's probably because
I've been in a lot
of different things.
You know,
"Fear the Walking Dead,"
"Four Seasons,"
"Lincoln," "Sing Sing."
I was Carly in "iCarly."
I was inside C-3PO's suit
in "Star Wars."
And I am also your uncle.
See, here's me at your
cousin's wedding in 1994.
The point is,
I'm practically in everything,
like raisins
at a Caucasian cookout.
And I love how I can
always guess
what people know me from.
You know, if you're
a Latin bro, I'm like,
"Oh, 'Fear the Walking Dead.'"
But if it's a girl under 20
or a creepy dude over 30,
that's "Euphoria."
So, sure, I'm an actor,
but what I'm most known for
is
when you come to my house,
the vibes are spectacular.
And tonight, I'm going to make
you feel like
you're at my house.
So, let's get a vibe going.
Music. I said vibe,
and that just happened.
How about the lights?
Let's get some lighting
that's extremely flattering
for
people of color.
Much better.
Leon and I look great.
Right, Leon?
Now for the camera.
Can I get a sexy,
slow push on this?
Also, I'm 56,
so boom the hell up.
There it is!
Look how adorable I am now.
My word.
And this works for everybody.
Jeremy, get out here.
-Hi.
-Now, Jeremy,
look into that camera.
-Okay.
-He looks fine.
No offense, but boom up.
-It almost worked.
Well, the vibe is getting
really good, really good.
But is it sexy enough?
Nowadays...
So let's see how the vibe
is working for our guests.
Oh! Hey, ma'am,
what brings you here tonight?
-Uh, I got tickets from someone
who works here.
-Oh. Inside connection.
That's hot.
I like the vibe.
Was it someone in the cast?
-No, it was a writer.
-Don't tell people that.
Wow! The vibes down here
are on point.
But looks like I made them
too good
because those people
are making out.
Ooh. They're straight.
You don't see that every day.
Well, everybody,
I think we kind of did it.
I think we nailed the vibe.
So, let's wrap this up, baby.
At my house, I always
end the party the same way,
by telling everybody
to get the hell out
so I can take a fiber pill
and go to bed.
But not tonight, babies,
'cause we got a show to do.
So, boom up.
We've got
a great show for you tonight.
Anitta's here,
so stick around
and we'll be right back.
-Good evening.
I'm Wesley Welch,
and you're watching
"New York 1."
Coming up,
it's almost summer.
We've got five spots
where you can experience
that famous NYC hot-urine smell
for yourself.
But first, our top story.
A bank robbery occurred
in the Fashion District
earlier today.
Our own Amy Asher is
live on the scene. Amy?
-Thank you, Wes. It was
around noon that the sounds of gunfire
erupted outside of
a bank here on 26th Street.
Miraculously,
nobody was injured,
but bystanders were shaken,
including this group
of students and faculty
from the Fashion Institute
of Design next door.
Let's speak to them
and their teacher,
D'Artagnan Meringue.
-I don't teach. I show.
I am the lesson.
-Got it. Now, can you
describe the suspect?
-I would say 30, 32 maybe?
-So, fairly young?
-No, not in age, honey.
Waist and inseam.
What else could I have
been referring to?
-I apologize.
Uh, could you describe
his clothing?
-Yes. Boho derogatory.
-Could you be more specific?
-Why? He sure as hell wasn't.
-Speak on it!
Listen, listen.
Give me that mic.
The look was all over the place
and baggy to a fault.
My man was swimming
in that fit.
-Swimming? Try drowning.
-Who was that?
-Oh, that's Tully Point,
the dean.
Who else could it have been?
-Okay, so I
really want to give our viewers
as clear
a description
of the suspect as possible.
-Be on the lookout for a mess!
-Again, I'm not
really understanding.
-Excuse you. I was not
done speaking.
Class, help this woman describe
the man's drip. Delaney?
-The fit must have been
in the unemployment line
because
it was not working.
-Good! Roscoe?
-The fit was giving
style by Stevie...
Stevie Wonder.
-Yes. Yes. Yes. Gabby?
-He had, like, a hoodie
and, like --
-Gabby, you are not
cut out for this!
Go to a normal college.
Look. The clothes
were a disaster,
but the accessories ate down.
-The accessories?
-His gun, woman!
What else could I have been
talking about?
-Oh. You're getting
smoke in my face.
-You're getting your face
in my smoke!
"Antyway," the gun was a
tasteful matte-black color.
-That he paired with
a brown belt
in spring.
Oh, no, baby.
Unalive yourself.
-Okay, a brown belt.
That's a good detail.
Any more specifics
on the color of his clothing?
-The colors flirted
with boldness
but couldn't get her in bed.
-Yes, Delaney. Roscoe?
-The colors were a statement.
And that statement was
"Mama raised a dumbass."
-Yes, Roscoe! Gabby?
-His jeans were,
like, dark blue.
-Gabby! Drop out!
I beg you.
Go back to Connecticut.
-But I like fashion.
-You have no future
in this industry.
None. Zilch.
"I like fashion."
Well, I like pornography,
but I do it as a hobby,
not a career.
-Okay, okay.
Can you please just describe
the suspect in a normal way?
-No!
But I snapped a photo of
the crime being committed.
-Oh, please show that.
There.
The crime of the century.
If you're going to be
sockless in Crocs,
invest in some lotion.
His heels were drier
than saltines.
In fact, when the police
asked which way he went,
I said, "Follow that
trail of Parmesan."
-Okay. All right, all right.
Enough. Let's just
forget the clothes.
-Believe me. I'm trying.
-Authorities have urged
the public to remain vigilant
as the suspect
is still at large.
-Try extra large.
-Stop! Stop crossing
my frame.
Jesus Christ.
If you have any information
on the suspect,
please contact police.
-And I hope the police do
to him what he should have
done to those raggedy-ass jeans.
Cuff 'em!
-More as the story develops.
Wes?
-Thanks, Amy.
I learned a lot from this story.
You know, hoping that maybe
now that I stepped up my drip,
you might reconsider my offer?
-Your offer to be friends
but hook up when
your wife's out of town?
Yeah. My answer is still no.
Reconsider, honey.
You could do worse,
but you won't do better.
-Okay,
what is your problem with me?
-Everything!
Everything. Your hair...
-After I got divorced,
I hit rock bottom.
-I was depressed.
I lost my confidence.
I just wasn't myself.
-And as a man, therapy never
seemed like a real option.
-Plus, there's no way
I could afford that now.
-But then I found out
about Uneek Kutz.
-Black barbershops is a
radically new alternative
to mental-health treatment for
white guys without the stigma.
-At first, I didn't
know what to make of it,
but they welcomed me right in.
-Well, sit your goofy ass down,
man.
-You bet.
-It doesn't matter who you were
before you walked in,
because the brothers
at Uneek Kutz
allow you to have
a fresh, new start.
-Oh, look at him. He look
like that boy. What's his name?
-Dahmer.
-That's right.
We gonna call you
Jeffrey Dahmer.
-I don't know.
-Shut your Jeffrey Dahmer-
looking ass up, boy.
-Look at all this baby hair.
-I've always had
a hard time opening up
and talking
about my feelings,
but they made it easy.
It's like they were
reading my mind.
-Little Epstein over here
say his wife just left him.
-My name is David.
-Little Epstein,
if you want to get
your wife back,
you need to start hitting it
right.
Get you a honey pack,
a couple of coconut waters,
and wear that ass out.
-I know that's right.
-Yeah. Just start clapping
them clappers,
like, clap, clap, clap.
-We were having some intimacy
issues in the bedroom.
It was really hard for me to
communicate my needs to Tara.
But then my barber said...
-Cheat!
-What?
Can't do that.
-What? You gay or something?
-What? No.
-And now our sex life
is thriving.
He's even lifting his leg up
like clap, clap, clap, clap,
clap, clap, clap, clap.
-Traditional therapy
can cost hundreds of dollars
an hour,
but the homies at Uneek
only charge 50 bucks,
and I can stay there all day,
even do some shopping.
-Yeah, that's 100% sea moss.
My girl makes it right
out of the ocean.
Cures Covid and eczema.
-It forces you to come out
of your comfort zone
and make some hard choices.
-It's a simple question, bro.
-I don't know what
you want me to say!
-Just answer
the damn question, Epstein.
Who would you rather clap?
Pam or Gina?
-I told you,
I don't know who
those ladies are!
-Oh!
-Come on, man.
-Boy!
-And no matter how
bad things may seem,
my dogs can always put things
back in perspective for me.
My two littles are
starting private school,
so I have to pay for that.
-Uh-huh.
-And then Sheila
wants a new kitchen.
-Word.
-I'm in a real pickle.
--Oh, my God.
-Yeah. Look like Lil Terry
done got shot again.
-"No Legs" Terry?
-Yeah.
-I thought he was in jail.
-Yeah, he came home
about a week ago.
Somebody said he
caught his wife
in the bed with a pastor
or something.
-Anyway, uh, Dahmer,
you were telling me
about your little pickle?
-Yeah, it's -- it's nothing.
-Man, we just wanted a spot
where brothers could kick back,
talk a little mess,
and get our drink on.
Plus, when you look good,
you feel good.
And that's what it's all about.
A man wanna feel good.
-I love it.
-All right, guys,
have a good night.
-See you next week, Epstein.
-Oh, by the way, fellas?
I'd smash Pam all day.
-Black barbershops -- get
your mental health lined up.
-On Friday,
the four crew members
of NASA's Artemis 2 mission
returned to Earth safely
after an historic 10-day trip
around the Moon.
During the mission, the crew
recorded a series of video logs.
This one was filmed on day nine.
-Hi, there.
This is Artemis 2
pilot Victor Glover.
We're on day nine of ten,
and we're almost home.
Speaking of home, if you
look out our window here,
you'll see a familiar sight...
Earth.
Seeing our pretty planet
like this
is pretty profound.
Being a man of faith,
this has certainly
brought me closer to God.
Oh, come on, guys!
You got to Velcro
your snacks to the wall.
Whose Pringles are those?
Whose?
-Oh, those are mine now.
-No, those are my Pringles.
-No, no. Finders keepers,
you loser!
-No! Give them to me now!
-No, dude.
Okay, fine.
Here, you can have them.
Just kidding.
-No, dude!
-Hey, hey.
I'm recording
a thoughtful video.
Can you guys stop
messing around, please?
-I'm sorry, Victor. It's just...
It's day nine, and we're
just kind of bored, okay?
Bye.
Canada slaps!
-Okay, there's a quote
from legendary Apollo
astronaut Jim Lovell
that I'd like to read.
"We do not realize
what we have on Earth
until we leave it."
Let me tell you.
Those words have very
different right now.
Hey, guys.
Christina fell asleep
unvelcroed again.
Someone stick her ass
to the wall, please!
Seeing Earth out the window,
this beautiful blue ball
in a sea of darkness,
really gives one pause.
-I'm so sorry, Victor.
We have to get this on camera.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is no-hands hat.
-You're not going
to believe this, Victor!
-Oh, oh, oh.
-No-hands hat!
-Oh!
-Oh! Oh!
-No-hands hat!
-Victor! I did it, Victor!
You proud of us?
-Reid, Hansen,
what are you doing?
-We're doing experiments,
Victor.
-Okay. Was breaking the toilet
an experiment, too?
-I'm sorry about the toilet,
Victor.
The toilet doesn't
make any sense.
-Go away.
Let me lock in.
-Okay. Sorry, but before
we go, check this out, Victor.
Check this out.
Watch this. Watch this.
-Victor! Victor, look at it!
-All right, all right.
I'd like to read another quote
from another great astronaut,
Sally Ride.
"Looking back at Earth
from orbit makes you realize
how fragile
our existence truly is."
Oh, my God,
are you guys serious?
You fools drew on poor
Christina's face?
Two grown men turning
our mission specialist
into Harry Potter.
Shame on you.
Sorry about that, folks.
When you see Earth like this,
it makes you realize how
lucky we are to live here.
-Um, so I just sneezed,
and this happened?
I mean, this is totally
happening right now.
-Okay. That's kind of amazing.
-Yeah, right?
-Make sure you get
a picture of that.
-Oh, I will, I will.
-Hey, Victor, my pee-pee is
stuck in the tube again.
I don't know what to do because
my pee-pee's stuck in it again.
You gotta get it off me, Victor,
please.
-I don't know. Figure it out.
I'm doing my video.
-Help me figure it out, Victor.
My pee-pee! Please, Victor.
-All right.
I'm gonna make this quick
because
folks are going space crazy.
My one hope for everyone
on Earth is this.
-Whoo!
I'm pulling him by his dong!
-Okay, screw it.
Video over.
Everyone, be kind
to each other.
The end.
-You're watching PBS.
At 5:00, "Masterpiece Theater"
presents
"Bleak House: Mother's Sad."
But now a rerun
of the cult classic
"The Knowledge Hour"
with Henry Debris.
-Hello, there.
I'm Henry Debris.
What if I told you there are
more trees on earth than stars
in the Milky Way?
What if I told you that
a magnitude-12 earthquake
would split the world in two?
Or what if I told you
this table is a man?
How cool was that?
I love stuff like that.
Thank you to our props
department for indulging me.
It just goes to show not
everything is as it seems.
Admire this simple
piece of coral.
Now, what if I told you
it's a seahorse?
Surprised?
What if I told you a cloud
can weigh over 1 million pounds?
What if I told you
this clock is a man?
I mean, this clock.
God, it gets me every time.
I think it's awesome.
It's just awesome.
Never gets old.
Speaking of old, did you know
our pupils get smaller
as we age?
So do our sweat glands.
What if I told you the atoms
inside you
are a billion years old?
What if I told you
these books are a man?
the fire is my niece?
And that this
simple vase is none other than
City Councilman
Keith Hawkins?
Wait a minute.
Hello? Hello?
Oh, my God. Where's Keith?
This is just a vase.
Now I look like an idiot.
Now I look like
I don't know Keith Hawkins.
Samuel?
-I'm sorry, Mr. Debris.
The councilman was called away
on city business.
-Oh, damn it. Well, you should
have told me. Damn it!
I'm so mad, I can hit you over
the head with this potted plant.
Oh, that's a man.
When I want it to be an object,
it's a man. And vice versa.
Well, that's rich.
That's really, really rich.
-Okay. Everyone out.
Oh!
What if I told you I really
wanted this to go well?
What if I told you
someone special is watching?
A girl I knew in college?
What if I told you she was hot?
Lily. Oh, we were young.
-Mr. Debris! Mr. Debris!
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I was at the zoo.
One of the polar bears
ate a kid.
I should specify a baby goat.
It was his food.
He was supposed to.
-It doesn't matter, Councilman.
I'm ending the show.
I blew the whole
budget trying
to impress some chick
from 40 years ago.
I'm pathetic.
-What if I told you...
you're not?
-What?
-What if I told you
you're a great man
who gets a kick out
of good, old-fashioned
American surprise?
No one could love
a man like that.
-What if I told you I could?
I'm no Lily, but I'm here,
dressed up like a vase
with flowers on my head
because two weeks ago,
I had a sexual dream about us
that blew up my marriage.
I'm not perfect, and I
don't know if I'm gay,
but I'd like to get married
and find out.
-What if I told you...yes?
And what if I told you
that painting is
an ordained minister?
-Good evening. I now pronounce
you husband and vase.
-Ladies and gentlemen, Anitta.
Choka Choka
-d Acelerada, no se comporta d
d Lo que puedan pensar ya
no le importa d
d Todas salieron a romper
la calle d
d Esto no va a parar hasta
que estalle d
d Choca, choca, cuerpo
con cuerpo, boca con boca d
d Tao pequenininha,
mas pode te dar uma volta d
d Cai na toca, cai na toca,
toca da cabocla d
d Obsesionao, todos ilusionao d
d Tu le dices "hola,"
ella te responde "chao" d
d Oh, wow, la rompe demasiado d
d Los hombres que se alisten
aunque no esten invitados d
d Acelerada, nao se comporta d
d E milionaria e ja tu nao
importa d
d Se eles sairam pra curtir
o baile d
d Ela foi encontrar
vossa majestade d
d Choca, choca, cuerpo con
cuerpo, boca con boca d
d Tao pequenininha,
mas pode te dar uma volta d
d Cai na toca, cai na toca,
toca da cabocla d
d Descontrolado,
esse lobo ta animado d
d Vai com a Shaki e fica
todo empolgado d
d Oh, wow, e loba e e mulher d
d E nao fica contente ate ter o
que ela quer d
d Viver, deixando
pra tras o passado d
d Viver sem lei,
fazendo sempre o que quiser d
d Choca, choca, cuerpo con
cuerpo, boca con boca d
d Tao pequenininha,
mas pode te dar uma volta d
d Cai na toca, cai na toca,
toca da cabocla d
d Choca, choca, choca, choca,
choca, choca, choca, choca d
toca da cabocla d
-It's "Weekend Update" with
Colin Jost and Michael Che.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone.
-Welcome to "Weekend Update."
I'm Michael Che.
-I'm Colin Jost.
Today the United States held
peace negotiations with Iran.
But then, just an hour ago,
President Trump posted,
"If Iran doesn't agree to peace,
the greatest military
of all time, ours,
will "f" Iran right up
their Strait of Hormuz.
Asalam alaykum,
you crazy bastards."
Now, I completely made that up.
But isn't it kind
of disturbing
that you all totally believed
that he had posted that?
President Trump did
genuinely issue a post
threatening to destroy
Iran's entire civilization
and then ended with the
phrase "praise be to Allah."
And I know that
almost makes Trump sound
like he is a radical terrorist.
But remember,
Trump has already been
to a paradise with 72 virgins.
-There is growing confusion
over whether
Israel being allowed
to continue bombing Lebanon
was part of the ceasefire
with Iran.
Ultimately, that decision
comes down to the man
controlling our military,
Benjamin Netanyahu.
Earlier tonight, J.D. Vance
announced that the U.S.
and Iran
have ended
negotiations without a deal
after talking
for 21 hours straight.
And, guys, I think
they're done for real,
based on how his
mascara's running.
-Before the talks fell apart,
President Trump warned Iran
about making any more demands, saying,
"The Iranians
don't seem to
realize they have no cards."
They're literally
holding a "straight."
J.D. Vance was asked...
J.D. Vance was asked about
Iran's right to enrich uranium,
and he made kind of
a weird analogy. Watch.
-My wife has
the right to skydive,
but she doesn't jump out
of an airplane because she
and I have an agreement
that she's not going to
do that
because I don't
want my wife jumping
out of an airplane.
-What the hell are you
talking about?
The only thing
that makes sense
in that entire analogy
is that
we can all understand
J.D. Vance's wife
having the urge to jump.
-First Lady Melania Trump made
a rare public statement
to deny reports that
Jeffrey Epstein introduced her
to Donald Trump
because they actually
met when Trump
cracked open
her shipping container.
On Friday, the Artemis 2
astronauts returned safely
from their 10-day trip around
a Hollywood soundstage.
-During the mission, the crew
of Artemis 2 sent back pictures
of the rarely seen
dark side of the moon,
revealing that the moon
has a rat tail.
He wanted more out of that.
The Justice...
The Justice Department
has formed a task force
intended to eradicate
anti-Christian bias,
which hopefully
works better than
the church's strategy
of molesting it out of you.
-California police have
arrested a man
who allegedly threw a Molotov cocktail
at the home of
ChatGPT founder Sam Altman,
after ChatGPT told him,
"That's a great idea!"
-Yesterday, Kamala Harris
said she is thinking
about running
for president again,
and I like her chances
as long as she finally
grows that penis.
Health Sec...
I tried to keep a straight face
as long as I could.
Health Secretary
Robert F. Kennedy Jr.
announced that he is
launching a new podcast.
The podcast is called...
-It's catchy.
-Yesterday, a report
showed inflation spiked
to its highest point in four
years due to the war in Iran.
Here to comment are two kids
from the back of the school bus.
-What's up, Mr. Jost?
Guys?
Calm down. Calm down.
Okay?
You're here to talk
about inflation, okay?
-Right, right.
But first, can I just use
your phone real quick, Mr. Jost?
I'm sorry.
Mine got "confiscated."
-Well, why did your phone
get confiscated?
-I don't know.
I didn't do nothing.
I didn't even do nothing.
-He didn't do nothing.
-I didn't even do nothing.
I don't know why they would take
it if I didn't even do nothing!
-I don't know.
I find that hard to believe.
-Okay, fine.
I posted a video of me
swiping a debit card
between
the bus driver's neck folds.
-It was funny. Back of neck
like a pack of hot dogs.
-It was like "rimp."
You know what I mean?
-Rimp!
Rimp, rimp!
-Declined! Rimp-rimp!
-This is serious, okay?
I want you guys --
You got to focus up, okay?
Focus up.
-Okay. Seriously?
Seriously? Okay.
Inflation was up 3.3%.
Prices are out of control.
Everyone has been affected.
Even my boy Grabon
can't afford these groceries.
-Nah, for real. I feel bad
for Grabon. Life is tough.
-Oh, my God, who's Grabon?
-Oh, Grabon
is a friend of ours.
It's Grabon Deez Nuts!
-Got him!
-Got ya!
-Yeah, I really
don't appreciate being
shot in the face
a bunch of times.
Also, you're supposed
to come out here
and talk
about the inflation report.
You've had this
assignment for weeks.
-Nah. Chill, chill, chill,
chill, chill.
Chill, chill, chill,
chill right now.
Chill.
Let me lock in.
-Lock in.
Let him cook. Let him cook.
-Okay. Inflation report.
Right? Let me ask you a
"basing" question of economics.
-Basing?
-Basing.
-You got it, you got it,
you got it.
-I got it,
-Lock in, man. Lock in.
-All right.
-You got it.
-Let me ask you a basic
question of economics, okay?
-Okay, great. Yeah.
-Would you rather eat 100 glizzies
or pass away
from big-booty disease?
-Good question.
Good question.
I guess I would obviously
choose the glizzies.
-Oh, hell, no!
-Mr. Jost a glizzy goblin!
-You nasty, bro.
-Sick boy.
-All right, you guys,
you're too rowdy, okay?
You guys need to calm down.
-Okay, fine. Jokes aside,
I don't think this
inflation will
predicate a noticeable shift
in the Federal Reserve.
-Yeah, but it does
put the Fed between
a rock and a hard place
because they have
to promote low inflation
while still encouraging
economic growth.
-The hell?
Is that...
Are you guys,
like, secretly smart?
-Yes, dude. We get tutoring
from Amanda Cahold.
She's a genius.
You know Amanda Cahold.
-Who is Amanda Cahold?
-Amanda Cahold deez nuts.
-Got him! Got him!
-Got him!
-Bitch!
-That is-- You know what?
I'm calling your mom.
-No, no, no!
-We didn't do nothing!
-We didn't do anything.
-We didn't even do nothing!
-I didn't even do nothing.
-He ain't even do nothing.
-Why would you call my mom
if I didn't even do nothing?
-Please don't call her.
She's gonna hit me.
Please, please, please, please.
Don't call.
She's gonna hit him.
Okay. We're sorry, Mr. Jost.
Okay? We didn't mean it.
-Have you even considered
how our home lives
affect our behavior?
-Yeah.
Did you ever stop to think
why we are the way that we are?
-Wow. You know,
I guess I haven't.
I apologize.
I guess I can be
insensitive sometimes,
because when I was younger,
I was diagnosed with ligma.
-Ligma?
-Yeah,
it's ligma fat nuts!
-My God.
-We're children.
-Bo!
Two kids in the back of
the school bus, everyone.
-You're an animal!
-Come at the king,
you best no miss!
-No, no!
-Why do you have
fat nuts, man?
A new study...
-Ask God.
-A new study reveals
that sharks
in the Bahamas
have tested
positive for painkillers.
In fact, the only animals
that consume more
painkillers
are tigers.
-A new report finds
that the state with
the most adult children
still living with their parents
is New Jersey.
Adult children in New Jersey
are calling the report
"Ma! Why You Gotta
Tell Them That For?"
British officials
have blocked Ye from
entering the country to
perform at a music festival
despite his offer to meet
with members of England's
Jewish community,
which he thinks are the bank
goblins from Harry Potter.
-It was announced that when
King Charles visits
the U.S. this month,
he will deliver a joint address
to Congress,
where, God willing,
he offers to take us back.
The Gilgo Beach killer
has pleaded guilty
to eight murders
on Long Island.
And, honey, I hope one of them
was your barber.
You like how sassy I am?
-Yes, I do.
A number of bars
around the country have
implemented a policy
banning cellphones,
this according to a recent
lie a man told his wife.
-A video has surfaced in which
a quadruple amputee
cornhole champion
accused of a road-rage shooting
is seen firing a semi-automatic
rifle
and standing on his head
snorting drugs
off a dollar bill.
So, what's stopping you
from living your best life?
-A pig named Merlin
that can talk using
pre-programmed buttons
has
set a new world record
for largest Instagram
following for a pig.
And then it set the record
for smartest pork chop.
-You still got that
mustache on your finger.
Doctors are warning
against a TikTok trend...
against a TikTok trend
which claims people can cure
their hemorrhoids by putting
sugar on their anus.
Putting sugar on an anus is also
the recipe for Hostess donettes.
You can't unsee it.
-Speaking of, a new book
on healthy bowel movements
has been published
called "You've Been Pooping
All Wrong."
And they're right. I have been.
Cowboy
-A new study has shown
that young people today
are having less sex than at any
other point in history.
Here to comment is Gen Z
Sexpert Lindt Greer.
-Hi, Michael.
Hi, Michael.
-How you doing, Lindt?
-So, sex, let's talk about it.
Sex is an incredible piece
of the human experience,
and there's nothing
to be ashamed of,
whether you're vanilla
or disgusting.
-So you're here to teach Gen Z
about healthy sex practices?
-Yes. And sex can look
like anything. What is it?
-Are you going to tell us?
-Of course, Michael.
Let's get granular.
Sex can be any shape.
It doesn't have to be
with someone you love.
It just has to be at night.
-And you say you're
a sex educator, right?
-I am. Sex is complicated.
It's impossible to understand,
which is why my sexpert
advice is just do whatever.
-I guess I would hope
that as an educator,
you'd have some guidance
beyond "just do whatever."
-Well, there are
only two rules in sex.
One, have fun
and two, no raping.
-You disagree, Che?
-No! I'm not...
I just mean
that came out of nowhere.
-Well, raping can
come out of nowhere.
-Okay.
-Now, sex. Let's get into it.
What is it?
-You keep asking that.
-To echo the famous quote,
"I can't define sex,
but I know it
when I'm having it."
-I have a question, and
don't take this the wrong way.
But have you had sex before?
-I must have.
If I hadn't, how would
I know all of this?
-All of what?
Look. It's okay if you haven't.
-Put it this way, Che.
I've had something
that might be sex,
and I've had it a lot.
If I haven't had sex,
then what do you think I had?
-Is that like a riddle
or something?
I don't know.
-Here's how it went. It's night.
My friend is there,
but I don't love him.
-Okay.
-I get on my hands and knees,
curl my head down
towards the bed,
kick my legs up
and go all the way over.
Then I fall back, breathless.
-That sounds like
you did a somersault.
-Yes. Sex can look
like anything.
-Yeah, but not anything.
-Well, here's something else
I had,
and I wonder if it was sex.
-Go for it.
-I sat on a catcher's mitt.
-That's not sex.
-But it left me breathless.
-Lindt Greer, everybody.
-Just do whatever.
-For "Weekend Update,"
I'm Michael Che.
-I'm Colin Jost.
Just do whatever.
-I was just looking
through the photo books.
Seems like Grandpa was
a really amazing guy.
-Oh. He was, honey.
I'll miss him.
-Yeah, I feel bad.
I feel like growing up
in Florida,
I never really got
to know Grandpa.
-Oh, well, he was
a difficult man to know.
He had his group of friends,
and that's really it.
I just hope some of them
show up today.
-Hello, Katie.
-Oh.
-He's in a better place now.
-Oh, thank you, Father.
-Yeah. Thank you, Father.
-Thank you, Father.
-Oh, that was Father Murphy
from my parish.
That's sweet of him to come.
Oh, look who it is!
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
-Yeah. Your father
will be missed.
Heaven has gained a freaky,
little angel today.
-Yes.
-Oh, genes came out a little
different with these two.
-Okay, well, Mom,
who-- who was that?
-Oh, that was Suede.
-How did Grandpa know Suede?
-Suede was one of his friends
from the life.
-What?
-Why?
-Oh, Crystalline, Tribeca,
you came.
- Hey, sorry
for your loss.
-Yeah, we brought a few items
we thought
he'd like to bring
to the beyond.
You mind if we casket 'em?
-Oh, go right ahead, girls.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
-Can't forget my purse.
-Oh, I'm sure wherever he is,
he's looking up
at those girls, smiling.
-Looking up?
-Mom, was Grandpa some
kind of like...pimp?
-Your grandfather
was incredible, man.
And when he put on that wig,
he was one of my best hos.
-Thanks for coming, Delicious.
-I'm sorry. Did he say "hos"?
-Yeah, that's what I said,
little man.
So, who's gonna flip him over?
He would have wanted
to be buried how he lived --
face down, booty up.
-What is he talking about, Mom?
-Honey, just a moment.
Just a moment.
So, how have you been,
Delicious?
You keeping the girls in line?
You keeping it 100?
-As always. As always.
Gosh, you know what I miss
about your daddy?
You could have your way with him
no matter what you looked like,
as long as you paid him
his dollar.
-That's right.
-One dollar?!
-Oh, where are my manners?
Delicious, these are my sons,
Mike and Jake.
Nice to meet you both.
You could earn.
You...go to college.
-What?
-Mom, was Grandpa
like a sex worker?
-Oh, no, honey!
He preferred the term
"boy whore."
Hey, I'm so sorry for your loss.
I'm gonna miss Jim,
but I'll always have
a piece of him right here.
-Oh, my gosh,
Grandpa is the father?
-No, Muffin is the father.
I was talking about my ink.
-Oh.
-Speaking of,
have you seen Muffin?
-Oh, I think he's saying
his final goodbyes.
Yo, I am pleased to report that
rigor mortis has set in.
-Dude, this is insane.
Why is he in there?
Why is he going back in there?
-Sorry. Are you
laughing or crying?
-Laughing because
the good times happened.
Crying because they're over.
-Oh. You're a poet, White Cocoa.
These are my sons,
Mike and Jake.
-Mm, pleasure.
"Pleasure" would be your street
name if you worked for me.
Think about it.
Nice to meet you, Jake.
-I'm sorry. How many
pimps did Grandpa have?
-How many pimps?
You might as well...
You're asking how many pimps?
You might as well ask how many
stars there are in the sky.
That'd be four.
I am very sorry for your loss,
Katie.
-Oh. Thank you,
Mac Daddy Vanilla.
-And you must be
the famous Mike
I've heard so much about.
You give me a call if you
want to live that life.
And you?
What were you, uh,
adopted from the shire?
Fugly-ass ho!
-Okay. Um, Mom,
what is "the life"?
-Yeah, and why can't I live it?
-Oh. Oh, honey,
you can do anything
you set your mind to.
-Really? All right, then.
I'm really gonna do it!
-Once again, Anitta.
-[ Singing in Spanish ]
[ Singing in Spanish ]
d Yeah, yeah d
d Yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah d
d Yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah d
d Yeah, yeah, yeah d
d Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah d
-I wonder what the
new teacher is gonna be like.
-Probably just like all
the other instructors here
at Sherwood Academy --
another boring, humdrum stiff.
-Discipline.
Memorization. Conformity.
All these things have
one thing in common.
They're not welcome
in my classroom.
-But, sir,
the Academy creed is
"the learned boy shall conform."
-Phooey, boys!
Throw your pencils on the floor.
-But the floor is
where the dirt is.
-Oh, do it anyway.
-Okay.
-This is crazy.
What we're doing is crazy.
-Let me tell you something.
You won't find anything
in a textbook
you can't find in your heart.
-Hey, man, I see what you're
doing with the whole
free-spirited teaching thing.
And that might work in
like a poetry class.
-Yes. Now you're getting it.
-Yeah, but this is math.
-Right. "Math."
You've probably all been taught
that 5 times 5 is 25.
But what if it wasn't?
-It is though. It's 25.
-But it doesn't have to be.
Boy Red...
Make up a number,
a number
no one's even heard of before.
-Um, beleventy?
Excellent. How did that feel?
-I mean,
it felt weird coming out.
-And it should. Oh!
You, a number.
-Um, um, christophthree?
-Wonderful!
Now, what do we get when we add
christophthree plus beleventy?
What should it be?
-Um, maybe, uh,
maybe flu-- uh, fludeetwo?
Yes. Maybe it's fludeetwo.
-Chills! I have chills.
Fludeetwo.
Yes. Now, that's math
without conformity.
-Okay. Yeah, but math needs to
conform in order
to solve, like, real-world
problems.
-Oh! We can solve problems.
Like 30.
Why do you think
we haven't solved 30 yet?
-Because 30 is not a problem.
It's a number.
-And what
if all the numbers had a color?
Like, what if I hold up this
many and say it was orange
and this many was one
of the other colors.
-Lilac.
That many could be lilac.
-Yes.
Now you've made up a color too.
Ha! Oh!
Let's try calculus.
-Hey, man, I don't
want to see you do calculus.
You were just counting on
your fingers.
I mean, we're trying
to get into college.
-Why?
So you can go off into the world
and get some kind of "job"?
-Yes.
-Or so you can invent
a machine.
-It was the first thing.
It was the first thing
that you said.
-There you go.
Student teaching the teacher.
I love it. Let's all go around.
Everyone do a lesson.
-Um, uh, why does Spanish math
have cuatro but not English?
-I don't know.
Let's put that in.
-Um, what if a one
and two were married
and three was their baby, and
then four was their neighbor?
-And what would five be?
Could five be like their friend?
-Uh, uh, I don't know,
I don't know, I don't know.
That was everything I had.
I'm sorry.
-Well, five would be the dog.
Genius. You're a genius!
Custodian, join us.
Put that down.
-Oh, okay.
Somebody buy that man
a beer after class.
-We're 14!
-Wait, I got one.
Um, when counting,
what if you could count
every number in one breath?
One-two-three-four-five!
One-two-three! Oh!
Never mind. You can't.
-Oh, why can you divide
two numbers
but not unite two numbers?
-Oh!
-You can! It's addition!
-This might get me in trouble,
but I think I'm attracted
to eight.
It's got that itty bitty waist
but that thang down below.
-Yes!
Academically speaking, eight...
...is slim thick.
-No, no, no, no!
This is all nonsense!
I mean,
we're just making crap up.
Why don't we call this my mom?
Oh, hello, Mommy.
What?
And look, Mother, oh,
this is a door,
and I'm a butterfly,
and I can fly!
-This did not happen.
I was not here.
He's the teacher. Good day.
-Okey-dokey, students.
Why don't we open
our textbooks to page fludeetwo?
And today we talkin' eight.
-We're just four normal
teens living in the suburbs.
-But we do have a secret.
-We transform into animals
to battle evil aliens,
but we always transform back
in time for dinner.
-Saving humanity?
That's easy.
The hard part is our homework.
-We're the Beastomorphs.
You crazy Earth kids may think
you've seen the last of me,
but I'll be back. Mwahahaha!
-Good job, gang.
We said that evil alien
Chumongous
back to the lousy planet
he came from.
-Uh-oh. It's 6:00 p.m.
My mom's meatloaf
is waiting for us.
-Let's Beastomorph.
-Nice. And my hair didn't
even get messed up.
-Who's chicken now?
-This little piggy
kicked some alien butt.
-Good one! Now my turn.
-What? What? Why are you
all looking at me like that?
Let me guess.
My hair got messed up.
-Lizzie, don't freak out,
but when you combination
sneeze-farted,
you got stuck mid-morph.
-You can't show up for Mom's
meatloaf looking like that.
-Brittany, stop!
We all know your mom's gone,
and you just eat chips.
-I don't just eat chips.
I eat chips...and soda.
-Okay. Hey, we can
figure this out, guys.
Let's put our heads together.
Oh, Lizzie, can you
just look at the wall
while we talk?
-Sure.
-A little hard to see.
I'm kind of looking
in two directions at once.
-Think, guys.
How can we fix this?
-Okay, maybe if I sneeze
and then fart again,
I can change back.
Ah-choo!
-Lizzie, stop.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
-Maybe if I fart twice,
then sneeze once, then burp?
-Yuck!
-That didn't work.
Okay, what about,
um, sneeze, fart, pause,
spin around,
fart three times quickly,
burp once, then fart again?
-Definitely not.
Maybe if I do it?
-Yeah.
-I have to go home.
-Oh, no! Chumongous is coming!
It's time to morph back.
-That's right! The great
Chumongous has returned.
You Earth kids may have
thought you've defeated me,
but I'm more powerful than ever!
Oh, my God, it smells
like [bleep] in here.
-Sorry. We've all been spinning,
farting, and burping
for the past few minutes.
-Why? Actually. Never mind.
I don't care.
Prepare to die!
You...
...beautiful creature.
You're just about the most
perfect thing I've ever seen.
- You really think so?
-Yes. There's just one problem.
-What is it?
-That frog hand
ain't got my thing in it.
-Ew, dude!
-Sorry. Is that, like,
a big deal for you guys?
That's, like, less
than first base where I'm from.
Where I'm from,
if you go visit your grandmother
in the hospital,
you lean over
and your grandma just
grabs your thing out of respect!
-What?
-So, what do you say?
You want to be
my queen of Chumonga?
-Well...it sure beats homework.