MESSAGE
>> HELLO EVERYONE.
IT'S REALLY ME, THE EASTER
BUNNY.
EITHER THAT OR YOU'RE AT
COACHELLA AND THE 'SHROOMS ARE
KICKING IN.
HOW IS EVERYONE TONIGHT?
EASTER
WARM HALLOWEEN
CHARACTER
EST
MAN-SIZE
WHO
SANTA
BASKETS
SUPPORT WOMEN
HAPPENS
NOW REMEMBER THE SMEAR SPIRIT OF EASTER
IS ABOUT RENEWAL AND THE
BIRTH.
THAT'S WHY I'VE INVITED FOLKS
FROM ALL WALKS OF LIFE
TO SHARE THEIR HOPES
FOR THIS EASTER SEASON.
TAKE IT AWAY, DR. ANTHONY FAUCI.
>> IT'S ME, YOUR BOY, FAUCI, I
KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M STILL HERE.
TURNS OUT I'M LIKE LIZARD.
NO MATTER HOW HARD YOU TRY TO
GET RID OF ME, I'M STILL
HAIR OR FACE
COVID
I'M NOT STUPID ENOUGH TO THINK
YOU'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO FOLLOW
IT.
ALL I CAN SAY IS COVID CASES ARE
A LOT LIKE JESUS,
THEY'VE RISEN
AGAIN.
IF YOU'RE VACCINATED, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE FINE.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO SAY THIS,
BUT I HONESTLY DON'T CARE WHAT
HAPPENS TO YOU.
HAPPY EASTER, EVERYBODY.
HI.
I'M MARJORIE TAYLOR GREENE.
AND AS I'VE BEEN SAYING
AGGRESSIVELY TO ALL MY JEWISH
AND MUSLIM COLLEAGUES, HAPPY
EASTER.
DON'T WORRY.
THIS RIFLE IS CHOCOLATE, BUT THE
BULLETS ARE REAL.
NOW, I'M WORRIED ABOUT EASTER.
BETWEEN THE PASTELS AND THE
JELLY BEANS,
THIS HOLIDAY'S
GOTTEN A LITTLE TOO LGBQRSA FOR
ME.
AND THERE IS NOTHING GAY ABOUT EASTER,
A DAY WHEN A BUNCH OF
MALE PRIESTS WORSHIP A GUY WITH GREAT ABS
AND TALK ABOUT WANTING
TO EAT HIS BODY.
THAT'S STRIKE STUFF.
HAPPY
RUSSIA
MEAN AMERICA
BOTH
ERIC ADAMS
TELEVISION
SPRING
LOOKING
PLAYING
BEST NEWS
WE GOT SUGAR
SUSPECT
BUT WE GOT
CASE CLOSED
FIXED
OUTFIT
PRESS
JOE
YANKEES
SEXY
VIOLENT
BITCH
>> HELLO.
SO, I AM ELON MUSK.
I AM HERE TO OFFICIALLY BUY
EASTER.
I'M OFFERING 43 BILLION PEEPS.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
DO YOU GET IT?
THAT'S WHY AFTERWARDS, I SAY,
THAT WAS A JOKE,
SO YOU KNOW IT
WAS A JOKE.
LOOK, I KNOW PEOPLE DON'T WANT
ME TO BUY TWITTER,
BUT WHY?
YOU'RE WORRIED I'LL MAKE TWITTER
BAD?
WHAT ARE YOU SCARED I'LL BUY
NEXT?
THE OSCARS?
THAT WAS A JOKE.
HEY, Y'ALL, IT'S ME, BRITNEY.
AND I BET YOU DIDN'T THINK I
COULD DO THIS.
REMEMBER SIX MONTHS AGO WHEN
EVERYONE WAS LIKE,
WE NEED TO
GET HER OUT OF THIS
CONSERVATORSHIP.
AND NOW YOU'RE ALL LIKE,
SOMEONE'S GOING TO CHECK IN ON
HER, RIGHT?
WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I'M FINALLY FREE,
AND  I'M HAVING A
BABY.
I JUST PRAY THAT MY BABY IS BORN
HAPPY, HEALTHY,
AND WITH POWER
OF ATTORNEY.
HAPPY EASTER, EVERYONE.
>> HEY.
IT'S ME, JESUS CHRIST.
JUST KIDDING.
I'M JARED LETO.
IT'S WHAT I WORE TO KIDS CHOICE
AWARDS.
YOU KNOW, MY EASTER MESSAGE THIS
YEAR IS SIMPLE.
POSITIVITY.
SO, IF YOU GO TO SEE MY NEW
MOVIE, "MORBIUS," PLEASE DON'T
REVIEW IT.
IF YOU'RE THE KIND OF PERSON WHO
REVIEWS MOVIES, "MORBIUS" JUST
ISN'T RIGHT FOR YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU ON THE BIG SCREEN.
AND THE TWO LITTLE SCREENS
BEHIND YOUR EYELIDS WHEN YOU GO
TO SLEEP.
LOVE PEACE.
>> SO MANY FASCINATING
VIEWPOINTS.
I GUESS IT'S TRUE WHAT THEY SAY,
SPRING IS A BEAUTIFUL REMINDER
OF WHAT CHANGE CAN BRING.
>> EXCUSE ME.
I WAS TOLD WE WERE DOING EASTER
WISHES.
AND I WAS NOT
GIVEN MY TURN.
THIS IS VERY, VERY UNFAIR.
ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF HOW WHITES
ARE BEING HORRIBLY MISTREATED IN
THIS COUNTRY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FINE.
GO AHEAD.
>> EASTER IS A TIME FOR BASKETS
AND BUNNIES
AND FRANKLY BONNETS.
AND LET'S NOT FORGET EGG.
YOU HAVE EASTER EGG, CADBURY EGG,
AND MY FAVORITE, WHICH IS
REESES EGG.
THE REESES EGG DOESN'T LOOK LIKE EGG,
BUT I LIKE REESE.
I'M VERY GOOD FRIENDS WITH
REESE.
WE'RE VERY GOOD FRIENDS.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT REESE SAYS?
HE SAYS, NOT SORRY.
REESE SAYS IN A VERY DEEP VOICE,
NOT SORRY.
AND THAT'S GOOD.
WE DON'T LIKE FOOD TO APOLOGIZE,
DO WE?
LIKE THAT AWFUL CAPTAIN CRUNCH.
HE WAS VERY RUDE TO ME AT COUNT
CHOCULA'S 500TH BIRTHDAY.
BUT HE WAS DOING OOPS ALL
BERRIES.
YOU'RE HEARING IT ALL THE TIME.
OOPS ALL BERRIES.
BAD THING
WHY SAY OOPS?
WE LIKE CRUNCH BERRIES.
BERRIES SO BEAUTIFUL.
I'VE HEARD WE HAVE SOME OF THE
BEST BERRIES.
RIGHT MR. BUNNY?
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
SOME PEOPLE ARE SAYING I'M NOT
HEALTHY, OKAY?
I'M VERY GOOD WITH HEALTH.
VERY GOOD HEALTH.
HEALTHY LIKE A HORSE, LIKE SEA
BISCUIT.
SEA BISCUIT -- I EAT BISCUIT.
FRANKLY WE'RE DOING GREAT THINGS
WITH BISCUIT AND BUN
AND BREAD.
WE'RE DOING CRAZY BREAD.
LITTLE CAESARS, YOU KNOW?
LITTLE
LONG TIME
I ACTUALLY TOLD HIM TO SAY PIZZA
PIZZA.
HE NEEDS TO SAY IT ONCE.
I SAID, WE SHOULD BE SAYING IT
TWICE.
WE SHOULD SAY IT TWICE.
>> OKAY.
I'M ACTUALLY JUST GOING TO WALK
AWAY.
YOU WIN.
YOU CAN HAVE EASTER.
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WOULD LOVE TO MEET BUNNY
BECAUSE I TOLD AMERICA COVID
WOULD BE OVER BY EASTER.
I JUST SAY WHICH ONE.
SO, SAY IT EVERYONE, HAPPY
EASTER
>> LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN --
LIZZO!
>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
MY NAME IS LIZZO, AND, YES, I'M
SHOCKED I HAVE CLOTHES ON TOO.
I'M REALLY EXCITED.
TONIGHT WE'RE GOING TO BREAK THE RECORD
FOR THE AMOUNT OF TIME BITCH IS
SAID ON LIVE TV!
BITCH, BITCH, BITCH.
THAT'S THREE MORE.
I HATE CUSSING IN FRONT OF MY
MOM.
HEY MAMA.
BABY
YEARS
THE FIRST TIME MY MOM CAME TO
SEE ME PERFORM, I HAD TO WARN HER,
MOM, WHEN I'M ON STAGE, I'M
GONE SAY SOME BAD WORDS.
AT THE TIME, SHE DIDN'T LIKE THAT,
BUT NOW RICH SO SHE'S
LIKE, "BITCH, CUSS ME OUT."
FIVE
BUT REALLY, THE LIZZO YOU SEE ON
STAGE IS DIFFERENT FROM THE REAL
ME.
I GOT A SERIOUS SIDE AS WELL.
LIKE, LAST YEAR, I HAD THE HONOR
OF GIVING A TED TALK.
IT WAS VERY SERIOUS STUFF.
IT WAS ABOUT TWERKING.
GOOGLE IT.
IT WAS ACTUALLY ABOUT THE
HISTORY OF TWERKING
AND HOW IT
COMES FROM WEST AFRICAN DANCES
LIKE MAPOUKA.
YEAH, I'M DEEPER THAN YOU
THOUGHT, RIGHT?
I'VE GOT BRAINS AND BOOTY.
EINS
BUT WHILE I'M HERE, I DO WANT TO
ADDRESS SOME RUMORS.
I READ A LOT ONLINE THAT I'M
DATING EVERY LITTLE WHITE BOY IN
HOLLYWOOD.
THEY THINK I'M COLLECTING
MEMBERS OF ONE DIRECTION LIKE
INFINITY STONES.
AND I EVEN HEARD A RUMOR THAT
I'M PREGNANT WITH CHRIS EVANS'
BABY.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE THAT ONE
STARTED.
IT COULD BE THE TIKTOK WHERE I SAID,
I AM PREGNANT WITH
CHRIS EVANS' BABY, Y'ALL.
IT'S CALLED MANIFESTING, OKAY?
BUT I AM HONORED TO BE UP HERE
ON THIS STAGE.
WHEN I GOT THE CALL TO HOST
SNL, I WAS PRETTY NERVOUS.
I KNOW IT'S SHOCKING
BECAUSE I'M THE ONE WHO
SAID,
"I JUST TOOK A DNA TEST, TURNS OUT
I'M 100% THAT BITCH."
NUMBER ONE.
WELL, TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
I'M REALLY LIKE 50% THAT BITCH,
10% BOSS BITCH,
AND 40% FLUTE
PLAYING, BAND NERD BITCH.
BUT I'M THRILLED TO BE HOSTING
THIS PARTICULAR EPISODE,
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE I DO LOVE
TONIGHT'S MUSICAL GUEST.
ME!
NO, FOR REAL, I DO LOVE MYSELF.
EVERYBODY SHOULD LOVE
THEMSELVES.
YOU KNOW, AT EVERY SHOW, I TELL
MY AUDIENCE THE SAME THING, AND
I'LL TELL Y'ALL TOO.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
AND YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
I'M LIVING PROOF OF THAT.
I USED TO LIVE IN MY CAR.
NOW I'M UP HERE HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT
STICK AROUND WE'LL
BE RIGHT BACK
TIME
HOST
>> WELCOME TO "GUESS THAT!"
CLINT LITTERS.
AND WE HAVE THREE WONDERFUL
CONTESTANTS PLAYING --
TRACY,
NICOLE, AND KENNY.
NOW, WE ALL KNOW HOW THE GAME
GOES.
I'LL ASK YOU GUYS A SERIES OF
RAPID FIRE TRIVIA QUESTIONS,
AND
IF YOU GET THEM RIGHT, I'LL GIVE
YOU SOME MONEY.
SOUND GOOD?
>> YEAH, LET'S PLAY.
>> SOUNDS GREAT, CLINT.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S START.
FIRST QUESTION -- THIS AMINO
ACID FOUND IN TURKEY
IS KNOWN TO
MAKE YOU SLEEPY.
>> THAT WOULD BE TRYPTOPHAN,
CLINT.
>> CORRECT.
$100 ON THE BOARD FOR TRACY.
NEXT QUESTION.
THIS SURGERY USES LASER
TECHNOLOGY TO RESTORE VISION.
>> I'VE ACTUALLY HAD THIS, IT'S
LASIK SURGERY.
>> YES.
THAT'S $100 FOR YOU, KENNY.
OKAY.
THIS NEW YORK CITY AIRPORT
WAS NAMED AFTER THE 35TH PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> ROBERT KENNEDY AIRPORT.
>> OH, SORRY, THAT'S ACTUALLY
INCORRECT.
>> NO, IT'S NOT!
I WAS JUST THERE.
>> THAT'S STILL WRONG, NICOLE.
>> HOW YOU GONE TELL ME?
I WAS JUST STUCK IN THAT AIRPORT FOR FIVE HOURS
'CAUSE I PET A
BOMB-SNIFFING DOG AND THEY SAID
I RUINED HIM.
>> THAT'S VERY CONFUSING TO
HEAR.
KENNY?
>> IS IT JOHN F. KENNEDY
AIRPORT?
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> I -- I JUST SAID THAT.
>> UH, NO, YOU SAID "ROBERT
KENNEDY."
>> OKAY, BUT YOU KNEW WHAT I
MEANT.
>> OKAY, NICOLE.
WE HAVE A LOT MORE QUESTIONS.
SO, THAT'S $100 FOR YOU, KENNY.
>> AND WHAT DO I GET?
>> YOU DON'T -- YOU DON'T GET
ANYTHING.
>> I GAVE HIM HALF THE ANSWER,
SO I SHOULD GET HALF THE MONEY.
>> WELL, THAT'S NOT HOW THE GAME
WORKS.
>> OH, OKAY, SO THEY GIVE YOU A
LITTLE SUIT AND SOME BLUE CARDS
AND NOW YOU'RE THE MAYOR OF GAME
TOWN?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT YOU'RE SLOWING UP THE GAME.
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT QUESTION.
IN 1492, THIS EXPLORER --
NICOLE, YOU HAVE AN ANSWER
ALREADY?
>> I DON'T WANNA PLAY NO MORE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YOU SAID I CAN'T WIN, SO I
DON'T WANNA PLAY NO MORE.
>> I NEVER SAID YOU CAN'T WIN.
>> UH-UH, DON'T GASLIGHT ME.
>> WHO'S GASLIGHTING?
>> Y'ALL SEE THIS, RIGHT?
IF HE WANT ME TO LOSE SO BAD,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST LET ME QUIT,
CLINT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
QUIT.
I DON'T CARE.
>> OKAY.
GIVE ME MY MONEY FIRST.
>> WHAT MONEY?
YOU HAVE A SCORE OF ZERO.
>> WELL THEY SAY I GET $500 JUST
FOR PLAYING.
>> YEAH, THAT'S IF YOU FINISH
THE GAME.
>> OKAY, SO YOU'RE FORCING ME TO
PLAY, EVEN THOUGH YOU SAID I
CAN'T WIN.
THIS MAN IS A CLASSIC
GASLIGHTING NARCISSIST, Y'ALL.
>> CAN I JUST FINISH ASKING THE
QUESTIONS, NICOLE?
>> GO AHEAD, BUT THAT HOTEL YOU
PUT US IN IS NASTY.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY YOU FEEL THAT
WAY.
IN 1492, THIS EXPLORER SET SAIL
TO DISCOVER THE NEW WORLD.
KENNY?
>> CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS.
>> YES.
THAT IS CORRECT.
$100 FOR YOU, KENNY.
NICOLE?
>> CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS.
>> YEAH, HE ALREADY SAID THAT.
>> OKAY.
SO WHEN I REPEAT HIS ANSWER, I
DON'T GET NO MONEY, BUT WHEN HE
REPEAT MINE, HE GET $100?
>> YOU GUESSED THE WRONG ANSWER,
NICOLE.
>> NO, YOU HATE WOMEN.
>> YO, CAN I -- CAN I JUST GIVE
HER 50 OF MY DOLLARS?
>> YES.
>> NO.
THAT IS NOT HOW THE GAME WORKS.
AND STOP USING THE BUZZER EVERY
TIME YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING.
WHO DIED AND MADE YOU THE MAYOR
OF GAME TOWN?
>> GIRL, HE THINK HE THE MAYOR
OF GAME TOWN JUST BECAUSE HE GOT
A LITTLE SUIT AND A GUN.
>> I DON'T HAVE A GUN.
AND I'M NOT THE MAYOR OF
ANYTHING.
WHAT, NICOLE?
>> WELL, IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
THE MAYOR NO MORE, CAN I DO IT?
>> NO!
NO!
>> OH, OKAY.
SO, A WOMAN CAN'T BE A MAYOR OF
GAME TOWN?
>> HOW YOU GONE BE THE MAYOR OF
GAME TOWN, YOU DON'T EVEN
BELIEVE, BRO?
>> 'CAUSE SEE, NOW I'M THE NEW
MAYOR.
AND THE FIRST THING I'M DOING IS
PUTTING US IN A BETTER HOTEL
WITH AN ESPRESSO MACHINE.
>> YO, I LOVE THE NEW MAYOR, YO.
>> LOOK.
Y'ALL GONE BURN UP THE BATTERIES
ON THEM BUZZERS.
NOW, HAVE ANY OF Y'ALL EVER BEEN
ON A GAME SHOW?
>> I WAS ON "PEOPLE'S COURT."
I BROKE INTO MY EX'S HOUSE AND
TOOK A WAFFLE IRON.
>> THAT'S NOT A GAME SHOW.
>> THEN HOW COME I WON SO MUCH
MONEY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WRONG.
THE ANSWER IS I BURNT MY HAND.
NOW YOU OWE US $100.
>> WHAT?
WE SPLIT THE $100 3 WAYS,
50, 50, 50!
>> YES, GIRL!
>> FINE, I QUIT.
YOU'RE THE NEW MAYOR.
I'M GOING BACK TO MY SUITE AT
THE LA QUINTA.
>> HEY Y'ALL, I'M THE NEW MAYOR
OF GAME TOWN.
* I'M CRYING
I'M SO BAD
'CAUSE I'M AT THE --*
* 1-877 --*
>> P.O.V. YOU WOKE UP AT TONY'S.
>> HEY, MORNING BEAUTIFUL.
SLEEP OKAY?
GOT BREAKFAST FOR YOU.
COFFEE, FRESH FRUIT.
NAME'S TONY, BY THE WAY.
>> OKAY.
THIS IS DAY 342 OF ME WALKING ON
ALL FOURS.
MAKING MAJOR GAINS.
TESTOSTERONE IS OFF THE CHARTS.
* WE'RE ALL SMILES
ON THE SURFACE *
* BUT WE'RE SAD INSIDE *
* JUST WHEN SHE -- *
**
>> YO, JUST HOOKED UP MY BOY
WITH A FRESH CUT.
HOW YOU FEEL, MAN?
>> I LOVE -- I LOVE IT.
>> HEY, GRANDMA.
YOU EVER MISS GRANDPA?
>> I MISS HIM EVERY DAY.
>> OH, GOD!
>> ACTUALLY, JUST CUSS A LITTLE.
>> FOR REAL?
>> WHAT'RE YOUR FAVORITE CURSE
WORDS?
>> PROBABLY [ BLEEP ] MY
[ BLEEP ][ BLEEP ][ BLEEP ][
BLEEP ]
>> OKAY, WHAT IS THAT?
A HAIRLESS DOG?
OH, IT'S A MAN.
>> ARE YOU MARRIED?
YES.
ARE YOU A VIRGIN?
WILL YOU EVER HAVE SEGGS?
WE TRY EVERY DAY.
* I'M WAITING
AT THE COUNTER *
* MAN POUR THE COFFEE *
* OH LET'S GO BRANDON *
>> HEY Y'ALL, GABBY64, I LOVE TO
DANCE AND HAVE FUN.
I WANT TO ASK Y'ALL IF YOU LIKE
ME BETTER WITH, OR WITHOUT --
**
HERE'S WITH.
HERE'S WITHOUT.
**
AND ONCE MORE WITH.
>> Y'ALL KEEP MESSING THESE TWO
UP.
LOOK HERE.
THESE ARE NOT THE SAME.
YOU'RE PISSING ME OFF.
I WILL END YOUR LIFE.
[ BEEP ]
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
SO, HERE IS AN EXPLAINER ON THE
WAR IN UKRAINE.
SO --
**
>> I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD BE
YOUR BOYFRIEND MAYBE?
IT'S TONY, BY THE WAY.
>> THAT TIME T.I. TRIED STANDUP
COMEDY.
>> -- AND YOU'LL NEVER GET IT
EXPEDITIOUSLY.
AND HUNDREDS OF DOLLARS -- WHAT,
YOU A STRIPPER?
WHAT AM I, A STRIPPER OR
SOMETHING?
>> WHAT?
>> GOD IS GOOD, Y'ALL.
>> WHAT'S UP, GANG.
CRITICAL RACE THEORY, WHAT IS IT
AND WHY AM I MAD ABOUT IT?
LET'S TALK.
>> NO!
NO!
JESUS!
[ BLEEP ]
OH, GOD!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
**
>> OKAY, EGGS.
>> NAME'S TONY, BY THE WAY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
TONY CAN GET IT.
>> WHEN YOUR FRIENDS SAY YOU
LOOK EXACTLY LIKE KATHY FROM
EUPHORIA.
**
>> WHAT ARE YOUR FAVORITE CURSE
WORDS?
>> PROBABLY [ BLEEP ] [ BLEEP ]
[ BLEEP ]
[ BLEEP ] [ BLEEP ] [ BLEEP ]
>> SO YEAH, BASICALLY I DIDN'T
GET INTO LAW SCHOOL, AND NEXT
THING I KNOW, I'M DOING THIS.
>> RAWR.
>> BUZZ, WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN
HERE?
>> DAD, STAND UP!
3 OF THE BIGGEST POP SONGS OF
ALL TIME WERE RECORDED AT
INTERSCOPE STUDIOS.
AND THE NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN
FOOTAGE FROM THE SESSION IS
FINALLY BEING RELEASED.
>> THE LABEL IS SO EXCITED ABOUT
THE RECORD.
WE CAN'T WAIT TO WORK ON THIS
NEW SINGLE WITH Y'ALL.
>> YEAH, WE KNOW IT'S A WORK IN
PROGRESS, BUT LET'S HEAR WHAT
YOU GOT SO FAR.
>> OKAY.
HIT THE TRACK.
* GOTTA GET THAT *
* GOTTA GET THAT
THAT THAT THAT THAT *
* BOOM BOOM BOOM *
* GOTTA GET THAT *
>> UM, YEAH, THAT'S ALL WE GOT
SO FAR.
>> WOW.
WILLIAM, THAT'S A REALLY GOOD
START.
>> IT'S WILL.I.AM.
AND I KNOW.
>> I LOVE -- I LOVE HOW IT'S
SOUNDING.
BUT I THINK WE MIGHT HAVE TO
CHANGE THE LYRICS A LITTLE?
>> WHAT YOU MEAN?
THE LYRICS ARE --
* BOOM BOOM BOOM *
I MEAN, WHY WOULD WE CHANGE
THAT?
>> UGH.
PRODUCERS ARE LIKE LEECHES, AND
ART IS BLOOD TO THEM.
>> WELL, THOSE WERE ACTUALLY THE
TEMP LYRICS WE SENT TO DESCRIBE
THE BEAT OF THE TRACK.
>> YEAH, YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
REPLACE THEM WITH YOUR OWN
LYRICS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, WITH WORDS?
>> PRODUCERS ARE LIKE LEECHES.
>> NO ONE UNDERSTANDS OUR
VISION.
* BOOM BOOM BOOM *
IT'S PERFECT, I'M FREAKING OUT!
>> HOW ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE --
* I GOT THAT
BOOM BOOM POW *
>> OKAY.
THAT'S KIND OF CLOSER.
UH, WHAT'S YOUR NAME AGAIN?
>> APL.DE.AP.
>> OF -- OF COURSE.
AND HOW DO YOU SPELL THAT?
>> A-P-L --
APL.DE.AP.
>> OKAY.
UH, SO, WE DEFINITELY HAVE
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
UM, BUT LET'S EXPAND, RIGHT?
LIKE, WHAT'S SOMETHING WE HAVE
TO GET?
>> LIKE, FOR EXAMPLE, MONEY OR
HOT GIRLS?
* GOTTA GET THAT *
>> OKAY.
YOU GOTTA GET THAT WHAT,
THOUGH?
* GOTTA GET
THAT THAT THAT *
>> YOU'RE SUFFOCATING ME!
>> TABOO, RELAX.
LET'S THINK.
WHERE WOULD THIS SONG BE
PLAYING?
MAYBE A NIGHT CLUB, OR A FULL
SIZE BAR.
>> OOH, OKAY.
I'M GOING TO RIFF ON THAT IDEAS.
HOW ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE --
* PEOPLE IN THE PLACE *
>> OKAY, FERGIE, UH, THAT'S A
GREAT START.
BUT WHERE WOULD THEY ACTUALLY
BE?
* THE PLACE *
>> OKAY.
AND -- AND WHO WOULD BE THERE?
* THE PEOPLE *
>> UH-HUH.
BUT WHERE IS IT THEY WOULD BE
GOING?
* TO THE PLACE *
>> OKAY.
AND WHERE ARE THEY NOW?
* IN THE PLACE *
>> BUT WHO ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
* THE PEOPLE IN THE PLACE *
>> LET'S MOVE ON.
>> THAT WAS AMAZING, FERGIE, I'M
FREAKING OUT!
>> AND I'M APL.DE.AP.
>> WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT YOUR
VERSE?
I WAS THINKING IT WOULD BE COOL
IF IT WAS LIKE --
* I GOT THAT
BOOM BOOM POW *
* THEM CHICKENS
JACKING MY STYLE *
* THEY TRY TO COPY
MY SWAGGER *
* I'M ON THAT NEXT -- NOW *
* I'M SO 2008
YOU SO 2000 AND LATE *
>> YES.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S AMAZING.
BUT I WANT IT TO BE "3008."
>> OKAY.
WHY?
>> 'CAUSE IT'S BIGGER.
>> FINE.
UH, DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER NOTES?
>> MY HUMPS!
>> OKAY!
THANK YOU, FERGIE.
>> YEAH, WELL, LET'S JUST DO THE
NEXT TRACK.
HERE'S WHAT IT SOUNDS LIKE SO
FAR.
**
YEAH, SO, WE WANT THE LYRICS TO
BE ABOUT THE CONCEPT OF
TONIGHT.
>> LET'S START BY BRAINSTORMING
ANSWERS TO THE QUESTION, "HOW IS
TONIGHT GONNA BE?"
>> I'M THINKING -- I'M THINKING
SOMETHING LIKE --
* TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT *
>> THAT'S AMAZING WILL.I.AM.
>> OKAY.
UH, ANYONE ELSE?
* GOTTA GET
THAT THAT THAT *
>> OH, I'M FREAKING OUT!
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, TABOO, IT'S OKAY.
UH, BUT WE ACTUALLY ALREADY HAVE
THAT.
>> MAZEL TOV!
>> YES!
WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE.
NOW I'M GONNA GO DOWN THE LINE.
EVERYONE JUST SAY ONE EXAMPLE OF
SOMETHING YOU'RE GONNA DO
TONIGHT.
ARE YOU READY?
* LET'S DO IT *
* AND DO IT *
>> OH, MY GOD, THIS IS GONNA BE
A HIT.
>> YEAH.
YEP.
AND -- AND NOW, BEFORE OUR
SESSION IS OVER, LET'S GET TO
THE SONG THAT YOU'LL BE MOST
KNOWN FOR TO THE END OF TIME.
>> YES.
THE WORKING TITLE IS --
* LET'S GET -- *
#ИМЯ?
UM, ANY IDEAS FOR WHAT IT COULD
BE?
>> HM.
>> "LET'S GET" WHAT?
OKAY.
WELL, IT HAS TO BE SOMETHING
THAT WE CAN SAY FOREVER.
**
* LET'S DO IT LET'S DO IT LET'S
DO IT *
* LET'S DO IT LET'S DO IT *
**
>> I HAD AN AMAZING TIME AT
DINNER.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
FULL OF CHEESE.
I FEEL LIKE I'M A LITTLE LUIGI.
>> YOU ALREADY SAID THAT IN THE
CAR.
YOU KNOW, I USUALLY DON'T BRING
GUYS HOME AFTER A FIRST DATE,
BUT SOMETHING ABOUT THIS JUST
FEELS RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
>> OH, BY THE WAY, I SHOULD
MENTION, I LIVE HERE WITH MY
GRANDPA.
SORRY, I SHOULD HAVE SAID
SOMETHING EARLIER.
IF YOU WANT TO GO --
>> OH, NO, NO.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD I LEAVE?
I THINK THAT'S REALLY SWEET.
>> IS THAT MY GRANDDAUGHTER?
>> OH, HI GRANDPA.
>> I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T REALIZE
WE HAD COMPANY.
WELL, PRETEND LIKE I'M NOT EVEN
HERE.
>> WHAT?
THAT IS YOUR GRANDPA?
>> DON'T MIND ME.
>> I'LL LEAVE YOU KIDS TO IT.
HE'S HANDSOME.
CAN WE PAUSE.
YOUR GRANDPA KIND OF THREW ME.
>> I'D RATHER NOT MAKE IT A
THING, BUT YEAH.
MY GRANDPA'S WHITE.
>> NO.
I WAS REFERRING MORE TO THE FACT
THAT HE'S THE GUY FROM THE SIX
FLAGS COMMERCIAL.
>> WOW.
>> I GOT MY BOILING HOT TEA.
OH, I SPILLED MY TEA.
>> NOW, SHOULD WE GET BACK TO
BUSINESS?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, SHOULD WE?
HERE?
I MEAN, WE COULD GO TO MY PLACE
IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT US
MAKING NOISE.
>> TRUST ME, HONEY, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO MAKE ME MAKE
ANY NOISE.
>> I JUST FEEL --
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> OH, GREAT, GRANDMA'S STILL
UP.
>> WAIT, YOUR GRANDMA?
>> HEY, WAIT, WAIT.
SO, THEY'RE BOTH THE SIX FLAGS
GUY?
>> NO, NO.
MY GRANDPA'S THE SIX FLAG GUY.
SHE'S JUST A SIX FLAGS GUY.
>> HELLO.
WHO'S THE LUCKY FELLOW?
>> OH, JUST A FRIEND, GRANDMA.
>> NOW, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
DOING SOME LAUNDRY?
>> OH, YES, JUST FINISHING UP A
LOAD OF BOW TIES.
>> I GOT MORE BOILING HOT TEA.
OFF TO BED.
140 YEARS OLD?
>> WHAT?
>> NOW, ARE WE GOING TO PLOW OR
NOT?
>> YOU STILL WANT TO?
YOU'RE STILL FEELING IT RIGHT
NOW?
>> OH, TRUST ME, BABY, WITH YOU,
I'M NOT GOING TO FEEL A THING.
>> WHAT?
>> THURSDAYS MY GRANDPARENTS
HAVE POKER NIGHT WITH SOME OF
THEIR FRIENDS.
BUT DON'T WORRY, IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU THINK.
>> YEAH, I FEEL LIKE IT IS GOING
TO BE WHAT I THINK.
>> COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> THERE'S LIKE A COMMUNITY OF
THEM?
>> READY TO LOSE SOME MONEY?
>> I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD LEAVE.
>> WOW.
YOU WANT TO LEAVE?
WHY?
BECAUSE MY GRANDPARENTS AND
THEIR WHOLE FRIEND GROUP ARE SIX
FLAGS GUYS?
OR BECAUSE WE ALL DROVE HERE IN
FIVE SEPARATE SIX FLAGS VESPAS?
>> OR BECAUSE YOU KNOW YOU'LL
NEVER BE SATISFIED BY THAT DINKY
LITTLE TWIG IN HIS PANTS?
>> COME ON.
>> IF YOU WANT TO BE WITH ME,
YOU HAVE TO EXPECT MY CULTURE.
AND MY CULTURE, WELL, WE LIKE TO
PARTY.
WE LIKE -- WE LIKE TO PARTY.
NOW, LET'S DANCE.
>> LIZZO, YOU'RE GOING TO KILL
AT HOSTING THIS WEEK.
>> I KNOW, LIKE, HOSTING?
I THINK I CAN HANDLE THAT.
>> I'D SAY SO.
>> IT'S JUST LIKE, THE WHOLE
MUSICAL GUEST THING THAT I'M
STRESSED OUT ABOUT.
I MEAN, TWO NEW SONGS?
I DON'T HAVE THOSE.
I'M NOT JOKING.
>> I GOT WRITER'S BLOCK.
>> WHAT?
>> CAN YOU WRITE ME A NEW SONG?
>> NO.
>> I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO WRITE
ME A NEW SONG.
>> WE CAN'T.
>> NEW SONG NOW, BITCH.
>> NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
>> GO.
* GIRL YOU ALWAYS
LEAVE ME ON READ *
* BROTHER
YOU LEAVE ME ALL BLUE *
* YOU THE BABY GIRL
YOU LOOK LIKE MY DAD *
>> WE'RE -- WE'RE NOT SONG
WRITERS.
>> YOU SOUND HURT.
>> MAYBE IT'S MORE REAL.
MAYBE IT'S LIKE --
* I JUST GOT A HAIRCUT *
* I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN SEE
TOO MUCH OF MY FACE *
* TOO MUCH OF HIS FACE *
>> ARE YOU FEELING VULNERABLE?
>> NO, I WRITE SONGS ABOUT
FEELING CONFIDENT.
I NEED Y'ALL TO WRITE A BLACK
WOMAN ANTHEM.
>> ARE WE THE GUYS TO DO THAT?
>> WE CAN MAYBE WRITE A WHITE
MAN ANTHEM?
>> OH, YEAH, LIKE AN ANTHEM FOR
WHITE MEN.
NO
>> HEY LIZZO, GONNA NEED YOU
DOWNSTAIRS IN TEN TO REHEARSE
THOSE NEW SONGS.
CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR 'EM.
>> YOU KNOW I GOT THOSE BANGERS.
>> ALL RIGHT!
>> WE GOT TEN MINUTES, I NEED A
SONG.
YOU!
SEXY DADDY, COME ON.
>> SEXY?
>> SONG, NOW.
AND A BOTTLE OF JACK *
>> OKAY.
LET'S TRY CALL ON --
- * I WOKE UP FEELING -- *
- * ANXIOUS *
>> PLEASE, -- OUR SKETCH!
>> HEY, WE'RE ALMOST READY FOR
YOU.
AND BY THE WAY, IF THOSE NEW
SONGS AREN'T GOOD,
I'M GONNA
KILL YOU.
>> HE CAN DO THAT?
>> HE'S DONE IT BEFORE.
>> SONGS, NOW, GO!
* I WOKE UP THIS MORNING *
>> THAT'S THE "SOPRANOS" THEME
SONG.
>> DAMN IT.
* WHY MEN GREAT
'TIL THEY GOTTA BE GREAT *
>> I ALREADY WROTE THAT ONE.
* MY GIRLFRIEND DRESSED
LIKE SPONGEBOB *
JESUS
GIRLFRIEND
>> DO YOU HAVE, LIKE, A CRUSH ON
MARTIN?
>> WHAT IS GOING ON WITH YOU
TWO?
>> THIS ISN'T WORKING.
>> WE'RE TRYING SO HARD TO MAKE
A SONG FOR YOU.
>> BUT WE CAN'T.
>> GUESS I GOTTA GO GET KILLED
BY ANDREW DISMUKES.
>> I'M SO SORRY, LIZZO.
>> BUT BEFORE I GO, PITCH ME
ANOTHER AMAZING SKETCH IDEA YOU
GUYS GOT.
>> WELL, IT'S GOING TO SOUND
STUPID NOW, BUT --
IT'S CALLED "HORNY ZOOKEEPER."
IT'S ABOUT A ZOOKEEPER WHO'S A
LITTLE HORNY.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S DUMB.
>> NO, I LIKE THIS.
>> WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YEAH, THIS IS A GREAT SONG.
SKETCH
* THE BEDROOM
IS MY PETTING ZOO *
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S HAPPENING.
* SAID THE BEDROOM
IS MY PETTING ZOO *
* LITTLE MAMA *
* I GOT --
AND YOU'RE MY LLAMA LLAMA *
* GONNA SET YOU ON MY LAP
LIKE A DUCK
THAT'S THE PLAN *
* THEN I MAKE YOU EAT
A QUARTER WITH THE SEEDS
OUT THE PALM OF MY HAND *
* 'CAUSE I'M A
HORNY ZOOKEEPER *
* YOU KNOW THAT I'M A
HORNY HORNY HORNY ZOOKEEPER *
>> OH, MY GOSH.
DO THIS
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ME.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
BUT I'M STILL FLIRTY *
* IS EVERYBODY BACK UP
IN THE BUILDING
IT'S BEEN A MINUTE
TELL ME HOW YOU HEALING *
* CAUSE I'M ABOUT TO GET
INTO MY FEELING
HOW YOU FEELING
HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW *
* OH, I BEEN SO DOWN
AND UNDER PRESSURE
I'M WAY TOO FINE
TO BE THIS STRESSED YEAH *
* OH, I'M NOT THE GIRL
I WAS OR USED TO BE
I MIGHT BE BETTER
TURN UP THE MUSIC *
* TURN DOWN THE LIGHTS
I GOT THE FEELING
I'M GONE BE ALL RIGHT
OKAY, OKAY, IT'S ALL RIGHT *
* IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME
TURN UP THE MUSIC
LET'S CELEBRATE
I GOT A FEELING *
* I'M GONE BE OKAY
OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT
IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME
IN A MINUTE *
* I'MMA NEED A SENTIMENTAL
MAN OR WOMAN TO PUMP ME UP
FEELING FUSSY WALKING
IN MY CAUSE *
* I GIVE A WAY TOO MUCH
NEED LIKE TWO SHOTS IN MY CUP
OH I BEEN SO DOWN AND UNDER
PRESSURE *
* I'M WAY TOO FINE TO
BE THIS STRESSED, YEAH
OH I'M NOT THE GIRL I WAS
OR USED TO BE *
* BITCH I MIGHT BE
BETTER TURN UP THE MUSIC
TURN DOWN THE LIGHTS
I GOT A FEELEN *
* I'M GONE BE ALL RIGHT
OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT
IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME
TURN UP THE MUSIC *
* LET'S CELEBRATE
I GOT A FEELING
I'M GONE BE OKAY
OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT *
* IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME
BITCH *
>> Y'ALL KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS.
**
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT *
* I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT
IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME *
* I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT *
* I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT *
* I'M COMING OUT TONIGHT
HEY BITCH
OH, YEAH, OH
IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME *
WEEKEND
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
NEW POLL
FALLEN TO AN ALL-TIME LOW OF
33%.
FOR PERSPECTIVE, THAT'S LESS
THAN HALF THE APPROVAL RATING OF
SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 2.
SONIC 2, FEATURES THE CHARACTERS
TAILS AND KNUCKLES,
WHICH ARE
ALSO THE NAMES OF TWO GANG
MEMBERS JOE BIDEN CLAIMED HE
FOUGHT IN THE 1960S.
A VIDEO HAS ALSO GONE VIRAL OF
PRESIDENT BIDEN FINISHING A
SPEECH IN NORTH CAROLINA
AND
APPARENTLY TURNING TO SHAKE
HANDS WITH AN INVISIBLE PERSON.
HEY, HER NAME IS KAMALA.
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN SEEN HERE
TRYING TO REMEMBER WHERE HE LEFT HIS MASK,
ANNOUNCED NEW FEDERAL
REGULATIONS FOR GHOST GUNS.
I MEAN, I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA OF
PEOPLE HAVING GHOST GUNS EITHER,
BUT "IF THERE'S SOMETHING
STRANGE IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD,
WHO YOU GONNA CALL?"
LIKE
>> ELON MUSK OFFERED TO BUY
TWITTER FOR OVER $40 BILLION
SO
HE CAN LOOSEN ITS FREE SPEECH
RULES.
THAT'S HOW BAD WHITE GUYS WANT
TO USE THE N-WORD.
>> HONESTLY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WOULD WANT TO OWN
TWITTER.
IMPORTANT FUN
CONFUSING
DEPRESSING
JUL
ELON BUILT
ELECTRIC CARS AND IS GOING TO
MARS.
WHY IS HE EVEN INVOLVING HIMSELF
WITH TWITTER.
IT'S LIKE IF THE PRINCE OF
ENGLAND GAVE IT ALL UP
TO MARRY
AN ACTOR FROM "SUITS."
PLUS TWITTER ISN'T EVEN THAT
PROFITABLE ANYMORE.
IT JUST FEELS LIKE A BAD
BUSINESS DECISION.
AND I SAY THAT AS SOMEONE WHO
BOUGHT A STATEN ISLAND FERRY
WITH PETE.
MARCH
>>> INFLATION COVERS THE HIGHER
PRICES MILLIONS OF FAMILIES
HAVE
BEEN FORCED TO PICK OUT A SECOND
ONLY FANS ACCOUNT.
>> THE MANHUNT FOR THE NEW YORK
CITY SUBWAY SHOOTER ENDED
WITH
THE SUSPECT CALLED THE POLICE
TIP LINE TO SAY HE WAS IN EAST VILLAGE MCDONALD'S,
WHERE,
JUDGING BY THIS PHOTO, HE WAS
AUDITIONING FOR THE ROLL OF
GRIMACE.
JET BLUE HAS OFFERED TO BUY
SPIRIT AIRLINES.
SPIRIT SAID 500 FOR THE NIGHT.
NO KISSING.
>>> NEW TECHNOLOGY CAN PREDICT
WHEN SOMEONE HAVING A FATAL
HEART ATTACK.
IT'S CALLED PELOTON.
>>> MENTAL HEALTH EXPERTS ARE
RECOMMENDING CHILDREN
BE
SCREENED FOR ANXIETY AT EIGHT YEARS OLD
BECAUSE IT
WITH BE STRESSFUL AT THE iPHONE
FACTORY.
>>> BARBIE DOLLS WERE LAUNCH
UNDER TO SPACE FOR THE FIRST
TIME EVER
ABOARD THE INTERNATIONAL SPACE
STATION.
FINALLY THEY'RE GONE, SAID TWO
KEN DOLLS.
>>> A BRAZILIAN MAN --
THERE WE GO.
SORRY.
A BRAZILIAN MANNED TO THE
UNDERGO EMERGENCY SURGERY
AFTER
HE GOT FOUR-POUND DUMB BELL
STUCK IN HIS IN AS.
HE SHOVED IT BACK UP THERE AND
SAID TWO.
ANYWAY.
THAT'S WHY YOU ALWAYS WIPE DOWN
THE EQUIPMENT.
>>> A NEW JERSEY MAN WAS ARRESTED
AFTER HE RAN OVER A
WOMAN MULTIPLE TIMES IN A ROAD RAGE INCIDENT,
SAID THE WOMAN,
SORRY, SORRY.
>>> GOOGLE EARTH HAS RELEASED A
NEW FEATURE THAT ALLOWS PEOPLE TO SEE A TIME LAPSE
OF HOW THEIR
NEIGHBORHOOD HAS CHANGED IN THE
LAST 40 YEARS.
DON'T REMIND ME, SAID MY
GRANDPA.
VIDEO POSTED
A POLICE OFFICER IN SAN
FRANCISCO PULLING OVER A DRIVERLESS CAR
AND PULLING AWAY
AFTER THE OFFICER SAW NO ONE WAS
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
STILL AMAZING, HE STILL MANAGED
TO SHOOT AN UNARMED BLACK GUY.
>>> KRISPY KREME
>>> KRISPY KREME IS RUNNING A
PROMOTION OFFERING A DOZEN DOUGHNUTS FOR $4.11,
THE AVERAGE
PRICE OF A GALLON OF GAS.
NOW YOUR CAR IS GOING TO HAVE TO
WORK HARDER
TO DRAG YOUR FAT ASS
AROUND.
DO SOME COMEDY AND I'VE ALWAYS
SAID NO.
WE'RE A SERIOUS NEWS PROGRAM AND
LAST WEEK I GOT DRUNK ENOUGH TO
SAY YES.
HERE TO MAKE HIS NETWORK DEBUT,
MY DRIVER, CAESAR PEREZ.
>> HEY.
85 WINBOARD AVENUE EAST HAMPTON,
RIGHT?
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO SAY MY
HOME ADDRESS.
YOU WANTED TO TRY STAND UP?
>> I GOT TO.
I HOPE THIS CROWD CAN HANDLE IT.
>> WE'LL SEE.
TAKE IT AWAY.
>> HEY, WEEKEND UPDATE, HOW ARE
ARE YOU?
>> ANYONE HERE GOT A FAMILY?
ME TOO MAN, I GOT A CRAZY FAM
ILIA.
LIKE MY CRAZY NEPHEW, CAR LETO.
HE HAS NINE LIZARDS AND NOW
WANTS ANOTHER ONE.
HOW ABOUT INSTEAD YOU GET ONE
GIRLFRIEND.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD CAESAR.
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
IB THINK THAT WAS KIND OF MEAN.
CAN WE EDIT THAT OUT?
>> OH, SORRY, WE'RE FAMOUSLY
LIVE.
>> WHAT KIND OF MAN SAYS
SOMETHING LIKE THAT ABOUT HIS
NEPHEW?
I GOT TO APOLOGIZE.
CAR LETO, I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU GET A GIRLFRIEND WHENEVER
YOU'RE READY.
WHATEVER MAKES YOU HAPPY.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A GREAT DAD
ONE DAY.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> THAT'S REALLY SWEET BUT I
DON'T THINK WE NEED WORRY.
JUST TRUST YOUR MATERIAL.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
ANYONE HERE GOT A PISTON?
I GOT A CRAZY SISTER.
LOOK AT HER.
SHE GOT PURPLE HAIR.
YOU TRYING TO LAND A DAY WITH AN
OOMPA.
LOOMPA.
THAT'S THE WORST MISTAKE SHE
MADE SINCE GIVING BIRTH TO
CARLITO
>> CAESAR.
>> I DID IT AGAIN.
IT'S ALMOST EASTER.
JESUS IS GOING TO WAKE UP IN HIS
GRAVE AND BE SO DISAPPOINTED IN
ME.
YOUR FAMILY DOESN'T CARE THAT
YOU SMELL OR NAME YOUR LIZARDS
AFTER SUBSTANCE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE JOKES AREN'T YOUR
THINGS OR APOLOGIES.
>> I SHOULD STICK TO
IMPRESSIONS, LIKE THE ONE OF MY
AUNT LISA.
SHE'S CRAZY OLD.
SHE'S LIKE MY SKIN IS SO
WRIRNGALLED.
WHY DOES CARLITO KEEP TAKING MY
LOTION?
CAESAR.
EASY, SEIZER.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S TEARING ME APART.
CARLITO, LISTEN.
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED.
YOU WERE ONLY STAELTING IT TO
MOISTURIZE YOUR LIZARD.
YOU CAN BE A GROSS NERD YOUR
WHOLE LIFE IS AND STILL BE
SUCCESSFUL.
JUST LOOK AT COLIN JOST.
>> MY DRIVER, CAESAR EVERYBODY.
THE WEEKEND UPDATE.
GOODNIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
HI.
I'M TARNURIA.
>> AND I'M EZRA --
>> AND WE'RE IN CHARGE OF THE
GOD KING'S WEEKLY DEBAUCHED
PARTY HERE IN THE THRONE ROOM.
WHY DON'T WE START BY GIVING
OURSELVES A ROUND OF APPLAUSE?
>> YEAH, THIS PARTY, ORGY,
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT.
IT'S A BIG PART OF MASTER'S
IMAGE AS THE DEPRAVED, INSANE
GOD KING.
SO, OBVIOUSLY WE WANT EVERYONE
TO MAKE SURE THEY KNOW THEIR
PART, OKAY?
>> NOW, IS OUR SNAKE GUY HERE?
>> YES, THAT'S ME.
>> LOVE THE SNAKE.
AND WHAT WILL YOU BE DOING
DURING THE PARTY?
>> WELL I WAS TOLD TO CRUISE THE
ROOM AND MENACE PEOPLE WITH THE
SNAKE, BY SORT OF STICKING IT IN
THEIR FACES.
KIND OF JUST LIKE, "MM.
HM, LOOK AT THE -- YEAH, LOOK AT
THE SNAKE IN YOUR FACE."
A-HA, THAT KIND OF THING.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I LOVE THAT.
VERY THREATENING AND SEXUAL,
WHICH IS DIVINE.
NOW, DO I HAVE ANY SENSUOUS
WOMAN AND HER TENDER BOY?
>> OH, I BELIEVE THAT'S ME.
>> AND MOI.
>> UH, ONE QUESTION.
WHEN IT COMES TO MY LITTLE
TENDER BOY, SHOULD I TEASE HIM
WITH SWEET TEMPTINGS LIKE SO?
>> OH!
OH!
OH, OH!
>> OR MAYBE, I CAN PUNISH HIM
FOR BEING INSOLENT BY SMACKING
HIM ON HIS VIRGIN BEHIND.
>> AND CAN WE AUDITION THAT?
>> OH!
OH!
OH, OH, OH!
>> SO, SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
>> HONESTLY, I LOVE BOTH.
>> HI, I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
UM, I'M THE GUY WHO SPITS FIRE
BALLS AT PEOPLE ENTERING THE
ROOM.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE
GOOD WITH THE ACTION.
SO, I'LL BE BY THE DOOR, AND
WHEN SOMEONE COMES IN, IT'LL
JUST BE LIKE, "WELCOME TO THE
DEN OF EARTHLY DELIGHT!"
AND I CAN DIAL THAT UP OR DOWN,
WHATEVER YOU NEED.
>> IT'S FEELING GOOD TO ME RIGHT
THERE.
AND I LOVE THE NO EYEBROWS.
>> OH, MY GOSH, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
YEAH, THEY BURNED OFF.
>> OH.
NOW, IS OUR OLD WOMAN CAKED IN
MAKEUP WITH ROTTEN TEETH WHO
LAUGHS HERE?
>> PRESENT.
YEAH, I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I WAS
THINKING FOR THE LAUGH.
UH, JUST LET ME FIND IT.
LIKE THAT?
>> EXACTLY.
>> YEAH, I WAS TOLD TO JUST HANG
IN THE SHADOWS, BUT EMERGE IN
MOMENTS OF UNEASE.
>> YEAH.
WELL, GREAT, YEAH.
UNSETTLING MUSIC HERE?
>> UH, YEAH.
WE JUST WANTED TO GIVE YOU GUYS
A TASTE FOR TONIGHT.
I WAS THINKING SOMETHING, LIKE,
LOUD AND ABRASIVE LIKE --
**
DOES THAT WORK?
>> YES, THAT REALLY CAPTURES THE
FEELING OF SEXUAL DOOM, SO,
UM --
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A CURSED ORGY
AFTER ALL.
>> YES, RIGHT.
AND SPEAKING TO THE ORGY OF IT
ALL, WHO IS HAVING SEX?
>> THAT WOULD BE US.
NEVER WORK A DAY IN YOUR LIFE.
>> YES, SO TRUE.
NOW, WE WANT THE SEX TO BLEND IN
WITH THE PARTY, YOU UNDERSTAND?
BUT NOT THE EVENT, GOT IT.
>> RIGHT.
IT'S HAPPENING, BUT IT'S NOT THE
FOCUS.
I CAN DO THAT.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
EXACTLY.
'CAUSE I FEEL WE WANT THIS TO
LOOK LIKE ONE BIG UNDULATING
MASS OF SKIN AND HAIR AND
FLUIDS.
THAT'S OUR NORTH STAR.
OH, OH, AND DO WE HAVE SOMEONE
WHO WILL BE FANNING THEM WITH A
HUGE FEATHER?
>> I'M ON IT.
>> AND I ASSUME YOU HAVE --
>> AN ENORMOUS PENIS THAT I'LL
JUST HAVE OUT THE WHOLE TIME?
>> SORRY, I'M LATE.
I'M FROM THE TEMPLE OF --, AND I
WAS TOLD YOU WANTED A GOAT FOR
THE ORGY?
YEAH, SO AM I WORSHIPPING IT, OR
MAKING OUT WITH IT, OR WHAT ARE
WE DOING?
>> OH, WELL, MAKING OUT WITH IT
IS INTERESTING.
UM.
LET'S WALK THROUGH THAT AT HALF
SPEED, JUST SO WE HAVE IT DOWN.
UM, I'LL CUE YOU FOR THE GOAT
AND --
LOVING THIS.
GREAT, GREAT FEATHER WORK.
>> YEAH.
>> GREAT WRITHING.
AND ACTION, GOAT.
>> BLESSED BE THE HORNED WONDER.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> WOW, YEAH.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> THAT IS GONNA BE SUCH A SHOW
STOPPER.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
CAN -- CAN I ASK, WHEN THE
ORGY'S IN FULL SPRING, SHOULD I
PUNISH MY TENDER BOY FOR
WATCHING, SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
>> OH!
>> -- DIRTY BOY, SO DIRTY.
DOES THAT PLAY?
>> I THINK THAT PLAYS
BEAUTIFULLY.
>> OKAY.
>> WELL, I THINK THAT'S
EVERYONE.
OH, WAIT, IS OUR PUCKISH IMP
HERE?
>> THAT'D BE ME.
>> OH.
NOT WHAT I EXPECTED.
>> I KNOW I'M A LITTLE OLDER
THAN MOST PUCKISH IMPS, BUT I
WAS TOLD THE GIG WAS MOSTLY
STEALING PEOPLE'S WINE AND
SCAMPERING AWAY.
MAYBE I COULD SHOW YOU WHAT I
WAS THINKING?
>> OKAY, LET'S GET --
>> OKAY, WOW, I STAND CORRECTED.
>> REALLY GOOD.
REALLY PUCKISH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S HERE.
OKAY, EVERYONE, PLACES EVERYONE!
MUSIC.
THIS IS IT.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, MY DAUGHTER,
LIZZO.
* WOKE UP THIS MORNING *
TO SOMEBODY IN A VIDEO
TALKING ABOUT SOMETHING
I POSTED IN A VIDEO *
* FAMOUS, PRETTY, NEW
BUT I'VE BEEN USED
TO PEOPLE JUDGING ME
THAT'S WHY I MOVE *
WITH ME
I'M USED TO FEELING ALONE *
* SO, I THOUGHT THAT
I'D LET YOU KNOW
IN CASE NOBODY
TOLD YOU TODAY *
* YOU'RE SPECIAL
IN CASE NOBODY
MADE YOU BELIEVE
YOU'RE SPECIAL *
* WELL, I'LL ALWAYS
TELL YOU THE SAME
YOU'RE SPECIAL
I'M SO GLAD THAT *
* YOU'RE STILL WITH US
BROKEN, BUT DAMN
YOU'RE STILL PERFECT
CAN YOU IMAGINE A WORLD *
* WHERE EVERYBODY'S THE SAME
AND YOU CAN CANCEL A GIRL
'CAUSE SHE JUST
WANTED TO CHANGE *
* HOW CAN YOU THROW STONES
IF YOU AIN'T BEEN
THROUGH HER PAIN
THAT'S WHY WE FEEL *
* SO ALONE
THAT'S WHY WE FEEL
SO MUCH SHAME
I'M USED TO FEELING ALONE *
* SO, I THOUGHT THAT
I'D LET YOU KNOW
IN CASE NOBODY
TOLD YOU TODAY *
* YOU'RE SPECIAL
IN CASE NOBODY
MADE YOU BELIEVE
YOU'RE SPECIAL *
* WELL, I'LL ALWAYS
TELL YOU THE SAME
YOU'RE SPECIAL
I'M SO GLAD *
* THAT YOU'RE STILL
WITH US
I'M SO GLAD, SO GLAD, SO GLAD
BROKEN, BUT DAMN *
* YOU'RE STILL PERFECT
I'M SO GLAD, SO GLAD
SO GLAD *
>> I KNOW IT'S BEEN HARD, BUT
I'M STILL GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
* IN CASE NOBODY
TOLD YOU TODAY
YOU'RE SPECIAL
IN CASE NOBODY *
* MADE YOU BELIEVE
YOU'RE SPECIAL
WELL, I'LL ALWAYS *
* TELL YOU THE SAME
YOU'RE SPECIAL
I'M SO GLAD THAT
YOU'RE STILL WITH US *
* I'M SO GLAD, SO GLAD
SO GLAD
BROKEN, BUT DAMN
YOU'RE STILL PERFECT *
* I'M SO GLAD, SO GLAD
SO GLAD
BECAUSE YOU ARE
YOU ARE YOU ARE *
* SO SPECIAL
HEY *
>>> STOP, STOP.
THIS IS A DISASTER.
AND OUR FLAUTIST GETS FOOD
POISONING?
HOW AM I GOING TO FIND A
REPLACEMENT ON SUCH SHORT
NOTICE?
SOMEBODY LOOKING FOR A FLUTIST?
>> A FLAUTIST, BUT, YES.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> THE NAME'S TONY BANKS.
AND I JUST HAPPEN TO BE MANAGING
THE GREATEST FLUTIST OF OUR
TIME.
ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE TO YOU THE
MASTER OF HER CRAFT.
LIPS AND LUNGS SENT FROM GOD
HERSELF.
THE INCOMPARABLE BEVERLY GAGS.
>> GOOD EVENING, YOUR HONOR.
>> I'M NOT A JUDGE.
I'M A CONDUCTOR.
MS. GAGS, IS IT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE AFTER YOU HERE HER PLAY,
YOU GOING TO GAG.
I MADE IT UP MYSELF.
>> OKAY, WELL, THAT'S WONDERFUL.
BUT THIS IS THE DEVRY INSTITUTE
SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA.
IF SHE WANTS FIRST CHAIR, I MUST
HEAR HER PLAY.
>> YOU AIN'T SAID NOTHING BUT A
WORD.
>> BITCH, SHOW THAT MAN WHAT YOU
GOT.
**
>> WOW.
LOOK AT THAT BREATH CONTROL.
>> YEAH, AND EVERYTHING ELSE
GOING ON TOO.
>> SO, SHE GOT THE PART?
>> WELL, SHE'S CLEARLY TALENTED,
BUT I JUST DON'T THINK SHE'S OUR
STYLE.
>> I DON'T KNOW, SIR, WE'RE IN
QUITE A BIND.
>> THE SHOW IS IN THREE HOURS.
DON'T DO THIS.
>> WELL, WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT
WAY, I SUPPOSE WE CAN ALLOW A
QUICK AUDITION.
SO, TAKE YOUR SEAT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
YOU WON'T REGRET IT,
MR. CONDUCTOR.
>> FROM THE TOP OF ODE TO JOY.
* *
>> STOP, STOP.
PLEASE.
>> WHY YOU STOPPING, JIM?
SHE WAS JUST GETTING IN THE
GROOVE?
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE BECAUSE SHE WAS TWERKING
ON OUR BASSOONIST.
THIS IS A TRADITIONAL SYMPHONY.
YOU KNOW, ONE WHERE YOU SIT DOWN
AND PLAY.
>> OH.
SO, YOU WANT ME TO SIT DOWN ON
THE TWERK.
I GOT YOU.
**
>> NO, NO, NO.
NO.
NOBODY WANTS THAT.
>> I MEAN -- I WOULDN'T SAY
NOBODY.
>> LOOK.
MS. BEVERLY --
>> GAGS.
>> YOU THINK WE SAID HER LAST
NAME ENOUGH, OKAY?
>> I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> YEAH, SIR, THAT'S A TALL
ORDER, BUDDY.
>> HOW IS THAT A TALL ORDER?
YOU JUST SIT DOWN AND YOU PLAY A
SOLO.
>> IF YOU SAY SO.
>> STOP.
STOP.
WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU WERE PLAYING SO WELL BEFORE.
>> WELL, SIR, THE TRUTH IS --
**
THANKS, GIRL.
THE TRUTH IS THE ONLY WAY I CAN
PLAY THE FLUTE IS IF I'M
TWERKING.
SEE, TWO YEARS AGO, I COULDN'T
PLAY ANY INSTRUMENT.
AND THEN ONE DAY LAST SUMMER,
THE ICE CREAM TRUCK PULLED UP,
AND I HEARD THAT JINGLE.
AND THAT BEAT HAD MY BODY MOVING
IN WAYS THAT MADE ME FEEL
POWERFUL, LIKE I COULD DO
ANYTHING, EVEN PLAY THE FLUTE.
AND THE REST IS HISTORY.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT THIS IS
OUR FINAL PERFORMANCE OF THE
SEASON, AND IT WILL BE JUST TOO
DISTRACTING IF SOMEONE IS
TWERKING.
>> WELL, THEN, WHAT IF WE ALL
ARE TWERKING?
>> WHAT?
>> WE ARE THE DEVRY INSTITUTE
ORCHESTRA.
WE CAN DO THIS TOGETHER.
AND IF THAT MEANS I HAVE TO POP
THIS BOOTY FOR BEETHOVEN, THEN
SO BE IT.
**
>>> MAY THE NEXT CHAPTER BE AS
EXCITING AS THE LAST.
>> THANKS, BUDDY.
>> STILL CAN'T BELIEVE I FINALLY
QUIT MY JOB.
I REALIZED WHY AM I WASTING MY
LIFE AT A JOB I HATE WHEN I
DON'T HAVE TO WORK.
SO, I TOLD MY BOSS I QUIT.
>> I'M SO GLAD HE DID.
NOW WE CAN FINALLY START LIVING
OUR LIVES.
>> SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
WHAT'S NEXT?
>> EUROPE, BRAZIL, YOU NAME IT.
AND AS FAR AS MONEY GOES, WE'RE
NOT WORRIED.
STEVE HAS HIS INVESTMENTS.
>> INVESTING.
I GOT TO GET INTO THAT.
>> YOU MUST, PAUL.
FINANCIAL SAFETY IS SO
IMPORTANT.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE YOUR MONEY WORK
FOR YOU.
YOU CAN INVEST IN A FUND, A
BUSINESS OR, IN MY CASE, I HAVE
MY BEANIE BABIES.
>> OH.
WOW.
>> I'M HOLDING ON TO THESE BAD
BOYS SINCE 1993 AND MY FRIENDS
ARE, IT'S TIME TO CASH IN.
>> NEEDLESS TO SAY, WE WON'T BE
WORRYING ABOUT MONEY FOR QUITE
SOME TIME.
>> THAT IS REALLY COOL.
BUT YOU KNOW THOUGH, I THINK I
HEARD A LOT OF BEANIE BABIES
AREN'T ACTUALLY WORTH THAT MUCH.
>> HOW DO YOU MEAN?
>> I MEAN, YES, THEY'RE
ESSENTIALLY WORTHLESS.
>> HUH.
ALL OF THEM?
>> MOST.
>> HUH.
GOD DAM IT.
>> THAT WAS OUR SAVINGS.
>> IT WAS WORTHLESS.
DON'T YOU SEE MY LIFE'S WORK IS
WORTHLESS.
>> YOU HAVE CAN GO TO YOUR JOB.
>> I CAN'T BECAUSE I BENT OVER,
GRAB MY CHEEKS AND PUFFTED THEM
LIKE HE COULD HAVE DONE IN THE
POCKETS.
I WENT SOMETHING LIKE SCREW YOU
GUYS, I'M OUT OF HERE.
>> THAT'S TERRIBLE.
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO,
STEVE?
WE'RE GOING TO LOSE THE HOUSE.
>> MAYBE I START DRAWING MARIO
FULL TIME.
LAST WEEK I DREW YOU A MARIO.
IO SAID IT WAS THE BEST ONE YOU
HAD EVER SEEN.
>> IT WAS.
IT WAS BETTER THAN THE ACTUAL
MARIO BUT DRAWING MARIO ISN'T A
DRAW, STEVE.
>> SOMEBODY SOMEWHERE IS DRAWING
MARIO.
DO YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
NINTENDO HAS NO INTEREST IN THE
MAN WHO DID THIS?
>> I'M SORRY.
BUT THAT ISN'T REALLY A VERY
GOOD MARIO.
>> IS THAT LOUIGI?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE FOOLIE.
IT'S AN OBJECTIVELY PERFECT
MARIO.
>> BETTER THAN THE ACTUAL MARIO.
>> BUT STEVE, THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
I SHOULDN'T BE DRINKING THAT.
THE REASON I'M WORRIED ABOUT
MONEY IS BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO
BE A DADDY.
>> MY GOD.
I'M GOING TO BE A DADDY?
BABY, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>>> TONIGHT WAS THE BEST NIGHT
EVER.
>>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THE
CAST AND CREW.
THANK YOU, ME.
HA HA!
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY!
**