>>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S ALMOST
CHRISTMAS.
- IS IT ALREADY YEAH.
- THAT'S RIGHT
MARIAH CAREY SAW HER SHADOW.
BEEN
I'M STILL SIGNING MY CHECKS 2019.
I'M CONCERNED YOU'RE STILL
WRITING CHECKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
THE WHOLE WORLD IS SO
OVERWHELMING SOMETIMES
WAR
PRINCE HARRY AND MEGHAN DOCUMENTARIES.
HELPLESS
I SHOULD
BE DOING MORE FOR MYSELF AND FRIENDS AND SOCIETY,
BUT THEN I REMEMBER--
♪ IT'S CHRISTMAS,
AND ALL OF MY STRESS FADES AWAY ♪
♪ ALL THE PROBLEMS AND  ISSUES AND CRYING AND TISSUES
CAN WAIT UNTIL JANUARY ♪
YOU JUST GIVE YOUR CONCERNS A
DELAY?
♪ TILL CHRISTMAS
YOU JUST BLOCK ALL OUT. BURY YOUR FEELINGS
DEEP INSIDE SO THEY CAN'T HURT YOU
EXACTLY.
LIKE--
♪ MY DRINKING,
IT'S STARTING TO GET OUT OF HAND ♪
♪ I KNOW IT MAY HAVE CROSSED
INTO A DARK PLACE
WHEN BURGER
KING SAID I WAS BANNED ♪
♪ MAYBE I'LL JUST MAKE THAT MY BRAND,
TILL CHRISTMAS ♪
YOU'RE GETTING IT
- WHAT ABOUT YOU
- I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME TRY
♪ MY MENTAL HEALTH
HASN'T BEEN GREAT ♪
♪ I WAKE UP AT NOON, THE SUN
SOMEHOW SETTING,
AND I FALL BACK
ASLEEP AROUND 8:00 ♪
♪ BUT I CAN LIVE IN A DELUSIONA STATE
FOR CHRISTMAS ♪
WE HEARD YOU GUYS SING ABOUT
YOUR ANXIETY IN AN UNHEALTHY WAY.
JOIN
BACKGROUND
SURE. WE CAN COMPLAIN ABOUT
SPECIFIC PEOPLE TOO LIKE--
♪ ELON,
WHY DOES HE OWN ALL THE STUFF ♪
♪ WHY DOES HE HAVE TO RUN TESLA
AND TWITTER,
WAS OUTER SPACE NOT
ENOUGH ♪
♪ AND HITLER,
WHEN DID HITLER COME BACK ♪
♪ DID WE BASICALLY ALL AGREE YEARS AGO
HITLER SHOULD NEVER
COME BACK ♪
♪ AND WHY ARE HIS NEW FANS
BLACK ♪
♪ CHRISTMAS,
LET'S BLOCK IT ALL
OUT FOR CHRISTMAS ♪
♪ IT'S OVER OCTOBER AND
NOVEMBER ♪
INTRODUCE
♪ FAMILY VISITS, YOU JUST WANT
TO HIDE ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY I DRINK EGGNOG WIT
THE XANEX INSIDE ♪
WRONG
♪ FORGET YOUR UNCLE IF YOU WAIT
TOO LONG ♪
♪ YOUR GRANDMA WON'T WHISPER
YOU'RE LIVING IN SIN ♪
♪ SO JUST TIKTOK ON THE TOILET
TILL YOUR ASS GIVES IN ♪
GIFTS
♪ IT'S EASIER TO BUY A GUN THAN
TICKETS TO TAYLOR SWIFT ♪
♪ STOP STRESSING ABOUT EVERY
DECISION ♪
MENTAL
♪ JUST FOCUS ON WHO'S GOING TO
DIE IN WHITE LOTUS ♪
♪ CUZ IT'S CHRISTMAS
DID SOMEBODY ORDER GRUB HUB
MY DINNER IS HERE
I GOT ITALIAN.
THAT'S ONE ORDER OF GARLIC
BREAD AND 12 BOTTLES OF WINE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN LEAVE THE WINE OVER
THERE.
- DID YOU WANT TO GARLIC BREAD?
- I THINK YOU KNOW I DON'T.
I FEEL LIKE ALL OUR HOLIDAY
WORRIES HAVE GONE AWAY.
ME TOO.
EXCEPT FOR A COUPLE OF THINGS
HEAD
♪ SCHOOLS ARE FAILING, KIDS
DON'T KNOW JACK ♪
♪ COVID NEVER LEFT AND ALSO IT'
BACK ♪
AWFUL
♪ R. KELLY DROPPED AN ALBUM
CALLED I ADMIT IT ♪
♪ I REALLY WANT TO SHOUT,
BUT I'M BLOCKING EVERYTHING OUT
FOR CHRISTMAS ♪
OKAY.
SO YOU BURY ALL YOUR FEELINGS
FOR CHRISTMAS, OKAY,
BUT WHAT
HAPPENS IN JANUARY
WELL, THEN, WE EXPLODE.
♪ WE FREAK OUT AND THREATEN OUR
EX ♪
♪ WE DRINK TO THE POINT WHERE WE
CONTEMPLATE MURDER
AND ACCEPT
VENMO PAYMENTS FOR SEX ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S JUST WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
BECAUSE FOR NOW
IT'S CHRISTMAS ♪
HO, HO, AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK--
WAIT
DID YOU SAY VENMO PAYMENTS FOR
SEX?
IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT
MUSICAL GUEST, BRANDI CARLILE.
AND YOUR HOSTS, STEVE MARTIN AND
MARTIN SHORT
LADIES
>>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU SO MUCH
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE
I'M--
AND I'M STEVE MARTIN.
- AND WE'RE SO EXCITED--
- AND WHAT A THRILL IT IS FOR US
TO BE HOEGS "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE."
STEVE, HOW MANY TIMES HAVE
YOU HOSTED
OH, GOSH, I HAVEN'T REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT IT
HIT IT
AND HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU
HOSTED, MARTY?
HIT IT.
I'M KIND OF AN A NOSTALGIA MODE
I WANT TO SHOW YOU A PHOTO FROM
ONE OF MY EARLY HOSTING YEARS.
THAT'S ME WITH JOHN, DAN AND
MICK JAGGER.
AND RIGHT AFTER THIS PHOTO WAS TAKEN,
WE TESTED POSITIVE FOR EVERYTHING.
STEVE, WE ARE LIKE HARRY AND
MEGHAN
NO ONE IS ROOTING FOR US, BUT
YOU'LL TUNE IN TO WATCH ANYWAY
WHAT'S BEEN SO FABULOUS THIS
WEEK IS GETTING TO KNOW THE NEW CAST
STEVE, HONESTLY, THEY LOVE YOU
BEHIND YOUR BACK, THE NEW CAST
REFER TO YOU AS A WHOLE
ENTERTAINER.
THAT'S SWEET.
WELL, I ADDED THE WORD
ENTERTAINER.
AND I HAVE TO SAY THAT FOR
ME, WORKING WITH MARTY SHORT
IS
LIKE WORD CUP SOCCER.
SOMEHOW, I JUST CAN'T GET
INTO IT.
WE ARE CURRENTLY WORKING ON
THE THIRD SEASON OF OUR HULU SERIES
"O"ONLY MURDERS IN THE
BUILDING".
OUR SHOW IS LIKE STEVE AT THE URINAL,
IT STREAMS FOR 32 MINUTES.
NOW, YOU KNOW, THIS IS KIND
OF INTERESTING
EVERY NIGHT BEFORE THE SHOW,
MARTY AND I HAVE A RITUAL WE DO
TO PREPARE FOR THE EVENING'S
PERFORMANCE.
WE WERE DOING IT BACKSTAGE,
AND I NOTICED ONE OF THE BACK STAGE
CREW WAS VIDEO TAPING US,
AND I
THOUGHT, THAT WOULD BE
INTERESTING TO SHOW THE AUDIENCE
SO HERE IS MARTY AND I GETTING
READY FOR TONIGHT'S SHOW.
AND CAN I SAY, STEVE--
LET THEM LAUGH.
CAN I SAY TRUTHFULLY I ADORE
WORKING WITH YOU
AND I HOPE WE CAN DO THIS
FOREVER.
OF COURSE I THOUGHT ABOUT
THAT, BUT I REALIZED YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO LIVE FOREVER,
AND THAT
IS SAD BECAUSE YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO HEAR THE WONDERFUL THINGS
I'M
GOING TO SAY AT YOUR MEMORIAL.
SO I THOUGHT, WHY WAIT
SO WHAT I DID WAS I WROTE UP
YOUR EULOGY
SO YOU CAN HEAR IT NOW.
THAT IS SUCH A COINCIDENCE
BECAUSE
I DID THE SAME THING
I WROTE YOUR EULOGY.
REALLY?
- LET'S READ THEM TOGETHER
- WHY NOT.
THIS IS A SAD MOMENT.
CAN YOU PLAY SOMETHING SAD FOR
US, PLEASE
NOT SAD ENOUGH.
ANYTHING SADDER?
NO, NO, NO.
DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING REALLY,
REALLY SAD
SO, MARTY, I DEDICATE THIS
EULOGY TO YOU.
WOW, NOT MUCH OF A TURNOUT
MARTY DID NOT WANT TO BE DE CREMATED.
TOO LATE
BUT I'LL ALWAYS BE HAUNTED BY
MARTY'S LAST WORDS
TESLA AUTO PILOT, ENGAGE
THERE ARE SO MANY GREAT THINGS
THAT I COULD SAY ABOUT
STEVE MARTIN,
BUT THIS HARDLY
SEEMS THE TIME NOR THE PLACE
OH, STEVE, YOU BLAND OVERRATED
WHITE HAIRED SON OF A BITCH.
WHERE DID YOU GO
I KNOW STEVE IS LOOKING DOWN ON
US RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE HE ALWAYS
LOOKED DOWN ON EVERYBODY
AND YES, I LEARNED SO MUCH FROM
STEVE.
FOR EXAMPLE, HE TAUGHT ME YOU
DON'T NEED TO RESTRICT A URINAL
TO JUST NUMBER ONE
EVEN AT THE END, MARTY HAD A
WONDERFUL GIRLFRIEND
SMART, BEAUTIFUL, AND SO REALISTIC.
BUT MARTY WAS ALWAYS SEXUALLY ACTIVE
AS LONG AS THERE WERE
BATTERIES IN THE HOUSE
BUT MARTY WAS TAKEN AWAY FROM US
TOO SOON
BUT SADLY, NOT BEFORE HE PLAYED
JACK FROST IN "SANTA CLAUS 3".
OH, STEVE
OH, STEVE, IT'S SO HARD TO
LOOK AT YOU IN THAT OPEN CASKET,
MOTIONLESS, COLORLESS, STIFF,
SO LIFE LIKE.
AND YET, SEEING YOU IN YOUR
CASKET REMINDS ME OF THAT
CLASSIC SNL SKETCH,
DICK IN A BOX.
THANK YOU.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WITH STEVE
GONE,
DOWNLOADS SHOULD BE SO
MUCH FASTER ON PORN HUB.
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME WHAT STEVE
WAS REALLY LIKE,
AND I WOULD
SAY, I DON'T KNOW, YOU'RE HIS WIFE
AND HE'S SUCH A GREAT DAD,
AND
YOU CAN TELL THAT FROM HIS CHILDREN
THEY'RE SO POLITE.
YOU GO TO HIS HOUSE AND THEY
SAY, WOULD YOU LIKE ANYTHING,
MR. SHORT?
CAN I GET YOU A DRINK,
CAN YOU GIVE THIS NOTE TO THE
POLICE, MR. SHORT?
NOW THAT MARTY IS GONE, WHO
WILL I EVER WORK WITH?
HOW ABOUT ME?
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW
STICK
BYE
PBS
CURIOUS GEORGE
SCIENCE ROOM
CHEMISTRY,
HOW LOVELY ARE THY
IONS ♪
I LOVE THAT SONG SO MUCH.
- HEY, KIDS, I'M DR. SCIENCE.
- AND I'M MR. SCIENCE.
AND WHAT BETTER TIME THAN THE
HOLIDAYS TO LEARN ABOUT THE
SCIENCE OF SNOW.
HELPING US TODAY ARE LONI AND
JOSH
HI
HAPPY HOLIDAYS, GUYS
LONI, WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE
HOLIDAY TRADITION?
- CHRISTMAS.
- OKAY.
MYSELF
WELL-- JOSH, WHAT DO YOU WANT
FOR CHRISTMAS?
TO FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENED TO MY BROTHER
OKAY.
WELL, I WAS NOT EXPECTING THAT
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD SAY YOU WANT
A SKATEBOARD OR SOMETHING,
BUT
I'M SURE YOUR BROTHER WILL BE
FINE
LET'S TALK ABOUT SNOW.
WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT SNOW?
FOR ONE, SNOW FORMS IN THE BIG
THINGS IN THE SKY CALLED--
- LONI
- STARS.
NO.
JOSH
STARTS WITH A C.
SI, SENOR.
NO, THE LETTER
C. C-WORD
THE C WORD IS BAD.
CAN'T SAY THAT.
NOT THE C WORD.
IT'S BIG, IT'S WHITE IT'S PUFFY.
MY DAD?
CLOUDS.
SNOW FORMS INSIDE CLOUDS.
LET'S THINK BEFORE WE ANSWER.
NOW SNOW FORMS WHEN IT GETS SO
COLD THAT THE WATER VAPOR INSIDE A CLOUD
- DOES WHAT, LONI?
- SNOWS.
NO. IT'S HOW WATER TURNS INTO AN ICE.
IT STARTS WITH AN F.
JOSH
PHFOE SYNTHESIS.
WRONG
STARTS WITH AN F--
- FREE--
- BRITNEY
GUYS, FREEZE. FREEZE.
NO, YOU.THE WORD WAS FREEZE.
JUST LIKE THERE ARE
RAINSTORMS, ALREADY ALSO SNOWSTORMS.
TRUE.
I WASN'T ASKING, BUT YES,
THAT IS TRUE.
YOU DON'T HIGH FIVE EACH
OTHER BASED--
DON'T FIST BUMP
EITHER
STOP IT RIGHT NOW.
FOR OUR EXPERIMENT TODAY,
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE OUR OWN SNOWSTORM.
IT WILL OBVIOUSLY NOT BE AS BIG
AS A REAL ONE.
BUT EVEN IF SOMETHING'S SMALL,
IT CAN STILL--
FEEL GOOD FOR THE GIRL?
I DON'T FOLLOW THIS.
BECAUSE MY SISTER TOLD ME
THAT EVEN IF THE GUY HAS A SMALL THING,
IT CAN STILL FEEL GOOD IF
THE GUY KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
NO.
IT'S TEACH A BIG LESSON.
YOU WERE VERY, VERY WRONG.
YOUR SISTER, HOWEVER, IS
VERY, VERY RIGHT
NOW, TO DO THIS AT HOME,
WE'LL NEED SOME WATER IN A GLASS, BABY OIL--
DON'T TOUCH THAT, PLEASE, GUYS.
STOP IT.
AND PAINT-- STOP TOUCHING
IT, PLEASE.
MAKE SURE TO HAVE A GROWN UP
HELP YOU FIRST
SAFETY FIRST.
I HAVE A FUN SAFETY JOKE, JOSH
- KNOCK, KNOCK.
- COME IN.
NO. JOSH
YOU SAY, KNOCK, KNOCK, WHO'S
THERE.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
WHO'S THERE SAFETY. HI.
I'M JOSH.
DO YOU NOT KNOW HOW THIS
WORKS?
YOU SAY SAFETY WHO
KNOCK, KNOCK.
SAFETY WHO.
OH, GAH
ARE YOU OKAY, MR. SCIENCE
I'M UPSET.
COME BACK, LITTLE BUDDY
COME BACK.
BREATHE IN, BREATHE OUT
OKAY.
WE PUT EVERYTHING INTO OUR GLASS
HERE EXCEPT THE ALKASELTZER TO
SHOW YOU WHAT HAPPENS WHEN COLD
AIR MEETS WARM AIR
GET IN CLOSE, GUYS
THREE, TWO, ONE, SCIENCE. WOW
JOSH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOT MUCH.
WE HAVE TWO WEEKS OFF FOR WINTER BREAK.
NOT IN YOUR LIFE.
IN HERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
DO YOU SEE WHAT I SEE?
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
YOUR FINGER
NO.
SOMETHING'S GOING ON
DO YOU SEE WHAT I SEE?
♪ DO YOU SEE WHAT I SEE, A STAR
A STAR ♪
SHUT UP, YOU IDIOTS
LOOK WHAT WE'VE MADE
IT'S A WHAT?
IT'S A ME, MARIO.
NO.
IT'S NOT A ME MARIO.
GO TO COMMERCIAL.
TURN THE CAMERA OFF
I'M GOING TO CHOKE THIS KID!
CHELSEA?
YOUR EX CHELSEA YEAH.
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT HER
IN A WHILE.
WHEN YOU GUYS BROKE UP, IT
WAS SUCH A RELIEF.
SHE WAS SUCH A NEGATIVE PERSON.
A BAD PERSON.
WHENEVER SHE WOULD WALK INTO
A ROOM, IT WAS LIKE, I GUESS
THIS ROOM IS GOING TO SUCK A
LITTLE BIT.
I WOULD HAVE DAY TREATMENTS
OF HER BEING STEPD ON BY A GIANT.
SHE WOULD ALWAYS HAVE FOOD ON
HER SHIRT LIKE A BABY.
LIKE DOES THIS FOOD BELONG IN
MY NOUGT OR ON MY SHIRT.
SHE STUNG.
SHE WAS STINKY.
EWW, CHELSEA.
WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH CHELSEA
WE GOT BACK TOGETHER.
YOU DID
AND SHE'S RIGHT HERE. CHELSEA.
CHELSEA.
IT IS SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
JOHN, WHAT THE HELL?
SO ARE YOU GUYS SERIOUS OR CASUAL
JOHN JUST PROPOSED.
WEDDING IS IN JUNE.
LOVE IT
CAN'T WAIT TO MEET THE FAMILIAR.
YOU ALREADY DID
THEY'RE ON ZOOM.
WHAT'S UP, FAMILY
Y'ALL DON'T SEEM TOO HAPPY
WITH ME.
ANYONE TALKS CRAP ABOUT MY
DAUGHTER, I'LL HUNT YOU DOWN--
TURN THAT OFF
YOU REMEMBER THAT STUFF WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT EARLIER?
I DO.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT JOHN'S
OTHER EX COURTNEY.
COURTNEY WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
LIKE A FUGLY NERD.
WOW.
COURTNEY, DIDN'T SEE YOU.
WE DIDN'T MEAN TO INSULT YOU.
READ BACK THE WORDS.
SHE WAS LIKE A SLOPPY SEWER SCUM.
GET OUT OF HERE YOU WEIRDO.
DON'T TALK ABOUT HER THAT WAY.
SHE'S MY WIFE.
STEVE, COME ON.
YOU'RE OUR FAVORITE HOST.
FAVORITE HOST
DAMN IT
I'M TELLING MICHAEL CHE.
COME ON, GUYS
WHAT DID I TELL YOU ABOUT THE
RULES?
A, B, C RULE. YEAH.
ALWAYS BE KIND
YOU BROKE THE RULES.
BEN'S THE ONE WHO STARTED THIS.
CAN YOU NOT TALK ABOUT BEN
THAT WAY
HE'S RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S REALLY NOT COOL, MAN.
COME ON, EVERYBODY.
MARTIN, LET'S GO BACK TO MY APARTMENT.
YOU CAN ALL TAKE ONE THING HOME
WITH YOU. YEA
THANK YOU, STEVE.
ONE THING. AWESOME
♪ NOW I'M ALL ATO LOAN
YOU TALK CRAP ABOUT MY
DAUGHTER, YOU'RE DEAD.
A HAD, H!
BUFFALO.
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT
BUFFALO, I CAN HARDLY WAIT TO
GET THERE.
WOW, A REAL CHRISTMAS IN BUFFALO.
IT'S FINALLY HAPPENING.
JUST LIKE DEAR OLD PEPOO AND
MOO MOO USED TO TALK ABOUT.
THEY WOULD BE SO PROUD OF US.
MINUS SOME OF THE STUFF WE'VE
DONE.
WELL, I'M GLAD I SAT WITH YOU THREE.
YOU SEEM LIKE A FUN GROUP.
WE ARE FUN.
THANK YOU FOR NOTICING THAT.
WHERE YOU HEADED, MISTER?
ARE YOU GOING TO BUFFALO TWO OR
BUFFALO THREE?
THAT'S MY BUFFALO JOKE THAT I
DO.
YEAH.
NO, I'M JUST HEADING THERE ON
BUSINESS
THE ONLY REASON ANYONE WOULD
WANT TO GO TO BUFFALO.
ONLY REASON
BUT IT'S THE BEST PLACE TO SEE IT.
SEE WHAT?
ARE YOU MESSING WITH US
SNOW, OF COURSE.
♪ SNOW, SNOW, SNOW, SNOW
♪ IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE WE'LL
ALL BE THERE WITH SNOW ♪
♪ SNOW, I WANT TO WASH MY HANDS
MY HAIR, MY ASS WITH SNOW ♪
OH, WOW
THAT SOUNDS COLD
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE SNOW.
WE DON'T KNOW, SIR.
WE'VE NEVER SEEN IT.
NOT IN PERSON, ANYWAY
♪ SNOW, I WANT TO GO OUTSIDE AN
TOUCH A BUNCH OF SNOW ♪
♪ SNOW, TO KISS A GREAT BIG MAN
ENTIRELY MADE OF SNOW ♪
JUST KISS
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER JUST KISS. OKAY.
YEAH
MAYBE MORE
I'M JUST SO EXCITED FOR SNOW
IF I CLOSE MY EYES, I FEEL LIKE
I CAN ALMOST SEE IT.
♪
♪ WHERE IT'S SNOWING, THAT'S
WHERE I WANT TO BE ♪
♪ SNOWBALL ATE OOETING, THAT'S
WHAT I'LLDO ♪
♪ HOW I'M LONGING TO SLEEP ALL
NIGHT IN THE SNOW ♪
SLEEP IN THE SNOW
ARE YOU CRAZY?
FOR SNOW.
NOW I'M EXCITED FOR SNOW.
♪ WHAT IS CHRISTMAS WITH NO
SNOW ♪
♪ NO WHITE CHRISTMAS WITH NO,
NO, NO, SNOW ♪
♪ I'LL WASH MY HAIR WITH SNOW
WHY NOT
♪ FILL MY UNDERWEAR WITH SNOW.
IF THAT'S YOUR THING ♪
AND WHEN I SEE THE SNOW, I'M
GOING TO KNOW IT'S SNOW ♪
WELL, I WOULD HOPE SO.
♪ SNOW
SO YOU'VE REALLY NEVER SEEN SNOW
WHERE ARE YOU FROM
THE WOODS.
THE WOODS
YES.
ISN'T THERE SNOW THERE?
AT TIMES, BUT WE ALWAYS SLEEP
THROUGH IT.
OTHERWISE, WE WOULDN'T
SURVIVE THE WINTER.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE ALL THESE
NUTS WITH US.
OH, WOW NUTS.
THOSE ARE OURS!
OKAY.
SORRY.
BUT LISTEN, IT'S GETTING LATE.
♪ I WOULD LOVE TO STAY AND BEG
WITH YOU, BUT I HAVE TO GET SOME
SHUT EYE, GO TO SLEEP AND
DREAM ♪
♪ OF SNOW, SNOW, SNOW, SNOW,
SNOW ♪
OH, GOSH.
WELL, THAT SONG MADE ME SLEEPY
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
BUT IF YOU FALL ASLEEP, WE
BREAK THE SPELL.
WHAT SPELL?
OH, WE WON'T GET OUR
CHRISTMAS WISH
OH, BROTHER.
WHAT WISH
I WAS REALLY HOPING THEY
WOULD MAKE IT THIS TIME.
THOSE BEARS MAKE THE SAME
CHRISTMAS WISH EVERY YEAR, TO
TURN INTO HUMANS AND RIDE THE
TRAIN TO BUFFALO TO SEE SNOW
BUT THEY ALWAYS FALL ASLEEP AND HIBERNATE.
BEAR SNS WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING-- HEY
WAKE UP!
IT'S SNOWING OUTSIDE.
DON'T WAKE THEM UP.
ARE YOU INSANE
THEY'LL KILL US.
THEY'RE BEARS.
GOOD POINT.
WELL, MERRY CHRISTMAS, BEARS
OH, NUTS.
THOSE ARE OURS!
>>> CHILDREN OF ALL AGES, YOU'VE
COME TO THE RIGHT PLACE.
THE ACTUAL MR. CHRIS CRINGLE HAS
COME ALL THE WAY FROM THE NORTH POLE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
MY SCHEDULE IS A LITTLE CRAZY
RIGHT NOW, BUT THERE'S NO PLACE
I WOULD RATHER BE.
RI
RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S SPRINKLES, BUT SOMETIMES I
GET EXCITED AND I SAY PRINGLES
I DON'T KNOW
I LIKE PRINGLES.
I HAVE BEEN CALLING YOU
SPRINKLES FOR HUNDREDS OF YEARS.
IT'S SPRINKLES.
I MADE A MISTAKE
DROP IT!
OKAY.
SORRY.
WHO'S FIRST.
THIS IS PENNY
SHE'S NINE
SHE'S YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
I LOVE YOU, SANTA.
THAT'S SWEET.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE THIS YEAR.
I WOULD LIKE A MAGIC
CHRISTY'S CRYSTAL BALL AND A
WHAT THE FLUFF INTERACTIVE TOY
CAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE THAT.
OH, AND ALSO--
THAT'S ENOUGH
YOU ASK FOR TWO THINGS
THAT'S ENOUGH.
READ THE ROOM.
BUT I WANT A RAINBOW DOLL.
I SAID NO
IT'S TOO MUCH.
HE CAN'T DO IT.
OF COURSE I CAN DO IT
I'M SANTA.
YOU'LL GET ALL YOU ASK FOR AND
MORE
I PROMISE YOU.
NEXT!
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEP
IT IS
I SAID YES!
THIS IS DANNY
HE'S 11.
MY MOM SAYS SOON I'LL BE TOO
OLD TO COME SEE YOU. NONSENSE.
YOU'RE NEVER TOO OLD
WHAT DO YOU WANT THIS YEAR
I WANT A SKATEBOARD, AND
BEATS HEADPHONES, AND A HOODIE.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL HIM
WHAT?
HE CANNOT OPERATE ON THIS LEVEL.
YOU WANT A TODAY SNIDER WHAT
POPOVER HOODIE.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
OF COURSE I DO.
IT'S A HOOD DID I WITH A THING
IT'S A WONDERFUL GIFT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE AIR PODS
HE GOUT LAST YEAR?
I LOST THEM.
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
GET OUT OF HERE.
NOW STAY OUT
NEXT
SPRINKLES, YOU HAVE LEGS!
MY GOSH.
FOR THREE YEARS NOW
THANKS FOR NOTICING.
THAT'S AMAZING.
I'M NOT SURE THIS IS A GOOD
IDEA, BUT THIS IS AMANDA
OH, HI, AMANDA.
AREN'T YOU CUTE?
I WANT TAYLOR SWIFT TICKETS.
SAY THAT AGAIN.
I DARE YOU.
I WANT TAYLOR SWIFT TICKETS.
THEN GET A JOB!
SPRINKLES.
I'M SORRY.
CAN I TALK WITH YOU
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE JUST SAYING YES TO EVERYTHING.
BUT I LOVE CHILDREN.
THERE ARE 2 BILLION OF THEM,
AND THEY ALL WANT A FORTNIGHT
BATTLE PASS, WHATEVER THE HELL
THAT IS.
CALM DOWN.
EVERY YEAR WE'RE AFRAID WE CAN'T
PULL IT OFF, BUT WE ALWAYS DO.
AND THIS YEAR, WE WILL TOO
I PROMISE.
WITH CHRISTMAS MAGIC?
WELL, THERE'S THIS OTHER
STUFF I HEARD ABOUT.
IT'S CALLED SPEED.
SPEED, WHAT'S THAT?
WELL, IT'S SOME KIND OF
VITAMIN THAT MAKES YOU GO FASTER
WE JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
TO GET SOME.
CAN'T YOU ASK ONE OF THE KIDS
IF THEY HAVE ANYTHING.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO ASK THEM
FOR STUFF, BUT MAYBE IF ONE OF
THEM BRINGS IT UP--
LET'S TRY.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I'M LISA, SKI WANT A PONY.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT SPEED?
NO.
WHAT IS THAT.
THIS KID'S NOTHING.
GET OUT OF HERE.
HEY, WAIT
THAT GUY KNOWS, I BET.
WHO
ME
OH, HE KNOWS.
HE DEFINITELY KNOWS
COME HERE, LITTLE BOY.
UH-HUH
AND THEY TAKE CASH
DICKENS A CHRISTMAS CAROL.
OH, SPIRITS, PLEASE
I WANT TO BE A BETTER MAN.
I WANT TO LIVE
I'M ALIVE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT I'M ALIVE
THANK YOU, SPIRITS
THANK YOU FOR SHOWING ME THE
WAY!
OH, I'M AS LIGHT AS A FEATHER.
I'M AT GIDDY AS A MAN.
I WILL CHANGE.
I SWEAR I'LL CHANGE.
I HOPE FS NOT TOO LATE
OH, YOU, LAD
YOU DOWN THERE
ME?
YES, YOU.
COME HERE.
WHAT DAY IS TODAY?
WHY, IT'S CHRISTMAS DAY, SIR.
AH, CHRISTMAS, THEN I HAVEN'T
MISSED IT.
MY DEAR BOY, YOU KNOW THE PRIZED
GOOSE IN THE WINDOW DOWN THE STREET
THE ONE AS BIG AS ME?
THAT'S THE ONE.
GO AND BUY IT SO THAT TINY TIM
AND HIS FAMILY CAN HAVE A FEAST.
WHAT SHALL I BUY IT WITH, SSI
SIR?
I'M SO POOR.
WHY WITH THIS, OF COURSE. AHH
OH, MY GOD
WHATTHE HELL ARE YOU DOING
I'M BLIND!
WHY DIDN'T YOU CATCH IT
YOU'RE BLAMING ME. HERE.
TAKE THIS FOR YOUR MEDICAL BILLS.
WHAT'S THAT
AHH!
OH, MY GOD
THIS CRAZY OLD MAN IS
WHIPPING COINS INTO THE EYES OF ORPHANS.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS AN
ORPHAN.
OH, YEAH, LIKE I LOOK LIKE I
HAVE LIVING PARENTS?
HEY, SCROOGE, JUST THOUGHT
YOU WOULD CHECK IN ON YOU AND
SEE-- OH, MY GOSH.
SOMEONE ARREST THAT MAN
HE'S BLINDING CHILDREN FOR SPORT.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN A CRUEL OLD MAN.
LET ME GUESS, YOU TOSSED THE
COIN WAY UP IN THE AIR, RIGHT?
THAT'S A CLASSIC MISTAKE
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS TOSS THE
COIN STRAIGHT DOWN
NOW WATCH THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I COULDN'T SEE WHAT HAPPENED.
HE'S BLINDING THE WHOLE TOWN,
HE IS.
THAT WAS MY BAD
HERE, KID.
PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
AHH
THAT WAS HIM.
YEAH, THEY CAN'T SEE ME
BECAUSE I'M A GHOST, SO YOU LOOK
LIKE A TOTAL SIGH OWE PATH NOW.
IS IT TRUE, MR. SCROOGE
ARE YOU BLINDING PEOPLE FOR FUN?
OF COURSE NOT, TINY TIM.
I'M A CHANGED MAN.
NOW, TAKE THIS MONEY TO FIX YOUR LEGS
I'LL THROW IT ON THE GROUND AND
YOU CAN PICK IT UP, OKAY
SCROOGE JUST THREW TINY TIM
INTO THE SUER.
HE'S THE DEVIL, HE IS.
MY NEW ADVICE IS LAWYER UP.
IT'S FINE
I CAN TAKE CARE OF THIS.
LET'S EVERYONE KEEP QUIET ABOUT
THIS WHOLE INCIDENT, SHALL WE,
AND I'LL MAKE IT WORTH YOUR WHILE.
PLEASE STOP YELLING AND
THROWING SHINY OBJECTS
YOU'RE GOING TO SPOOK THE HORSE!
OKAY.
WELL, WE'VE ALL LEARNED A LOT
TODAY, HAVEN'T WE?
BUT THE MOST IMPORTANT LESSON
IS-- MERRY CHRISTMAS.
APPLE PAY
NEVER USE COINS AGAIN.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, BRANDI CARLISLE
The Story
♪ ALL OF THESE LINE
ACROSS MY FACE
TELL YOU THE STORY
OF WHO I AM ♪
♪ SO MANY STORIES OF
WHERE I'VE BEEN
AND HOW I GO
TO WHERE I AM ♪
♪ BUT THESE STORIES
DON'T MEAN ANYTHING
WHEN YOU'VE GOT NO ONE
TO TELL THEM TO ♪
♪ IT'S TRUE
I WAS MADE FOR YOU
I CLIMBED ACROSS
THE MOUNTAINTOPS ♪
♪ SWAM ALL ACROSS
THE OCEAN BLUE
I CROSSED ALL THE LINE
AND I BROKE ALL THE RULES ♪
♪ BUT BABY
I BROKE THEM ALL FOR YOU
OH BECAUSE EVEN WHEN
I WAS FLAT BROKE ♪
♪ YOU MADE ME FEEL LIKE
A MILLION BUCKS
YOU DO
AND I WAS MADE FOR YOU
♪ YOU SEE THE SMILE
THAT'S ON MY MOUTH
IT'S HIDING THE WORD
THAT DON'T COME OUT ♪
♪ AND ALL OF MY FRIENDS
WHO THINK I AM BLESSED
THEY DON'T KNOW
MY HEAD IS A MESS ♪
♪ NO THEY DON'T KNOW
WHO I REALLY AM
AND THEY DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ LIKE YOU DO
AND I WAS MADE FOR YOU
AND ALL OF THESE LINES
ACROSS MY FACE ♪
♪ TELL YOU THE STORY
OF WHO I AM
SO MANY STORIES OF
WHERE I'VE BEEN ♪
♪ AND HOW I GOT
TO WHERE I AM
OH BUT THESE STORIES
DON'T MEAN ANYTHING ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'VE GOT NO ON
TO TELL THEM TO
IT'S TRUE
I WAS MADE FOR YOU
OH YEAH ♪
♪ WELL IT'S TRUE
THAT I WAS MADE FOR YOU ♪
WEEKEND
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO WEEKEND UPDATE
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, IT WAS SHAPING UP TO BE A
GOOD WEEK FOR JOE BIDEN.
HE GOT BRITNEY BRINER BACK, HE
KEPT MARRIAGE GAY,
AND HE'S ONLY
GOT 14 MORE SLEEPS TILL SANTA.
UNDER CONTROL
KYRSTEN SINEMA SAID,
HOLD MY WIG.
ARIZONA SENATOR KYRSTEN SINEMA
SEEN HERE REALIZING SOMEONE IS
ACTUALLY WAVING TO THE PERSON BEHIND HER,
ANNOUNCED THAT SHE
IS LEAVING THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
AND IS REGISTERING AS AN INDEPENDENT.
EXPLAINS SINEMA, PAY ATTENTION
TO ME.
WNBA STAR BRITTNEY GRINER WAS
FREED FROM PRISON
IN EXCHANGE
FOR RUSSIAN ARMS DEALER, VICTOR BOOT
GREAT
BOOT WAS ONLY AVERAGING FIVE
POINTS AND TWO REBOUNDS A GAME.
RAPHAEL WARNOCK DEFEATED
HERSCHEL WALKER IN GEORGIA'S
SENATE RUNOFF RACE
I DON'T THINK THIS IS THE LAST
YOU'LL HEAR FROM HERSCHEL WALKER,
I MEAN, THLS HE'S YOUR
BIOLOGICAL FATHER.
WITH WARNOCK'S WIN, DEMOCRAT SENATORS
WILL NO LONGER AHAVE TO RELY
ON VICE PRESIDENT
HARRIS FOR TIE BREAKING VOTE
HARRIS CAN NOW FOCUS ON WAITING FOR
A BIKE ACCIDENT.
THE SUPREME COURT HEARD A
CASE THIS WEEK OVER WHETHER A
CONSERVATIVE EVANGELICAL WOMAN
CAN REFUSE TO DESIGN
HONEY, I DON'T KNOW GAY COUPLE WHO'S GOING
TO HIRE A DESIGNER
WITH THOSE HIGHLIGHTS
- HONEY?
- I'M SO SORRY
I APOLOGIZE.
DURING ORAL ARGUMENTS IN THE
CASE, JUSTICE SAMUEL ALITO
RAISED THE QUESTION,
COULD A
BLACK DEPARTMENT STORE SANTA BE
FORCED TO TAKE A PICTURE
WITH A
CHILD IN A CLAN ROBE
ALITO ADDED HE WOULD LOVE AN ANSWER
BEFORE HE TAKES HIS GRAND KIDS
TO THE MALL NEXT WEEK.
DONALD TRUMP SAID THE RESULTS
OF THE 2020 ELECTION SHOULD BE
OVERTURNED
AND CALLED FOR THE
TERMINATION OF THE CONSTITUTION.
TRUMP PLANS TO TERMINATE THE
CONSTITUTION BY ASKING HERSCHEL
WALKER TO DRIVE IT TO THE
CLINIC
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU GUYS SAW
TODAY, MOROCCO BEAT PORTUGAL
IN QUATERFINAL
IT'S THE BEST WORLD CUP
SINCE THE AFRICANS WHO BUILT THE STADIUMS.
I DIDN'T DO IT
PORTUGAL'S HEAD COACH DECIDED
NOT TO START SOCCER LEGEND
EVEN MORE INSULTING, AT HALF
TIME, HE TRIED TO TRADE RENALDO
FOR BRITTNEY GRINER.
BUT THE BIGGEST UPSET WAS THAT
FAVORITE BRAZIL WAS ELIMINATED,
EXCEPT FOR A TINY STRIP DOWN THE MIDDLE
NIKE HAS OFFICIALLY CUT TIES
WITH BROOKLYN NETS STAR KYRIE IRVING
OVER THE
ANTI-SEMITISM SCANDAL.
HE SAID HE'S SO DEPRESSED, HE
MIGHT JUMP OFF THE EDGE OF THE
WORLD.
TODAY WAS THE SANTA CON BAR
CRAWL IN NEW YORK CITY
YEAH
THE ANNUAL REMINDER THAT WHILE
SANTA MAY EXIST,
GOD DOESN'T.
WELL, FOLKS, THE HOLIDAY
SEASON THE OFFICIALLY UPON US.
HERE WITH SOME TIPS ON HOW TO
GET YOUR SHOPPING DONE QUICKLY
IS MOST CHAOTIC
MARY ANN LOUISE FISHER.
HELLO, MICHAEL.
WE GOT THREE MINUTES TO DO THIS.
I STILL GOT SEVEN STORES TO HIT
ON THIS BLOCK.
- SO YOU HAVE BEEN PRETTY BUSY.
- I HAVE.
SEE I'M ONE OF 27 CHILDREN, SO I
GOT A LOT OF SHOPPING TO DO.
AND I NEED TO DO IT FAST AND CRAZY.
YOU EVER SEEN THE AISLES AND
CROSS DRESS FOR LESS
YEAH.
RACK.
MOST OF THE MERCHANDISE IS ON
THE GROUND.
YEAH, THAT'S ME, MICHAEL.
ME
EVERY SINGLE ROSS, THAT'S ALL
ME.
SO YOU'RE SINGLE HANDEDLY
TRASHING ALL THE ROSSS
YOU EVER TRIPPED OVER A PAIR
OF SHORTS
STRUCK TO A WINNY THE
POOH TEAPOT?
THAT WAS ME, MICHAEL.
- WHY MESS EVERYTHING UP?
- POWER, MICHAEL.
I NEED TO LEAVE MY MARK.
AND SOMETIMES, TO FIND THAT ONE
PERFECT SHIRT,
YOU HAVE TO
UNFOLD 40 AND DUMP THEM ALL ON
THE FLOOR.
ALL RIGHT
WELL, YOU'RE HERE TO GIVE US
SOME HOLIDAY SHOPPING TIPS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
TIP NUMBER ONE
GET YOU ONE OF THESE
DID YOU KNOW ANYONE CAN BUY A
NECK BRACE
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO GO TO A DOCTOR
THESE THINGS MAKE PEOPLE STAY
OUT OF YOUR WAY.
THEY THINK YOU'RE WOUNDED, BUT
ONLY YOU KNOW, YOUR NECK IS
STRONG AS HELL
NOW, MICHAEL, GUESS HOW MUCH ALL
THESE SANTA PLATES WERE?
- WHAT?
- $3.
GUESS HOW MUCH THIS SHIRT WAS.
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE--
- $3.
- YOU WANT TO SEE HOW I GOT IT
- SURE.
SO HOLD THIS, AND PRETEND YOU'RE
A CUSTOMER LOOKING AT IT.
AIN'T THAT A LOVELY BLOUSE.
GIVE ME THAT DAMN SHIRT
THAT WAS IN MY BASKET!
THAT WAS INTENSE.
I SEE HOW THAT WORKS FOR YOU
BUT DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER TIPS
TIP NUMBER TWO, IF YOUR BLOOD
ISSUING GAR DROPS,
J.C. PENNY
GOT NUGGETS.
WHAT?
J.C. PENNY GOT CHICKEN
NUGGETS.
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS GET
YOURSELF STUCK TOEN THAT
ESCALATOR, MAKE A FUSS,
AND THE
MANAGER WILL FIND YOU SOME
NUGGETS, OKAY?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT
- NO, MICHAEL
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
I KNOW TOO MUCH.
I'VE SEEN TOO MUCH
IT'S A WAR ZONE OUT THERE, AND I
JUST GOT DONE DOING THREE TOURS
IN NORDSTROM IRAQ.
IT'S JUST A DEPARTMENT STORE.
IT'S NOT THAT SERIOUS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
I'M THE ONE OUT HERE ON THESE
FRONT LINES.
NOW, MY THIRD AND FINAL TIP--
AND I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO SAY
THIS, BUT IF YOU CAN, BE BLACK
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE WHITE ACTING
LIKE THIS, SOMEONE WILL TAKE A
VIDEO, AND YOU WILL LOSE YOUR JOB.
OKAY
YOU SEE, MICHAEL, THERE'S NO
SUCH THING AS A BLACK KAREN.
I COULD SLAP THE HELL OUT OF YOU
RIGHT NOW, AND NOBODY WOULD SAY
A WORD
MY JOB IS SAFE.
WHAT DO YOU EVEN DO FOR WORK?
I SUE THE CITY.
THE CITY HAS A LOT OF MONEY AND
A BUNCH OF UNEVEN SIDEWALKS, BABY
OKAY
MARY ANN LOUISE FISHER, EVERYBODY.
I GOT YOU SOM
IT'S IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
I'M GOOD.
IT'S OKAY.
FLIGHT TO NEWARK AFTER SHE
ACCUSED A FAMILY OF SMUGGLING
COCAINE THEN ASSAULTED MULTIPLE
OFFICERS BY BITING THEM AND
KICKING THEM IN THE GROIN.
SHE'S BEEN SENTENCED TO LIFE IN
THE NEW JERSEY HALL OF FAME.
A NEW ALBUM FROM R. KELLY WAS
REMOVED FROM A STREAMING ALBUM
MINUTES AFTER IT WAS UPLOADED.
IT WAS NOT EASY TO REMOVE HIS
STREAMS, SAID THE MAID WHO
CLEANED HIS HOUSE.
ON CHRISTMAS.
THE LOS ANGELES ZOO ANNOUNCED
THAT EVYLYN HAS BEEN EUTHANIZED,
NOT BECAUSE SHE'S SICK BUT
BECAUSE IT'S LA AND SHE'S IN HER
40s.
DAMN
THIS WILL GET YOU BACK
A WOMAN IN TEXAS ALLEGEDLY
DUMPED THREE BUCKETS OF HUMAN
WASTE IN FRONT OF A POLICE
DEPARTMENT AND DROVE AWAY.
IT'S A RARE CASE OF E RADIC
BEHAVIOR FROM A LADY WHO POOPS
IN A BUCKET.
AS DIS-TURK AS THIS STORY IS,
IT'S NOT AS DISTURBING AS
IMAGINING THE WOMAN'S DRIVE TO
THE POLICE STATION WITH FULL
BUCKETS OF FECES BECAUSE ONE
SPEED BUMP TURNS HER STAR INTO A
STARBUCKS BATHROOM
FRANCE ANNOUNCED THAT IT WILL
START PROVIDING FREE CONDOMS FOR
PEOPLE BETWEEN THE AGES OF 18
AND 2 5(
COOL
NOW DO DEODERANT.
HOLIDAY MUST HAVE LISTS.
HERE IT'S AUTHORS CURT AND DIB
FROM WYOMING
HEY, GUYS.
HOW DID THIS BOOK COME ABOUT
WE HAVE BEEN MARRIED CLOSE TO
20 YEARS NOW
THINGS KIND OF FIZZLED OUT IN BED.
BUT WE DISCOVERED MY WIFE HAS A
TALENT FOR DOING VOICES OF
FAMOUS PEOPLE, SO WE TOOK THAT
INTO THE BEDROOM.
SO SORT OF LIKE ROLE PLAYING?
YEAH, BUT WITH CELEBRITIES.
FOR EXAMPLE, WE'LL SHOW YOU OUR
TECHNIQUE AT WORK.
BABY, YOU WANT TO SHOW THEM DREW
BARRYMORE?
LIKE THIS.
OH, MY GOD, THAT FEELS
AMAZING.
YOU LIKE THAT, DREW
YES, IT'S FANTASTIC.
HOW MUCH?
SO MUCH LOUDER.
COME ON.
IT'S LITERALLY BLOWING MY MIND.
LOUDER.
COME ON!
IT'S ORGASMIC.
I'M THE MASTER.
IS THAT NOT HOT AS HELL.
I CAN SEE
WE'RE ALL GETTING REALLY TURNED ON.
YEAH, YOU ARE, YOU HORN DOG
SO DREW IS A GOOD GIRL, BUT SHE
DOES BAD GIRLS TOO LIKE THAT
RUSSIAN CON ARTIST LADY FROM
INVENTING ANNA DO ANNA DELVEY
FOR ME.
OH, YOU'RE NOTHING, LITTLE
BOY.
YES, MS. DELVEY.
YOU'RE SO WEAK AND POOR.
YES, PLEASE RUIN MY CREDIT SCORE.
RUIN MY CREDIT SCORE.
MY ORGASM IS ON THE WAY.
YEAH, IT IS, MS. DELVEY DAMN
THAT'S GREAT.
I'M CURIOUS HOW MANY VOICES DOES
SHE DO
MAN, I THINK I MADE LOVE TO
ABOUT A THOUSAND CELEBRITIES AT
THIS POINT
I MEAN, LAST NIGHT I WAS WITH
MS. MERYL STREEP
OH, OKAY.
I GOT TO USE A PROP.
YOU CAN USE A PROP.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT'S
DELICIOUS.
YEAH?
OH, IT'S UTTERLY DIVINE.
YOU'RE SO TALENTED.
IT'S LIKE MUSIC.
YEAH?
OH, YEAH.
I FINISHED
THERE IT IS
WHOO
I GOT A QUESTION.
DOES SHE DO ANY BLACK ONES
NO, SHE DOES NOT.
BUT SHE CAN DO-- WHAT'S HER NAME
SCARLETT JOHANSSON
DO YOU-- DO YOU KNOW HER?
YES, I DO.
YOU KNOW HER?
YEAH.
HAVE YOU SEEN THAT MOVIE
UNDER HER SKIN
I THINK IT'S UNDER THE SKIN.
OF COURSE YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S
CALLED YOU HORN DOG.
LOOK AT YOU CORRECTING ME.
24 MINUTES, 11 SECONDS
ALL RIGHT.
DO SCARLET
HEY, I'M MARRIED TO COLIN,
BUT I NEED A REAL MAN.
YEAH, YOU DO.
WHY DON'T YOU GET OVER HERE
BLACK WIDOW.
COME ON, BLACK WIDOW
THIS SPIDER BITES, COLIN.
I THINK WE'RE GOOD ON THAT ONE.
I JUST WANT TO POINT OUT, IT
DOES SEEM LIKE DEB KIND OF DOES
ALL THE WORK WHILE YOU REAP THE BENEFITS.
I'M NOT AS GOOD AT VOICES AS
DEB, BUT I CAN SAY LIKE ONE
THING AS A FEW CARTOON
CHARACTERS, AND DEB GOT INTO IT.
DIDN'T YOU
UH-HUH.
I LOVE LITTLE STEWY.
YOU WANT ME TO DO IT?
HELLO, BRIAN.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO TO
ME, STEWY?
NOW DO MR. BURNS.
EXCELLENT.
DO SHAGGY FROM SCOOBYDOO.
DO YOU DESERVE IT
I DO.
UP FOR THE KING OF 90s, MINKY CARMICHAEL.
I'M FEELING GOOD.
WELCOME TO HOW TO TREAT YOUR MAN
WITH ME, MINKY CARMICHAEL.
THE SHOW WILL GIVE ADVICE FOR
ALL FINE FEMALES WHO ARE LOOK TO
GO LAND A MAN AND KEEP HIS ASS
I'M JOINED BY MY SIDE KING, JEN
FONGER-BHANG.
I STARTED DRINKING EARLY.
YES, YOU DID.
NOW, WOULD YOU LOOK AT ALL THE
BEAUTIFUL LADIES IN THE AUDIENCE TONIGHT.
WHO DON'T KNOW A DAMN THING
ABOUT HOW TO TREAT THEIR MAN
HIT IT
♪
NOW, THAT'S HOW IT IS.
THIS IS MY CHURCH, AND MINKY
IS MY PRIEST.
THAT'S 100% TRUE.
NOW, WHO'S GOT A QUESTION FOR
ME
ME.
RIGHT HERE.
OKAY.
WHITE GIRL WITH A LITTLE HEAD.
OH, ME?
OKAY
WELL, HI, MINKY.
SO AFTER A FIRST DATE, I DIDN'T
SLEEP WITH THE GUY, RIGHT,
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO SEEM
LOOSE, BUT NOW HE'S NOT CALLING
ME BACK.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
HMM, LET ME CONSULT WITH MY
RELATIONSHIP CALCULATOR.
YOU WENT ON A DATE, YOU DIDN'T
PUT OUT, AND THAT EQUALS-- OF
COURSE HE'S NOT CALLING BACK
HIT IT
♪
AND THAT'S JUST HOW IT IS.
AW, COME ON, MINKY.
HE SAID WHAT HE SAID.
SHUT UP.
NEXT QUESTION
OH, MINKY, HI
SO HERE'S WHAT'S UP.
I WAS ON A DATE AND WOUND PORNO
IN THIS GUY'S VCR.
IS THAT A RED FLAG
WHAT SHOULD I DO
GIRL, THE ONLY VCR I CARE
ABOUT IS A VERY COOL RACK.
SLAM IT!
♪
AND THAT'S-- WHAT?
JUST HOW IT IS.
WHO'S NEXT?
HI, MINKY
HERE'S MY PROBLEM.
I WAS FLIRTING WITH THIS GUY,
AND HE GAVE ME HIS NUMBER, BUT I
NEVER CALLED HIM
DOES THAT MAKE ME A BAD NUMBER.
UH, YEP
SLAM IT!
♪
I'VE NEVER FELT BETTER IN ANY LIFE NEXT
YES
HI, EVERYONE
I'M JADA.
OH, NO, NO.
AND I WENT ON A DATE WITH
MINKY CARMICHAEL.
CAN WE CUT HER MIC?
AND I HAVE TO SAY, HE HAS H
THE WORST PENIS I'VE EVER SEEN
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE MEAN, BUT
IT LOOKED LIKE AN ESPRESSO CUP.
THAT'S NOT 100% TRUE.
ANYONE ELSE HAVE A QUESTION?
YEAH, I HAVE A QUESTION
WHAT WAS SO HORRIBLE ABOUT HIS
THING?
THE LENGTH WAS OKAY
FELT LIKE THERE WAS NOTHING
INSIDE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
LIKE AT A CERTAIN POINT, HE
ASKED ME, DO YOU WANT ME TO
CLOSE IT.
HOLD UP
WHAT WAS THERE TO CLOSE?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I WOULD DESCRIBE IT AS OPEN,
LIKE HOLLOW.
MINKY, SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
PACKING THE WORM FROM DOOM.
YOU KNOW WHAT
LET ME CONSULT MY BULL CRAP
DETECTING COMPUTER.
LOOKS LIKE I'M GETTING A
FAX-- BEEP, BEEP, BOOP, BOOP,
OH, MY GOD, IT'S FROM THE PENIS
HOSPITAL
THEY SAY YOU NEED AN EMERGENCY APPOINTMENT.
SLAM IT ZBL NO.
I'M THE ONE WHO SLAMS IT
YOU DON'T SLAM IT.
I HEAR FROM THE PRODUCERS
THAT WE ARE OUT OF TIME AND
CANCELED, WHICH MEANS I GOT TO
GO BACK AND FINISH HIGH SCHOOL
BYE, Y'ALL
AGAIN
You and Me on the Rock
♪ THEY BUILD WOODEN HOUSE
ON FROZEN POND
IN THE SUMMERTIME
WHEN THE WATER'S GONE ♪
♪ DIAGONAL LINE
IN THEIR ROLLED-OUT LAWN
AND THE SAGE
ALWAYS SMELLS SO PRETTY ♪
♪ BUT NOBODY CARE
WHERE THE BIRDS HAVE GONE
WHEN THE RAIN COMES DOWN
ON BABYLON ♪
♪ THE STONEMASON'S PHONE
RINGS ALL DAY LONG
AND YOU GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE CITY ♪
♪ I BUILD MY HOUSE
UP ON THIS ROCK BABY
EVERY DAY WITH YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHIN'
IN THAT TOWN I NEED
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ ME OUT IN MY GARDEN
AND YOU OUT ON YOUR WALK
IS ALL THE DISTANCE
THIS POOR GIRL CAN TAKE ♪
♪ WITHOUT LISTENIN'
TO YOU TALK
I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND ME
ON THE ROCK
I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY ♪
♪ I BUILT PAPER PLANE
WHEN I LEARNED TO FLY
LIKE A 747
FALLIN' OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ I FOLDED 'EM CROOKED
AND NOW I'M WONDERIN' WHY
I COULD ALWAYS
END UP IN THE WATER ♪
♪ BUT NOBODY'S ASKIN'
WHY SHE LOOKIN' SO THIN
WHY SHE'S LAUGHIN' TOO HAR
WHY SHE DRINKIN' AGAIN ♪
♪ A FALLING STAR
SHE'S A PAPER PLANE
AND SHE WAS GOIN' DOWN
WHEN YOU CAUGHT HER ♪
♪ I BUILD MY HOUSE
UP ON THIS ROCK BABY
EVERY DAY WITH YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHIN'
IN THAT TOWN I NEED
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ ME OUT IN MY GARDEN
AND YOU OUT ON YOUR WALK
IS ALL THE DISTANCE
THIS POOR GIRL CAN TAKE ♪
♪ WITHOUT LISTENIN'
TO YOU TALK ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY
JUST YOU AND ME
ON THE ROCK ♪
♪ IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE
IT'S A HARD WIND
IT'S A RECORD-BREAKIN' TIDE
AND IT IS ROLLIN' IN ♪
♪ OH IT'S A BIG SEA
BUT IT CAN'T TOUCH YOU AND ME
IT'S JUST A WATER VIEW
AND WHAT A VIEW ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY
♪ I BUILD MY HOUSE
UP ON THIS ROCK BABY
EVERY DAY WITH YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHIN'
IN THAT TOWN I NEED
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ ME OUT IN MY GARDEN
AND YOU OUT ON YOUR WALK
IS ALL THE DISTANCE
THIS OLD GIRL CAN TAKE ♪
♪ WITHOUT LISTENIN'
TO YOU TALK
I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND ME
ON THE ROCK
I DON'T NEED
THEIR MONEY BABY
IT'S YOU AND ME
ON THE ROCK ♪
OUR HOME
MAPLE DRIVE
WE BOUGHT IT WHEN ANNY WAS IN
GRAMMAR SCHOOL
SHE EVEN GOT MARRIED HERE.
SO MANY MEMORIES
HEY, DADDY.
IS THAT MY BEAUTIFUL DAUGHTER
GUESS WHAT, I'M ENGAGED,
AGAIN.
WHAT
FATHER OF THE BRIDE, PART EIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT, THREE DECADES AND
SEVEN DIVORCES LATER,
ANNY IS
BACK AND READY TO GIVE MARRIAGE
AN EIGHTH SHOT.
ANNY, WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I CAN
AFFORD AN EIGHTH WEDDING
I'M FINANCIALLY DRAINED.
- I'M YOUR LITTLE GIRL.
- YOU'RE 52
YOUR MOTHER STARTED DRIVING FOR
LYFT TO PAY FOR YOUR LAST WEDDING.
DID SOMEONE SAY MOM
DIANE KEATON IS BACK.
MORE THAN EVER
SHE'S AN ICON IN BEIGE, AND
WE'RE HERE FOR IT.
SO WHO THE HELL PLANNING
THIS THING
OH, MY-- DON'T TELL ME IT'S--
HELLO
LOOK AT YOU.
NO.
NOT AGAIN.
HE WILL LE, GEORGE.
I CAN'T DO THIS, HOWARD.
HI, GEORGE.
YOU STILL HAVE AN OUTSTANDING
BALANCE FROM THE FIFTH WEDDING
YOU OWE ME FOR THE SHRIMP TOWER
AND THE PERFORMANCE FROM NICKI
MINAJ.
CAN WE GET NICKI MINAJ AGAIN?
WHAT?
THAT'S RIGHT, MARTIN SHORT IS
BACK AS THE BELOVED WEDDING
PLANNER FRANCK,
DOING AN ACCENT
THAT I THINK IS OKAY
ALL AGREE
YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE USED GOODS.
THESE ARE NOT--
I'VE SEEN
BIGGER LUMPS IN OATMEAL.
SO PUT THEM TOGETHER AND MAKE
ONE BIG ONE OR DO SOMETHING.
GET THE FAKE ONE-- WHATEVER YOU
DO, IT LOOK LOVELY
I THINK YOU NEED A LITTLE
PLIMPING, TUCKING, TUGGING,
AND
MAYBE DOWN THERE, A LITTLE PROCEDURE.
ARE YOU SUGGESTING I PAY FOR
MY DAUGHTER'S VAGINAL REJUVENATION
CAN WE NOT TALK ABOUT MY
SISTER'S PRIVATES RIGHT NOW?
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT BLOW CHUNKS.
DID YOU FORGET HE WAS IN THIS
MOVIE?
SO DID WE AND SO DID HE,
AND NOW HE'S ON SUCCESSION, AND GOOD FOR
HIM.
IT WOULDN'T BE A WEDDING WITHOUT
THE WHOLE FAMILY THERE.
MY SISTER IN A WEDDING DRESS?
GROSS TO THE MAX
BY THE WAY, NO CAKE FOR ME
I HAVE A COLONOSCOPY TOMORROW.
SO BEAUTIFUL.
MATURE
YOU REALLY ARE BEAUTIFUL.
MY LITTLE MENOPAUSAL GIRL.
SO NICE: FATHER
TIME FOR THE BIG SURPRISE,
YOUR WEDDING PERFORMER
WHAT'S UP
I'M THE WEDDING SINGER.
MY GOD, SELENA GOMEZ.
YOU'RE EVEN MORE BEAUTIFUL IN
REAL LIFE.
I KNOW.
THANKS.
- HOW MUCH IS SHE GOING TO COST ME
- 1.8 MILLION EASY.
COME ON, GEORGE
SING IT TO EVERYBODY
LET'S SING
♪ EVERYBODY HAS A POOPER,
THAT' WHY WE INVITED YOU, A PARTY
POOPER ♪
GREAT TIME
HOSTING "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
THANKS TO BRANDI CARLISLE,
SELENA GOMEZ,
AND THIS BRILLIANT
CAST
WE LOVE YOU.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
translate