>>> EASTER, THE CELEBRATION OF
THE RESURRECTED CHRIST.
THE BIBLE TELLS US JESUS
TRAVELED TO JERUSALEM FOR PASSOVER
WHERE HIS MESSAGE OF
PEACE AND LOVE ENRAGED THE
AUTHORITIES.
IN THE COMING DAYS, HE WILL BE
ARRESTED, TRIED, AND EXECUTED.
THIS HE TELLS HIS DISCIPLES ON
THEIR FINAL EVENING TOGETHER,
A MEAL WILL COME TO CALL.
THE LAST SUPPER.
>> MY FRIENDS,
AND JUDAS.
HEAR ME NOW FOR SOON I WILL LEAVE YOU
AND JOIN MY FATHER IN
HEAVEN.
>> WE CANNOT LOSE YOU, JESUS.
WE WILL PROTECT YOU.
>> TLL NEVYO
>> ALAS, ONE OF YOU ME.
>> NO.
>> WHAT?
>> IT IS FORETOLD, AND THOUGH I
HAVE COMMITTED NO CRIME,
I WILL
BE ARRESTED, TRIED, AND FOUND
GUILTY.
>> SOUND FAMILIAR?
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
A FAMOUS, WONDERFUL MAN ARRESTED
FOR NO REASON AT ALL.
IF YOU HAVEN'T PUT IT TOGETHER, FOLKS,
I'M COMPARING MYSELF TO
JESUS AGAIN.
AND WHAT BETTER TIME THAN ON HIS
BIRTHDAY, EASTER?
AS WE SPEAK, I AM BEING
PERSECUTED
ON A LEVEL THE LIKES
OF WHICH THE WORLD HAS NEVER SEEN,
EVEN WORSE THAN THE LATE,
GREAT JESUS.
YOU KNOW, MANY PEOPLE ARE SAYING
WE'RE VERY SIMILAR.
WE'RE BOTH VERY TALL, VERY POPULAR,
AND BOTH FRANKLY WHITE
AMERICANS.
YOU KNOW, JESUS DID SOME
INCREDIBLE THINGS.
SOME WOULD CALL THEM MIRACLES.
IN TERMS OF FISH AND WITH REGARD
TO BREAD.
FISH AND BREAD.
HE ROSE FROM THE DEAD ON THE
THIRD DAY.
I WOULD HAVE DONE IT FASTER,
POSSIBLY TWO DAYS.
I THINK WE COULD HAVE DONE IT A
LOT FASTER.
HE HAD A GOOD MIND FOR BUSINESS.
WATER INTO WINE.
PURE PROFIT.
AND HE HAD BIG, BIG RALLIES JUST LIKE ME,
AND A LOT OF HIS
FOLLOWERS GOT IN BIG, BIG
TROUBLE, JUST LIKE MINE.
ALL BECAUSE I TOLD THEM EXACTLY
WHAT JESUS WOULD HAVE SAID,
GET
VERY VIOLENT AND START A WAR.
AND I'VE EVEN GOT MY VERY OWN JUDAS,
RAN DeSANTIS.
RON DeSANTIS CAME TO ME, TEARS
IN HIS EYES, HE SAID,
HELP ME,
MR. TRUMP.
I'M GOING TO LOSE MY ELECTION.
SO I VERY GENEROUSLY PRETENDED TO LIKE HIM,
AND THEN, HE DID A
JUDAS.
AND NOW HE CAN'T EVEN GET THE
GAYS OUT OF DISNEY WORLD.
LOOK AT THESE GUYS BACK HERE,
HUH?
THEY JUST HAVE TO SIT HERE
FROZEN WHILE I TALK.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
MR. JESUS, QUITE A GUY.
BUT NOW PEOPLE ARE SAYING
PERHAPS I'M EVEN BETTER THAN JESUS
BECAUSE I'M A SELF-MADE
BILLIONAIRE, AND CHRIST WAS --
LET'S CALL IT WHAT IT IS -- A
NEPO BABY.
OKAY?
I MEAN, HIS DAD WAS GOD.
IT'S PRETTY EASY TO START A
RELIGION WHEN YOUR DAD IS GOD.
HE DID GOOD FRIDAY.
I SAID, WHY NOT MAKE IT GREAT?
WE CAN MAKE IT GREAT.
WITH ME, WE'LL BE DOING GREAT
FRIDAY, PERHAPS EVEN TGI-FRIDAYS
WITH THE STUFF ON THE WALLS AND
EVERYTHING.
BUT WE LOVE EASTER, WE LOVE
HIDING THE EGG.
DON'T WE, FOLKS?
WE LOVE HIDING THE LITTLE EGGS.
YOU KNOW I HAVE MANY BEAUTIFUL
EGGS FROM MY TIME AT THE WHITE HOUSE,
AND NOW THE DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE ARE SAYING, WHERE ARE
THE EGGS?
WE NEED THE EGGS BACK.
BUT I HID THEM.
THEY'RE MY EGGS TO TAKE, OKAY?
SO TOMORROW, I WILL EAT MY
EASTER HAMBURGER WITH MY FAMILY,
OR HOPEFULLY NOT.
AND THEN AFTER THAT, THEY WILL
COME FOR ME, LOCK ME AWAY.
BECAUSE JUST LIKE JESUS, ALL I DID
WAS BE FRIENDLY TO A SEX
WORKER, AND NOW THEY WANT TO PUT
ME IN JAIL.
JUST AWFUL.
BUT WHO KNOWS, FOLKS, MAYBE
PRISON WILL MAKE ME EVEN MORE
POPULAR.
LIKE THAT GUY BACK THERE,
JESUS OF ASKABAN, THAT GUY.
JESUS OF ASKABAN, HE'S CALLED.
AND THAT IS THE STORY OF EASTER.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, JESUS.
LOOK AT THE FINGERS.
DIDN'T STOP DOING THE FINGERS
THE WHOLE TIME.
WEIRD CHOICE WITH THE FINGERS.
LOOK AT JESUS.
SO HAPPY HANUKKAH TO ALL THE
PASSOVERS,
AND ALL THE RAMADANS
DO.
WE LOVE TO SAY RAMADAN.
BUT MOSTLY HAPPY EASTER BECAUSE
WE LIKE JESUS, RIGHT?
STILL FROZEN WITH THE LITTLE
HANDS.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN GOING TO GET TO
SAY THE BIG LINE.
MAYBE IF YOU BREAK A BIG
POLITICAL CHARACTER, YOU CAN SAY
THE BIG LINE.
I'M GOING TO DO IT BY MYSELF
RIGHT NOW.
SO HAPPY EASTER
AND LIVE FROM
NEW YORK, IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MOLLY
SHANNON!
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S SO GREAT TO BE BACK.
I'VE HAD SUCH A FUN YEAR.
MY DAUGHTER STELLA STARTED
COLLEGE.
MY SON NOLAN'S ABOUT TO GRADUATE
HIGH SCHOOL.
AND I WROTE A BOOK ABOUT MY LIFE
CALLED "HELLO MOLLY."
AND YOU KNOW, IT'S INTERESTING
BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED BY
HOW HONEST I WAS
ABOUT SOME OF THE HARD TIMES MY
FAMILY HAD.
I MEAN, WE ALL HAVE PROBLEMS,
RIGHT?
BUT MY DAD ALWAYS TAUGHT ME TO
KEEP MY CHIN UP
AND NEVER GIVE
UP ON MY SHOW BIZ DREAMS.
HE WOULD PLAY ME OLD CLASSIC
MUSICALS
AND HE WOULD TELL ME,
YOU KNOW, MOLLY, NO MATTER WHAT
PROBLEMS YOU FACE,
IF YOU KEEP A
POSITIVE ATTITUDE, EVERYTHING
WILL TURN OUT OKAY.
I CAN ALMOST HEAR HIM NOW
SAYING --
♪ YOU'LL BE SWELL, YOU'LL BE GREAT,
GONNA HAVE THE WHOLE
WORLD ON A PLATE ♪
♪ STARTING HERE, STARTING NOW,
HONEY, EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
ROSES ♪
♪ CURTAIN UP, LIGHT THE LIGHTS,
YOU GOT NOTHING TO HIT BUT THE
HEIGHT ♪
>> MOLLY, SORRY TO CRASH YOUR MONOLOGUE,
BUT I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU MEAN.
I'VE GOT PROBLEMS TOO.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> WELL, I'M NOT REALLY IN THE SHOW TONIGHT,
SO I'M
INTERRUPTING YOUR SONG TO GET
SOME MORE CAMERA TIME.
GREAT
CAN I STAY?
>> NO.
Clear the decks, clear the tracks
NOTHING TO DO
♪ BLOW A KISS, TAKE A BOW,
HONEY, EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
ROSES ♪
KENAN, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> I CAN'T STOP BUYING FAKE
ROLEXES.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU GUYS?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> I STILL DRESS LIKE A LITTLE
BOY.
>> I PRETEND TO HAVE A PEANUT
ALLERGY FOR ATTENTION.
>> I'M ATTRACTED TO MY
THERAPIST.
>> I JUST TESTED POSITIVE FOR
COVID.
>> WAIT, WHAT?
♪ HONEY, EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
ROSES ♪
>> HOW ABOUT YOU, THE AUDIENCE?
WHO HERE IS EMBARRASSED BY HOW
OFTEN THEY CHECK INSTAGRAM?
WHO'S IN AN UNHEALTHY
CODEPENDENT RELATIONSHIP?
OH, WE GOT A FEW.
WHO LOST THEIR JOB DURING THE
PANDEMIC AND SECRETLY HOPES THAT
OTHER PEOPLE ARE SUFFERING TOO?
WHAT ABOUT YOU, LAUREN, WHAT'S
YOUR PROBLEM?
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY PROBLEMS.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU, MARTIN SHORT?
>> I RAN OUT OF OZEMPIC!
>> ERYONE, COME UP HERE.
COME ON.
PUT AWAY YOUR PROBLEMS AND STOP
WORRYING.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE --
♪ YOU'LL BE SWELL, YOU'LL BE GREAT,
I CAN TELL, JUST YOU
WAIT ♪
♪ AND NOTHING'S GONNA STOP US
TILL WE'RE THROUGH ♪
♪ HONEY, EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
ROSES AND DAFFODILS ♪
♪ EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
SUNSHINE AND SANTA CLAUS,
EVERYTHING'S COMING UP
ROSES FOR ME AND FOR YOU ♪
>> THANK YOU, DADDY.
SUPERSTAR!
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
JONAS BROTHERS ARE HERE,
SO STICK
VALETS.
NOW, BEING A VALET IS THE
HARDEST JOB IN THE WORLD.
FORGOT ABOUT BRAIN SURGERY.
IT'S THE SECOND HARDEST JOB IN
THE WORLD.
>> GOT IT.
>> YES.
>> TOTALLY.
>> OKAY.
NOW, I BELIEVE THAT EVERYONE CAN
BE A GREAT VALET, SO LONG AS YOU
FOLLOW THESE THREE SIMPLE RULES.
LIL JOKE, LIL BOW, LIL JOG.
THIS IS THE CORNER STONE OF
QUALITY VALET.
ALLOW ME TO DEMONSTRATE.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> OH, THANKS, LADIES.
HEY, YOU KNOW, YOUR SISTER'S
QUITE THE LOOKER.
>> OH, YOU'RE BAD.
>> Y'ALL ENJOY YOURSELF NOW.
>> THAT WAS NEAT.
>> THAT WAS THE LITTLEST JOG
I'VE EVER SEEN I THINK.
>> THANK YOU.
STEVEN, YOUR TURN.
REMEMBER, LIL JOKE, LIL BOW, LIL
JOG.
>> YES, SIR.
HOWDY FOLKS.
>> IT'S A PORSCHE.
>> OH, A PORSCHE.
COMPENSATING FOR SOMETHING?
MY CONDOLENCES, MISS.
SHE'S ALL, IS IT IN YET, AND
YOU'RE ALL, I'M GIVING IT ALL
SHE'S GOT, CAPTAIN.
Y'ALL ENJOY YOURSELF NOW.
>> NOPE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T EVEN SAY IT.
I GAVE HIM BACK HIS KEYS.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> THAT AND YOUR JOKE WAS ABOUT
A CUSTOMER'S PENIS, AND YOU RAN
AWAY AT TOP SPEED.
>> THAT WAS NOT CLOSE TO MY TOP
SPEED, BUTTOCK.
>> JUST REMEMBER, KEEP IT LIL.
YOU SEE, SEE HOW LIL THIS IS,
TOOK ME TEN YEARS TO GET THIS
LIL.
>> THAT IS LIL.
>> OKAY, JENNY, YOU WANT TO GO
GET THEIR KEYS.
>> SURE, OKAY.
>> AGAIN, LIL JOKE, LIL BOW, LIL
JOG.
>> GOT IT.
HI, THERE, FOLKS.
DID I GET THE TICKET?
HERE YOU GO.
UM.
>> OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> NICE CAR YOU GOT THERE.
I MAY HAVE TO FEEL THAT BABY.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
I ACTUALLY COULD.
JUST KIDDING.
I'M ACTUALLY IN LOVE WITH YOU.
NO.
I'M NOT.
I'M REALLY MARRIED, WE BROKE UP,
THOUGH.
I MET HIM ONLINE, AND TURNED OUT
HE WAS A SICK MIDDLE SCHOOLER
USING A HOSPITAL COMPUTER.
>> OKAY, NO.
BRING IT ON BACK.
OVER HERE.
YEAH.
GOOD TRY.
BUT I ALMOST WISH YOU STOPPED
AFTER THE FIRST THING YOU SAID.
>> OH.
WELL, HOW WAS THAT?
>> NOT VERY GOOD.
>> I'LL DO IT NEXT TIME.
>> STANLEY, YOU WANT TO GIVE IT
A TRY?
>> OKEYDOKEY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU EVER COME HERE BEFORE?
>> WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T REALLY HEAR WHAT YOU --
>> PASS!
>> YIKES.
YOU WANT TO TELL US WHAT
HAPPENED THERE, STANLEY?
>> YES.
I TALKED TOO QUIET, AND THEN I
SAID PASS REAL LOUD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, STANLEY.
GOOD.
WE GOT ANOTHER CUSTOMER.
>> CAN YOU LET ME TRY THE NEXT
ONE?
>> OKAY.
FINE.
BUT TAKE IT SLOW, JENNY.
>> OKAY.
>> CAREFUL.
SHE'S GOT A TEMPER.
>> OKAY.
ACTUALLY, ME TOO.
I'M KIDDING.
NO.
ACTUALLY, I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
HOW ABOUT YOU RIP OFF THIS
TURQUOISE AND PUT A BABY INSIDE
OF ME.
>> BAIL.
BAIL.
>> GUYS, THIS IS SO HARD THE.
>> I THINK I GOT IT NOW, SIR.
>> OKAY.
ARE YOU SURE, STANLEY?
>> YEAH.
IT'S A LIL JOKE, LIL BOW, AND A
LIL JOG.
PRETTY SIMPLE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HR.
GO GIVE IT A SHOT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET DO THIS.
AHH!
I'M GONNA STEAL YOUR CAR, YOU
BLACK BITCH!
BEFORE YOU SAY ANYTHING, I KNOW
THAT WASN'T RIGHT.
>> JUST FORGET IT.
I MEAN, IF WE CAN'T GET THIS
RIGHT, WE MIGHT AS WELL SHUT
DOWN.
I GUESS RICH PEOPLE CAN PARK
THEIR OWN CARS.
>> HEY.
HEY, DON'T SAY THAT.
I PROMISE I'LL MAKE YOU PROUD.
>> AND I'LL PRACTICE MY JOG
EVERY DAY.
>> YOU WILL?
AW, THANKS, GUYS.
>> YEAH.
ALSO, I ACCIDENTALLY SWALLOWED
ALL THE KEYS.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
>>> THEY'RE READY FOR YOU.
NETFLIX
SECOND EVER
>> HAVE YOU GUYS HEARD OF THIS
TIKTOK THING?
THE ONLY TIKTOK I HEAR IS MY
BIOLOGICAL CLOCK.
DON'T GET ME STARTED.
DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED.
>> JEANNIE DARCY, SELECTIVE
STARTAGE.
>> NO ONE BRINGS IT LIKE JEANNIE DARCY,
AND THIS TIME THE
DARCINATOR IS LIVE,
WHICH MEANS
YOU'RE HEARING HER JOKES AT THE
SAME TIME SHE'S TELLING THEM,
INSTEAD OF STREAMING IT LATER,
WHICH IS THE REASON MOST PEOPLE
GET NETFLIX.
NO MERCY
>> I HAD A BRA FITTING THE OTHER
DAY.
I TRIED ONE ON AND HAD A FIT.
MEN MUST DESIGN THESE THINGS.
HAS ANYONE EVER SEEN A JOCK
STRAP WITH UNDERWIRE?
AM I RIGHT, LADY FRIENDS?
YOU GET MY 411?
DO NOT EVEN THINK OF GETTING ME
STARTED.
>> JEANNIE DARCY IS A LEGEND.
THAT GIRL INSPIRED A WHOLE
GENERATION OF LESBIAN COMEDIANS.
>> SHE'S NOT A LESBIAN.
>> SAY WHAT NOW?
>> JEANNIE DARCY TAKES NO
PRISONERS.
>> MY FRIEND GOT A DOG AND
ALWAYS COMPLAINS HE MESSES UP
HER HOUSE AND JUMPS IN HER BED.
I SAID, ARE YOU SURE IT'S A DOG,
OR IS IT MY EX-HUSBAND?
WHO'S WITH ME?
DON'T GET ME STARTED.
DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
JEANNIE IS AWESOME.
SHE EVEN GAVE ME HER SET LIST.
GET STARTED
>> I PICKED UP ONE OF THOSE NEW
TESLA ELECTRIC CARS.
I COULDN'T GET IT STARTED.
DON'T GET ME STARTED.
>> JEANNIE DARCY, SELECTIVE STARTAGE,
STREAMING LIVE
TONIGHT.
>> DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED.
THAT IS SO NICE, JACKIE.
>> WELL, I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU COULD DO SUNDAY MORNING
WAFFLES WITH YOUR LITTLE GIRL.
>> THAT'S SO SWEET I COULD CRY.
>> WE'RE JUST SO HAPPY FOR YOU,
SUSIE.
>> YEAH.
AND WE'RE REALLY GOING TO MISS
YOU.
>> WELL, I'LL BE BACK IN A FEW
MONTHS, UNLESS JIM FIRES ME.
>> OH, COME ON NOW.
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
THAT WOULD BE SUPER ILLEGAL.
>> AND HEY, EVEN THOUGH I'M
STARTING MATERNITY LEAVE, I'M
SURE YOU'LL ALL BE SEEING PLENTY
OF ME.
>> I HOPE SO.
AFTER ALL, I'M THE GOD FATHER.
YOU GAVE ME AN OFFER I COULDN'T
REFUSE.
I'M STILL WORKING ON THE
IMPRESS.
>> I JUST CAN'T GET OVER HOW
BEAUTIFUL YOU LOOK.
>> CAN YOU T YOU, KENNEDY.
HONESTLY, I'VE ACTUALLY NEVER
FELTBETTER.
MY NAILS ARE STRONG, MY SKIN
LOOKS GREAT.
I'M JUST GLOWING.
THIS IS EVERYTHING I'VE EVER
WANTED.
>> WELL, I'LL LEAVE YOU GUYS
WITH THIS SAYING I FOUND ON
BRAINY QUOTE.COM THAT REALLY
CAPTURES KIND OF THE WAY I'M
FEELING RIGHT NOW.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
A MOTHER ALWAYS HAS TO THINK
TWICE, ONCE FOR HERSELF, AND
ONCE FOR HER CHILD.
>> AWW.
>> THAT JUST ABSOLUTELY NAILS
MATERNAL FEELINGS SURGING
THROUGH MY BODY.
ANYWAY, LET ME JUST GRAB THIS
WAFFLE MAKER.
GODDAMNIT, NOT AGAIN!
HOW MANY FREAKING TIMES IS THIS
GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME?
>> UM, I'M SORRY.
WAS THAT --
>> A FART, YES, JIM, I RIPPED A
BIG OLD FART.
ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> NO.
I DEFINITELY WOULDN'T SAY HAPPY.
>> SO IT WAS --
>> NOT A BABY, JUST GAS, YEAH,
KENNEDY, OBVIOUSLY.
GUESS YOU CAN HAVE YOUR WAFFLE
MAKER BACK.
I CAN'T MAKE SUNDAY MORNING
WAFFLES FOR A FART.
>> JUST KEEP IT.
I'M TOO EMBARRASSED TO EXPLAIN
WHY I'M RETURNING IT.
>> DAMN IT.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING MOZART TO A
GAS BUBBLE FOR EIGHT FREAKING
MONTHS.
I'M SO STUPID.
>> SMELLS LIKE MAYBE IT WAS
TWINS.
>> DIDN'T YOU GO TO A DOCTOR?
>> WHAT KIND OF A DOCTOR,
JACKIE, A FART DOCTOR?
WELL, WHATEVER, AT LEAST I STILL
GET SIX MONTHS MATERNITY LEAVE.
>> YOU DEFINITELY DO NOT.
YOU FORFEITED YOUR MATERNITY
LEAVE WHEN YOU STUNK UP THE
OFFICE.
>> SO, SUSIE, THIS HAS HAPPENED
MORE THAN ONCE?
FOUR TIMES?
>> HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE,
SUSIE?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT?
>> I JUST REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
I FEEL SO BAD BECAUSE I ARE EM
THIS MORNING ON THE BUS, AN OLD
MAN GAVE ME HIS SEAT, AND THEN
THE BUS HIT A BUMP, AND HE FELL
DOWN IN THE AISLE, AND HE DIED.
>> THAT WAS THIS MORNING?
>> WHATEVER.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS I CAN
START DRINKING AGAIN.
>> YOU DO KNOW YOU AT WORK,
RIGHT?
>> HEY, SUSIE.
I GOT YOUR LUNCH ORDER FROM TH
CAFETERIA.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVAN.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> WHAT DID YOU GET?
>> OH, I GET THE SAME THING
EVERY DAY.
I GET CAT FISH SLIDERS.
>> WOW.
>> MM.
THIS IS REALLY HITTING THE SPOT
IN A VERY UNBELIEVABLE WAY.
MM.
>> SUSIE, LOOK AT YOUR STOMACH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S A MIRACLE.
>> NO.
>> IT'S A MIRACLE.
>> GUYS, I HAVE SOME REALLY
EXCITING NEWS.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT I'M
PREGNANT AGAIN.
WELL, THERE'S NO NEED TO TAKE A
PREGNANCY TEST.
CALL IT A MOTHER'S INTUITION.
I REALLY THINK IT WILL BE A NICE
GESTURE FOR ALL OF YOU TO
ORGANIZE A BABY SHOWER FOR ME.
>> YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT, SUSIE.
IT'S JUST GAS FROM YOUR HUNGRY
ASS CAT FISH SLIDERS AT 11:00
A.M.
>> LOOK, KENNEDY, I KNOW YOU'RE
A SINGLE GAL WHORING AROUND THE
CITY, SO YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
UNDERSTAND HOW --
OH, MY GOD.
NO.
HOW MUCH SUFFERING CAN ONE
MOTHER BEAR?
WHATEVER.
WELL, AT LEAST I CAN SMOKE
AGN.
>> WAIT, SUSIE -- DON'T LIGHT
THAT CIGAR!
>>> HEY.
ARE YOU GUYS FREE TO TALK?
>> MOLLY!
>> HEY, MOLLY.
>> COME ON IN.
WE'RE PLAGUE SOME VIDEO GAMES.
NICE
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH --
>> WAIT, WHAT GAME IS THIS.
>> MOLLY 2 K 23.
>> IT'S REALLY FUN.
YOU PLAY AS MOLLY SHANNON
BOUNCING YOUR CAREER AS AN ACTOR
WITH RAISING A FAMILY.
TONIGHT SHOW
>> AND THAT'S HOW I EMBARRASSED
MYSELF IN FRONT OF OBAMA.
UNLOCKED
>> OH, YOU JUST CRACKED JIMMY
UP.
>> THERE'S A GAME ABOUT MY LIFE?
>> OH, DUDE.
WE UNLOCKED AN NYU COMMENTMENT
SPEECH.
PRESS A TO GET KIDS --
OR PRESS B
CANCEL CULTURE
DON'T
>> THIS GENERATION IS A BUNCH OF
SNOWFLAKES.
>> CAREER SETBACK.
>> DAMN IT.
THAT MADE US DROP ALL OUR
TURNUPS.
>> WHAT ARE TURNUPS?
>> THEY ARE DOLLARS.
YOU CAN USE THEM TO BUY OUTFITS.
- TALK
- DON'T TALK TO ANYONE
>> SHOULDN'T I BE GETTING PAID
OR SOMETHING.
>> I WOULD ASSUME SO.
THEY HAVE BEEN MAKING THEM FOR
YEARS.
>> WE'VE BEEN PLAYING THEM SINCE
WE WERE KIDS.
MARIO
>> OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT MY DAUGHTER?
>> YEP.
JUST GIVING STELLA THE BIRDS AND
THE BEES TALK.
>> AND REMEMBER, ALWAYS USE TWO
CONDOMS.
>> THANKS, MOM.
>> HERE'S A TURNIP.
>> I WOULD NEVER SAY THAT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW.
>> COMBAT MODE.
OUR MOLLYS ARE FIGHTING TO THE
DEATH.
BITCH
WE CAN ALSO DO THE SKATE LEVEL.
WE JUST LEARNED HOW TO MAKE
TWISTS.
BITCH
>> 2 K 24 IS SUPPOSED TO BE
FLAWLESS.
>> EMOTIONAL LEVELS ARE LOW.
WE GOT TO GO TO THE THERAPIST.
VALU
>> IN COLLEGE I ACTUALLY DATED A
WOMAN.
>> HOW DOES IT KNOW THAT?
>> THIS GAME RULES.
YOU CAN BE ANY MOLLY SHANNON YOU
WANT.
YOU CAN BE A SUPERHERO OR A
RAPPER.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE A RAPPER.
I WANT TO BE MYSELF.
>> I'M TIRED OF GETTING YELLED
AT FOR A HOPBY I HAVE.
SEE YOU LATER, MOLLY.
BYE
THREE
>> OH, MY -- MOLLY, ARE YOU
PLAYING THE GAME STILL.
>> I BECAME A RAPPER.
>> WHAT?
>> MY NAME IS MOLLY THE RAPPER,
AND I'M REALLY GOOD NOW.
I'M ON LEVEL 99.
LIKE A CANNON
♪ SAY MY MOTHER-LOVING NAME,
YOU KNOW IT'S MOLLY SHANNON ♪
♪ DOING HIGH KICKS, AND YOU KNOW
WHAT THE VERDICT IS.
GAME
COLLECTING
ROLL THEM OUT
GOT MY FINGERS IN MY ARMS, CAN'T
PULL THEM OUT ♪
♪ LIKE A CALIBER, SEASON 25
CALIBER,
PUNKS GETTING MARY
CATHERINE GALLAGHER,
BITCH.
>> OH, MY -- MOLLY SHANNON THE
RAPPER.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
>> THAT WAS SO GOOD.
>> THAT'S NOT GATORADE.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>>> WOW, MY GIRLFRIEND SOPHIE, A
FANCY PLAY WRITE.
I'M SO PROUD.
>> THANKS, BRIAN.
>> I'M SO SORRY TO BUG YOU.
I'M A HUGE FAN OF YOUR WRITING.
I SEE ALL YOUR PLAYS.
YOU'RE SO BRILLIANT.
>> THAT'S SO SWEET.
THIS IS T FIRST PLAY THAT'S
ACTUALLY ABOUT MY LIFE.
I'M NERVOUS, BRIAN.
>> DON'T BE.
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO LOVE IT.
>> SOPHIE, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT'S YOUR WEDDING DAY.
AND EVERYONE'S EXPECTING YOU TO
SAY I DO.
BUT DO YOU?
OR FOR ONCE, WOULD YOU RATHER DO
YOU?
GIRL, YOU DON'T LOVE HIS SORRY
ASS.
>> GOD, THIS ACTRESS, SHE'S
AMAZING.
>> WHOA, YOU ALMOST GOT MARRIED?
OKAY.
I'M SURPRISED THAT NEVER CAME
UP.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO LIVE YOUR
TRUTH, SOPHIE.
YOU'RE GOING TO LEF THIS CHUMP,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A YEAR
OF A THOUSAND MEN.
AND SO I DID.
I DATED A THOUSAND MEN IN ONE
YEAR.
AND THAT'S WHEN EVERYTHING
CHANGED.
♪ CHANGE, CHANGE, CHANGE ♪
>> DID SHE SAY A THOUSAND?
THAT'S MORE THAN TWO A DAY.
>> IT EXPLAINS.
>> WHO DID I DATE, YOU ASK?
EVERYONE FROM FINANCE BROS WITH
PERFECT ABS TO BROOKLYN ARTISTS
WITH UNCUT DONGS.
AND THE LESS I WANTED THEM, THE
MORE THEY WANTED ME.
I WAS PULLED IN ALL DIRECTIONS.
>> SOPHIE.
>> I WANT TO GET DRUNK ON YOUR
FUMES.
>> AND I DON'T WANT TO USE A
CONDOM.
>> FINE BY ME.
>> I THINK I'M GOING TO HEAD
OUT.
>> BABE, DON'T.
'S LOOSELY BASED ON MY LIFE.
IT'S NOT ALL TRUE.
>> ALL OF THIS IS TRUE.
AS GOD AS MY WITNESS, THERE HAVE
BEEN NO EMBELLISHMENTS.
ABOUT 998 BANGS LATER, I WAS
STILL FEELING TOTALLY
UNFULFILLED.
BUT ALL OF THAT WAS ABOUT TO
CHANGE, BECAUSE I MET THE ONE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S SWEET, I GUESS.
>> MY EX, TREVOR, THE ONE THAT
GOT AWAY.
>> HEY, BABE.
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T MIND BEING ON
TV WHILE WE SAT COURTSIDE AT THE
LAKERS GAME.
>> NO.
THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW ALL THOSE GUYS ANYWAY.
>> WHAT?
THE LAKERS?
>> BUT THEN I FOUND OUT AN UGLY
TRUTH ABOUT HIM.
>> DOCTORS TOLD ME I HAVE A
CONDITION.
WHERE ANY TIME YOU CLIMAX IN THE
FUTURE, IT WILL STILL BE BECAUSE
OF ME.
>> AND THEN, HE BROKE UP WITH
ME.
HE MOVED TO ANAHEIM TO PURSUE
HIS DREAM OF RUNNING SOCIAL
MEDIA FOR GRUB HUB.
SO THE NEXT DAY, I WENT TO A
BOWLING ALLY TO GET SLOPPY DRUNK
WHEN -- SOME GUY APPROACHED ME.
>> HELLO.
I'M BRIAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO OUT?
>> UM, WHATEVER, I GUESS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WELL, MY GIRLFRIEND, SOPHIE,
A FANCY PLAY WRITE.
I'M SO PROUD.
HIGH FIVE.
NOBODY?
OKAY.
>> AND AFTER FOUR WEEKS OF
DATING, I COULDN'T HOLD HIM OFF
ANYMORE.
I HAD TO BUCK UP AND FINALLY
HAVE SEX WITH HIM.
>> WHOO!
AS THEY SAY, THERE'S A FIRST
TIME FOR EVERYTHING.
>> IT WAS ONE OF THE MOST
PAINFULLY BLAND EXPERIENCES OF
MY LIFE.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THERE IT WAS, I HAD
REACHED MY 1,000th MAN.
IT WAS TIME TO OFFICIALLY SETTLE
IN, UNTIL, I MET SOMEONE WHO
WOULD CHANGE MY LIFE.
>> SORRY TO BUG YOU.
I'M JUST A HUGE FAN OF OUR
WRITING.
I SEE ALL YOUR PLAYS.
YOU'RE BRILLIANT.
>> I MET MR. 1,001.
>> WAIT.
IS THAT THE GUY FROM FIVE
MINUTES AGO?
OH, COME ON!
♪ HEY NOW
WE NEVER KNEW
HOW TO FORFEIT ♪
♪ HEY NOW
WE ALWAYS KNEW
HOW TO TALK♪
HEY NOW ♪
♪ COUPLE NIGHTS
THREW GASOLINE
ON THE FIRE
HEY NOW ♪
♪ WE NEVER HOW TO PERFECT
HEY NOW
WE ALWAYS KNEW
IT WOULD WORK 'CAUSE ♪
♪ IF SOMETHING MISREAD
OR IF SOMETHING GOT SAID
KNOW BEFORE THE NIGHT ENDS ♪
♪ NO DON'T GET STRESSED IT'S
GONNA GET FIGURED OUT
OH DEEP CONVERSATIONS
AT THE WAFFLE HOUSE ♪
♪ HEADSTRONG FATHER
AND A DETERMINED MOTHER ♪
♪ OH, THAT'S WHY SOME NIGHTS WE
WOULD TRY TO KILL EACH OTHER ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW IT'S ALWAYS LOVE,
HEY NOW ♪
♪ WE NEVER KNEW
HOW TO FAKE IT
HEY NOW ♪
♪ WE ALWAYS KNEW
HOW TO BREAK
HEY NOW ♪
♪ COUPLE NIGHTS
THREW GASOLINE
ON THE FIRE 'CAUSE ♪
♪ IF SOMETHING MISREAD
OR IF SOMETHING GOT SAID
KNOW BEFORE THE NIGHT ENDS ♪
♪ NO DON'T GET STRESSED IT'S
GONNA GET FIGURED OUT
OH DEEP CONVERSATIONS
AT THE WAFFLE HOUSE ♪
♪ HEADSTRONG FATHER
AND A DETERMINED MOTHER ♪
♪ OH, THAT'S WHY SOME NIGHTS WE
WOULD TRY TO
KILL EACH OTHER ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW
IT'S ALWAYS LOVE ♪
♪ NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA
YOU KNOW IT'S ALL LOVE ♪
♪ NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW IT'S ALWAYS
GON' GET FIGURED OUT
DEEP CONVERSATIONS
AT THE WAFFLE HOUSE ♪
♪ HEADSTRONG FATHER
AND A DETERMINED MOTHER ♪
♪ OH THAT'S WHY SOME NIGHTS
WE TRIED TO KILL EACH OTHER
BUT YOU KNOW
IT'S ALWAYS LOVE ♪
♪ NA NA NA ♪
OH YEAH NA NA NA NA
YOU KNOW IT'S ALL LOVE ♪
♪ NA NA NA
HEY NA NA NA NA
YOU KNOW IT'S ALWAYS LOVE ♪
♪ NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THE WALL STREET JOURNAL IS
CALLING ON RUSSIA TO RELEASE ONE
OF THEIR JOURNALISTS
WHO WAS
ARRESTED ON ESPIONAGE CHARGES,
AND I MIGHT HAVE THE PERFECT
IDEA FOR A PRISONER SWAP.
FORMER PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS
ARRAIGNED ON TUESDAY,
AND A
PHOTOGRAPHER RELEASED THIS PHOTO
OF TRUMP IN THE COURTROOM,
AND I
DON'T LIKE THAT HE'S SLANKED BY
AN O.J. AMOUNT OF LAWYERS
BECAUSE THAT TELLS ME HE'S
DEFINITELY GUILTY AND HE'S
DEFINITELY GETTING AWAY WITH IT.
TRUMP'S LAWYER, JOE TACOPINA,
AKA, PHONY SOPRANO,
SAID THAT HE
DOESN'T THINK TRUMP IS GOING TO
GET A FAIR TRIAL IN MANHATTAN.
I AGREE.
EVEN THE COURTROOM SKETCH ARTIST
SEEMS TO HATE HIM.
I THOUGHT HE
LOOKED PERFECTLY NICE.
HE HAD BLENDED HIS FOUNDATION.
HE HAD STAPLED DOWN HIS HAIR.
BUT THE GUY STILL DREW HIM LIKE
THE MUD MONSTER FROM SCOOBY-DOO,
>> AFTER HIS ARRAIGNMENT, DONALD
TRUMP SPOKE TO SUPPORTERS AT MAR-A-LAGO
AND SAID THERE WAS A
VERY DARK CLOUD OVER OUR BELOVED COUNTRY,
WHICH IS ALSO WHAT HE
USED TO CALL OBAMA.
INSIDERS ARE SAYING THAT SINCE
DONALD TRUMP'S INDICTMENT,
HIS
DAUGHTER IVANKA HAS BEEN ABSENT,
AND HIS OTHER DAUGHTER TIFFANY
IS TRYING TO TAKE HER PLACE BY HIS SIDE,
JUST AS SOON AS SHE
GETS THROUGH SECURITY.
REPRESENTATIVE MARJORIE TAYLOR
GREEN SEEN HERE SHOUTING, JUMP,
YOU COWARD!
VISITED NEW YORK TO PROTEST THE
ARREST OF DONALD TRUMP
AND
CALLED THE CITY FILTHY,
DISGUSTING, AND REPULSIVE.
AS A NEW YORKER, LET ME JUST
SAY, YOU FORGOT RAT INFESTED.
DON'T FORGET OUR RATS.
>> NEVER.
A NEW REPORT DECLARES FOR
DECADES, CHARNS THOMAS AND HIS WIFE
WENT ON LUXURY TRIPS BY
REPUBLICAN MEGADONOR,
AND
WHITEST GUY WITH THE BLACKEST
NAME, HARLAN CROW.
BECAUSE JUSTICE THOMAS HANDLED
GIFTS FROM REPUBLICANS THE SAME WAY
HE HANDLES SUPREME COURT
CASES, WITH NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
IT WAS ALSO REPORTED TODAY THAT
HARLAN CROW HAS A VAST
COLLECTION OF NAZI MEMORABILIA,
INCLUDING COPIES SIGNED BY
HITLER.
THE SIGNATURE READS, DEAR
HARLAN, BIG FAN.
ADOLF
>> TENNESSEE REPUBLICANS
EXPELLED TWO BLACK LAWMAKERS FOR
PROTESTING GUN VIOLENCE,
BUT DID
NOT EXPEL A WHITE PROTESTOR.
THEY SAID, THEY KNOW WHAT IT
LOOKED LIKE, BUT THEY WERE
ACTUALLY EXPELLED
BECAUSE THEIR
SKIN WAS BLACK.
>> FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON
DeSANTIS, WHO ALWAYS LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE TOLD HIM TO GO HOME AND
GET HIS SHINE BOX
SIGNED A BILL
THAT ALLOWS PEOPLE TO CARRY GUNS
WITHOUT A PERMIT.
BECAUSE FLORIDA IS DANGEROUS,
AND YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN SOMEONE
IS GOING TO RUN UP TO YOU AND
SAY GAY.
BIDEN
CHARLES
THAT JILL BIDEN WILL ATTEND THE
CORONATION
ALONG WITH HER PLUS
ONE, THE IOWA WOMEN'S BASKETBALL
TEAM.
>> KING CHARLES SAID RESEARCHERS
WILL BE GIVE ACCESS TO ROYAL AR KOOIS
AFS IT WAS DISCOVERED HIS
ANCESTORS HAD STAKE IN A
SLAVE-TRADING COMPANY.
YEAH, IT WAS CALLED ENGLAND.
>> THIS WEEK, RON DeSANTIS
RAMPED UP HIS WAR ON DISNEY.
HERE TO COMMENT IS THE VILLAIN
FROM THE MOVIE ALADDIN, JAFAR.
>> HELLO, MICHAEL.
SO THIS IS THE FAMOUS
ROCKEFELLER PALACE.
>> OKAY.
SO, JAFAR, AS A DISNEY
CHARACTER, WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
RON DeSANTIS?
>> YOU MEAN, THE BOY?
WELL, MICHAEL, AS FAR AS
VILLAINS GO, THE BOY IS AN
AMATEUR.
HE HAS NO RIZ, NO SPARK, NO
DRIP.
THE LOOK IS GIVING BABY MAYOR.
HE DID WEAR THOSE WHITE COWBOY
BOOTS, BUT LET'S BE HONEST, THEY
WORE HIM.
>> WELL, HE MIGHT NOT LOOK THE
PART, BUT ARE YOU SAYING
DeSANTIS ISN'T BAD ENOUGH?
>> NOT AT ALL.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
THE BOY IS PLENTY EVIL.
BANNING ROSA PARKS IN SCHOOLS.
I'M A DARK SOURCER, AND HEN I
WAS LIKE, IT'S ROSA PARKS.
>> NOW HE'S COMING AFTER DISNEY
BECAUSE OF HIS STANCE OF THE
DON'T SAY GAY BILL.
>> YOU CAN'T PREVENT DISNEY
WORLD FROM BEING GAY.
THAT CARPET HAS FLOWN.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> NO, I REALLY DON'T.
>> I MEAN IF YOU OPEN UP GRINDER
ON MAIN STREET USA, YOUR PHONE
EXPLODES.
EVERYWHERE ELSE IN THE PARK,
IT'S NOTHING BUT 40-YEAR-OLD MEN
WITH BRACES.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS, BUT
IT AIN'T STRAIGHT.
>> OH, ARE YOU SAYING THAT
YOU'RE --
>> A LITTLE LIGHT IN THE
LOAFERS?
DID MY STASH NOT TIP YOU OFF?
OF COURSE I'M GAY, YOU FOOL.
MY EYE LINER ON POINT.
MY FORM AS A YOLKED GENIE WITH
NAILS.
YEAH, MICHAEL, I LOVE COOCH.
>> I GOT IT.
WELL, SEEMS LIKE DeSANTIS
DOESN'T EVEN WANT ANYTHING
REMOTELY GAY HAPPENING AT DISNEY
WORLD AT ALL.
>> THERE'S ALREADY A DISNEY
WORLD WHERE NOTHING GAY HAPPENS.
IT'S CALLED SIX FLAGS.
THERE ARE LOTS OF DIFFERENCES AT
DISNEY, MICHAEL.
URSULA IS A LESBIAN, SCAR IS BI,
AND MULAN JUST GOT TOP SURGE ARE
I.
NOW IF I MAY, I WOULD LIKE TO
ADDRESS THE BOY, DeSANTIS.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T THE SWAMP RAT.
BRAVO ATTEMPTING TO SEE THE
PRECIOUS LAND ONLY IT WOULD BE
THWARTED AGAIN BY THE HOUSE OF
MOUSE.
YOU CAN TRY TO STOP US, BOY, BUT
WE WILL OUTSMART YOU AT EVERY
TURN.
DON'T SAY GAY?
WELL, IF THERE IS NO GAY, THERE
IS NO DISNEY, AND EVERYONE LOVES
DISNEY, INCLUDING YOU BECAUSE
YOUR DUMB ASS GOT MARRIED THERE,
AND THAT'S THE GAYEST THING YOU
CAN DO!
SO I'M SORRY, THE GAYS SHALL
STAY, AND YOU CACHE AWAY.
WHERE WERE WE, MICHAEL?
OH, YES, YOUR EARRING, IT
INTRIGUES ME.
>> NO, NO, NO.
JAFAR, EVERYBODY.
>> I SAW YOU AT THE GRAND
FLORIDIAN.
IT WAS A GORGEOUS WEDDING.
>> FLORIDIAN.
>> THAT'S A GREAT EARRING.
A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT THE
AVERAGE CHILD THROWS A TANTRUM
FOUR TIMES A WEEK, WEEKNIGHTS ON
FOX.
>> RUPERT MURDOCH'S ENGAGEMENT
TO ANN LESLIE SMITH HAS BEEN
CALLED OFF.
APPARENTLY, SHE GOT COLD FEET
AFTER MURDOCH PASSED HIS
PHYSICAL.
IN A NEW DOCUMENTARY, POPE
FRANCIS PRAISES THE SIR CHEWS OF
SEX, CALLING IT ONE OF THE
BEAUTIFUL THINGS THAT GOD HAS
GIVEN TO THE HUMAN PERSON.
NOT THE WAY I DO IT.
AM I RIGHT, COLIN?
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
>> I HOPE NOT.
I DON'T KNOW.
A WOMAN HAS BEEN TRAVELING THE
WORLD SO SHE'S GONE ON 34 FIRST
DATES IN NEARLY 20 COUNTRIES.
HERE SECRET?
SHE'S BEING SEX TRAFFICKED.
>> THERE WAS CONTROVERSY THIS
WEEK WHEN LSU WOMEN'S BASKETBALL
STAR ANGEL REESE REFUSED AN
INVITATION TO THE WHITE HOUSE TO
CELEBRATE HER TEAM'S NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
BUT NOW SHE HAS DECIDED TO GO.
SO HERE TO COMMENT IS ANGEL
REESE.
>> YEAH, THE BAYOU BARBIE IS IN
THE BUILDING.
LOUISIANA, STAND UP.
>> WELL, ANGEL, YOU HAD QUITE A
WEEK.
>> YEAH.
I GOT PEOPLE BIG MAD.
FIRST THEY WAS MAD BECAUSE I WAS
TAUNTING, BUT ALL I DID WAS
THIS.
YOU WOULD HAVE THOUGHT I PULLED
MY NIPPLE OUT AND FLICKED IT ON
NATIONAL TV.
THEN THEY WERE MAD BECAUSE I
DIDN'T WANT TO GO TO THE WHITE
HOUSE.
BUT, CHE, THEY INVITED IOWA TOO.
>> BUT THEY LOST.
>> EXACTLY.
IN THE HISTORY OF SPORTS, WHEN
YOU LOSE, YOU TAKE YOUR ASS
HOME.
BUT THEN, WHITE GIRLS LOSE, AND
SUDDENLY, IT'S ALL TEAMS MATTER.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD YOU CHANGED
YOUR MIND.
THAT WILL BE PRETTY COOL.
>> YEAH.
IT WILL BE COOL, FOR THEM.
I'M A BIG DEAL NOW, CHE.
SINCE COLLEGE PLAYERS GET
ENDORSEMENTS NOW, I'M ABOUT TO
CASH IN.
AND MY BRAND WORKS FOR ANYTHING.
HOW THIS SOUND, CHE?
DEGREE DEODERANT, Y'ALL STANK.
>> IT SEEMS AGGRESSIVE.
>> OKAY.
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
GARDEN GNOMES, MAN, GET YOUR LIL
ASS OUT MY FACE!
>> THAT'S A COMMERCIAL FOR
GARDEN GNOMES?
>> YEAH.
IT'S THE MONEY, RIGHT?
NOW, HERE'S MY FAVORITE.
BIG-ASS EYELASHES, EMPOWERING
WOMEN BALLERS AND -- SINCE 1972.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE ENJOYING THE
MOMENT.
>> YEAH, I AM.
LAST WEEK, WOMEN'S SPORTS WAS
BORING, NOW ALL Y'ALL TALKING
ABOUT WOMEN SPORTS THIS WEEK.
MAN, I DROPPED 15 ON IOWA.
I WENT HARD IN THE PAINT.
I DROPPED TEN BOARDS WITHOUT
EVEN MESSING UP ANY EYELASHES.
THE ONLY THING I REGRET IS NOT
GETTING MORE BUCKETS.
I COULD HAVE PICKED THAT BALL
UP, DROPPED IT ON THE GIRL'S
HEAD LIKE I WAS ON AN AND-ONE
TOUR, BUT I WAS IN FOUL TROUBLE,
SO I HAD TO CHILL.
AND NOW I'M SITTING BACK GETTING
ALL THIS BABY GAP MONEY.
>> WHY ARE YOU ENDORSED BY BABY
GAP?
>> BECAUSE ALL THESE BITCHES IS
MY SON.
>> ANGEL, REESE, EVERYBODY.
>> YOU CAN'T SEE ME.
WE GOING BACK TO BACK.
ANGEL REESE.
>> A NEW APP CALLED GREET HER IS
DESIGNED TO HELP WOMEN TRAVEL
ALONE SAFELY BY PROVIDING PEOPLE
TO GREET THEM WHEN THEY ARRIVE
AT AIRPORTS OR HOTELS, AND IT'S
BEING USED FOR MURDER.
>> A VIRGINIA MAN WHO PRANKS
PEOPLE FOR YOUTUBE VIDEOS WAS
SHOT WHILE TRICKING SOMEONE IN A
MALL.
GOOD.
A 106-YEAR-OLD WOMAN IN THE
PHILIPPINES HAS BECOME THE
OLDEST VOGUE COVER MODEL EVER,
BEATING THE PREVIOUS RECORD OF
29.
>> A JEOPARDY CONTESTANT THIS
WEEK WAS FORCED TO QUIT SOCIAL
MEDIA AFTER PEOPLE SAID HIS
MUSTACHE LOOKED LIKE HITLERS.
THE CONTESTANT SAID HE'S SO MAD
THAT HE'S HAD IT UP TO HERE.
>> NASA HAS NAMED THE FOUR
ASTRONAUTS IT WILL SEND ON THE
ARTEMIS II MISSION TO THE MOON.
IF ANYTHING GOES WRONG, I THINK
I KNOW WHO'S DYING FIRST.
HE CAN DO THE HITLER SALUTE,
THOUGH.
>> LAST WEEK, DATA SHOWED MORE
AMERICANS ARE RETURNING TO THE
OFFICE IN PERSON.
HERE TO COMMENT IS YOUR COWORKER
SEEMINGLY BUSY DOING NOTHING.
>> WE GOT TO MAKE THIS QUICK
BECAUSE I REALLY GOT TO GET
BACK.
I GOT TO GET BACK.
>> OH, OKAY.
WELL, YOU JUST GOT HERE,
CRYSTAL.
AND THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> ICE BREAKER, ICE BREAKER.
COLIN, HOW ARE YOU?
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
LITERALLY DON'T HAVE TIME TO
HEAR YOUR ANSWER.
I AM SO SLAMMED.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU DO FOR WORK.
>> UM, THIS.
>> WOW.
OKAY.
WELL, I GUESS I WOULD LOVE TO
GET A SENSE OF WHAT YOU DO IN A
DAY.
>> UM, YEAH.
WHAT DON'T I DO?
OKAY.
ASK MY TEAM.
WHERE ARE THEY?
ON MY BACK.
AND MY PHONE'S BLOWING UP.
I'M IN HELL.
>> I'M SORRY YOU'RE SO SLAMMED,
CRYSTAL.
>> I NEED A VACATION, BUT
KNOWING ME, I WOULD BRING MY
WORK PHONE, AKA, MY HUSBAND.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I DON'T LOVE THAT YOU
KISSED YOUR PHONE.
I'M SO CURIOUS ABOUT WHAT YOUR
JOB IS.
>> COLIN, TO EXPLAIN IT, THE
LEVEL I WOULD HAVE TO START OUT,
I LITERALLY DON'T HAVE THE BAND
WIDTH -- OH, MY -- OH, MY -- OH,
MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LOOK.
>> YEAH.
THIS IS A SIGNUP SHEET FOR
BIRTHDAY CAKE.
>> YEAH.
YEP.
AND THEN BRINGING OREO
CHEESECAKE.
THAT AIN'T GONNA WORK.
THERE GOES MY EASTER SUNDAY.
>> WHY WOULD THERE GO YOUR
EASTER SUNDAY?
>> AND DOO, DOO, DOO, DOO, I'M
SCREWED.
>> CRYSTAL, CAN YOU JUST TELL ME
ONE THING YOU DO?
>> YEAH.
OKAY.
LOOK
ALL RIGHT.
SO LOOK AT MY SPREAD SHEET,
OKAY?
THESE ARE ALL EMAILS I RECEIVED.
NOW YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> NO, I DON'T.
NO, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHERE DO YOU WORK?
>> IN THE WEEDS.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN SPECIFICALLY.
SPECIFICALLY.
SPECIFICALLY, WHERE?
>> NECK DEEP.
>> THAT'S NOT AN ANSWER.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I
DON'T DO, EAT.
HAVEN'T EATEN IN A MONTH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CRYSTAL, YOU NEED TO TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
>> MM, KALE SEE CZAR.
MY FAVORITE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, IT'S KIND OF NICE
EATING AT THE TABLE AND NOT ON A
TOILET.
>> YOU EAT ON THE TOILET?
>> AND I SHOT GOT A CALL ON MY
SALAD PHONE.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> I'M SCREWED.
>> STOP THROWING THINGS!
>> KEEP TALKING BECAUSE I AM
LISTENING.
AND I -- OH, MY GOD.
I JUST PULLED MY PINKY.
>> CRYSTAL, JUST STOP.
I JUST SAW ON YOUR COMPUTER THAT
ALL YOU HAVE OPEN IS A BUNCH OF
TABS FOR ANN TAYLOR LOFT.
>> FOR WORK CLOTHES BECAUSE I AM
ALWAYS HERE.
>> RIGHT.
AND WHERE?
LIKE HONESTLY, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M CHE'S ASSISTANT.
>> OKAY.
>> HEY, MAN, CRYSTAL'S THE BEST.
>> YOUR VERY BUSY COWORKER,
>>> OKAY.
LOOKS LIKE OUR AORS HAVE
ARRIVED ON SET.
WHAT DO YOWE DO THIS
THING?
>>NOW I'M READY.
>> YES.
>> KEITH, I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR LETTING ME
DO THIS DRUG COMMERCIAL.
I'M SOMEONE WHO NEVER THOUGHT
MUCH ABOUT MEDICATIONS UNTIL I
RELY SEN TO WOMEN'S  I
ISSUES AND HONESTLY I THINK WILL
HELP PEOPLE.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
I HOPE SO TOO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GIVE IT A
TRY, HUH?
>> I THINK THAT SOUNDS TERRIFIC.
>> ALL RIGHT.
PLACES, EVERYBODY
AND ACTION
♪ THERE'S A NEW DRUG FOR GALS
OVER 40, IT'S HORMONE-FREE AND
MADE JUST FOR ME ♪
♪ EASY TO USE AND IT'S SUPER
EFFECTIVE ♪
♪ THAT'S UNEXPECTED, SO WHAT IS
IT CALLED ♪
♪ IT'S CALLED VA JERTED, HOW
GREAT A NAME IS THAT, IT'S
CALLED VAGERTED ♪
♪ AND WHERE IS IT INSERTED ♪
♪ YOU ALREADY KNOW ♪
>> NOT BAD FOR A FIRST TAKE,
Y'ALL.
>> I ACTUALLY HAVE A QUESTION.
>> YOU DON'T THINK IT'S
DIGNIFIED ENOUGH.
>> NO.
I ACTUALLY LOVE WHAT YOU'RE
DOING WITH VAGERTED.
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF WE'RE
ALL DOING IT JUSTICE.
SOME OF US ARE UP HERE REALLY
SELLING IT AND SOME OF US, OR
MAYBE ONE OR TWO OF US ARE NOT
GIVING IT THE SAME ENERGY.
I DON'T WANT TO POINT FINGER.
IT WOULD BE SO SAD IF PEOPLE
DIDN'T BUY VAGERTED BECAUSE THE
DANCING WAS MID.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT WAS.
BUT I ALSO HAVE A QUESTION.
THIS DRUG IS FOR MEN PAUSE,
RIGHT, SO WHY DOESN'T THE SONG
COME OUT AND SAY THAT?
>> WELL, WE DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO
CHANGE THE CHANNEL.
LET'S TRY THIS NEXT VERSE AND
GIVE IT MORE ENERGY THIS TIME.
>> THAT'S A GREAT NOTE.
IT'S A GREAT NOTE FOR EVERYONE.
>> AND ACTION!
♪ IN JUST ONE WEEK, YOU'LL
NOTICE A DIFFERENCE, INSERT IT
DOWN THERE JUST AS DEEP AS YOU
CAN ♪
♪ GOOD-BYE LABIDO, VAGERTED,
THAT'S THE NAME THEY CLOSE, THEY
CLOSE VAGERTED ♪
COME ON, GIRLS, LET'S DANCE.
>> VAGITA IS NOT FOR EVERYBODY,
SO ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF IT'S RIGHT
FOR YOU.
IF HE SAYS NO, FIND ANOTHER
DOCTOR.
JUST KEEP GOING TO DIFFERENT
DOCTORS UNTIL ONE OF THEM SAYS
YOU CAN TAKE VAGITA.
>> WHAT DID HE CALL IT?
>> DO NOT USE VAGITA IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO VAGITA.
IF YOU ARE ALERNL IT TO PEANUTS,
DON'T PUT IT IN YOUR VA JURY TA.
SOME PEOPLE LIKE VAGITA, SOME
PEOPLE DO NOT.
I THINK IT'S VERY NICE.
CLINICAL TRIALS HAVE NOT BEEN
COMPLETES IN THE SENSE THAT THEY
HAVE NOT STARTED.
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> VAGITA SHOULD NOT BE TAKEN
ORALLY, EVEN THOUGH IT TASTES
REAL GOOD.
VAGITA IS HIGHLY ADDICTIVE.
IT GIVES YOU AN ALCOHOL-LIKE
BUZZ WITHOUT A HANGOVER.
I WISH I HAD VAGITA SO I COULD
TAKE IT.
TRY VAGINA TODAY.
>> OKAY, CAN WE STOP.
>> YEAH.
HE JUST SAID TRY VAGINA TODAY.
THIS PRODUCT SOUNDS REALLY
AWFUL.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S AWFUL.
LOOK AROUND.
IT'S LIKE ONE OF US IS BEYONCE
AND THE OTHER TWO ARE REALLY BAD
AT DANCING.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU WERE SO NICE AT THE
AUDITION.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
>>KAY.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
>> GOOD LUCK, KEITH.
YOU'LL NEVER REPLACE US.
>> WELL, NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
>> HIT THE MUSIC.
♪ THERE'S A NEW DRUG FOR GALS
OVER 40, IT'S CALLED
VA-JAY-JAY ♪
>> I THINK IT'S VAGERTED.
>> WHATEVER.
>> ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF VA-JAY-JAY
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
♪
♪ I GET TO SEE
LIGHTNING IN HER HEART
NEVER ENDING LIGHT
WHAT A THOUGHT ♪
♪ DARLING YOU'D MAKE
THE WALLS CRY
DARLING YOU'D MAKE
THE WALLS CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TIME IS A DOORFRAME
I WANNA GO THROUGH
AS LONG AS IT LEADS ME
BACK TO YOU YEAH ♪
♪ IF YOU EVER LEFT ME
I WOULD DIE
AND EVEN THE WALLS
WOULD CRY ♪
♪
♪ WHENEVER YOUR HEADLIGHTS
DO YOUR HEART
I LOVE YOU ALL OVER
EVERY START OHH ♪
♪ DARLING YOU'D MAKE
THE WALLS CRY
DARLING YOU'D MAKE
THE WALLS CRY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TIME IS A DOORFRAME
I WANNA GO THROUGH
AS LONG AS IT LEADS ME
BACK TO YOU YEAH ♪
♪ IF YOU EVER LEFT ME
I WOULD DIE
AND EVEN THE WALLS
WOULD CRY ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
LEVANTATE EN AMOR
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ LEVANTATE
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
LEVANTATE
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ AS WE PROCEED
AS WE PROCEED
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
AS WE PROCEED
TO GIVE YOU WHAT YOU NEED ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
AS WE PROCEED
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ AS WE PROCEED
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
AS WE PROCD
TO GIVE YOU WHAT YOUEED ♪
♪ EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY
EVEN THE WALLS WOULD CRY ♪
♪
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
GIRLS, TAKE A GREAT.
GRETEL, TURBO.
COME ON, WE NEED TO TALK.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WELL, AS THE JONAS BROTHERS
MANAGER, PART OF MY JOB IS TO
DELIVER BAD NEWS.
THE BOYS WANT TO HIRE A NEW
CHOREOGRAPHER.
>> YOU CAN'T FIRE US.
WE INVENTED JOE BRO CORE OWE.
>> I GAVE NICK HIS HEAD BOP.
I TOLD HIM T GO SIDE TO SIDE
WITH A FINGER SHIMMY.
>> BE THAT AS IT MAY, THE BOYS
FEEL THEY'RE NOT A TEENY BOPPER
BAND ANYMORE.
AND THEY WANT A MORE MATURE
STAGE ACT.
>> THAT MA CHUR?
WHO DO THEY THINK CAN DO THAT?
>> HARD TO DESCRIBE.
EASIER TO SEE.
LET HER IN.
>> MY NAME IS SALLY O'MALLEY.
I'M 50 YEARS OLD.
NOT ONE OF THOSE GALS WHO'S
AFRAID TO TELL HER REAL AGE.
AND I LIKE TO KICK, STRETCH, AND
KICK!
AND I'M 50 YEARS OLD.
50 YEARS OLD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE BOYS WERE VISITING THEIR
GRANDMOTHER, AND SHE TOOK THEM
TO HER SENIOR CENTER'S
PRODUCTION OF ANNIE, AND SALLY
HERE WAS STARRING, AND SHE
ROCKED THEIR WORLD.
THEY DON'T WANT TO FIRE ANYBODY.
THEY WERE JUST HOPING YOU COULD
LET SALLY ADD A LITTLE
SOMETHING.
>> OKAY, SALLY, WHAT LITTLE
SOMETHING DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
ADD?
>> 45 DECADES OF LITTLE DANCING
AND RED PANTS DANCING.
I GOT HALF A CENTURY OF SHIZZLE
IN MY LADY SNIZZLE.
NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT.
BEING A WOMAN.
THE GRAND CANYON'S GOT NOTHING
ON ME.
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE ENGINEERED BY
ENTIRE LIFE SO I WOULD NEVER
HAVE TO E WHAT I JUST SAW.
AND RUSSELL, ARE YOU SURE SHE'S
50?
>> HONEY, I'VE BEEN 50 SINCE
BEFORE YOU WAS BORN.
>> CAN YOU PLEASE JUST GIVE IT A
TRY?
THE BOYS FEEL THAT SALLY
REPRESENTS WHO THEY ARE NOW.
>> DO THEY?
THEN TELL US WHO YOU ARE, SALLY.
>> LISTEN, I'M A CHOO CHOO
CHARLIE AND A CLASS ACT.
>> HEY, RUSSELL, I LOVE YOU.
I JUST THINK THE JONAS BROTHERS
ARE MAKING A HUGE MISTAKE.
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK, HUH?
WELL, WELL, WELL, IF IT ISN'T
NEIL, CALVIN, AND JOHN.
>> NICK, JOE, AND KEVIN.
WE CAME BY BECAUSE WE HAD A
FEELING THEY MIGHT NOT
UNDERSTAND YOUR NEW CONCEPT.
>> SO WE WANTED TO SHOW THEM.
>> LOOKING GOOD.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD, BOYS.
NOW PUT SOME BONUS?
YOUR JONAS.
NOW, HIT IT, RUSSELL.
HIP, HIP, ARMS, ARMS, NOW KICK,
STRETCH, AND KICK, STRETCH,
KICK, STRETCH.
>> WAIT A SECOND.
WAIT A SECOND.
OH, MY GOD.
I AM SO SORRY I EVER DOUBTED
YOU, SALLY.
I SEE IT NOW.
THEY ARE GOING TO PUT THE BOYS
ON STAGE IN PACKED STADIUMS
AROUND THE WORLD, AND THEY'RE
GONNA.
>> KICK.
>> STRETCH.
>> AND JUMP.
>> JUMP?
NEIL, YOU'RE FIRED.
>> WHAT?
>> WAIT A SECOND, SALLY, YOU CAN
TAKE HIS PLACE.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
DO YOU KNOW ANY OF OUR SONGS?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I'M 50 YEARS OLD.
50.
OVERWHELMED.
SURE, TRUMP GOT INDICTED, BUT
NOW EVERYONE SAYS THE CASE
AGAINST HIM IS WEAK AND THAT
HE'LL NEVER SERVE ANY JAIL TIME.
AS SOMEONE WHOSE ENTIRE
PERSONALITY IS HATING DONALD
TRUMP, YOU NEED MORE.
YOU NEED TO FEEL CALM AND
REASSURED.
YOU NEED THE NEWEST MEDITATION
APP.
CNZ.
NEW DETAILS FROM TRUMP'S ARREST,
FEATURING YOUR FAVORITE CNN
ANCHORS.
>> HE'S THE FIRST AMERICAN
PRESIDENT TO EVER BE INDICTED.
THIS IS TRULY A HISTORIC AND
HUMILIATING MOMENT.
>> TRUMP IS A BRAD, DEFEATED
MAN.
THEY MADE HIM COME FROM FLORIDA
WHERE IT'S 80 DEGREES TO NEW
YORK WHERE IT'S ONLY 60 DEGREES.
HOW DEPRESSING.
>> HIS MOTOR CADE WASN'T THAT
BIG.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE BIGGER,
BUT IT WAS SO SMALL.
>> DONALD WAS ALL ALONE, NO
FAMILY OR FRIENDS TO SUPPORT
HIM.
I SHOULDN'T SAY THIS AS A
JOURNALIST, BUT THAT A LOSER.
>> THAT NEW YORK TIMES REPORTER
MAGGIE HABERMAN SOOTH YOU TO
SLEEP.
>> THAT IS A NIGHTMARE, AND HE'S
REALLY FREAKING OUT BECAUSE NOW
HE KNOWS THERE ARE CONSEQUENCES.
>> YOU CAN ALSO LISTEN TO CLIPS
OF TRUMP AND HIS ALLIES
SPIRALING.
>> PLEASE, DONALD J. TRUMP IS AN
INNOCENT MAN AND HE NEEDS YOUR
HELP.
SEND HIM ALL YOUR MONEY TODAY AT
DON'T J. TRUMP RU/FUND RAISING
SCAM.GUILTY.
>> HIS COURT APPEARANCE WON'T BE
UNTIL AT LEAST DECEMBER.
THAT'S WHY THEY HAVE A WHOLE
LIST OF TRUMP INDICTMENT ASR.
>> CAN YOU HEAR HIM GETTING
FINGERPRINTED, AND THE DA
OPENING HIS BIG LEATHER
BRIEFCASE, AND A LITTLE GAVEL
FROM THE JUDGE.
I WONDER IF HE'LL EVEN HEAR HAND
CUFFS.
>> WITH ADDITIONAL IN-APP
PURCHASES LIKE AUDIO E RAT KA OF
ALVIN BRAGG READING ALL 40
FELONY ACCOUNTS.
>> COUNT ONE, FALSIFYING
BUSINESS RECORDS IN THE FIRST
DEGREE.
COUNT TWO, FALSIFYING BUSINESS
RECORDS IN THE FIRST DEGREE.
COUNT THREE, FALSIFYING --
>> YOU WAITED SEVEN YEARS FOR
THIS INDICTMENT, AND YOU WANT
EVERY DELICIOUS DETAIL.
>>, WHAT ETHNICITY IS TRUMP'S
JUDGE AGAIN?
>> HISPANIC.
>> CNZN, IN YOUR MIND, HE'S
ALREAWe aN JAIL.
MARTIN SHORT.
I LOVE YOU, LAUREN MICHAELS.
YOU ARE THE BEST.
AND THIS BRILLIANT CAST, OH, MY
GOD.
SO GOOD!
AND OUR WONDERFULCREW.
THIS IS JUST A GIFT TO BE BACK.
THANK YOU!
>> YEAH!