>>> AND NOW, A MESSAGE FROM THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
>>> MY FELLOW AMERICANS,
THIS TUESDAY, OUR MIDTERM ELECTIONS
WILL DETERMINE THE FATE OF OUR DEMOCRACY,
AND LET'S JUST SAY,
BIG YIKES.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I GUESS THE DEMOCRATS MESSAGE
JUST AIN'T GETTING THROUGH.
PLUS, I'M OVER HERE TALKING TO
PEOPLE WHO DON'T EXIST.
I DOT KNOW MUCH.
WHO'S THAT?
NOBODY'S THERE.
FOLKS, I'M TRYING LIKE HELL, I
PROMISE.
PELOTON
TEMPTING FATE
I PASS THAT BIG ASS
INFRASTRUCTURE BILL.
REMEMBER THAT?
$65 BILLION.
LOT OF YOU RED STATE  GOT
BROADBAND INTERNET
SO YOU CAN
SHARE YOUR PAUL PELOSI GAY
INTERNET FICTION AT LIGHTNING
SPEED.
BY THE WAY
YOU RIGHT THINKERS SURE DO LOVE
THINKING UP THESE GAY SCENARIOS.
KIND OF SUS.
I GET IT.
I'M NO SPRING CHICKEN,
BUT PEOPLE ARE YELLING AT OBAMA
CALLING HIM HOT.
HOW DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME
FEEL?
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR, GOOGLE
YOUNG JOE BIDEN
AND START A
BUBBLE BATH.
YOU GUYS THINK I'M BORING NOW?
WELL, I CAN DO CRAZY STUFF TOO.
I SCARED MYSELF.
LISTEN, FOLKS, THAT'S THE
PROBLEM.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY STARS ANYMORE.
TOO MANY RAPHAEL WARNOCKS AND
NOT ENOUGH HERSCHEL WALKERS,
WHICH IS WHY WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
SOME CHANGES BEFORE NEXT TUESDAY
WITH THE DEMOCRATS
EXCITING
SIZZLE
HEY, CALIFORNIA, SICK OF ADAM
SCHIFF?
MEET THE NEXT CONGRESSWOMAN.
PRESIDENT
IT'S MARIANNE WILLIAMSSON.
>> AS A PROMINENT AUTHOR AND
LEVEL FOUR ENCHANTRESS,
I'M
READY TO FIGHT FOR THE AMERICAN
DREAM,
WHICH I CAN'T IN THIS
BOWL.
>> SOUNDS COOL.
AMERICA'S NEXT DEFENSE AGAINST
THE DARK ARTS TEACHER, FOLKS.
NOW, I LIKE DR. OZ, THIS NEXT
GUY HAS POLITICAL EXPERIENCE.
HE WAS THE MAYOR OF FLAVOR TOWN
FOR OVER 20 YEARS,
GUY FIERI.
>> LISTEN, MAN, AMERICA'S HUNGRY
FOR CHANGE,
BUT DO Y'ALL WANT A
FULL PLATE OF PAID FAMILY LEAVE
DRIPPING IN DONKEY SAUCE?
FULL THROTTLE, WHOO!
>> LOVE THAT GUY.
DREAM JOB.
HEY, OHIO, MEET YOUR NEXT
SENATOR.
TEKASHI
>> HEY!
I WANT NO CAP ON SOCIAL
SECURITIES.
NO CAP.
DEMOCRATS, BABY.
TRE WAY.
TRE WAY!
>> WHAT A TERRIFYING YOUNG MAN.
TIRED OF GRETCHEN WHITMER?
NEXT
MEET STORMY DANIELS.
>> HI, TV.
I MAY BE A FORMER ADULT STAR,
SEASON SEVEN
BUT I'M WILLING TO DEBACE MYSELF
AND ENTER U.S. POLITICS.
I CAN WORK WITH ANYONE,
AND I'M WILLING TO REACH AROUND THE
AISLE TO GET THINGS DONE.
>> I THINK IT'S REACH ACROSS THE
AISLE.
>> SURE.
YOU DO YOU.
>> TALENTED ACTRESS.
NOW INTRODUCING SOMEONE WHO'S
GOING TO BEAT MARCO RUBIO
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT AFRAID TO
FIGHT.
SHE'S YOUR NEXT SENATOR FOR
FLORIDA, AZAELIA BANKS.
>> I'M A WITCH, BITCH!
>> OKAY.
FINALLY, PEOPLE GOT MAT AT ME
ABOUT STUDENT LOAN FORGIVENESS,
BUT HE'S IN CHARGE OF IT NOW.
TRACY MORGAN.
>> OKAY.
Y'ALL WANT THAT MONEY?
WHY DON'T YOU COME ON OVER HERE
AND RUB MY BELLY.
>> THANK YOU, TRACY.
EVERYBODY, GET UP HERE.
THERE THEY ARE, YOUR NEW
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES.
ALL RIGHT, TEAM.
WHAT DO WE WANT?
>> I KIND OF WANT SOME
SUGAR-FREE WHITE CASTLE.
>> WHEN DO WE WANT IT?
>> I MEAN, MY MIND IS LIKE
WHENEVER YOU GOOD, BABY GIRL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO, TEAM.
WE'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, AMY
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S SO GREAT TO BE BACK HERE
HOSTING "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
I HAVE BEEN SO BUSY.
YOU MAY HAVE SEEN MY HULU SHOW,
LIFE AND BETH
AND "INSIDE AMY
SCHUMER IS BACK ON PARAMOUNT+"
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE THE
HONOR OF BEING THE FINAL HOST
BEFORE THE MIDTERM ABORTIONS --
ELECTIONS.
WHAT DID I SAY?
SORRY.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT WHAT'S AT
STAKE IF WE DON'T VOTE.
PEOPLE LOVE GIVING PREGNANT
WOMEN ADVICE, DON'T THEY?
THE WHOLE TIME I WAS PREGNANT, I
HAD THIS ONE FRIEND TELLING ME,
YOU GOT TO DO PRENATAL YOGA.
IT REALLY HELPS WITH THE BIRTH.
SO I IMMEDIATELY SIGNED UP FOR A
C-SECTION.
BUT NO, I DID.
I HAD A C, HE CAME OUT THE
SUNROOF.
NO MATTER HOW YOU GIVE BIRTH,
THE DOCTORS ALL TELL YOU --
IT
COULD BE VAGINAL, C-SECTION.
THEY ALMOST NEVER COME OUT OF
YOUR BUTT HOLE.
BUT THEY TELL YOU, NO MATTER WHAT,
THE DOCTORS SAY,
YOU CANNOT HAVE SEX FOR SIX WEEKS.
YOU GOT IT?
SIX WEEKS, NO SEX.
I WAS LIKE, OKAY.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU JUST
WOLVERINED ME OPEN?
REMEMBER THAT?
HOW ABOUT SIX YEARS?
THAT'S WHEN I THINK I'LL BE
READY.
OKAY?
REMEMBER, HIS FOOT GOT CAUGHT ON
MY INTESTINES.
WHEN CAN I GET RAW DOGGED FROM
BEHIND?
PLEASE.
BUT MY HUSBAND AND I, WE DO HAVE
A GOOD SEX LIFE.
MARRIED PEOPLE, WE HAVE FOUND
THAT THE BEST WEEKDAY TO HAVE SEX
IS ALWAYS TOMORROW.
YEAH.
WE'RE LIKE, WE ATE TODAY.
MAYBE WE WON'T EAT TOMORROW.
THAT WILL BE A GOOD DAY FOR US.
MY HUSBAND'S THE BEST.
HE ALWAYS -- BEFORE WE HAVE SEX,
HE PUTS THE LIGHTS ON,
YOU KNOW,
AND I SHUT THEM OFF, AND HE PUTS
THEM ON.
AND HE'S LIKE, AMY, WHY ARE YOU
SO SHY?
YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL BODY.
I'M LIKE, OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
YOU THINK I DON'T WANT YOU TO
SEE ME.
SO SWEET, RIGHT?
BUT IT IS.
I'LL BE HONEST, IT'S AWKWARD
HAVING SEX WITH YOUR SPOUSE, IT
IS.
BECAUSE, LIKE, THAT'S YOUR
FAMILY.
YOU KNOW?
LIKE I HAVE THANKSGIVING WITH
YOU.
I LAY OUT YOUR SWEATERS, YOU
KNOW?
LIKE I CAN'T GO DOWN ON YOU.
YOU'RE MY EMERGENCY CONTACT FOR
CHRIST'S SAKE.
IT'S SICK.
WE CAN'T TALK DIRTY TO EACH
ANYMORE.
WE KNOW EACH OTHER TOO WELL.
I'M ALWAYS LIKE, I'M GOING TO --
HE'S LIKE, NO, YOU'RE NOT.
I'M LIKE, NO, NO, I'M NOT.
WE DO A LOT OF ROLE PLAY.
BUT I ALWAYS PICK THE SAME ROLE.
I'M ALWAYS LIKE, OKAY, I
AM IN A COMA.
GO.
MY HUSBAND IS DIAGNOSED, HE'S ON
THE AUTISM SPECTRUM.
HE HAS AUTISM SPECTRUM DISORDER.
USED TO BE CALLED ASPERGER'S,
BUT TURNS OUT
THAT HAD LIKE NAZI
TIES, KANYE.
ISN'T THAT CRAZY?
BUT NO.
IT'S BEEN REALLY POSITIVE FOR
OUR FAMILY
TO HAVE HIM
DIAGNOSED.
I UNDERSTAND SO MUCH MORE ABOUT
HIS BEHAVIOR,
AND IT'S GIVEN HIM
SO MANY TOOLS.
NOW, IF SOMEBODY IS IN THE
MIDDLE OF A LONG, BORING STORY,
HE WILL STRAIGHT UP JUST WALK
AWAY.
AND WHEN PEOPLE FIND OUT THAT HE
HAS AUTISM, THEY DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT IT.
THEY'RE LIKE, OH, DOES HE LOVE
TO COUNT?
SHOULD WE DROP A BUNCH OF STRAWS ON THE FLOOR
AND HE CAN GATHER
THEM AND COUNT THEM?
I'M LIKE, YEAH, THAT SOUNDS
PRETTY FUN.
I WOULD LIKE TO DO THAT.
HE NEVER REALLY LANDS A
COMPLIMENT WITH ME.
HE TELLS ME I LOOK COMFORTABLE A
LOT.
WE HAVE DIFFERENT LOVE
LANGUAGES.
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO, WE WERE
SITTING OUTSIDE.
IT WAS A NICE NIGHT.
IT LOOKED LIKE IT WAS GOING TO
RAIN.
I WAS FEELING SENTIMENTAL.
I WAS LIKE, EVEN THOUGH THESE
PAST COUPLE OF YEARS
WITH THE
PANDEMIC AND EVERYTHING, IT'S
BEEN SO STRESSFUL,
STILL THIS
TIME, BEING WITH YOU AND OUR SON,
THEY HAVE BEEN THE BEST
YEARS OF MY LIFE.
AND HE JUST LOOKED AT ME AND SAID,
I'M GOING TO GO PUT THE
WINDOWS UP IN THE CAR.
YEAH.
MY GUY.
ONE OF THE TIMES WE PLAY THE
GAME AUTISM OR JUST A MAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
AND I'LL LEAVE YOU WITH WHAT HE
SAID TO ME RIGHT BEFORE I CAME
ON STAGE TONIGHT.
I SAID, BABE, IS THIS OKAY?
AND HE SAID, WELL, IT'S TOO
LATE.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
STICK
>>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WE HAVE TWO HOUSE SALADS.
AND THE MATSA BALL SOUP.
>> ME, ME, ME.
THAT'S FOR ME.
THANK YOU.
I HAVE BEEN CRAVING THIS SOUP.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL YOU.
IT JUST LIKE BRINGS ME HOME.
>> SMELLS AMAZING.
>> WELL, YOU CAN'T HAVE ANY.
I'M KIDDING, BUT I'M NOT BECAUSE
LIKE I HAVE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS SOUP LIKE NONSTOP.
FOR REAL, I WOKE UP OUT OF A
DEAD SLEEP IS OTHER NIGHT JUST
THINKING ABOUT THIS SOUP.
SAT STRAIGHT UP, EYES WIDE OPEN,
AND THOUGHT MATSA BALL SOUP FROM
MANNY'S LIKE A PSYCHO.
I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
>> I GUESS I HAVE SOME NEWS.
>> OOH, WHAT IS IT?
>> MATT AND I ARE SEPARATING.
>> OH, NO.
WHAT?
>> GIRLY, FOR REAL?
>> YEAH.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO RUIN LUNCH.
JUST EAT.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
LET'S LIKE EAT AND THEN TALK.
THAT FEELS RIGHT.
>> OF COURSE WE'RE NOT GOING TO
EAT.
THAT IS SO SAD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW.
GOD.
THANK YOU FOR TELLING US.
OBVIOUSLY, LET US KNOW LIKE HOW
IT WORKS OUT.
>> HE SAID HE'S GOING TO TAKE
THE KIDS.
>> MY GOD.
THAT MONSTER.
WHAT A BASTARD.
>> GOD.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I SAY, GOOD
RIDDANCE, RIGHT?
>> GOOD RIDDANCE TO HER KIDS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WE GOT TO MAKE A PLAN.
>> I'M ALREADY TALKING TO A
LAWYER.
OH, HERE HE IS NOW.
>> OH, GOD.
YOU BETTER TAKE THAT CALL.
TAKE AS LONG AS YOU NEED.
LIKE, GO OUTSIDE.
>> WHAT?
NO!
>> NOW WHAT?
>> MY LAWYER GOT DISBARRED.
MY LIFE IS JUST SUCH A MESS
RIGHT NOW.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW THE HALF OF
IT.
LIKE I TOLD YOU GUYS, I GOT THAT
VP OF MARKETING JOB, AND IT WAS
TOTAL BS.
I NEVER EVEN APPLIED FOR IT.
THERE'S ALL THIS OTHER STUFF
TOO.
LIKE I HAVE BEEN DRINKING LIKE
AS SOON AS I WAKE UP.
AND I STEAL MY SON'S ADDERALL,
AND HE REALLY NEEDS IT.
♪ HOW LONG MUST I WAIT TO EAT MY
SOUP WITHOUT LOOKING LIKE AN
A-HOLE ♪
♪ NOT THAT I DON'T CARE ABOUT
HER, BUT I CARE ABOUT MY SOUP A
LITTLE MORE ♪
♪ MY GOD, SHE'S STILL TALKING,
BUT, HEY, AT LEAST SHE'S NOT
CRYING ♪
♪ NEVER MIND, SHE JUST STARTED
♪ OH, BUT I HAVE A GREAT IDEA ♪
♪ IF I PRETEND TO TAKE A SIP OF
MY WATER, I CAN TAKE THE STRAW
AND PUT IT IN MY SOUP ♪
♪ AND PLANT IT PERFECT.
THE STRAW IS HITTING BROTH ♪
♪ AND OH, MY GOD.
SHE JUST ASKED ME A QUESTION ♪
>> I MEAN, SO WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
>> I THINK, YEAH, YOU SHOULD GO
FOR IT.
>> REPRESENT HERSELF IN COURT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WOULD YOU MIND IF I HAD A SIP OF
YOUR WATER?
I FINISHED MINE
♪ HOT DAMN, SHE'S TAKING MY
WATER ♪
♪ I BETTER HIDE THE STRAW IN MY
SHIRT ♪
♪ BUT, OH, WHAT IS THIS, SHE'S
SOBBING AT LAST ♪
♪ HER HEAD'S IN HER HANDS, CAN'T
LET THIS MOMENT PASS ♪
♪ GOT TO EAT THIS SOUP ♪
>> I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER.
THANK YOU GIRLS FOR LETTING ME
VENT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
ANY TIME, YOU JUST DO YOU, GIRL.
OKAY?
>> HOW'S YOUR SOUP?
>> IT IS HOTTER THAN I THOUGHT,
BUT I'M GOOD.
♪ GOT TO EAT THIS SOUP ♪
>>> ARE YOU FEELING TIRED AND
WORN DOWN?
SICK OF THE ENDLESS GRIND AT
WORK?
EXHAUSTED BY YOUR FAMILY,
DESPERATE FOR SOME PEACE AND
QUIET.
>> DANIEL, YOUR KIDS WANT YOU!
>> THEN ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
COVID.
AS SOON AS GETTING COVID, YOU'RE
GUARANTEED
A FIVE AND SOMETIMES
EVEN TEN-DAY VACATION FROM ALL
OF LIFE'S PROBLEMS.
>> I NEEDED A BREAK,
SO MY
DOCTOR SUGGESTED I GET COVID,
AND IT WAS THE GREATEST WEEK OF
MY LIFE.
ALL I WANTED TO DO WAS
WATCH THE NETFLIX I WANTED TO WATCH,
AND I WAS FINALLY ABLE TO THANKS TO
COVID.
>> AT FIRST I WAS WORRIED ABOUT
GETTING COVID, BUT MY DOCTOR
ENSURED ME IT WAS OKAY.
HPV
>> SIDE EFFECTS OF COVID INCLUDE HAVING COVID,
WHICH IS STILL
KIND OF BAD, BUT DOESN'T IT FEEL
DIFFERENT NOW?
>> I DEFINITELY GOT SICK.
I ALSO GOT PAID FOR TEN DAYS TO
NEVER LEAVE THE BLANKET.
PLUS I GOT TO TELL PEOPLE ABOUT
IT AT WORK.
IT WAS LIKE I HAD A BAD COLD FOR
THREE DAYS.
>> OF COURSE I HAD TO ISOLATE
FROM MY KIDS
BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT TO GET THEM SICK.
>> WHAT DO THEY EAT?
>> I GAVE IT 14 DAYS TO BE EXTRA
SAFE.
>> FOR AN EXTRA FEE, WE'LL KNOCK
OUT THE WI-FI NEAR YOUR HOUSE SO
YOU CAN'T DO ANY ZOOM.
>> OH, WELL, TOO BAD.
>> COVID IS THE PERFECT WAY TO
GET OUT OF JURY DUTY
WEDDING
NEIGHBOR'S
ADULT BAPTISM, AND HUSBAND'S
MURDER TRIAL.
AT THIS POINT, COVID IS A
TEN-DAY CRUISE,
WHICH IS ALSO A
GREAT WAY TO GET COVID.
>> COVID ISN'T FOR ANYONE.
THAT'S WHY THERE'S THE NEW
ALWAYS POSITIVE COVID HOME TEST
THAT COME WITH TWO PINK LINES ALREADY
DRAWN.
>> AGAIN?
>> YOU JUST HAD IT A WEEK AGO.
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS TO ME.
COVID. BECAUSE SOMETIMES THE ONLY
WAY TO GET MENTALLY HEALTHY
IS
TO GET PHYSICALLY SICK.
>> SURE.
THERE MIGHT BE LONG-TERM MEMORY
PROBLEMS,
BUT THAT MIGHT BE
AMAZING BECAUSE THERE'S SO MUCH
I WANT TO FORGET.
>> MY BRAIN IS ALREADY REALLY
BAD.
BUT IF I DON'T HAVE TO TALK TO
PEOPLE IN A WEEK,
I'LL TAKE THAT
DEAL IN A HORSE BEAT.
>> YOU MEAN HEART BEAT.
>> EITHER WAY, THANKS COVID.
>> THANKS, COVID.
VANKS
>> I THINK I'LL GET COVID AGAIN.
TODAY.
>> COVID, GO AHEAD.
YOU DESERVE A BREAK.
>>> SO WITH THAT SAID,
MR. HUBBARD COULD NOT HAVE BEEN
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
YOUR WITNESS.
>> THANK YOU, COUNSEL.
MOVING ON TO CROSS-EXAMINATION.
>> SO ON THE NIGHT OF YOUR
WIFE'S DISAPPEARANCE, WHAT DID
YOU DO?
>> I CALLED THE POLICE.
>> REALLY?
BECAUSE RECORDS SHOW THAT YOU
DID NOT.
AND IN FACT, THE POLICE DIDN'T
SHOW UP UNTIL YOUR NEIGHBORS
CALLED.
>> OH!
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND WHEN THE FORENSIC TEAM
EXAMINED YOUR CLOTHING, THEY
FOUND TRACES OF BLOOD.
>> ORDER IN THE COURT.
WE DON'T NEED ANY VOCAL
REACTIONS FROM THE JURY.
>> FROM US?
>> SORRY.
WE JUST DID NOT EXPECT TRACES OF
BLOOD.
>> PROSECUTION, THE FLOOR IS
YOURS.
>> PER THE FORENSIC
INVESTIGATION, THE VICTIM WAS
FOUND WITH MULTIPLE LACERATIONS
TO HER ABDOMEN.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> DO WE NEED TO TAKE A RECESS.
>> IT WAS JUST GETTING GOOD.
>> I'M SERIOUSLY AT THE EDGE OF
MY SHEET.
I'M SHAKING.
>> MY HEART IS BEATING SO FAST
MY APPLE WATCH THINKS I'M
GETTING STEPS.
>> ORDER IN THE COURT, OR I WILL
HOLD YOU IN CONTEMPT.
>> WE HEAR THAT.
>> GUYS, GUYS.
>> KEEP IT DOWN.
>> PROSECUTION, PLEASE, ON TO
YOUR NEXT LINE OF QUESTIONING.
>> MR. HUBBARD, YOU CLAIM YOU
WERE AT THE OFFICE ON THE 14th,
BUT AS THE DEFENSE WAS SAYING --
I'M SORRY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING NOW?
>> POSING FOR THE SKETCH ARTIST.
>> HOW MUCH FOR THE DEATH
PENALTY?
>> NOW THE MURDER IS YELLING AT
US.
>> I'M LIKE CRAZY TRIGGERED.
CAN I LIE DOWN AND LOOK AT MY
PHONE FOR A WHILE.
>> JURORS, THIS IS YOUR FINAL
WARNING.
>> OKAY.
NOW THE JUDGE IS TRYING TO
SILENCE THREE WOMEN OF COLOR.
>> OKAY.
CAN WE PLEASE MOVE ON?
AS I WAS SAYING --
>> OH, MY GOD.
WAIT.
I'M LITERALLY SO BORED.
>> CAN WE JUST LIKE PUT ON MUSIC
OR SOMETHING?
>> MIDNIGHT!
♪ MIDNIGHT, I STAY UP, I'M
TAYLOR SWIFT ♪
>> THAT IS NOT A SONG FROM
MIDNIGHT.
>> I JUST NEED TO FINISH MY
CROSS EXAM.
MR. HUBBARD, HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
THE STEAK KNIFE THAT WAS MISSING
FROM YOUR SET.
>> IT HAD BEEN MISSING SINCE WE
MOVED IN.
>> REALLY?
BECAUSE IN A STORM DRAIN NEARBY,
DETECTIVES FOUND THIS SUPPOSEDLY
MISSING KNIFE.
BAILIFF, SHOW THE COURT EXHIBIT
B.
>> IT'S NOT IN HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU NEED THIS?
I'M SORRY.
THIS CHICKEN IS TOUGH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT IS IT.
YOU THREE ARE IN CONTEMPT OF
COURT FOR DISORDERLY CONDUCT.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
SORRY.
BUT REAL QUICK, WHO AM I?
>> YOU'RE HIM!
>> THE MURDER!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
AND WHO AM I?
WHO AM I?
>> OH, YOU THE DEAD WIFE.
>> YES.
>> YOUR HONOR, SHE'S USING THE
MURDER KNIFE TO CUT UP THE
CHICKEN.
>> RELAX.
I CAN'T EVEN CUT THE CHICKEN
ANYWAY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
>> THE LAWYER LADY IS SAYING HE
KILLED HER WITH THAT KNIFE.
>> BUT THE KNIFE ISN'T EVEN
SHARP ENOUGH --
>> TO CUT THROUGH HER CHICKEN.
>> WHICH MEANS --
>> HE'S INNOCENT!
>> THAT'S WHAT I HAVE BEEN
SAYING!
>> YEA!
>>> ON OCTOBER 27, ELON MUSK
COMPLETED HIS $44 BILLION
PURCHASE OF TWITTER.
ON OCTOBER 28, MUSK PUBLICLY
ANNOUNCED A CONTENT MODERATOR TO
REVIEW PREVIOUSLY DISRUPTED
ACCOUNTS.
WE NOW GO LIVE.
>> GOOD MORNING, EVEN.
TODAY WE WILL DECIDE IF
SUSPENDED ACCOUNTS WILL BE LET
BACK ON TWITTER.
>> WHO BETTER TO DO IT THAN US,
THE ONLY TWO TWITTER EMPLOYEES
WHO HAVEN'T BEEN LAID OFF.
>> YET.
>> LET'S BEGIN OUR FIRST FAN
ACCOUNT.
SAY YOUR NAME.
>> YOU WISH.
BUT HERE'S WHAT I WILL TELL YOU.
THE COVID PANDEMIC WAS CREATED
BY BIG PHARMA TO SILENCE ME.
EVERYBODY TRIES TO SILENCE ME.
MA'AM, PLEASE SPEAK AT A LOWER
VOLUME.
I'M SORRY.
AM I TOO LOUD FOR YOUR PRECIOUS
INTENSIVE CARE UNITS.
YOU AREN'T EVEN SICK.
>> WHY WERE YOU BANNED?
FINE.
WE HAVE BANNED TWITTER USER
ALPHA DOG OF WAR.
>> A VETERAN.
>> IN A MANNER OF SPEAKING, YES,
I SERVED HONORABLY IN CALL OF
DUTY, MODERN WARFARE TWO.
>> AND WHY WERE YOU BANNED?
>> ONE OF MY OWN SQUAD MATES
KILLED ME AND LAUGHED ABOUT IT.
I POSTED HIS REAL NAME, HOME
ADDRESS, AND MIDDLE SCHOOL
SCHEDULE AND SAID, TWITTER, DO
YOUR THING.
>> I MEAN, SOUNDS HARMLESS,
RIGHT?
NEXT.
>> HI.
OH, MY GOD.
YOUR PROFILE IS SO FUNNY.
I LOVE FUNNY GUYS.
>> WELL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BUT WHY WERE YOU BANNED?
>> THEY SAID I WAS A BAT, WHICH
IS CRAZY.
I'M ALL WOMAN, AND I LOVE FUNNY
GUYS LIKE YOU.
IN FACT, YOU SHOULD CHECK OUT
THIS WEBSITE WHERE ME AND SOME
OTHER GIRLS HANG OUT AND MEET
CUTE GUYS.
WWW.SEX PALACE.BIT SCAMS.IRAQ.
>> SOUNDS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE SO FUNNY.
I BET YOU HAVE AN AWESOME SOCIAL
SECURITY NUMBER.
>> NAH.
IT'S NOTHING CRAZY.
IT'S JUST 043 --
>> NO, NO.
DON'T TELL HER.
>> WHY NOT?
WE VIBING.
>> WHO'S NEXT?
>> WHAT'S GOOD?
I'M HERE ON BEHALF OF BLACK
TWITTER, AND WE HEARD MUSK WAS
GOING TO CHARGE US $8 TO USE
TWITTER, AND WE SAY, NAH DOG.
WE GOING TO RUN OUR AS OVER TO
MY SPACE AND GET THAT POPPING
AGAIN.
>> NOTED.
I WILL SEE YOU THERE.
NEXT ACCOUNT.
OH, MY GOD.
HELLO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ME DONALD TRUMP.
JUST JOHN, NOT JONATHAN.
BUT I KNOW MANY JONATHANS, AND I
REPRESENT ALL OF THEM.
NO MORE THAN JTT HIMSELF,
JONATHAN TAYLOR THOMAS WHO IS A
PERSONAL FRIEND OF MINE.
I SAW HIM ON HOME IMPROVEMENT,
AND I SAID THAT KID IS GOING TO
BE A STAR, AND HE WAS FOR A VERY
BRIEF TIME.
BUT JTT WASN'T VERY NICE TO
CHEVY CHASE IN MAN OF THE HOUSE,
WAS HE?
WON'T BE BACK FOR A REBOOT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
>> SURE.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO BE BACK ON
TWITTER?
DIDN'T YOU START YOUR OWN SOCIAL
MEDIA WEBSITE?
>> EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME.
YES, WE'VE ALL MOVED TO TRUE
SOCIAL, AND WE LOVE TRUE SOCIAL.
IT'S VERY GREAT, AND IN MANY
WAYS ALSO TERRIBLE.
IT'S VERY BAD.
VERY, VERY BAD.
IT'S A LITTLE BUGGY IN TERMS OF
MAKING THE PHONE SCREENS CRACK
AND THE AUTOMATICALLY DRAINING
OF THE VENMO.
LET ME BACK ON TWITTER, I WON'T
DO ANYTHING BAD EXCEPT MAYBE
COUP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MIGHT AS WELL ROLL THE DICE,
RIGHT?
>> OH, ELON JUST TWEETED, AND
WE'RE LAID OFF TOO.
>> YEA!
WE'RE FINALLY FREE.
LOOKER
>>> DAVID, FOR THE LAST TIME,
YOU HAVE TO UNPACK YOUR CLOTHES.
WE MOVED IN A MONTH AGO, HONEY.
>> I WILL, MOM.
I HAVE JUST BEEN BUSY.
>> BUSY FLIRTING WITH EVERY GIRL
IN SCHOOL.
>> SHUT UP.
>> HONEY, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> I JUST FOUND THIS LETTER
SLIPPED UNDER OUR DOOR.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S STRANGE.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> DEAREST NEW NEIGHBORS AT 322
OAK RIDGE BOULEVARD,
ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM THE LOOKER, AND I SEE
EVERYTHING YOU DO.
>> IS THIS SOME KIND OF SICK
PRANK?
>> I DON'T KNOW, CAROL.
>> I SEE YOU'RE SETTLING IN
NICELY.
YOUR DAUGHTER LIKES TO WRITE IN
HER DIARY ABOUT THE BOY WHO MOES THE LAWN,
AND YOUR SON HAS BEEN
HARD AT WORK PRACTICING HIS
GUITAR.
>> THIS IS CREEPING ME OUT.
>> AND YOUR WIFE, AFTER
EVERYONE'S ASLEEP,
SHE GOES TO
THE KITCHEN AND EATS AN ENTIRE
SECOND DINNER.
>> THAT'S LIKE -- WHAT?
>> SHE EATS IT LIKE A GREEDY
RACCOON
AFRAID OF GETTING
CAUGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> AS FOR YOU, DADDY DEAREST.
I HOPE YOU ENJOY YOUR MORNING
JOGS AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
I KNOW YOUR WIFE DOES.
AFTER YOU LEAVE, SHE GETS A
SNACK, TURNS ON THE TV,
AND
PLEASURES HERSELF.
TO THE PROPERTY BROTHERS.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S NOT RINGING A BELL.
>> BUT HE KNOWS ABOUT MY JOGS,
CAROL.
>> AND MY DIARY AND DAVID'S
GUITAR.
>> I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY IT'S SO WEIRD THAT
ALL MY STUFF IS CLEARLY MADE UP.
SENSE
>> YOUR LIFE MAY SEEM PERFECT,
BUT THE LOOKER KNOWS IT'S NOT,
AND YOUR POOR WIFE SEEMS TO BE
HAVING TROUBLE IN THE BATHROOM.
SLOWLY ROCKING BACK AND FORTH,
TRYING TO MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
BITCH
GIVING HERSELF PEP TALKS.
>> COME ON, COME ON.
>> SHE GETS SO FRUSTRATED SHE'LL
GO DOWNSTAIRS AND BLOW OFF MORE
STEAM WITH PROPERTY BROTHERS.
WHY IS SHE SO AROUSED BY THAT
SHOW?
IS IT THE BROTHERS OR THE
PROPERTY?
>> SOMEONE DOWNLOADED EVERY
EPISODE OF PROPERTY BROTHERS.
WHAT?
>> AND WATCHED FIVE MINUTES OF
EACH ONE.
WHAT
>> SO THIS WEIRDO SNUCK INTO OUR
HOUSE AND MESSED WITH THE TV?
NOW I'M WEIRDED OUT OFFICIALLY.
>> THEN SHE SAYS, TIKTOK DANCES,
YOUR MOM WAS ON HER EXERCISE
BIKE.
>> THAT ONE'S REAL!
DONE
>> SHE DOESN'T EVEN PEDAL.
JUST SITS ON THE BIKE AND LOOKS
AT HER PHONE.
SWEAT
THEN GOES BACK TO THE BATHROOM
TO TRY AGAIN.
>> WHY CAN'T I GO!
NEXT TIME
>> WE NEED TO GO TO THE POLICE
AND TELL THEM THIS GUY IS MAKING
UP LIES ABOUT JUST ME.
>> WE WILL.
I THINK IT WILL BE SAFEST IF WE
STAY IN THE HOTEL TONIGHT.
>> ONE OF US SHOULD STAY.
I GUESS I'LL DO IT SINCE THIS
GUY'S GOT NOTHING ON ME.
>> IF YOU'RE WATCHING, IT'S THE
NOT BROTHERS
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, STEVE
LACY.
♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW
YOU WANTED ME
I WISH I KNEW I WISH I KNEW
YOU WANTED ME ♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW
I WISH I KNEW YOU WANTED ME
WHAT YOU, OOH, UH
WHAT YOU DO ♪
♪ MADE A MOVE
COULDA MADE A MOVE
IF I KNEW I'D BE WITH YOU
IS IT TOO LATE TO PURSUE ♪
♪ I BITE MY TONGUE
IT'S A BAD HABIT
KINDA MAD THAT I DIDN'T
TAKE A STAB AT IT ♪
♪ THOUGHT YOU WERE TOO GOOD
FOR ME, MY DEAR
NEVER GAVE ME TIME OF DAY
MY DEAR ♪
♪ IT'S OKAY, THINGS HAPPEN
FOR REASONS THAT I THINK
ARE SURE, YEAH
I WISH I KNEW ♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW
YOU WANTED ME
I WISH I KNEW I WISH I KNEW
YOU WANTED ME ♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW
I WISH I KNEW YOU WANTED ME
I WISH I KNEW I WISH I KNEW
YOU WANTED ME ♪
♪ SAY TO ME
PLEASE JUST SAY TO ME
IF THIS COULD WIND UP
I WISH YOU WOULDN'T ♪
♪ PLAY WITH ME
I WANNA KNOW
UH, CAN I BITE YOUR TONGUE
LIKE MY BAD HABIT ♪
♪ WOULD YOU MIND IF
I TRIED TO MAKE A PASS AT IT
WERE YOU NOT TOO GOOD
FOR ME, MY DEAR ♪
♪ FUNNY YOU COME BACK
TO ME, MY DEAR
IT'S OKAY
THINGS HAPPEN FOR REASONS ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T IGNORE
I WISH I KNEW
I WISH I KNEW YOU WANTED ME
I WISH I KNEW ♪
♪ WISH I KNEW
I WISH I KNEW YOU WANTED ME
YOU CAN'T SURPRISE A GEMINI
I'M EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ I'M CROSS-EYED, AND
NOW THAT YOU'RE BACK
I CAN'T DECIDE
IF I DECIDE ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE INVITED
YOU ALWAYS KNEW
THE WAY TO WOW ME
AROUND GET TONGUE-TIED ♪
♪ AND I TURN IT ON
I MAKE IT ROWDY
THEN CARRY ON
BUT I'M NOT HIDIN' ♪
♪ YOU GRABBIN' ME HARD
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU FOUND
IS BISCUITS ♪
♪ IS GRAVY, BABE, AH-AH
♪
YOU CAN'T SURPRISE A GEMINI
BUT YOU KNOW IT'S BISCUITS
IS GRAVY, BABE ♪
♪ I KNEW YOU'D
COME BACK AROUND
'CAUSE YOU KNOW IT'S BISCUITS
IT'S GRAVY, BABE ♪
♪ LET'S IN THE BACK
OF THE MALL, LOSE CONTROL
GO STUPID, GO CRAZY, BABE
I KNOW I'LL BE ♪
♪ IN YOUR HEART 'TIL THE END
YOU'LL MISS ME
>>> IT'S WEEKEND UPDATE WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
PRESIDENT BIDEN SEEN HERE
BEGGING FOR ONE MORE YEAR BEFORE
THE MIDTERMS
LEARNED ABOUT
REPUBLICAN CANDIDATES WHO SAY
THEY WILL REFUSE TO ACCEPT
ELECTION RESULTS
WARNING THEY
COULD SET THE NATION ON A PATH
TO CHAOS.
SO, WAIT, THIS IS JUST THE PATH
TO CHAOS?
I THOUGHT WE HAD BEEN LIVE NOT
GUILTY CHAOS FOR AT LEAST SIX
YEARS.
NANCY PELOSI'S HUSBAND WAS
ATTACKED IN THEIR HOME BY A GUY WITH A HAMMER,
AND INSTEAD OF
BASIC SYMPATHY, REPUBLICANS WERE
LIKE, WE HEARD HE GAY.
DONALD TRUMP JR. MOCKED THE ATTACK
BY POSTING AN IMAGE AND A
PAIR OF UNDERPANTS
SAYING, I GOT
MY PAUL PELOSI HALLOWEEN COSTUME READY,
AND I WOULD AGREE CON JR.
IS PROBABLY THE THE MASTER
OF GETTING HAMMERED IN HIS
UNDERWEAR.
YOUR
DIRTY
YOU WERE TRYING TO BURN PAUL PELOSI,
BUT NOW I'M WONDERING IF
YOU WEAR YOUR DAD'S OLD
UNDERWEAR.
ANTI DEF
KYRIE IRVING ANNOUNCED FROM
NOW ON, HE WILL PRETEND TO NOT
BE ANTI-SEMITIC.
HE TWEETED A LINK
WAKE UP BLACK
AMERICA.
IN A HEGRO TO NEGROS WAS ALSO
THE NAME OF MY FAVORITE RNB GROUP IN
THE '90s.
>> JUST DAYS BEFORE THE MIDTERM
ELECTIONS, OPRAH ENDORSED JOHN FETTERMAN
INSTEAD OF THE MONSTER
SHE UNLEASHED UPON US.
ISN'T IT CRAZY THAT OPRAH GAVE
DR. OZ HIS CAREER AND EVEN SHE'S
TURNED AGAINST HIM?
IT'S LIKE IF ROBIN RAN FOR MAYOR
OF GOTHAM,
AND BATMAN WAS LIKE I
ENDORSE PENGUINS.
>> HERSCHEL WALKER CRITICIZED BARACK OBAMA
SAYING, PUT MY
RESUME AGAINST HIS RESUME.
FINE.
SO HERE'S OBAMA'S RESUME,
AND HERE'S HERSCHEL WALKER.
BETTER THAN I THOUGHT.
>> COUPLE OF TYPOS.
THE LATEST JOB REPORTS SHOWS
THAT LAST MONTH THE U.S. ECONOMY
ADDED OVER 200,000 JOBS.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT, SAID ELON
MUSK.
HALF THEIRE STAFF
SINCE ELON MUSK TOOK OVER
TWITTER,
USE OF THE N WORD ON
THE SITE HAS REPORTEDLY JUMPED
500%.
IT'S THE BIGGEST INCREASE IN THE
USE OF THE N WORD
SINCE THE LAST
TIME I STUBBED MY TOE.
>> KANYE WEST WAS SUSPENDED FROM
INSTAGRAM AGAIN
FOR POSTING A
DESPAIRING MESSAGE ABOUT JEWISH
PEOPLE.
SEEMS LIKE HE'S DOING THE SAME
THING OVER AND OVER AGAIN AND
EXPECTING DIFFERENT RESULTS,
WHICH I'VE HEARD IS THE
DEFINITION OF SOMETHING.
KANYE
HIS BUSINESS DEALS WENT BAD,
AND HE JUST STARTED CALLING IT A
JEWISH CONSPIRACY
LIKE WHEN HIS
ALBUMS WENT BAD AND HE STARTED
CALLING IT GOSPEL.
>> TOMORROW IS THE NEW YORK CITY MARATHON,
OR AS FOX NEWS WILL REPORT IT,
UNDOCUMENTED AFRICANS
RUN WILD IN STREETS OF NEW YORK.
>> CHINA HAS LAUNCHED THE THIRD
AND FINAL MODULE
FOR ITS
PERMANENT SPACE STATION.
NOW ALL THEY HAVE TO DO IS
LAUNCH SOME CHILDREN TO ASSEMBLE
IT.
NEW YORK CITY IS NOW REQUIRING EMPLOYERS
TO DISCLOSE SALARY
RANGES IN ALL JOB LISTINGS.
EMPLOYERS MUST LIST EVERYTHING
RANGING FROM THE TOP SALARY
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE FEMALE
SALARY.
>> CNN HAS ANNOUNCED THAT DUE TO
BUDGET CUTS
THEY ARE SCALING
BACK ON ORIGINAL SERIES AND
DOCUMENTARIES.
APPARENTLY THERE WAS A FLAW WITH
THE BUSINESS MODEL
OF GIVING
STANLEY TUCCI MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS TO EAT GILATO.
A ZOO IN ATLANTA WILL ALLOW
VISITORS TO CARRY FIREARMS.
YOU WANT TO TRY LAUGHING AT ME
AGAIN, MONKEYS?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU, MAN?
TENSIONS ARE ON THE RISE AFTER
NORTH KOREA
LAUNCHED MORE THAN
20 MISSILES INTO THE OCEAN
AND
ALL BECAUSE THE LITTLE MERMAID
IS BLACK.
NOT REAL.
>> A LINGUISTICS EXPERT HAS
RELEASED A LIST OF THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL SOUNDING BABY NAMES
WITH THE TOP SPOTS GOING TO
MATTHEW AND SOFIA
WHILE THE
WORST SOUNDING NAMES ARE MOIST
AND SLURP.
IN EASTERN OREGON ARE WARNING
RESIDENTS ABOUT SEVERAL HAND
GRENADES THAT HAVE WASHED ASHORE ON A BEACH
DISCOVERED
WHEN ONE BEACH GOER SAID,
MOMMY, LOOK AT THIS SHELL
I FO --
>> NASA HAS RELEASED AN IMAGE OF
THE SUN IN WHICH IT APPEARS TO
BE SMILING.
SO IF THE SUN CAN SMILE, WOULD
IT KILL YOU LADIES TO TRY IT?
>> AN ARIZONA WOMAN WAS ARRESTED
AFTER SHE ALLEGEDLY WENT DAY DRINKING
WHILE HER 5 MONTH-OLD
CHILD WAS SITTING HOME ALONE
LIKE A LOSER.
WOULD SOMEBODY -- CALLING THE
BABY A LOSER.
WITH SO MANY MIDTERM RACES
TIGHTENING, IT'S HARD TO PREDICT
WHAT WILL DRIVE MORE TO THE
POLLS.
HERE TO COMMENT IS TAMMY THE
TRUCKER WHO PROMISES SHE'S HERE
TO TALK ABOUT GAS PRICES AND
DEFINITELY NOT ABORTION.
WHAT?
>> HEY, THERE.
IT'S ME.
TAMMY THE TRUCKER.
BREAKER, BREAKER, OVER.
>> WOW, TAMMY.
SO YOU ARE A TRUCKER WHO WAS
VERY AFFECTED BY GAS PRICES.
THAT MAKES SENSE TO ME.
>> I THOUGHT IT WOULD, COLIN
JOST.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
>> WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT NOT
TALKING ABOUT ABORTIONS?
>> NO, NO, NO.
BREAKER, BREAKER, I GOT A BIG
DADDY ON MY TAIL.
ALL I'M HERE TO TALK ABOUT IS
GAS EVEN THOUGH THE SUPREME
COURT SENT ROE V WADE TO THAT
BIG PIT STOP IN THE SKY.
50 YEARS OF PRECEDENT.
BEEP, BEEP.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
IT SEEMS LIKE MAYBE YOU DO WANT
TO TALK ABOUT ABORTION.
>> CALM YOUR COOTER DOWN.
I'M TINA THE TRUCKER, WHATEVER
NAME I GAVE YOU.
I GOT TO BE IN RANCHO KUNKARUMBA
BY NIGHT FALL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO GET
THROUGH THIS MOMENT, SNOK GAS
PRICES ARE UP, AND FAMILIES ARE
HURTING, BUT THAT'S NOT GOING TO
MAGICALLY DISAPPEAR NO MATTER
WHO YOU VOTE FOR.
WE'RE IN A GLOBAL RECESSION
FUELED BY CORPORATE GREED AND
WAR.
HONK, HONK.
BUT WHAT WILL KEEP DISAPPEARING
IS SAFE ACCESS TO ABORTION.
IT'S NOT REALLY MAGIC BECAUSE
THEY TOLD US THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE
GOING TO DO, AND THEY HAVE BEEN
DOING IT.
BREAKER, BREAKER.
I GOT A DOUBLE NICKEL ON THE
FLAB.
>> DID YOU JUST GOOGLE TRUCKER
TERMS?
>> LIKE RESEARCH?
YEAH.
HOLD THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
ABORTION ON LIVE TV OR PEACOCK,
WHATEVER THAT COUNTS AS.
BUT THESE ARE SCARY TIMES, OKAY?
BECAUSE THEY DON'T WANT TO JUST
TAKE AWAY ACCESS TO HEALTHCARE.
THEY WANT TO CRIMINALIZE IT TOO.
IT'S SO BAD, US TRUCK DRIVERS
ARE WARNING EACH OTHER TO DELETE
OUR PERIOD TRACKING APPS.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHAT WEEK TO
WEAR MY BAD UNDERWEAR.
BUT I CAN'T BECAUSE SOME DICK
HEAD IN ARIZONA THINKS IT'S
EVIDENCE OF A CRIME.
ARUBA!
>> I THINK IT'S AROOGA!
>> WHY ARE YOU ON MY ASS?
THE POINT IS, YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE A DOCTOR ABOUT YOUR
ANATOMY WITHOUT THEM HAVING TO
CALL THEIR LAWYER FIRST.
BEEP, BEEP.
CHECK MY REAR.
AM I CLEAR?
IS MY REAR CLEAR?
BEEP.
I'M BACKING UP ABOUT 50 YEARS
INTO THE PAST.
>> I GOT YOU.
I GOT YOU.
>> I KNOW THIS WASN'T FUN FOR
YOU.
LET ME GIVE YOU SOME LITTLE
TRUCKER TOYS.
HERE'S A NUDEY MAG, AND HERE'S
THIS.
>> IS THIS GATORADE?
>> IT WAS AT ONE POINT.
TRUTH IS, I HAVE FELT PRETTY
HELPLESS OVER THE PAST YEAR, AND
IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO
MAKE OTHER TRUCKERS FEEL BETTER.
SO HERE'S THE THING I CAN SAY.
THERE'S ONE MOTHER TRUCKING
THING WE CAN DO TO FIGHT FOR
MOTHER TRUCKING FREEDOM TO MAKE
OUR OWN HEALTHCARE DECISIONS,
AND THAT'S VOTE.
AND I HOPE TO HELL EVERYONE
VOTES.
BECAUSE REMEMBER, WE ALL LOVE
SOMEONE WHO'S HAD AN ABORTION --
I MEAN, DRIVES A TRUCK.
BEEP, BEEP, AROOGA!
>> FROM WEEKEND UPDATE, I'M
>>> KIDS, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
RUNNING.
THIS IS SO FUN.
I'M SO GLAD WE WERE ABLE TO GET
THIS TOGETHER.
>> IT IS A GREAT DAY FOR A GAME.
>> COULDN'T ASK FOR BETTER
TAILGATING WEATHER.
IT SHOULD BE A GREAT GAME.
>> BILLS ARE TOP OF THEIR
DIVISION.
THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD.
>> SO IS THIS MACARONI SALAD.
>> WHEN DID YOU HAVE TIME TO
MAKE THIS.
>> I THREW IT TOGETHER LAST
NIGHT.
IT'S NOTHING.
>> WELL, GIVE ME MORE NOTHINGS.
UH-OH, BILLS FAN COMING.
HEY!
BILLS JERSEY!
YOU'RE WEARING THE FREAKING
WRONG SHIRT YOU A-HOLE!
>> YOU LOOK LIKE A FREAKING
MORON!
KEEP WALKING, MORON!
>> FREAKING DEAD TODAY, MORON!
>> BY THE WAY, DID I TELL YOU,
HENRY IS HAVING A TOUGH TIME AT
SCHOOL.
>> REVOLVE, OH, NO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I GUESS HE'S GETTING BULLIED.
>> NO.
>> FOR HIS HAIR CUT.
>> THAT'S AWFUL.
>> WHERE DO KIDS EVEN LEARN
THIS?
>> FROM THE INTERNET, I GUESS.
UH-OH, BAD ASS BILLS FAN ALERT.
>> MAYBE YOU DO A FEW JUMPING
JACKS!
>> MAYBE EAT A VEGETABLE NEXT
TIME, YOU FREAKING WHALE!
>> I'M PREGNANT.
>> YOU WANT A MEDAL?
HAVE A DRINK, SLUT!
>> MONKEY!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BY THE WAY, I WAS IN CVS
YESTERDAY, THEY ALREADY HAVE THE
CHRISTMAS STUFF OUT.
>> I KNOW.
THEY TAKE DOWN THE HALLOWEEN
STUFF, AND POOF, IT'S CHRISTMAS.
>> HEY, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
GUYS DOING?
>> IS THERE A PROBLEM, OFFICER?
>> THERE WILL BE IF YOU DON'T
PUT THAT CHARCOAL OUT BEFORE YOU
HEAD INTO THE GAME.
>> OF COURSE WE'LL PUT IT OUT.
>> I WOULD HOPE SO BECAUSE EVERY
WEEK -- HEY!
HEY, BILLS MAFIA!
YOU'RE IN THE WRONG STADIUM, YOU
FREAKING A-HOLE!
>> YOU WANT TO CRY TO YOUR
MOMMY?
KEEP WALKING YOU DOUCHE BAG!
>> I'LL BRING THE BARBECUE RIGHT
TO YOU!
>> YEAH, RUN RIGHT INTO TRAFFIC,
YOU FREAKING DOUCHE BAG!
>> YOU FOLKS ENJOY THE GAME.
>> THANKS OFFICER.
OH, MY GOD.
I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
MY SECOND GRADE CLASS IS SO
ADORABLE THIS YEAR, AND THEY'RE
SO EXCITED TO LEARN.
YEAH.
HEY!
BILLS, GET MY WHOLE THING!
>> SUCK MY SLEEVE, BUDDY!
SUCK IT FRONT TO BACK.
>> OH, YOU'RE GOING TO GO BY ALL
SLOW, HUH?
YOU THINK THAT SCARES ME?
I'M NOT SCARED OF YOU YOU PANSY.
>> YEAH, I PUT MY WHOLE FIST
THROUGH YOUR FACE, YOU FREAKING
A-HOLE!
>> KEEP MOVING YOU HUMP FREAKING
HUMP.
>> I AM REALLY FEELING THIS
WHITE CLAW.
>> EXCUSE ME FOR A SECOND.
HEY!
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
>> SO SHOULD WE START HEADING IN
SOON?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S ONLY FIVE MINUTES LEFT
IN THE GAME.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
DID WE MISS THE WHOLE GAME
AGAIN?
YEAH.
>> SO SHOULD WE JUST STAY OUT
HERE?
>> I'M HAVING FUN.
HEY!
>> HEY!
SUCK MY SLEEVE, YOU DUMB COW!
>> SUCK MY WHOLE SLEEVE!
>> J-E-T-S, JETS!
>> FIRST DATES, AM I RIGHT?
I WAS ACTUALLY EXCITED ABOUT
THIS ONE, BUT OF COURSE I GOT MY
PERIOD TODAY ZBLI WANT A PERIOD
OPTION THAT'S CONVENIENT AND
DISCRETE SO I DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT LEAKS, ODORS OR
ANYTHING.
>> WHAT I'M AT WORK, I DON'T
HAVE TIME TO RUN BACK AND FORTH
TO THE BATHROOM.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO FORGET ALL
ABOUT IT.
>> NOW YOU CAN WITH PINX
UNDERWEAR.
YOU'LL BE COVERED ALL DAY LONG
NO MATTER WHAT.
AND THE ONLY PERSON WHO HAS TO
KNOW YOU'RE ON YOUR PERIOD IS
YOU.
>> NOW MY PERIOD IS MY LITTLE
SECRET.
OH, A DOG.
>> FINALLY, AN UNDERWEAR THAT'S
AS NATURAL AS YOU.
IT'S MADE OF ALL ORGANIC
MATERIALS.
>> I LOVE NOT HAVING TO BRING A
BAG OF SUPPLIES WHEREVER I GO.
>> I LOVE NOT HAVING TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
>> NOW I GET TO DO ME, AND PINX
DOES THE REST.
>> WOW, DOGS REALLY LOVE YOU.
>> YEAH.
I HAVE A CHEESE BURGER IN MY
POCKET.
>> WHAT?
>> EVERYONE IS DIFFERENT.
PINX HAS OPTIONS FOR EVERY LEVEL
.
>> I LOVE STINKS -- SORRY, PINX.
>> NO MORE HIDING, PLASTIC, AND
NO MORE STRESS.
YOU SHOULD FEEL BEAUTIFUL.
HUMAN, ATTRACTIVE.
NOW, YOU CAN WALK PROUD.
HAVE YOUR PERIOD THE WAY NATURE
INTENDED WITH PINX.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO FOR
DINNER?
>> I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GET DINNER
OR --
>> I CANNOT HEAR YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD!
RUN!
>>> GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO
WKTVN NEWS.
>> LATER TONIGHT, BAKLAVA OR
BALA?
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE
TWO DELICIOUS TREATS.
>> I LOVE STUDIES LIKE THAT.
FIRST WE GO WHERE A FIRE HAS
SPREAD FORCING SEVERAL FAMILIES
OUT OF THEIR HOMES.
LET'S CHECK IN WITH OUR BRAND
NEW REPORTER, CHANCE HARMSTRONG.
>> THANKS.
I'M SO THRILLED TO BE JOINING
THE TEAM.
RIGHT NOW I'M WITH A LOCAL
RESIDENT.
MA'AM, TELL US WHAT HAPPENED.
>> SIR, I WAS HAVING MY NORMAL
CIGARETTE IN BED, AND I WAS
WOKEN UP BY A MAN WHO SAID,
BANG, BANG, BANG, AND I PUT TWO
AND TEN TOGETHER, AND I SAID
FIRE.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW THIS
FIRE COULD HAVE STARTED?
>> I'M NOT SURE HOW, BUT I KNOW
100% WHY.
I DO NOT WANT TO SAY NAMES, BUT
IT WAS MY COUSIN.
>> IT WAS YOUR COUSIN?
>> YES, AND SHE IS LOOKING RIGHT
AT YOU NOW, SIR.
>> WHAT?
OH, YOU TAKING A PICTURE OF ME?
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NOT FOR FREE, YOU'RE NOT.
>> SHE'S MAD BECAUSE SHE WANTS
TO GET WITH MY HUSBAND BECAUSE
LOOK AT HIM.
>> THIS FOR TV?
>> YES.
THIS IS THE NEWS.
>> OH, SNAP.
>> BACK TO THE FIRE.
>> IT'S A LONG STORY BUT SHE'S
MAD BECAUSE SHE CAN'T GET WITH
HIM BECAUSE HE CLOSE ME AND HE'S
MY COUSIN.
>> KEEP SAYING STUFF LIKE THAT,
I WILL SET YOUR HOUSE UPON FIRE
AGAIN.
>> SET MY HOUSE ON FIRE.
I'M SCARED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS WAS NOT AS INFORMATIVE AS I
HOPED.
BACK TO YOU.
>> HEY, HEY.
COME BACK TO ME.
TAKE MY PICTURE.
LOOK WHAT I CAN DO.
ONE HAND, ONE HAND.
>> HE'S SHOWING OFF FOR ME.
I WANT TO LAY WITH YOU.
>> I SAID I CAN'T.
>> WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT, AND
I THINK WE'RE ALL DONE HERE.
VICKIE AND ALICIA.
>> SIR, IF I MAY JUST INCLUDE,
THE TWO OF THEM ARE COUSINS.
>> YES, I KNOW THAT.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THE
FIRE.
>> NO, I DO NOT.
BUT SINCE HE GOT TO DO A TRICK,
LOOK WHAT I CAN DO.
>> OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
AND I'M NOT REALLY HERE TO LOOK
AT TRICKS.
>> HEY.
HE AIN'T EVEN MY COUSIN.
HE'S ONLY MY COUSIN BECAUSE HE
MARRIED MY COUSIN.
SO, HEY, I CAN STILL GET WITH
YOU BECAUSE I WANT TO LAY WITH
YOU.
>> NO ONE WANTS TO LAY WITH YOU.
>> I BET YOU SOMEONE WILL.
>> NO, THEY WON'T.
BECAUSE YOU AIN'T GOT IT LIKE
THIS.
>> LIKE HELL I DON'T.
>> OKAY.
NO.
THIS CANNOT HAPPEN.
IT'S LITERALLY MY FIRST DAY.
>> OH, SIR, IF I MAY.
I CAN CLEAR THIS UP 100%.
JUST --
>> JUST DON'T SAY THEY'RE
COUSINS.
>> EXACTLY.
THEY ARE COUSINS.
ALSO, LOOK WHAT I CAN DO.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
NOW I'M UNFORTUNATELY SEEING A
LOT OF PEOPLE LINED UP, AND I'M
ASSUMING NO ONE WANTS TO TALK
ABOUT THE FIRE.
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THAT, SIR.
BUT LOOK WHAT I CAN DO.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
YOU'RE VERY TALENTED.
>> LISTEN.
THE REAL REASON I AM MAD AT HER,
THE REAL REASON I AM MAD AT YOU
AND SET FIRE TO UPON YOUR HOUSE
AND YOUR TRAMPOLINE UPON FIRE IS
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NOT HAD SAID
ONE NICE THING TO ME MY WHOLE
LIFE.
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I LIKE YOU.
I LIKE YOUR SMILE.
YOUR HOME EMBRACE IS WORTH.
YOU MAKE GOOD FRENCH BREAD
PIZZA, AND I'M SORRY THAT THE
YEARS HAVE TORN US APART IN TERM
OF BEING COUSINS.
>> SO NOW WHAT?
>> I GUESS MAKE UP?
>> YEAH.
>> NO.
NO.
DO NOT FILM THESE THREE COUSINS
KISSING.
WELL, IT WAS MY FIRST DAY, AND
I'M ASSUMING IT'S MY LAST.
>>> SORRY, ROBIN, BUT DRAW FOUR.
>> OH, MAN.
>> HAHAHA.
SUCKS TO BE YOU.
>> SAVE YOUR GLOATING.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY TO GET SO COMPETITIVE,
GUYS.
>> IT'S FINE, GLENN.
>> NO, IT'S NOT FINE.
IT'S SOMETHING I HAVE BEEN
WORKING ON IN THERAPY.
>> YOU GO TO THERAPY?
THAT'S LIKE REALLY SURPRISING.
>> SERIOUSLY, TALK ABOUT A
COMPLETE 180.
>> I KNOW, REMEMBER HOW CRANKY
HE USED TO BE?
>> THAT'S ONE WAY TO PUT IT.
>> I WOULD HAVE SAID TOXIC AS A
MUG.
>> OKAY.
YOU GOT ME.
>> HONESTLY, EVER SINCE I
FINALLY CONVINCED HIM TO GO TO
BIG PENIS THERAPY, HE'S BEEN SO
MUCH HAPPIER.
HE'S LIKE A NEW PERSON.
>> ONE MORE TIME.
>> DID YOU SAY BIG PENIS
THERAPY?
>> YEAH.
IT'S A PLACE WHERE I CAN FINALLY
OPEN UP ABOUT MY PROBLEMS WITH
MY DAD, MY INSECURITIES, MY RAGE
ISSUES.
>> THAT SOUNDS LIKE REGULAR
THERAPY?
LET'S GO BACK TO THE GAME.
WHO'S TURN IS IT?
>> SHE HAS BEEN TRYING TO GET ME
TO GO TO THERAPY EVER SINCE I
CHEATED ON HER.
YOU REMEMBER THAT, BABE?
>> I SURE DO.
>> THERAPY ALWAYS SEEMED TO
FRUITY, BUT THEN I HEARD ABOUT
BIG PENIS THERAPY FOR MEN WITH
BIG OLD PENISES LIKE MINE.
>> BIG PENIS THERAPY HELPS
DESTIGMATIZE MEN FOR WORKING ON
THEIR MENTAL HEALTH.
>> THE GUYS RAISED ME, BUT THEN
I SHOWED THEM MY SWEET DAMAGE
FOR COMPLETING SIX MONTHS, AND
NOW THEY WANT THERAPY TOO.
>> GOD FORGIVE MY PAINES?
WHAT'S THAT?
>> MAYBE I SHOULD TELL MY JAKE
ABOUT THIS.
>> ARE YOU SURE JAKE QUALIFIES?
>> ACTUALLY, HE'S PRETTY OKAY.
>> WELL, UNFORTUNATELY, IT'S NOT
PRETTY OKAY SIZED THERAPY.
IT'S THERAPY FOR GUYS WITH GREAT
BIG ONES LIKE MINE, OR SHAQ'S OR
GUYS FROM LONG NATURALS
MAGAZINE.
>> SIZE ISN'T REALLY IMPORTANT.
>> PLEASE DON'T SAY THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
IT ACTUALLY IS IMPORTANT, AND
BEFORE THERAPY, I WOULD HAVE
CALLED YOU A STUCK UP BITCH FOR
SAYING THAT, BUT NOW I WON'T.
>> DID THEY MEASURE YOUR PENIS
FIRST TO MAKE SURE YOU QUALIFY?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I'M JUST SAYING, HOW DO THEY
KNOW IF YOU HAVE A BIG --
>> THEY DON'T HAVE TO MEASURE.
>> HONEY, RELAX.
IT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
THE DOCTORS CAN TELL FROM YOUR
OVERALL VIBE IF YOU HAVE A BABY
LEG LIKE I DO.
>> WELL, WHATEVER THEY'RE DOING,
IT SEEMS TO BE WORKING FOR YOU.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
YOU SEEMED TO HAVE EVEN LOST
WEIGHT.
>> THAT'S ALL THANKS TO MY FAT
ROD VEGAN PLANT.
>> HE'S ALSO DRINKING
NONALCOHOLIC BEERS.
>> AND I ALSO JOINED AN ACTIVIST
GROUP CALLED THREE EYED MONSTER
PECKERS.
>> WELL, GOOD.
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
DRAW FOUR.
>> AND BABE, YOU ONLY HAD ONE
LEFT.
YOU ALMOST WON.
>> STOP MAKING FUN OF ME!
>>> ONCE AGAIN, STEVE LACY.
♪ OH-OH, I'D BEEN CONSUMED
I'M NOT FOR SALE MAN
WHAT THE HELL
I BEEN WITH YOU ♪
♪ AND THIS AIN'T
GON' LAST ME FOREVER
ALL THAT I CAN BE
IS ME AND ALL ME ♪
♪ TIME TO GET OUT
I DON'T WANT YOU AROUND
ALL THAT I CAN SEE
IS YOU WITHOUT ME ♪
♪ NO, I CAN'T SCOLD YOU
HOWEVER
I TRIED TO PLAY PRETEND
TRY NOT TO SEE THE END ♪
♪ BUT I COULDN'T SEE YOU
THE WAY YOU SAW ME
NOW I CAN FEEL
THE WASTE ON ME ♪
♪ I TRIED MY BEST
TO BE WORTH ALL YOUR WHILE
YOU JUST GOTTA LET ME GO
AS I'M TRYNA LET GO OF YOU ♪
♪ SHO-DOO, DOO-DOO-DOO-DOO
DOO-DOO-DOO, DOO-DOO-DOO
OOH-OOH, I'LL BE THERE SOON
I'M KINDA SAD ♪
♪ WHAT SHOULD I DO
WHAT SHOULD I DO
GUESS I'LL MOVE ON
LOVE WON'T HARASS ME ♪
♪ FOREVER
ALL THAT I COULD BE
IS ME AND ALL ME
ALL THAT NOSTALGIA ♪
♪ BEEN UP ON A DOWNER
I CAN'T MAKE YOUR EYES SEE
GON' BE WHAT IT'S GON' BE
DON'T COME BACK AROUND ME ♪
♪ NO, NEVER
YOU WERE SO AUTOMATIC
SO YOU KNOW I HAD TO HAVE IT
BUT LOVIN YOU WAS A HAZARD ♪
♪ SO I GOT MY HEART A HELMET
I TRIED MY BEST
TO BE WORTH ALL YOUR WHILE
YOU JUST GOTTA LET ME GO ♪
♪ AS I'M TRYNA LET GO OF YOU
♪
LET ME LET ME
ALLOW ME TO LET GO OF YOU
OH-OH, LET ME, LET ME GO ♪
♪ OH, NO-OH, OH-OH, OH
YEAH ♪
♪
>>> FALL.
>> BEAUTY.
>> WOMEN.
>> HEY, GIRLY.
>> ARE YOU LIKE US?
A WELL-OFF WOMAN WITH PERFECT
MAKEUP AND LONG, STRAIGHT HAIR?
>> ARE YOU BETWEEN 20 AND 45 AND
IT'S FALL OUTSIDE?
>> DO YOU WANT A PERSONALITY YOU
CAN WEAR ON YOUR HEAD?
>> THEN YOU NEED, BIG DUMB HATS.
>> THIS IS THE HAT THAT MAKES
EVERYONE SAY, OH, HER.
>> THE HAT THAT MAKES PEOPLE
THINK, OH, SHE WENT HAT.
>> THE HAT THAT SAYS, WHEN I WAS
IN HIGH SCHOOL, I WASN'T MEAN OR
NICE.
>> BIG.
>> DUMB.
>> HATS.
>> BIG DUMB HAT COMES IN COLORS,
LIKE TAN OR THAT'S IT.
>> AND THE RIM IS PERFECT TO
TOUCH SO PEOPLE SEE YOUR BIG
DUMB ENGAGEMENT RING.
OH, THIS?
YEAH, IT A BIGGY.
>> AM I A COWGIRL IN NO, GIRL.
>> I'M PLANT BASED, EXCEPT FOR
MY COY BASE.
>> IF YOU SEE ME WEARING AT THE
AIRPORT, YOU KNOW I'M GOING TO
PUSH MY WAY ON BEFORE MY
BOARDING GROUP.
>> WOW.
IS YOUR HAT EVEN BIGGER THAN
BEFORE?
>> YOU TELL ME.
>> YOU CAN WEAR BIG DUMB HAT
ANYWHERE.
THE BEACH.
>> OR A SOCCER GAME.
>> IF YOU SEE THIS HAT IN
STARBUCKS, YOU KNOW IT'S GOING
TO BE OAT MILK.
>> BIG DUMB HATS.
>> WANT TO HEAR A SECRET?
I MADE A BABY IN THIS HAT.
>> I NAMED MY KID, POET, STORY,
LIRIC AND ARCADE.
>> I POST A PICTURE OF MY
WEDDING EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> CAN YOU DANCE IN THE HAT?
WELL, YOU'LL WISH WE DIDN'T.
♪ TAKE ME TO CHURCH ♪
>> DON'T YOU HATE HOW WE DANCE?
>> HATS.
>> DUMB.
>> BIG.
>> BIG DUMB HAT THE HAT THAT
MACKS YOUR BOYFRIEND SAY, IT'S
ME OR THE HAT.
>> IT'S THE HAT THAT SCREAMS,
WAIT.
I THINK I FORGOT TO VOTE.
DID I MISS IT?
CAN I STILL GET A STICKER?
>> HAT.
>> PAIR IT WITH TINY LITTLE
CURSIVE TATTOO, COMPLICATED
MORNING ROUTINE AND FAKE GLUTEN
ATOR JI.
>> YELLOW STONE WATCH PARTY AND
A WOOD FIRED PIZZA OVEN.
OOH, LOOK AT THAT CHAR.
>> AND AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A BIG OLD
CREASE ON YOUR FOREHEAD FROM THE
HAT.
>> CAN A MAN WEAR A BIG DUMB
HAT?
>> I THINK SO, BUT LET'S FIND
OUT.
>> HELLO, LADIES.
LET'S GET VULNERABLE.
>> NO, NO.
>> NO.
>> SO GET YOUR BIG DUMB HAT
TODAY.
WAIT.
IS YOUR HAT EVEN BIGGER?
>> MAYBE.
>> BIG DUMB HATS.
>>> THANKS TO STEVE LACY, THE
ENTIRE CAST AND CREW AND
AUDIENCE.
AND PLEASE VOTE, AND I LOVE YOU
SO MUCH, I CAN'T WAIT TO GET
HOME AND SEE YOU GUYS.