-Welcome back.
Welcome back, Mr. President.
That was quite a journey
you took.
-Yep. I did what every doctor
recommends for an 80-year-old --
a two-day whirlwind trip
to China.
I just flew home from China,
and, boy, are my legs swollen.
- Very, very good, sir.
-That doesn't look good at all.
What are you talking about?
-That's bad.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know what?
I'm sorry I didn't take you
with me to China, JD.
I would have,
but I didn't want to.
But I brought you a present that
President Xi Jinping gave me.
A finger trap.
Uh, it's very nice.
Did you --
What did you give him?
-Taiwan.
Now, JD,
I need some time to relax
and to not be around you.
-Okay. Do you --
Do you want me to leave?
-Is the Pope Catholic?
Not enough for me!
-Well, it's time for one
of my patented mid-work naps.
Just gonna rest my head
on this gold bar
that Switzerland gave me
as a straight-up bribe
and sleep the sweet sleep
of an addled, jet-lagged mind.
-Donald. Doooonaaald.
-Who's that?
Who's in here?
-Don't worry, Donald.
It's me -- your best friend,
Jeffrey Epstein.
-Jeffrey?!
But I-I thought you were dead.
-I am, remember?
I killed myself -- wink!
So, how you doing, Donny Baby?
-Not so good, Jeffie.
My approval rating's in the 30s.
-Oh, the 30s? Gross.
Call me when it hits 17.
-Dark. Very dark.
It's a dark situation.
So, what are you up
to these days, Jeff?
How's Heaven?
-It's really, really hot.
But you know me -- I keep busy.
Mahjong every Wednesday
with Stalin and John Wayne Gacy.
That guy has stories.
What else?
Oh, I just wrote
for the Kevin Hart roast.
Had some fun zingers in there.
What about you, Donny Baby?
Any fun summer plans?
-Well, you know,
we've got the World Cup,
a UFC fight on my lawn like
I'm white trash on WorldStar,
and we're also doing
the Patriot Games,
where high-school athletes
come from all over the country.
-Boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!
-Give me some.
-You know what? This time,
I'm gonna leave you hanging.
-Wow.
-Wonderful.
Tremendous.
-Man, we had some fun times
together, didn't we, Donny?
-Yeah.
-We should have taken
more pictures.
- No, it's really bad
that we took any.
-Damn it.
I miss you, homie.
In case you're curious,
like all ghosts,
I have the power to show you
visions of the future.
-Wow!
I'm surprised there is one.
-First, let me show you
to where Kristi Noem is at
in six months.
-My fellow Americans,
I know exactly what we need
to transform this country.
-Oh, good.
She's back in politics.
-Not exactly.
-It's the Shark Wand
Vacuum Cleaner.
And for only $129.99,
it's the best way to clean up that mess
your dog made...
besides a gun.
And it can even handle
balloon scraps left over
from when your husband's
giant balloon breasts pop.
-Oh, wow,
I completely forgot
about her husband's
"balloobies" thing.
-Yeah. Hey,
that's a credit to you, buddy.
Your administration's so crazy,
secret balloon tatas
were only a one-day story.
-That's actually worrisome.
You know what else about --
What about Pete Hegseth?
-Oh, let me show you Pete
six months from now.
-Well...
I guess that's the last of it.
-Wow! He gave up drinking.
-Oh, no, he's not pouring it
down the sink.
That's a giant beer bong.
-Yeah, baby! Come on!
Welcome back
to "The KaaaaashCast
with Kash and Pete."
Shoutout to our sponsor, my own
personal line of cologne --
Incompetence for Men.
Every bottle
is full of my forehead sweat
from my many Senate grillings.
A smell so strong,
it'll cross your eyes.
-And I've got an ad to read,
too, so listen up, buttwads!
You want people to think
you're drinking water,
but you're actually
getting wasted?
Then reach for Poland Sprung.
It's the first ever hard water.
So when everyone around you
tells you to stop,
that's when you know
you gots to get Sprung.
-Well, if Pete's podcasting,
I guess that means
that the war in Iran is over.
-Yep. We came in second.
But, Donny, just remember --
no -- no matter
how many wars you start
or how -- how bad you tank
the economy as a distraction,
people will always associate you
with me.
And that, my dear close friend,
that is a beautiful thing.
-♪ Cause, darlin',
when the morning comes ♪
-♪ And I see the morning sun ♪
♪ I wanna be the one with you ♪
-♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ Building big castles
way up high ♪
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ You and I ♪
And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Will Ferrell!
-Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very, very much.
I'm thrilled to be back here
hosting "Saturday Night Live."
Thrilled!
I was a cast member here
for seven years,
and now I'm hosting
for the sixth time.
Amazing!
It really --
It really feels like --
It really feels
like coming home.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
-I love everybody here.
This --
-Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Excuse me! What --
-What the hell do you think
you're doing?
-I think I'm hosting the show.
-You're not the host -- I am.
You're Chad Smith
of the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
No. Shut up! Shut up!
Everyone, shut up!
What the hell is wrong with you?
-Nothing.
-He pushed me down backstage.
And I fell -- hard.
Lorne had to give me
mouth to mouth.
Seriously, what are
you even doing here?
-Okay, I'm the musical guest
tonight.
-No, you're not.
No, you're not, Chad.
No, Paul McCartney
is the musical guest.
Yeah.
Yeah. Now you can clap.
So just get off the stage.
Get off the stage now! Go!
-All right.
No, no, don't clap for him.
Don't.
Don't clap for him.
He's a bad guy.
God. I'm sorry.
That was weird, right?
It was really weird.
Okay.
You know what?
Let's just do a hard reset,
all right?
Yeah. Okay. Okay.
It's so great to be here,
hosting "SNL"
for the sixth time,
the season finale.
It's still weird, right?
Yeah, it feels off.
You guys feel that?
It's very off. I'm sorry.
Chad Smith -- he took
the wind out of my sails.
This sucks.
I don't even know
if we should do the show.
That's where I'm at emotionally.
Whatever. Okay, fine.
You know what?
I'll just do --
I'll just do what the host does
when he --
when they don't have any ideas.
So I'll just -- I'll take
questions from the audience.
Uh, yeah. You, sir.
Yeah, the cute one right there.
Yeah. I have a question.
What do you think you're doing,
Chad?
-No, no, Sir Paul McCartney.
Wow.
Why don't you come up here?
Just come on -- come on up.
Look. Look.
I understand your confusion.
Me and Chad do look a lot alike,
but I'm Will.
I'm hosting tonight.
-Nice try, Chad.
Get back -- Get back behind
the drums where you belong.
-Paul, with all due respect,
you look like a fool right now.
Now, I know you've written
a lot of good songs.
"Let It Be"
"Hey Jude."
"Eleanor Rigby."
"Yesterday."
"Hello, Goodbye."
"Lady Madonna."
"Back in the U.S.S.R."
"Jet."
"Maybe I'm Amazed."
"Helter Skelter."
"Rocky Raccoon."
"Goodnight" --
"Goodnight Tonight."
That's a --
That's a personal fave, yeah.
"Blackbird."
"Here, There And Everywhere."
"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da."
"I've Just Seen a Face."
-"Penny Lane."
-Yeah, sure. Fine.
There's that one.
But people often forget
there's some great songs
you didn't write.
"The Alphabet Song."
"Timber" featuring Pitbull.
I mean,
all the Smash Mouth stuff.
-Get your ass
behind the drums, Chad.
-Okay. Yes. Yes, sir.
Right away, sir.
But -- But, first, we got
a great show for you tonight.
Paul McCartney is here.
Stick around.
-We'll be right back!