>>> EASTER.
THE CELEBRATION OF THE RISEN
CHRIST.
THE BIBLE TELLS US THAT JESUS
AND HIS DISCIPLES TRAVELED TO
THE CITY OF JERUSALEM.
WHILE THERE, JESUS VISITED THE TEMPLE
AND, ENRAGED UPON SEEING
MONEY CHANGERS TRANSACTING
BUSINESS WITHIN ITS SACRED WALLS,
EXPELLED THEM ALL.
JESUS WOULD BE ARRESTED AND
CRUCIFIED
ONLY TO RISE AGAIN ON
THE THIRD DAY.
BUT IT BEGAN WITH THE CLEANSING
OF THE TEMPLE.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT TRANSPIRES IN THIS HOLY
PLACE?
>> JESUS, WHAT ANGERS YOU?
>> THIS SHOULD BE A HOUSE OF
PRAYER.
THESE MERCHANTS AND MONEY CHANGERS
HAVE TURNED IT INTO A
DEN OF THIEVES!
>> OH, JESUS MAD.
>> THIS WILL NOT STAND.
I WILL RID THIS PLACE OF ALL ITS
MONEY!
>> REMIND YOU OF ANYONE?
WOW, I ALSO GOT RID OF MONEY
LAST WEEK.
BUT INSTEAD OF ONE TEMPLE, I DID
A WHOLE COUNTRY.
MAYBE EVEN THE GLOBE.
THE MONEY'S GONE.
HI, IT'S ME, YOUR FAVORITE
PRESIDENT, DONALD JESUS TRUMP.
COMPARING MYSELF TO THE SON OF
GOD ONCE AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, MANY PEOPLE ARE EVEN
CALLING ME THE MESSIAH
BECAUSE
OF THE MESS I HAVE MADE OUT OF
THE ECONOMY.
MY BEAUTIFUL TARIFFS, SO
BEAUTIFUL.
THEY WERE WORKING SO WELL THAT I
HAD TO STOP THEM.
THE PRIME MINISTER OF CANADA, BIG GUY,
TEARS IN HIS EYES, HE
CALLED ME.
AND HE SAID, "SIR, IF YOU DO
THIS, YOU WILL UPEND THE GLOBAL ECONOMY,
TAKE THE STOCKS AND
BOND MARKETS, AND UNITE YOUR
ALLIES AGAINST YOU."
AND I SAID, "LET ME COOK!"
THEN I BURN DINNER BADLY.
SO WE HAD TO STOP.
NOW EVERYTHING IS BACK EXACTLY
HOW IT WAS.
MINUS A FEW TRILLION DOLLARS.
AN HISTORIC TRANSFER OF WEALTH
FROM THE MIDDLE CLASS TO MY
BUDDIES, OH WELL.
IT'S TRUE, THE STOCK MARKET DID
A JESUS.
IT DIED.
THEN ON THE THIRD DAY, IT WAS
RISEN.
THEN ON THE FOURTH DAY, IT DIED
AGAIN.
POSSIBLY NEVER TO RETURN, JUST
LIKE JESUS.
WHERE THE HECK IS THAT GUY?
COME BACK, GET ME OUT OF THIS.
OH, AND JESUS CHRIST IS A NAME
WE'VE BEEN SAYING A LOT LATELY.
WE'RE SAYING IT A LOT.
WE LOOK AT OUR 401(k), JESUS
CHRIST, WHERE DID IT ALL GO?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT WE'RE GOING TO FIX THAT,
OR NOT, WE'LL SEE,
SHOULD BE INTERESTING.
LOOK AT JESUS BACK THERE.
FLIPPING THE TABLE LIKE A REAL
HOUSEWIFE.
TERESA.
LOOK AT EMIL WAKIM, FEATURING
EMIL WAKIM!
HE THINKS HE SHOULD BE PLAYING
JESUS.
HE WAS TELLING EVERYBODY
BACKSTAGE, "THE REAL JESUS WOULD
HAVE LOOKED LIKE ME IRL."
BUT WE DON'T LIKE TO THINK ABOUT
THAT, WE HAVE MIKEY DAY THERE.
WITH HIS BIG, BEAUTIFUL BLUE
EYES.
HE'S LIKE, OH, NO, WAIT, MY
GREAT CLIPS MONEY, I NEED MY
GREAT CLIPS MONEY.
BUT IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR EASTER.
A HOLIDAY THAT IS SO SPECIAL,
AND FRANKLY UPCOMING TO ME.
AND TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY OF
PASSOVER FOR OUR JEWISH FRIENDS.
WE CALL IT PASSOVER.
BECAUSE IT'S WHEN I ABOUT PASS
OVER THE KOSHER SECTION IN THE
GROCERY STORE,
GO STRAIGHT TO
THAT EASTER CANDY.
ENVISION A JAR.
NO, THANKS, WASN'T A PEEP.
WE LOVE EASTER, WE LOVE BUNNY,
WE LOVE HUNTING FOR EGGS
JUST
LIKE EVERYONE'S DOING IN THE
GROCERY STORE RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE THEY COST A TRILLION
BILLION DOLLARS, PRICE OF EGGS.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS WHAT THE
WHOLE CAMPAIGN WAS ABOUT.
BUT I JUST CAN'T CRACK AN EGG
JOKE, HERE WE GO.
THAT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF
CREATIVE.
BUT WE LOVE EASTER.
IT'S THE DAY WHERE THE MOST
HOMOPHOBIC PEOPLE TRY TO DRESS
AS GAY AS POSSIBLE.
"DARLING, HAVE YOU SEEN MY"
BONNET?
DADDY LOOKS LOVELY IN HIS PINK
SEERSUCKER.
WE ARE LOOKING FORWARD TO EASTER
MASS.
EASTER MASS IS ALWAYS PACKED.
IT'S SAD.
SOME PEOPLE ONLY GO TO CHURCH ON
CHRISTMAS AND EASTER.
NOT ME.
I DON'T GO ON THOSE DAYS EITHER.
BUT I LOVE TO PRAY.
I PRAY A LOT.
I PRAY SO MUCH, THEY CALL ME
PREDATOR.
LOOK AT ALL THEM, LOOK AT SARAH
SHERMAN.
STUCK WITH HER MOUTH OPEN.
BAD CHOICE.
KENAN'S BACK THERE TOO.
I LOVE KENAN.
>> YEAH, I'M LEAVING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU CAN'T GO, KENAN.
>> YEAH, I CAN.
>> OKAY, I GUESS IT'S KENAN, SO
HE CAN GO.
THINKING ABOUT IT, SHE WANTS TO --
OH, SHE'S THINKING ABOUT
WALKING.
DO I HAVE THE JUICE TO SCOOT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE HAD A BIG HIT LAST WEEK,
MISS EGGY.
THIS IS NOT GOING TO DO.
DON'T SAY IT, WE'LL GET IN
TROUBLE.
ANYWAY, WHAT ELSE I GOT, WHAT
ELSE I GOT?
I HAD MY ANNUAL PHYSICAL THIS
WEEK.
THEY SAID I'M IN GREAT SHAPE.
ONE OF THE BEST SHAPES.
LUMP.
SO, IN CONCLUSION, THE U.S.
DOLLAR HAS DIED
AND GONE TO
MONEY HEAVEN, BYE-BYE.
SOME PEOPLE SAY I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IMDOING, BUT I ACTUALLY --
I'M PLAYING FOUR-DIMENSIONAL
CHESS, OKAY?
KING ME!
BUT IN THE HOLIEST OF SEASONS, EASTER,
LET US REMEMBER THE
LESSON THAT MR. JESUS TAUGHT US
WHEN HE WENT BUCK WILD ON THOSE
MONEY CHANGERS.
WE MUST NEVER MIX RELIGION WITH
COMMERCE.
YOU CAN READ ALL ABOUT THIS IN
MY TRUMP BIBLE.
NOW MADE IN AMERICA, SO IT COSTS
$1,300.
AND IT FALLS APART EVEN FASTER.
ALL RIGHT.
SHOULD I LET THEM SAY IT WITH ME
THIS TIME?
I THINK I WILL.
HAPPY EASTER, HAPPY PASSOVER,
AND -- LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, JON HAMM!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SPRINGTIME IN NEW YORK CITY,
HUH?
41 DEGREES AND DAMP.
OH, MAN.
I AM SO HONORED TO BE BACK HERE
HOSTING.
THIS IS MY FOURTH TIME.
BUT -- BEEN A MINUTE.
LAST TIME I HOSTED WAS OCTOBER
2010.
BUT EVEN THOUGH IT'S BEEN
AWHILE, I'VE STILL BEEN ON THE
SHOW A LOT.
IN FACT, I WAS CHECKING MY OWN
WIKIPEDIA.
WHICH I OFTEN DO.
AND I FOUND OUT THAT SINCE THEN,
I'VE MADE 14 CAMEOS.
AND YOU KNOW, MAKING A CAMEO
IS EVEN MORE SPECIAL THAN BEING THE
HOST.
WHICH IS SOMETHING LORNE'S TOLD
ME MANY TIMES.
ALWAYS RIGHT BEFORE HE LOSES
SERVICE GOING INTO THE TUNNEL.
HE'S ALWAYS IN THAT TUNNEL.
BUT YEAH, 14 CAMEOS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
OKAY.
I KIND OF MAYBE THOUGHT THEY'D
BE PLAYED SEPARATELY.
THAT'S A LITTLE WEIRD.
REALLY, ANY TIME THEY CALL ME TO
COME ON THE SHOW, I DO IT.
BECAUSE NOTHING BEATS THAT
MOMENT WHEN YOU WALK OUT UNEXPECTEDLY
AND THE AUDIENCE
JUST GOES WILD.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> HEY, BUDDY.
>> AMAZING.
I MEAN, RIGHT?
I LOVE WATCHING MYSELF.
AND THE BEST PART IS, I KNOW
THAT ONCE THE AUDIENCE DIES
DOWN, THE APPLAUSE DIES DOWN,
THE WRITERS HAVE WRITTEN ME A
JOKE THAT WILL ELECTRIFY THE
CROWD.
>> I DON'T JUST KISS AND TELL.
I KISS AND TELL, AND I TAKE
NOTES.
>> EXCEPT FOR THAT TIME.
EXCEPT FOR THAT AND A BUNCH OF
OTHER TIMES, I KNOW.
BUT LOOK, I KNOW A CAMEO MAY
SEEM INCONSEQUENTIAL.
BUT IT REALLY IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF THE SHOW.
LIKE WHEN A SKETCH NEEDS THAT
LITTLE SOMETHING EXTRA TO TAKE
IT FROM A MEDIUM SKETCH
TO A
MARGINALLY BETTER THAN A MEDIUM SKETCH
OR WHEN A MONOLOGUE IS
FEELING AIMLESS AND IT NEEDS A
JOLT OF ENERGY.
>> OH, HEY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU -- WHAT ARE YOU
EVEN DOING HERE?
THIS IS MY MONOLOGUE.
>> I KNOW, I'M JUST MAKING A
CAMEO.
>> WHY?
I'M A HUGE STAR, AND I'M DOING
REALLY WELL ALL BY MYSELF.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
HEY, I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
>> COOL.
GIVE ME YOUR OSCAR.
>> NO, WHY WOULD I -- LOOK,
DON'T YOU HAVE ENOUGH?
I'VE SEEN PHOTOS OF YOU IN YOUR
GREAT SWEAT PANTS.
MUST BE NICE.
>> WHATEVER, DUDE.
YOU KNOW.
MAD MEN IS BETTER THAN
SUCCESSION.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> "MAD MEN" IS BETTER THAN
SUCCESSION.
I THINK WE CAN AGREE.
I LOVE YOU, BYE!
LOOK, I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING TO
SAY IS WHETHER I'M HOSTING OR JUST POPPING BY,
IT'S GREAT TO
BE ON THIS SHOW IN ANY CAPACITY.
I MEAN, IT'S AN AMERICAN
INSTITUTION.
AND THERE'S LITERALLY NOWHERE
I'D RATHER BE THAN RIGHT HERE
LIVE ON THIS STAGE SAYING,
WE'VE
GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
LIZZO IS HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
CHANNEL."
>> WELCOME TO "CHECK-TO-CHECK
BUSINESS NEWS."
FINANCIAL NEWS FOR REGULAR FOLKS
LIVING CHECK-TO-CHECK.
YOU KNOW.
PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK.
I'M TASIA WALTON.
>> I'M KENNETH ALBRIGHT, AND
THIS SUIT IS FROM KOHL'S.
MARKETS ARE IN TURMOIL.
LET'S CHECK ON THE S&P 500 DOWN
2.38%.
THE NASDAQ COMPOSITE IS DOWN 265
POINTS.
AND DOW INDUSTRIALS ARE DOWN
2.88%.
OKAY.
DOES THAT MEAN ANYTHING TO
ANYONE?
>> I'M SURE IT MEANS SOMETHING
TO SOMEONE.
BUT SOUNDS LIKE A BUNCH OF
GIBBERISH TO ME.
TAKE A LOOK AT BOXED MAC AND
CHEESE WHICH IS UP 4.5% TO
$1.59.
>> WHOA.
ACROSS THE STREET?
>> EVEN ACROSS THE STREET,
KENNETH.
ALSO, BIG-ASS BOX OF BISQUICK IS
UP FROM $2.39 TO TOO DAMN MUCH.
CANDY BARS ARE UP FROM "SURE,
BABY" TO "PUT THAT BACK."
>> OVERALL PRETTY BAD NEWS FOR
THE GROCERY SECTOR.
>> MY FAMILY BEEN EATING SO MUCH
TOP RAMEN, MY FAMILY THINK WE
JAPANESE.
>> HEALTH CARE SAEK FOR, SO FAR
SPENDING ON DOCTOR VISITS
REMAINS STEADY AT ZERO.
>> BUT MILLIONS OF AMERICANS ARE
INVESTING IN HEALTH CARE
ALTERNATIVES SUCH AS, JUST GO
LAY DOWN.
TAKE AN ADVIL.
PRAY IT GOES AWAY.
>> ALL GREAT OPTIONS.
WELL, THE TRUMP TARIFFS HAVE
CAUSED T-BILL SELL-OFFS WHICH
HAVE ROCKED THE BOND MARKETS.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT THAT?
>> I'M NOT, AND I'LL TELL YOU
WHY, BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THAT IS.
>> EITHER WAY, THESE TARIFFS
HAVE REAL IMPLICATIONS FOR
CHECK-TO-CHECKERS.
HERE WITH THE INTERNATIONAL
COMMODITIES REPORT IS DAVID
HAYES.
>> THESE TARIFFS ARE GOING TO
RAISE PRICES ON ALL IMPORTED
GOODS.
YOU CAN WORK AROUND THEM IF
YOU'RE SMART.
FOR EXAMPLE, I OCCASIONALLY LIKE
PERRIER WATER FROM FRANCE.
INSTEAD, I DRINK THIS AMERICAN
VERSION, UNCLE BUBBLES.
THIS IS MADE FROM PURE TENNESSEE
TAP WATER, AND IT IS ONLY $1.89.
EVEN DOMESTIC PRODUCTS WILL
EXPERIENCE SOME FLUCTUATIONS.
I USED TO EAT CAP'N CRUNCH
CEREAL.
TODAY I BUY THIS.
LOWER PRICE, FLAVOR BAD.
ALTHOUGH I LOVE PIZZA FROM
DiGIORNO BUT IT'S PRICING HIGHER
LATELY.
NOW I EAT DeVONTAE.
THIS DELICIOUS ALTERNATIVE
CREATED BY MY COUSIN DeVONTAE.
IT'S NOT DELIVERY.
IT'S DeVONTAE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> GREAT TIPS, KENNETH.
WE COULD ALL USE THAT MONEY TO
PAYBACK OUR STUDENT LOANS.
HA HA HA!
>> HA HA HA!
¶ NEVER GONNA GET IT NEVER GONNA
GET IT ¶
¶ BOP BOP BOP BOP ¶
HA HA!
>> NO WAY.
OKAY.
AIN'T GOING TO GET THAT MONEY.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE A MOMENT FOR
OUR SPONSORS.
CHECK-TO-CHECK NEWS IS BROUGHT
TO YOU BY AMERICA'S MOST POPULAR
TOILET PAPER, CHIPOTLE NAPKINS.
'CAUSE CHARMIN PRICES BE
TRIPPING.
>> BY TACO BELL.
SHOULD MEAT COST LESS THAN GUM?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WELL, CHECK-TO-CHECKERS ARE
ALWAYS LOOKING FOR WAYS TO BOOST
THEIR INCOME.
HERE'S BRICE TERRY WITH THE
SIDE HUSTLE MINUTE.
>> HI, GUYS.
RECENT DOWNTURNS HAVE INVESTORS
ON EDGE, AND FOR MY MONEY,
THERE'S NO SAFER INVESTMENT THAN
FUNK-O-POPS.
I'VE SOLD MY FREDDIE FRUNG-O
BATMAN BEYOND ON EBAY, $560.
I ENDED UP BUYING SEVERAL NEW
FUNK-O-POPS WHICH SET ME BACK
$3,400.
I GUESS I BROKE EVEN.
>> BRICE, YOU SOLD $560 AND
BOUGHT OVER $3,000 WORTH?
THAT'S NOT BREAKING EVEN.
>> JUST GIVE IT A COUPLE YEARS,
KENNETH.
FUNK-O-POPS ARE A SOLID
INVESTMENT.
>> RIGHT, THEY'RE PLASTIC DOLLS,
RIGHT?
>> YES.
CUT AWAY FROM ME, PLEASE.
>> THANKS, BRILES.
WHEN WE COME BACK ON
CHECK-TO-CHECK NEWS, IT'S A
SHAMPOO, BODY WASH, AND SHAVE
GEL ALL IN ONE.
IT'S CALLED BAR SOAP.
>> RIGHT, BACK IN A BIT, Y'ALL.
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BYE-BYE!
MISSING
AVA 22
DIDN'T SHOW UP FOR WORK TODAY
AND HER ROOMMATES SAY SHE DIDN'T
COME HOME LAST NIGHT.
>> ANY RELATION TO COUNCILMAN
CLARKSON?
>> HIS SISTER'S KID.
>> JESUS CHRIST.
>> YEAH.
CITY HALL'S BREATHING DOWN MY
NECK.
WE NEED ALL HANDS ON DECK.
REVIEWING SURVEILLANCE.
CALLING CO-WORKERS, NEIGHBORS,
EVERYONE.
GOING TO BE A LATE ONE, SO ORDER
SOME PIZZAS AND
LET'S FIND THAT
GIRL.
>> PIZZA!
YES!
PIZZA!
>> CRAIG.
>> AWESOME SAUCE.
>> I'M SURE YOU'VE NOTICED, WE
HAVE FRIENDS FROM THE BUREAU
JOINING US TODAY.
AGENT MURPHY, DO YOU WANT TO
COME UP HERE?
>> THANKS, CHIEF.
YEAH, THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
MISINFORMATION CIRCLING ABOUT
THIS CASE ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
I'D LIKE TO OPEN IT UP TO
QUESTIONS.
>> WHAT TOPPINGS Y'ALL THINKING
ABOUT?
HEY
PEPPER RENO.
>> WHO SAID THAT?
>> DANIELS.
ENOUGH ABOUT THE PIZZA.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A LITTLE KID.
>> SORRY, CHIEF.
NOT A LITTLE KID.
>> NOW, AVA WAS LAST SEEN AT
WORK SUNDAY NIGHT.
A GARBAGE MAN PLACES HER ON
DREIGHTON AROUND 7:00 P.M.
BLOCKS
>> I DON'T WANT PIZZA ANYMORE.
>> ARE YOU CRYING?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO EAT PIZZA
EVEN THOUGH IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
>> NO, IT'S NOT, YOU JUST HAD
YOUR 50th AT DAVE & BUSTER'S.
>> DUDE, CHILL, NOT EVERYONE WAS
INVITED.
>> IT'S FINE YOU DIDN'T INVITE
ME, DANIELS.
>> I DON'T DESERVE PIZZA.
MAYBE I'LL HAVE A SODA AND
THAT'S ALL I'LL HAVE FROM THE
PIZZA PARTY.
>> IT'S NOT A PIZZA PARTY.
>> I'M LOST, CAN WE START OVER?
FOCUS UP AND TRY TO FIND THIS
DOG.
>> IT'S A MISSING GIRL!
>> WHATEVER.
OH, MY GOD IS SHE OKAY?
>> WE DON'T KNOW,
- THAT'S WHAT THIS IS.
>> WHY ARE WE SITTING AROUND
HERE AND HAVING A SLEEPOVER?
>> THIS ISN'T A SLEEPOVER, THIS
IS MAN.
WORK
I ORDERED PIZZAS TO BE NICE.
THREE CHEESE, THREE HAWAIIAN.
>> OH, MY GOD, ARE YOU KIDDING
ME?
>> YOU GOT HALF HAWAIIAN?
YOU JUST MADE THAT CALL?
HAND
>> [ BLEEP ] HAWAIIAN.
>> I LOVE HAWAIIAN.
>> JUST FOR YOU?
IT'S FOR EVERYBODY.
>> LOOK AT WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
HE'S GROWLING LIKE A DOG.
>> LIKE WE SAY AT QUANTICO, IT
AIN'T A SLEEPOVER WITHOUT MEAT
LOVERS, Y'ALL.
>> THANK YOU!
>> HEY.
I REALIZED IMMEDIATELY I
SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
>> PIZZA!
>> IT'S THE VICTIM'S MOTHER.
>> UGH, GREAT.
>> MA'AM, I'M SO DEEPLY SORRY
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
MY WHOLE WORLD IS UPSIDE DOWN.
>> I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
WHEN I WAS YOUNG, I HAD A DOG
RUN AWAY TOO.
>> DOG?
>> DANIELS, PLEASE, FOCUS ON
FINDING THE MISSING GIRL.
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO FIND HER IF
WE --
>> HELLO?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I GOT YOUR PIZZA.
>> PIZZA!
>> IT'S HAWAIIAN, RIGHT?
>> "GUESS THE CORRECT ANSWER!"
>> HELLO AND GOOD EVENING.
I'M MARKY MARK BRANDON MARCUS,
AND WELCOME BACK TO "GUESS THE
CORRECT ANSWER."
NOT A HUGE FAN OF THE TITLE,
MYSELF.
BUT THE FOCUS GROUP CALLED IT
FINE FOR NOW.
LET'S MEET OUR TWO TEAMS.
FOR OUR FIRST PAIR TODAY FROM
BOSTON, ANNA TILLMAN, FROM
QUEENS, PETER McGRAPH.
>> EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED.
>> FROM MAPLE WOOD, NEW JERSEY,
DAMIAN DRIVER.
FROM BURLINGTON, PAUL McCROSKEY.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS FEELING?
>> PUMPED TO BE HERE.
>> PRETTY NERVOUS, NOT GOING TO
LIE.
>> OH, WHY'S THAT, PAUL?
>> OH, GEEZ.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST HAVE A GREAT LIFE.
AND I'M AFRAID I COULD DO
SOMETHING EMBARRASSING THAT
COULD GO VIRAL AND RUIN IT ALL.
>> OH.
WELL.
DON'T THINK LIKE THAT, YOU'RE
GOING TO DO GREAT.
>> I HOPE SO.
I REALLY HOPE SO.
I GOT A GREAT FAMILY, BEAUTIFUL
WIFE, I'M A DENTIST.
WELL LIKED IN MY COMMUNITY.
I DON'T REALLY NEED THE MONEY.
NOT MUCH TO GAIN AND A WHOLE LOT
TO LOSE.
>> DAMN.
WELL, HOPE IT GOES WELL.
LET'S PLAY.
WE'LL START WITH YOU TWO.
THE RULES OF THE GAME ARE
SIMPLE.
DAMIAN, YOUR JOB IS TO GET PAUL
TO GUESS WHAT'S ON THE CARD IN
FRONT OF YOU.
YOUR CATEGORY IS, THINGS YOU
MIGHT FIND IN A WORKPLACE.
>> OH, NICE, NICE, NICE.
RIGHT UP MY ALLEY.
I WORK IN A WORKPLACE.
>> VERY GOOD.
>> YEAH.
I THINK THAT WAS -- TOTALLY
WRONG BEFORE, I THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE FINE.
>> EXCELLENT.
YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
>> OKAY.
SOMETHING THAT'S RACIST.
>> OH -- ME.
>> WHAT?
>> ME, MYSELF, MY FAMILY, MY
WHOLE FAMILY.
>> NO.
>> MY FRIENDS, MY BEST FRIEND,
MY GROOMSMAN, MY JOKES, MY FUNNY
ACCENTS, MY LOOKS --
>> YOU'RE DOING EXACTLY WHAT YOU
WERE WORRIED ABOUT.
COME ON, MAN.
IT'S SOMETHING SMALL.
>> MY PENIS.
>> SMALL BUT RACIST.
>> YEAH, MY PENIS.
>> NO, MAN.
PASS, PASS.
OH, OKAY.
WHAT YOU DRINK FIRST THING IN
THE MORNING.
>> VODKA.
>> WHAT YOU DRINK BEFORE WORK.
>> DON'T TALK TO ME BEFORE I'VE
HAD MY --
>> VEST COPY.
>> WHAT?
NO.
PASS.
OKAY.
WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT WHEN YOU'RE
ZONING OUT.
>> MY DAUGHTER'S FRIENDS.
MY DAUGHTER'S HOTTEST FRIENDS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT WOULD YOU CALL THE THOUGHTS
YOU HAVE ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER'S
FRIENDS?
>> UNSTOPPABLE.
UNSTOPPABLE.
>> NO, NO -- BUT WHAT ARE THEY?
>> OH, HYPERSEXUAL DAYDREAMS.
>> YES!
>> OH, YEAH, GOT IT.
I GOT IT.
IN YOUR FACES!
TRYING TO MAKE A VIRAL FAIL CLIP
OUT OF THAT ONE, SUCKERS.
OH -- DID I DO THAT?
HEY, LOOK, AT LEAST I GOT A
POINT, RIGHT?
THAT IS FABULOUS!
>> WOW.
WHAT A DISASTER.
>> OH, SO SORRY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT CAME OVER ME.
SHOULD WE SWING IT OVER TO THE
OTHER TEAM?
>> THEY LEFT AWHILE AGO.
>> DO I STILL GET TO BE A
DENTIST?
>> PROBABLY NOT.
JOIN US NEXT TIME ON -- "ANSWER
QUESTIONS CORRECTLY!"
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU CALLED IT
BEFORE.
WHITE
>>> HON.
DONALD, YOU GETTING READY?
HELLO!
EARTH TO DONALD.
IT'S YOUR WIFE, MELANIA.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> HUH?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, SORRY.
I -- I'LL BE READY IN A SEC.
MAC
I TOLD YOU, ERIC, IF YOU WANT TO
BE A MAN,
YOU GOT TO START
HAVING SHAKES.
NO.
ERIC, I MEANT PROTEIN SHAKES.
HERE, WHY DON'T YOU MAKE YOUR
OWN.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
>> OKAY.
>> BUDDY, DID YOU JUST BLEND
YOUR GOLD ROLEX?
>> YOU SAID IT WAS ABOUT TIME.
>> RIGHT.
WHERE'S IVANKA?
SHE'S BEEN M.I.A. FOR DAD'S
ENTIRE PRESIDENCY.
>> YOU MUST ASK YOURSELF,
AM I WILLING TO GIVE UP GREED AND
MATERIAL POSSESSIONS
AND LEAD AN
HONEST AND ETHICAL LIFE?
>> WE ARE SO LUCKY THAT AMERICA
WILL ALWAYS BE A RICH AND
POWERFUL NATION.
I MEAN, CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW
AWFUL IT WOULD BE
IF AMERICA LOST ALL ITS MONEY
AND NO ONE IN
THE WORLD RESPECTED US ANYMORE?
TRUMP
YOU WOULD NEVER LET OUR ECONOMY
GO TO PIECES.
RIGHT, HON?
>> I LOVE MY BUTTER NOODLES.
>> BY THE WAY, MOM, WHAT IS THAT
ACCENT?
AREN'T YOU FROM SLOVENIA?
>> NO, NORTH CAROLINA.
GO, TAR HEELS.
>> OH, AND YOUR COMMERCE
SECRETARY, HOWARD LUTNICK, IS
SITTING OVER THERE.
SAYS HE WANTS TO WATCH AMERICA
GET BENT OVER
AND RAILED BY
OTHER COUNTRIES?
>> YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE ARE
JUST WEIRD.
LIKE THAT MAN WHO ARRIVED ON THE
BOAT WITH US, RFK JR.
>> I ALWAYS HAVE CRAZY IDEAS.
I HAVE THIS SYRINGE FULL
OF ACTIVE MEASLES VIRUS.
I WANT TO STAB SOMEBODY WITH IT.
I'M HAVING THESE INSANE IDEAS
LIKE, WHAT IF WE TOOK ALL THE
FLUORIDE OUT OF THE DRINKING
WATER?
WHAT WOULD THAT DO TO PEOPLE'S
TEETH?
>> FLUORIDE?
WHAT'S THAT?
A MONKEY!
>> KILL IT AND EAT IT.
>> NO, NOT THE MONEY ONKY.
>> THESE OLD WHITE TRUMP DUDES
ARE TRYING TO RUIN MY LIFE.
OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S $5 MILLION IN MY BANK
ACCOUNT.
IT WAS $20 MILLION LAST WEEK.
>> KRISTI NOEM, I AM SO GLAD
YOU'RE SENDING ALL THOSE
VENEZUELANS BACK TO WHERE THEY
BELONG.
EL SALVADOR.
>> I COULDN'T DO IT WITHOUT YOU,
PAM BONDI,
YOU'RE THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
>> AND I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT
GENERALLY
EVERYTHING I'M DOING
IS ILLEGAL.
>> TOTALLY.
HEY, PEOPLE LIKE ME, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, YOU'RE GREAT, MARCO, WE
LOVE YA.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HEY, WE'RE GOING TO GO TAKE A
WALK OVER THERE FOR A SECOND.
>> HEY.
CAN I CHEER YOU UP?
>> VLADIMIR PUTIN?
>> IT'S VLAD.
COME.
DANCE WITH ME.
>> OKAY.
>> DON'T DO IT!
>> I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M GOING TO PUT A 500% CHERIF
ON CHINA.
NO
>> HEY.
>> VLADIMIR, I THINK WE'RE ALL
HAVING WEIRD DREAMS.
>> WHAT DID I DO LAST NIGHT?
YEAH, BABY.
>> SURPRISE, IT'S ME, TIGER
WOODS.
>> "WHITE LOTUS," AN AMERICAN
HORROR STORY.
>> AND THE MASTERS ONLY ON CBS.
¶ EVERYTHING LOOKS
SO MUCH DIFFERENT
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I NEED ¶
¶ REAL LOVE AND REAL LIFE ¶
¶ WIPE MY EYES
COMB MY HAIR ¶
¶ THERE'S A LOT OF
PAIN OUT THERE ¶
¶ I FEEL SAFER
IN MY BATHROOM ¶
¶ CLOSE THE DOOR
HIT IGNORE ¶
¶ ALL SHE REALLY
WANTS TO KNOW
IS IF I'M REALLY 'BOUT
TO GO DOWNTOWN ¶
¶ TONIGHT
OOH
I MIGHT MAKE AN APPEARANCE
SINCE I LOOK THIS FINE ¶
¶ AND PLUS IT'S BEEN A WHILE
TONIGHT
OOH ¶
¶ TEQUILA DO YOUR JOB
GIRL, HELP ME
CHANGE MY MIND ¶
¶ HOW MANY SHOTS THIS TIME
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR ¶
¶ HEY, HO, HEY, HO
GIVE ME SOMETHING
WITH A LITTLE TEMPO ¶
¶ HEY, HO, HEY, HO
GIVE ME SOMETHING I CAN
THROW IT BACK FOR ¶
¶ BY THE END OF THE WORLD
FEELS LIKE THE
END OF THE WORLD ¶
¶ IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD ¶
¶ I'M 'BOUT TO THROW
MY PHONE AWAY ¶
¶ CAN'T LET MY GIRLS KNOW
GROOVIN' MESSIN'
WITH MY DAY ¶
¶ HE ACT LIKE HE CAN'T
BE REPLACED, OKAY ¶
¶ WELL, HE GON' HATE
TO SEE ME LEAVE BUT
LOVE TO WATCH ME WALK AWAY ¶
¶ HE KNOCKED ME DOWN
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER
GET MY FINE ASS
OFF THE GROUND, OH-OH ¶
¶ BUT I'M READY NOW
FEELIN' CRAZY LATELY
BABY, LET'S GO OUT ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED A DRINK ¶
¶ LET'S TURN THIS PAIN INTO
SOME CHAMPAGNE, BABY ¶
¶ LIKE CHEERS, BITCH
IT'S BEEN A DAY ¶
¶ MIGHT TAKE THAT LAST
FLIGHT OUT TO VEGAS ¶
¶ WHAT Y'ALL THINK
OKAY ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED A DRINK ¶
¶ I DON'T KNOW WHY LIFE IS
SO MESSED UP LATELY ¶
¶ BUT AFTER EVERYTHING
I'M STILL SURVIVING
AND I'M STILL BAD, BABY
SO, BITCH I CAN'T COMPLAIN ¶
¶ PLOT TWIST
I'M DOING GREAT ¶
¶ I MAKE THAT BEEN THROUGH
IT LOOK SEXY
DON'T I, Y'ALL ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED TO THROW ASS
BEEN A MINUTE ¶
¶ BREAK FAST WITH MY BITCHES
REAL LOVE, REAL LIFE
DAMN I'VE BEEN MISSING ¶
¶ HE KNOCKED ME DOWN
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER
GET MY FINE ASS
OFF THE GROUND, OH-OH ¶
¶ BUT I'M READY NOW
FEELING CRAZY LATELY
BABY, LET'S GO OUT ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED A DRINK ¶
¶ LET'S TURN THIS PAIN INTO
SOME CHAMPAGNE, BABY ¶
¶ LIKE CHEERS, BITCH
IT'S BEEN A DAY ¶
¶ MIGHT TAKE THAT LAST
FLIGHT OUT TO VEGAS ¶
¶ WHAT Y'ALL THINK
OKAY ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED A DRINK ¶
¶ I DON'T KNOW WHY LIFE
BEEN SO MESSED UP LATELY ¶
¶ BUT AFTER EVERYTHING
WE STILL SURVIVING AND
WE STILL BAD, BABY
SO, BITCH I CAN'T COMPLAIN ¶
¶ I'M STILL BAD, BABY
WHO'S BAD ¶
¶ DON'T STOP, GET IT, GET IT
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
SHE BACK IN THE BUILDING ¶
¶ PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER WE
STILL BAD Y'ALL ¶
¶ STILL BAD, DON'T FORGET IT
I'M STILL BAD, BABE ¶
¶ COME ON ¶
¶ SHE BACK IN THE BUILDING ¶
¶ IT'S BEEN A YEAR I NEED A
DRINK ¶
¶ LET'S TURN THIS PAIN INTO
SOME CHAMPAGNE, BABY ¶
¶ LIKE CHEERS, BITCH
IT'S BEEN A DAY
OH, IT'S BEEN A DAY ¶
¶ MIGHT TAKE THAT LAST
FLIGHT OUT TO VEGAS ¶
¶ WHAT Y'ALL THINK
OKAY ¶
¶ I DON'T NEED HIM
I NEED A DRINK ¶
¶ I DON'T KNOW WHY LIFE IS
SO MESSED UP LATELY ¶
¶ BUT AFTER EVERYTHING
I'M STILL SURVIVING
AND I'M STILL BAD, BABY
SO, BITCH I CAN'T COMPLAIN ¶
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TRIED TO RESCUE
THE ECONOMY FROM THE DISASTROUS POLICIES
OF WHOEVER WAS
PRESIDENT LAST WEEK.
ON WEDNESDAY, TRUMP ANNOUNCED HE
WAS PAUSING MOST TARIFFS FOR 90
DAYS.
NOW, 90 DAYS MAY NOT SEEM LIKE A LONG TIME,
BUT REMEMBER, TRUMP
HAS ONLY BEEN PRESIDENT FOR 82
DAYS.
AND IT ALREADY FEELS LIKE A
GODDAMN DECADE.
JUST HOURS BEFORE, TRUMP PAUSED
THE TARIFFS.
HE TRIED TO CALM INVESTORS BY POSTING,
"BE COOL, EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO WORK OUT WELL."
BE COOL?
THIS IS A GLOBAL ECONOMY.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE GOT TOO HIGH
AND WE'RE TRYING TO GET THROUGH
DINNER WITH OUR PARENTS.
>>> THE CEOs OF MANY TECH
COMPANIES WHO SUPPORTED
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S CAMPAIGN
HAVE
SAID THEY WERE SURPRISED BY ALL
OF HIS TARIFFS.
WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, HE HARDLY EVER MENTIONED
THEM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SO MUCH
MONEY COMING IN FROM TARIFFS.
- TARIFFS ON PHARMACEUTICALS
- ON STEEL.
- CAR TARIFFS.
- HUNDREDS OF BILLIONS IN TARIFFS.
- SUBSTANTIAL TARIFFS.
10%.
25% TARIFFS.
50% TARIFFS.
BIG TARIFFS.
TARIFFS.
I LOVE TARIFFS.
>> IT'S LIKE LISTENING TO BUBBA
GUMP TALK ABOUT SHRIMP.
>> TRUMP RESPONDED TO THE
FALLOUT FROM HIS TARIFFS
SAYING
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO TAKE
MEDICINE TO FIX SOMETHING.
YEAH, BUT THIS FEELS LIKE WE
TOOK A WHOLE BOTTLE OF MEDICINE
WITH A GLASS OF VODKA
AND LAID
IN A WARM BATH.
IT WAS REPORTED ELON MUSK
PERSONALLY APPEALED TO PRESIDENT TRUMP
TO STOP HIS TARIFF PLAN,
AND IT WORKED.
THE STOCK MARKET WENT UP LIKE
THIS.
>>> CHINA'S RETALIATORY TARIFFS
WILL HURT U.S. FARMERS,
WHO SELL
PRODUCTS TO CHINA THEY CAN'T
SELL ELSEWHERE, INCLUDING CHICKEN FEET,
WHICH MEANS THOSE CHICKENS
WILL HAVE TO SELL THEIR FEET ON
ONLYFANS.
>>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT IF
iPHONES WERE MANUFACTURED IN THE U.S.,
THEY COULD COST UP TO
$3,500.
WHICH IS A LOT, BUT REMEMBER,
YOUR KIDS WOULD GET AN EMPLOYEE
DISCOUNT.
>>> THE U.S. EDUCATION
DEPARTMENT HAS LAUNCHED A WEBSITE
IN WHICH STUDENTS CAN
REPORT PUBLIC SCHOOLTEACHERS WHO
VIOLATE ANTI-DEI RULES.
REMEMBER, TEACHERS, YOU'VE GOT
TO SLEEP WITH THE WHITE ONES
TOO.
>>> HEALTH SECRETARY ROBERT FMT KENNEDY JR.,
WHOSE BEAUTY
ROUTINE INVOLVES ROLLING AROUND
UNDER 7-ELEVEN HOT DOG LAMPS --
SAID HE PLANS TO TELL THE CDC TO
STOP RECOMMENDING
THAT FLUORIDE
BE PUT IN DRINKING WATER
AND
START RECOMMENDING VENEERS FOR
KIDS.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT SEVERAL
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS ARE
REFUSING TO ANSWER MESSAGES FROM JOURNALISTS
IF THEIR EMAIL
SIGNATURES INCLUDE IDENTIFYING
PRONOUNS.
WHICH IS EXTREMELY FRUSTRATING
FOR "NEW YORK TIMES" REPORTER
SHEHERTHEYTHEM.
>>> THIS WEEK, PRESIDENT TRUMP
PAUSED HIS TARIFFS ON MOST
COUNTRIES EXCEPT CHINA, RAISING
THEM TO 145% AS THE TRADE WAR
ESCALATES.
HERE TO COMMENT IS CHINESE TRADE
MINISTER CHEN BIAO.
>> GOOD TO BE HERE, CHE.
>> ARE YOU READY TO COME TO THE
NEGOTIATING TABLE FOR A TRADE
DEAL?
>> HM, NOT YET.
I'VE JUST BEEN REALLY ENJOYING
MY DOWN TIME.
EVERY DAY I WAKE UP, I GO ON A
WALK, I JOURNAL, I CLAIM TAIWAN.
THEN AT NIGHT, I UNWIND BY BEING
A HECKLER AT "SHEN YUN."
>> SO HOW DOES CHINA FEEL ABOUT
TRUMP'S TARIFFS?
>> UM -- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE 145%?
COOL NUMBER, BRO.
I'VE GOT NUMBERS TOO.
12.
93.
1-877-CARS-FORKIDS.
>> YOU RAISED YOUR TARIFFS TO
125% IN RESPONSE.
>> RIGHT.
BOTH OF OUR COUNTRIES ARE GOING
TO FACE A LOT OF HARDSHIP.
BUT WAIT.
I'M JUST WONDERING, WHICH SIDE
IS MORE WILLING TO ENDURE
HARDSHIP FOR THE GLORY OF THEIR
NATION?
THE ONE THAT'S BEEN AROUND FOR
THOUSANDS OF YEARS?
OR THE ONE THAT'S SENDING KATY
PERRY TO SPACE?
>> TRUMP IS MEETING WITH SOUTH
KOREA AND JAPAN TO NEGOTIATE
THIS WEEK.
DON'T YOU FEEL LEFT OUT?
>> UM -- DOES THE HOT GIRL FEEL
LEFT OUT OF BRACES CAMP?
BESIDES, WHAT IS THERE TO
NEGOTIATE?
TODAY, TRUMP ANNOUNCED HE WAS
ALREADY WALKING BACK ON
SMARTPHONES AND COMPUTERS.
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT OUR
TECHNOLOGY, BUT I THINK WE'LL
SURVIVE WITHOUT YOUR -- NEWMAN'S
OWN SALAD DRESSING.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL NOT JUST
THAT.
THIS WEEK YOU DID THREATEN TO
BAN AMERICAN MOVIES FROM CHINA.
>> OH, NO, WE WON'T GET YOUR
HOLLYWOOD MOVIES?
THE ONLY THING THAT DISTRACTS US
FROM WORKING EVEN HARDER?
>> OKAY, FINE.
MAYBE YOU DO HAVE LEVERAGE ON
US.
>> YEAH, WELL, NOW THAT EVERYONE
IN AMERICA IS LOSING ALL THEIR
MONEY AND RIGHTS, IT'S KIND OF
LIKE WE'RE BOTH COMMUNISTS.
TWINS!
SO THE NEXT TIME YOU BUY A PAIR
OF TOMS, THEY'LL DONATE ANOTHER
PAIR TO YOU 'CAUSE YOU'RE THE
ONE THAT MADE YOU POOR, BITCH.
>> ARE YOU SURPRISED TRUMP HAS
BACKED OFF?
>> VERY SURPRISED.
HE WAS SO CONSISTENT ABOUT
TIKTOK, RIGHT?
OH, IT'S A THREAT TO NATIONAL
SECURITY!
BUT WAIT!
I CAN'T LOSE GEN-Z, DON'T WANT
TO PISS OFF DECLAN.
>> WHO'S DECLAN?
>> PROBABLY SOME 12-YEAR-OLD
LOSER WHO BULLIES WOMEN ONLINE
IN A PETER GRIFFIN "FORTNIGHT"
SKIN.
>> LET'S NOT BE MEAN.
>> I MEAN, J.D. VANCE CALLED
EVERYONE IN CHINA PEASANTS.
AND BY THE WAY, YOU CAN NOW OR
THE MY MEMOIR, "PEASANT ELEGY."
WHEREVER BOOKS ARE SOLD.
GLENN CLOSE WON A CHINESE OSCAR
FOR THE MOVIE VERSION, BECAUSE
WE APPRECIATE HER THERE!
>> CHEN BIAO, EVERYBODY!
>> TARIFFS, SAY WHAT?
>>> TESLA IS REPORTEDLY HAVING
TROUBLE SELLING CYBER TRUCKS.
PARTLY DUE TO ITS SLOGAN, "CYBER
TRUCK: WHAT IF KANYE WAS A CAR?"
>>> THE ASSISTANT GENERAL
MANAGER OF THE DETROIT TIGERS HAS RESIGNED
AFTER HE ALLEGEDLY
SENT LEWD PHOTOS TO HIS COLLEAGUES
ALL WITH THE CAPTION
NOW THIS IS A TORPEDO BAT.
>>> LeBRON JAMES HAS BECOME THE
FIRST PROFESSIONAL MALE ATHLETE
TO GET HIS OWN KEN DOLL,
AND
JUST LIKE THE ORIGINAL KEN, HE
HAS A BEARD.
I'M GOING TO CUT THAT FOR AIR.
>> YES.
>>> A WRITER FOR THE 1990s SHOW
MIGHTY MORPHIN POWER RANGERS
IS NOW SAYING IT WAS A MISTAKE
TO CAST A BLACK ACTOR AS THE BLACK RANGER
AND AN ASIAN ACTOR
AS THE YELLOW RANGER.
HE REGRETS HAVING A MEXICAN
ACTOR PLAY THE LAZY RANGER.
>>> A COMPANY IN CHINA HAS
RELEASED
A NEW ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE SEX DOLL.
IF YOU WANT THE SEX TO BE REALLY
GOOD,
SET THE INTELLIGENCE TO
LOW.
>>> IN CRACKDOWNS ON COLLEGE
CAMPUSES,
A NEW STUDY SHOWS 18%
OF YOUNG PEOPLE FEEL PROUD TO BE
AN AMERICAN.
HERE WITH HIS THOUGHTS IS EMIL
WAKIM.
>> HI, COLIN.
HELLO, MY FELLOW AMERICANS.
>> WOW.
EMIL, ARE YOU FEELING PATRIOTIC?
>> HONESTLY, NO, THIS IS TO BUY
GOOD WILL BEFORE THE STUFF I'M
ABOUT TO SAY.
IT'S A TOUGH TIME TO CRITICIZE
AMERICA PUBLICLY,
ESPECIALLY
WITH EYEBROWS LIKE THIS.
BUT I WANT EVERYONE TO KNOW,
IT'S OUT OF LOVE.
BUT I DO HAVE SOME NOTES.
I'M CONFLICTED ON AMERICA RIGHT
NOW.
BUT I AM GRATEFUL TO LIVE HERE.
MY DAD'S AN IMMIGRANT.
MY MOM IS, AS COLIN SAYS,
NORMAL.
BUT
I'M AN AMERICAN. YOU KNOW?
LIKE IN MY BONES, I AM.
I JUST -- I KNOW WE'RE BAD,
BECAUSE MY LIFE IS SO GOOD.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY IT'S CRUELTY
FREE.
YOU KNOW?
AND I LOVE MY LIFE.
I DO.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW HOW IT'S
MADE, YOU KNOW?
I'M HAPPY UNTIL I HAVE TO SEE,
LIKE, WHAT'S HOLDING IT ALL UP.
LIKE, I'M HAPPY TILL I HAVE TO
SEE THE UBER EATS DELIVERY
DRIVER.
YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST LIKE AN IMMIGRANT,
SOAKING WET, YOU'RE JUST LIKE,
OH, NO.
I'M A BAD PERSON.
BUT NO, I'M NOT GOING TO MEET
YOU IN THE LOBBY, WHAT?
I MEAN, COME ON.
IT'S A THREE-HOUR DELIVERY FEE.
COME UP TO MY APARTMENT.
YEAH, LEAVE THE BIKE, NO ONE'S
TAKING THE BIKE.
UP THE STAIRS, COME ON, UP, UP,
UP, UP!
COME ON.
THEN YOU OPEN THE DOOR FOR HIM
AN AMOUNT THAT IS JUST RACIST,
FRANKLY.
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY TO PUT IT.
JUST ENOUGH FOR THE BAG TO FIT
THROUGH.
YOU'RE IN YOUR UNDERWEAR BECAUSE
YOU HAD A HARD DAY
SENDING
EMAILS FOR HITLER OR WHATEVER.
WHATEVER ANYONE'S JOB IS.
AND HE'S SO NICE.
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
HAVE A GOOD ONE, YOU DO HIS
ACCENT BACK TO HIM.
NO
THEN HE'S GONE AND YOU'RE
STANDING THERE WITH A $40
BURRITO.
AND SOMEHOW, WE'VE ALL CONVINCED OURSELVES
THAT NONE OF US WOULD
HAVE OWNED SLAVES.
LIKE, NO, I WOULDN'T HAVE
BECAUSE I TIP AT COFFEE SHOPS
SOMETIMES.
>> WHAT?
HEY, I JUST WANT TO SAY, I
WOULDN'T HAVE.
>> THANKS, COLIN, NATURALLY.
TOTALLY, TOTALLY.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HARD TO NOT FEEL GUILTY
LIVING IN AMERICA.
I'M PART OF THE PROBLEM.
I KNOW CAPITALISM IS BAD BUT I'M
IN IT, YOU KNOW?
WE ALL ARE.
I'M SURE THERE'S PEOPLE IN THIS
ROOM THAT ARE LIKE, CAPITALISM
IS EVIL.
BUT LIKE, YEAH, YOU'RE NOT ABOVE
IT BECAUSE YOU LIVE IN BROOKLYN.
YOU STILL LIVE IN NEW YORK CITY.
NEW YORK CITY IS CAPITALISM WITH
A PHYSICAL LOCATION.
THERE'S AN M&Ms STORE NEXT TO A
CHURCH.
THIS IS HELL.
IT'S HARD.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIND MIDDLE
GROUND.
YOU LOSE PEOPLE WHEN YOU GO TOO
FAR TO ONE SIDE.
BILLIONAIRES ARE BAD, THAT'S
EASY.
I WAS TALKING TO A FRIEND THAT
WAS LIKE, I THINK WE SHOULD
ABOLISH MILLIONAIRES.
HEY, MAN, DON'T YOU BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF?
LIKE, COME ON.
HAVE A DREAM.
A GUY MAKES A MILLION DOLLARS
AND YOU'RE LIKE, HE'S CHEATING.
NO, YOU'RE DEPRESSED, HAVE A
GOAL.
>> THANK YOU FOR STOPPING BY.
I'M EXCITED TO READ ALL THE
YOUTUBE COMMENTS ON THIS ONE.
EMIL WAKIM, EVERYONE!
STUFF
>>> A GIANT POUCHED RAT TRAINED
TO SNIFF OUT LAND MINES
HAS SET
A NEW WORLD RECORD FOR MOST LAND
MINES DETECTED BY A RAT.
ONE.
THE MOST IT CAN DO.
>>> A NEW FASHION TREND FOR
WOMEN ARE NAP DRESSES.
PART OF THE LARGER TREND CALLED
CLINICAL DEPRESSION.
>>> NEW YORK CITY POLICE ARE
SEARCHING FOR A MAN
ACCUSED OF
ROBBING AND SEXUALLY ASSAULTING
A DEAD BODY ON THE SUBWAY.
¶ CONCRETE JUNGLE ¶
NOTHING YOU CAN'T DO, COLIN.
>> NO.
BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
>> THANK YOU.
THEY SHOULD PUT ME IN THE CAST.
>>> A GROUP IS ASKING NEW JERSEY
TRANSIT TO MAKE COMMUTES MORE JOYFUL
BY PUTTING GOOGLY EYES ON
THE FRONT OF TRAINS.
SO AT LEAST YOU'LL SEE A
FRIENDLY FACE COMING TO HELP
WHEN YOU'RE PUSHED ON THE
TRACKS.
>>> A TORE ADVERTISE AT THE
PHILADELPHIA ZOO HAS BECOME A MOTHER
FOR THE FIRST TIME AT AGE
100.
THE TORE ADVERTISE GOT PREGNANT
AFTER HER BOYFRIEND PULLED OUT
TOO SLOW.
TORE
>>> NEXT TUESDAY IS TAX DAY.
MANY PEOPLE ARE NERVOUS ABOUT
THE STATE OF THE ECONOMY.
HERE TO COMMENT IS MY
ACCOUNTANT, DAWN ALTMAN.
>> HELLO, COLIN.
>> HI, DAWN.
SO, THE ECONOMY IS PRETTY CRAZY.
ARE YOU STRESSED?
>> ME, STRESSED?
NO.
LOOK.
COLIN, SOMETIMES PRICES GO UP.
THAT'S JUST HOW IT IS, OKAY?
EVERYBODY'S COMPLAINING ABOUT
EGGS BEING EXPENSIVE.
IT'S LIKE, SO WHAT?
ADAPT.
I'VE BEEN EATING MY OWN EGGS FOR
MONTHS.
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW, THEY MAKE A
VERY RUNNY OMELETTE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING YOU SAID?
ALL RIGHT, HOW ARE ME TAXES
LOOKING?
>> THEY'RE GOOD, THEY'RE GOOD,
THEY'RE GOOD.
I ACTUALLY HAVE ALL YOUR
FINANCIAL RECORDS RIGHT HERE.
SO LET'S GO THROUGH YOUR BUDGET
LIKE YOU GO THROUGH AN AFTER
PARTY,
LINE BY LINE.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
ENOUGH ON THAT.
>> FIRST UP WE GOT THE
FERRYBOAT.
THAT IS A BIG EXPENSE.
THAT'S A BIG EXPENSE.
OH-OH, THIS ISN'T GOOD.
YOU'RE LETTING PEOPLE USE YOUR
PRIVATE JET FOR FREE?
AND OH-OH, IT'S FOR I.C.E.
DEPORTATION?
>> OKAY, THAT'S NOT --
>> YOU'RE SPENDING A HUGE AMOUNT
OF MONEY ON YOUR TAXES.
>> ISN'T THAT YOUR JOB?
>> SORRY, THAT'S MY PERSONAL
ABBREVIATION.
NOT TAXES.
TAINT WAXES.
>> YOU ABBREVIATE TAINT WAXES AS
TAXES?
>> OF COURSE I DO.
COLIN, YOU'VE GOT TO CUT BACK ON
ALL THESE EXPENSIVE MEALS.
>> WAIT, WHAT -- SORRY, I LOVE
TO EAT OUT.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT THEY SAY ON
THE INTERNS GROUP CHAT.
>> THE INTERNS HAVE A GROUP
CHAT?
OH-OH.
SO WAIT, YOU'RE SAYING I SHOULD
CUT BACK ON GOING TO
RESTAURANTS?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO CUT BACK ON
FOOD ENTIRELY, COLIN.
ARE YOU A WEBSITE?
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
ACCEPTING ALL COOKIES.
>> IS THAT A FAT JOKE?
>> IT WASN'T A SKINNY JOKE.
>> DAWN.
>> I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM STRESSED.
THIS ECONOMY IS EXPLODING,
COLIN.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JUST GIVE ME A
MOMENT.
I'M GOING TO PRACTICE THIS
REALLY COOL ANCIENT BREATHING TECHNIQUE
I LEARNED FROM A
SHAMAN IN THAILAND.
ALL BETTER.
THEN IT'S CRAZY DOWN THERE,
COLIN.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOUR CHAIR WAS
ALSO A TOILET.
>> WELL.
ANY CHAIR CAN BE.
SERIOUSLY, DAWN, HOW MUCH DO I
OWE IN TAXES?
>> RELAX, COLIN.
I KNOW YOU'RE NERVOUS
BECAUSE
YOUR LAST FINANCIAL ADVISER
KILLED HIMSELF IN HIS JAIL CELL.
DON'T WORRY, I'M COOL, OKAY?
MY SHAMAN TAUGHT ME ANOTHER
ANCIENT TECHNIQUE THAT HELPS ME
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> OH, WHAT IS THAT?
>> ONE MOMENT, PLEASE.
OH, MY GOD.
COLIN.
THERE ARE, LIKE, SO MANY WOMEN
TIED UP BACK THERE!
>> NO, THERE AREN'T.
DAWN ALTMAN, EVERYONE!
THERE'S NO WOMEN BACK THERE.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I
QUIET.
>> IS IT BAD TO SAY THAT I'M
KIND OF HAPPY THAT THE SCHOOLS
SENT THE KIDS ON A CAMPING TRIP
THIS WEEK?
>> I LOVE THEM, BUT I CAN'T
REMEMBER THE LAST TIME WE SAW
FRIENDS TWO DAYS IN A ROW.
ARE RANDY AND TREVOR STILL
COMING?
THEY SAID THEY WENT OUT LAST
NIGHT.
>> HI, HI, SORRY.
>> OH, MY GOD, WE'RE HERE, WE'RE
LATE, I'M SO SORRY, SORRY,
SORRY.
WE MADE IT.
>> UM -- HEY, GUYS.
>> HI, SORRY.
>> SORRY, WE'RE ON HER SCHEDULE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHOSE BABY IS THAT?
>> EXCUSE ME?
IT'S OURS.
>> WAIT.
BUT -- HOW?
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY, BUT GAY
PEOPLE CAN'T HAVE A BABY?
>> YEAH, BUT -- WHERE DID IT
COME FROM?
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> WOW.
YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO TALK LIKE
THAT.
>> THAT IS SO INVASIVE.
>> OKAY, BUT -- WE WERE WITH YOU
LAST NIGHT, AND YOU DID NOT HAVE
A BABY.
>> YEAH, AND YOU GUYS SAID AFTER
DINNER YOU WERE GOING TO A RAVE
CALLED BULGE DUNGEON.
NOW TODAY YOU HAVE A BABY.
>> WHAT WE'RE ASKING IS, HOW DID
THIS HAPPEN?
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY, WHY IS IT
WHEN IT'S US, AN INTERROGATION?
I DON'T ASK YOU WHY YOU'RE POOR.
>> I LOANED YOU $10,000.
>> I THINK WE'RE JUST WONDERING
WHO THE MOTHER IS?
>> WELL, BETWEEN THE TWO OF US,
I'M MORE EMOTIONAL.
AND I LIKE SHOPPING.
SO ME, I THINK.
>> YEAH, BUT I HAVE LONG HAIR,
AND HE IS AN ALCOHOLIC, SO I
GUESS IT'S TWO MOMS, I GUESS?
>> GUYS.
HOW DID YOU GET THIS BABY?
>> OKAY, WE DIDN'T PULL IT OUT
OF YOUR VAGINA, IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE ASKING.
>> PEOPLE THINK THEY CAN ASK GAY
PEOPLE ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
>> YEAH.
WE DON'T ASK YOU GUYS WHOSE BUTT
YOU USE FOR ANAL.
>> OKAY?
I MEAN, I GET -- WHAT'S
CONFUSING US IS YOU NEVER
MENTIONED THAT YOU WERE HAVING A
BABY.
SO THIS FEELS PRETTY SUDDEN.
>> UH, YEAH.
'CAUSE IT WASN'T PLANNED.
SOMETIMES IT'S AN ACCIDENT.
>> HOW DID A GAY COUPLE HAVE A
BABY BY ACCIDENT?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO US SAY,
THAT WE STOLE HER?
>> DID YOU?
>> WELL, WE LIKE TO THINK OF IT
AS SHE STOLE US.
>> SO DOES THAT MEAN YES?
>> WHY ARE YOU CONFUSED?
ENGLISH IS MY EIGHTH LANGUAGE,
AND EVEN I KNOW WHAT THAT
EXPRESSION MEANS.
>> WHAT OTHER LANGUAGES DO YOU
SPEAK?
>> YOU CAN'T ASK ME THAT!
WOW.
THE TRANSPHOBIA IS REAL.
>> WHAT?
I'M SO SORRY, IS ONE OF YOU A
TRANS MAN?
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU CANNOT JUST ASK THAT, GIRL.
BUT NO.
GOD, THEY SHOULD COME UP WITH A
WORD FOR WHEN PEOPLE HAVE A
PHOBIA TOWARDS HOMOS.
>> YOU MEAN HOMOPHOBIA?
>> I LITERALLY SPEAK EIGHT
LANGUAGES AND I'VE NEVER HEARD
THAT WORD.
>> OKAY, YOU NEED TO TELL US
WHICH EIGHT.
>> ENGLISH, FRENCH, AP FRENCH,
NAVI, SIM-LISH, BLACK-ISH,
GROAN-ISH, AND SINGING.
>> WHERE IS YOUR BABY FROM?
>> US!
>> HOW DID YOU GET IT?
>> IF YOU MEAN SHE/THEY, UNTIL
HE TELLS US OTHERWISE.
>> WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
>> THE WAY PEOPLE TALK TO GAY
PEOPLE IS CRAZY.
BY THE WAY, NO ONE HAS
ACKNOWLEDGED THAT IT'S NATIONAL
AAPI MONTH.
>> I THOUGHT MAY IS AAPI MONTH.
>> NO, THIS IS NOT THE AAPI THAT
YOU'RE THINK OF.
IT STANDS FOR --
¶ EVERYBODY EVERYBODY BREATHE I
NEED YA ¶
>> OKAY, OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT, FINE.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE LIKE THIS,
I DON'T WANT IT ANYMORE.
>> SHE'S WAKING UP, OH!
¶ EVERYBODY EVERYBODY PLEASE I
NEED YA ¶
¶ I'M A BABY BITCH ¶
>> WHAT?
HOW OLD IS THIS BABY?
>> YOU CANNOT ASK WOMEN THAT!
>>> ONCE AGAIN, LIZZO.
¶ AH, HERE WE GO
PLAYING WITH MY FEELINGS
PLAYING WITH MY SOUL
BUT I CAN'T LET YOU GO ¶
¶ I JUST WANT TO BE WANTED
AND FEEL BEAUTIFUL ¶
¶ YOU BETTER KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT
AND IF IT AIN'T ME ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME LOVE YOU
DON'T MAKE MY HEART
BEAT OUT OF MY CHEST ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME WANT YOU
IF YOU JUST WANT
SOMETHING ELSE ¶
¶ DON'T YOU -- WITH ME BABY
IF THIS AIN'T IT
JUST TELL ME TONIGHT ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME LOVE YOU
IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND
DON'T WASTE MY TIME ¶
¶ AYYYYY ¶
¶ I'M GOING ON A DRIVE
TO GIVE YOU A COUPLE
MINUTES TO MAKE UP
YOUR MIND ¶
¶ WELL BABY I'LL BE FINE
YEAH
'CAUSE I'M A
BIG FINE WOMAN ¶
¶ DON'T LOSE YOUR
PLACE IN LINE ¶
¶ IF YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT, OH-OH
LET ME BE FREE ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME LOVE YOU
DON'T MAKE MY HEART
BEAT OUT OF MY CHEST ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME WANT YOU
IF YOU JUST WANT
SOMETHING ELSE ¶
¶ DON'T YOU -- WITH ME BABY
IF THIS AIN'T IT
JUST TELL ME TONIGHT ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME LOVE YOU
IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND
DON'T WASTE MY TIME ¶
¶ YOU STARTED SLEEPING ON ME
DON'T YOU SLEEP ON ME ¶
¶ I'M FIGHTING FOR US
BUT YOU JUST WANT TO FIGHT ¶
¶ DON'T DO ME WRONG PLEASE
DON'T PROVE ME RIGHT ¶
¶ IF YOU DON'T WANT ME
BY THE END OF THE NIGHT
I'M MOVING ON WITH MY LIFE ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME LOVE YOU
DON'T MAKE MY HEART
BEAT OUT OF MY CHEST ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME WANT YOU
IF YOU JUST WANT
SOMETHING ELSE ¶
¶ DON'T YOU PLAY
WITH ME BABY
IF THIS AIN'T IT
JUST TELL ME TONIGHT ¶
¶ DON'T MAKE ME
WALK THROUGH THAT DOOR
I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ¶
¶ IF YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND
DON'T WASTE MY TIME
DON'T WASTE MY TIME ¶
ROCK CLIMBING
KAYAKING WITH YOUR SIGNIFICANT
OTHER.
HIKING WITH YOUR INTERRACIAL
FRIENDS.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF DOING ANY
OF THESE ACTIVITIES IN SLOW MOTION,
YOU MAY HAVE HERPES.
AS WE'VE LEARNED FROM VALTREX
COMMERCIALS,
THESE RECREATIONAL
ACTIVITIES ARE THE NUMBER ONE
INDICATORS OF HERPES INFECTION.
MEDICAL SCIENCE DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND WHY THE HERPES VIRUS
CAUSES PEOPLE TO SEEK ACTIVE FUN IN SLOW MOTION,
BUT WE KNOW THAT
IT DOES.
AND THAT MEANS IT'S TIME TO GET
TESTED.
>> ONE NIGHT, I FOUND MYSELF
HAPPILY SALSA DANCING IN SLOW
MOTION WITH MY WHITE HUSBAND.
THAT'S WHEN I KNEW I SHOULD
CONTACT MY DOCTOR.
SURE ENOUGH.
IT WAS HERPES.
>> I WAS EXPERIENCING PAINFUL
GENITAL SORES,
BUT THAT COULD BE
ANYTHING.
ROCK CLIMBING IN SLO-MO, THOUGH,
THAT ONLY MEANS ONE THING,
HERPES.
>> HERPES IS EASILY SPREAD.
JUST LOOK FOR SIGNS LIKE DANCING
IN AN OUTDOOR BEER GARDEN.
STRING LIGHTS.
WINNING A CARNIVAL GAME ON THE
FIRST TRY.
CHEERING IN THE FRONT ROW OF A
FOLK ROCK CONCERT IN A VERY
SMALL SPACE.
HANGING OUT WITH EXACTLY ONE
WHITE PERSON, ONE BLACK PERSON,
ONE ASIAN PERSON, ONE LATIN
PERSON.
IF YOU'RE HANGING OUT IN THE
SLO-MO GROUP, IT MAY BE HARD TO
KNOW WHICH FRIEND IS THE ONE
WITH THE HERPES.
IT'S SIMPLE.
IT'S THE ONE WHO'S HAVING THE
MOST FUN.
WHAT
NOT ALL SLO-MO ACTIVITIES ARE
SIGNS OF HERPES.
IF YOU'RE A WOMAN WEARING A
GENERIC MEN'S FOOTBALL JERSEY AND NO PANTS,
YOUR HUSBAND HAS
ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION.
IF YOUR CHILD IS SHOWING YOU A DRAWING,
YOU'RE CLINICALLY
DEPRESSED.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF IN A BIG
MUSICAL NUMBER IN THE MIDDLE OF AN OFFICE,
YOU HAVE DIABETES.
OR DIARRHEA.
SO BE SMART AND GET TESTED
TODAY.
OH, NO.
KNOW THE SIGNS AND TREAT THE
SYMPTOMS
WITH ONCE-DAILY
HERPE-STOPPER.
WE TRIED TO COME UP WITH A
BETTER NAME, BUT NOBODY COULD
THINK OF ONE.
WELCOME TO WILD FARM FOODS, INC.
REALLY EXCITED TO HAVE A NEW
BATCH OF EMPLOYEES.
>> GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> NOW, HAVE YOU GUYS EVER DONE
AN ICE BREAKER BEFORE?
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
>> PLENTY, LOVE THEM.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
WHAT I'D LOVE TO DO IS GO AROUND
THE ROOM, AND YOU CAN EACH SAY
YOUR NAME AND A FUN FACT ABOUT
YOURSELF.
THEN WE'LL TRY TO REMEMBER
EVERYONE'S NAMES AND FACTS.
I CAN GO FIRST.
I'M CHRIS, AND I LOVE GARDENING.
>> I AM DEREK, AND I HAVE A
TWIN.
>> OH!
>> WOW, OKAY.
>> I AM CASSIDY, AND I WAS A
COMPETITIVE SWIMMER.
>> NICE.
>> WOW.
>> I AM PHILIP, AND I LIKE TO
PAINT.
>> OH, NICE.
>> I AM GREG, AND MY MOM KILLED
MY DAD NAKED ON TV.
>> OKAY, SUSAN?
>> OH.
UM -- I AM SUSAN.
AND I -- FORGOT MINE.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT, JUST TAKE
YOUR TIME.
>> OKAY.
UM -- I'M SUSAN, AND -- I'M A
WOMAN.
>> IT'S OKAY.
SO, CAN ANYONE REMEMBER ANYONE
ELSE'S FACTS?
>> UM -- UH -- CHRIS LOVED
GARDENING, AND PHILIP LIKES TO
PAINT, AND GREG'S MOM KILLED HIS
DAD NAKED ON TV.
>> GOOD MEMORY, YEAH.
>> NICE.
ANYBODY ELSE?
>> UM -- CHRIS LOVES GARDENING,
DEREK HAS A TWIN, I DID
SWIMMING, AND GREG'S DAD KILLED
HIS MOM NAKED ON TV?
>> OH, CLOSE.
MY MOM KILLED MY DAD NAKED ON
TV.
>> OH.
SO SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I THINK I GOT THEM.
CHRIS LOVES GARDENING, DEREK HAS
A TWIN, CASSIDY WAS A SWIMMER,
PHILIP LIKES TO PAINT, MY MOM
KILLED MY DAD NAKED ON TV,
AND -- I KNOW YOU'RE A WOMAN,
BUT REMIND ME OF YOUR NAME?
>> JANET.
>> IT'S SUSAN.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> NOW IN THE GAME, IF YOU
REMEMBER SOMEONE'S NAME, YOU'RE
ALLOWED TO ASK A FOLLOW-UP
QUESTION ABOUT THEIR FACT.
DEREK, WHAT IS YOUR TWIN'S NAME?
>> JARET.
CASSIDY, WHAT SWIMMING STROKE
DID YOU DO?
>> BUTTERFLY.
GREG, WHAT SHOW WAS IT ON?
>> "JACKASS."
PHILIP, WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO
PAINT?
>> VAMPIRES.
SUSAN, WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PART
OF BEING A WOMAN?
>> MY BREASTS.
CASSIDY, WHAT DO YOU SWIM IN?
>> WATER.
>> GREG, WAS IT FUNNY OR SAD?
>> BOTH.
CHRIS, WHAT DO YOU GARDEN?
>> LETTUCES.
DEREK, IS YOUR TWIN IDENTICAL?
>> NO.
AND GREG, WHAT WOULD I TYPE INTO
GOOGLE IF I WANTED TO WATCH WHAT
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
>> OH.
"WOMAN JACKASS PARTY DONKEY"
PORT-A-POTTY WORLD RECORD
RAVEN-SYMONE LESBIAN NOVEMBER
5th 2002.
>> SEARCH ALL OF THOSE?
>> ANY TWO.
>> MAYBE WE JUST WIPE THE SLATE
CLEAN, PLAY SOMETHING ELSE, LIKE
TWO TRUTHS AND A LIE.
FOR EXAMPLE, I'M A CAPRICORN, I
HAVE A DOG, AND I LOVE TO COOK
VEGAN FOOD.
>> OH, I'LL GO.
>> OKAY, SUSAN, JUST GIVE ME TWO
TRUTHS AND A LIE.
>> ONCE I GOT ON THE BUS, AND A
MAN ASKED ME IF I WANTED $20.
I SAID YES.
WHEN I LOOKED DOWN, HE WAS NOT
HOLDING $20.
HE WAS HOLDING --
>> SUSAN --
>> LET ME FINISH.
>> OH, SORRY.
>> HE WAS HOLDING HIS PENIS.
>> I AM SO SORRY.
>> NO, NO.
I LIKED IT.
>> ARE YOU DONE?
>> WELL, THAT WAS JUST MY LIE.
>> THAT WAS PLENTY.
WELL, GANG.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
GOOD TO GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
IT WAS LEGIT A HUGE MISTAKE.
>> I REMEMBERED MY FACT.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
>> GREAT.
SO I THINK --
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING LEFT FOR
TO US DO.
>> WATCH THE VIDEO?
>> YOU KNOW IT!
>> I GOT IT RIGHT HERE.
HOLD ON.
>> WHOA!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> WHAT?
>> NO!
>> HA HA HA!
>> AWW!
>> EWW!
>> RAVEN?
>> YES!
>> OH, NO.
>> NO!
>> WHAT THIS.
>> COOL!
>> NO!
YOU GUYS FOR BRAVING THE
ELEMENTS, SPRINGTIME, LORNE
MICHAELS, THE CREW, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU, GUYS, FOR HAVING ME
BACK.
THIS WAS AMAZING.
HAVE A GREAT NIGHT!