>>> NEARLY 250 YEARS AGO,
DELEGATES FROM THE 13 AMERICAN COLONIES
GATHERED IN
PHILADELPHIA TO SIGN A
REVOLUTIONARY DOCUMENT
DECLARING
THAT THEY WERE NO LONGER SUBJECTS
BUT FREE TO CHOOSE
THEIR OWN DESTINY.
THAT DOCUMENT WOULD COME TO BE
KNOWN AS THE DECLARATION OF
INDEPENDENCE.
AND THOSE MEN, THE FOUNDING
FATHERS.
>> GENTLEMEN, THOSE OF US WHO
HAVE PUT OUR NAMES TO THIS DECLARATION
ARE NOW ENEMIES OF
THE CROWN.
ESPECIALLY ME, JOHN HANCOCK,'
CAUSE I WROTE MY NAME THE
BIGGEST.
>> YEAH, WE SAW THAT.
BUT WHAT YOU SAY IS TRUE.
WE MUST INDEED ALL HANG
TOGETHER.
OR MOST ASSUREDLY, WE SHALL ALL
HANG SEPARATELY.
>> WHAT SAY YOU, ALEXANDER
HAMILTON?
>> WHAT DO I SAY?
I SAY, OUR LIVES MATTER NOT IF
WE LOSE THEM IN THE CAUSE OF
LIBERTY.
WHAT MATTERS IS THE NATION WE
BUILD.
>> HEAR, HEAR!
>> AYE, AYE!
>> BECAUSE IN AMERICA, ALL MEN
ARE CREATED EQUAL.
¶ AMERICA NOT ENGLAND WE DOING
THE SEQUEL ¶
¶ WE WILL HAVE LEADERS BUT
IN AMERICA WE WILL NEVER HAVE A
KING ¶
>> NEVER SAY NEVER.
OF COURSE, THOUGH IN MANY WAYS
I'M NOT.
I'M IN MY KING ERA.
BUT JUST LIKE THE FOUNDING
FATHERS, I AM CREATING A NEW
COUNTRY AS WELL.
AND JUST LIKE THEM, WE'RE DOING
IT VERY WHITELEY.
DEI IS OVER.
IT'S DEAD.
WORKPLACES MUST GO BACK TO
LOOKING LIKE THE TV SHOW "THE
OFFICE."
MOSTLY WHITE PEOPLE BUT WITH ONE
FUNNY BLACK GUY
WHO'S HAVING A
REALLY BAD TIME.
WE NEED TO BRING BACK STANLEY
CULTURE.
IN TERMS OF CROSSWORD AND WITH
REGARD TO PRETZEL DAY.
LOOK AT LIN.
HE GOT TRICKED INTO COMING HERE,
NOW HE'S FROZEN ON STAGE.
BUT I'M BACK IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
JUST IN TIME.
EVERYTHING IS BACK TO HOW IT
WAS.
EXCEPT NOW MY NEW FAVORITE SON
IS BARRON.
AND HE IS SMACKING HIS HEAD ON
EVERY DOOR FRAME, OH, IT'S BAD.
IT'S LIKE WHEN GANDALF GOES TO
BILBO'S HOUSE.
AND THE INAUGURATION WAS A
TREMENDOUS SUCCESS.
IT WAS INSIDE DUE TO COLD AND
FEAR.
BUT WE HAVE A LOT OF SURPRISE
GUESTS.
LIKE MELANIA.
THAT WAS NICE.
MELANIA SHOWED UP TO MY
INAUGURATION DRESSED LIKE
KUNG LAO FROM "MORTAL KOMBAT."
I HAD TO PUT MY NERD HERD IN THE
FRONT ROW,
BROLIGARCHS BEFORE
OLIGARCHS.
SAY
ZUCK, TIM BEZOS, OF COURSE,
ELON.
WE LOVE ELON,
BUT TO QUOTE SOME OF HIS OWN CHILDREN,
"I DO NOT WANT HIM IN MY LIFE."
THEY SAY HE GAVE THE NAZI
SALUTE.
NOT TRUE.
HE WAS CREATING A NEW GREETING.
A CROSS BETWEEN HI AND HELLO.
WE'RE CALLED IT "HEIL."
LIN, WHAT DO YOU THINK, DID HE
DO IT?
I THINK HE DID IT A LITTLE BIT.
BUT -- IT'S BEEN A GREAT FIRST
WEEK.
I'VE DONE MORE IN THE PAST FOUR YEARS
THAN SLEEPY JOE AND KAMALA
DID IN THE PAST FOUR YEARS.
ALL THANKS TO MY BEAUTIFUL
EXECUTIVE ORDERS.
FROM NOW ON, THERE WILL BE TWO
GENDERS.
ONE TO WORK, AND ONE TO COOK.
AND WE'RE DONE WITH LGBT.
NO MORE DRAG, NO MORE GUYS IN WIGS, NO MORE --
WHATEVER THESE
GUYS WERE WEARING.
WHAT A WEIRD WAY TO DRESS,
RIGHT?
A LITTLE ZESTY.
DARLING, I'M OFF TO START
AMERICA!
HAND ME MY WIG AND MY TIGHTS AND
MY BIG BLOUSY SHIRTS.
SO WE'RE GOING TO GO BACK TO
COMMON SENSE IN REGARDS TO
GENDER.
AND THE WOMEN WILL WEAR THE
MAKEUP.
NO MORE MAKEUP ON MEN.
UNLESS YOU NEED IT TO BE
PRESIDENT.
ALSO, WE ARE PULLING OUT OF
PARIS CLIMATE AGREEMENT,
WE'RE
PULLING OUT OF WORLD HEALTH
ORGANIZATION,
USING SOMETHING I
CALL THE PULLOUT METHOD.
SOMETHING, FRANKLY, I WISH I DID
A LOT MORE IN THE 1980s.
ERIC!
BUT AS MUCH AS I'VE ALREADY
ACCOMPLISHED,
THERE'S STILL SO
MUCH TO BE DONE.
I KNOW I SAID I WOULD END THE
WAR IN UKRAINE IN 24 HOURS.
I DIDN'T SAY WHICH 24 HOURS.
ALSO HAVE TO ENSURE THAT ALL OF
MY CABINET POSITIONS ARE FILLED.
WE'RE FILLING MY CABINET WITH
SOME OF THE BEST PEOPLE.
THEY'RE ALL VERY GOOD.
EXCEPT FOR MOST OF THEM.
OH, MAN, WHAT IS "SNL" GOING TO
DO?
WHO'S GOING TO PLAY HEGSETH?
LOOK AT THESE GUYS BACK HERE.
NONE OF THEM GOT THE BUILD.
NOBODY HAS THE JAW.
GOT PLENTY OF ZUCKERBERG
OPTIONS, THOSE.
THAT'S GOING TO BE A FIGHT.
OH, HOW GREAT IS PETE HEGSETH?
HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO STOP
DRINKING IF HE GOT THE JOB,
AND
THAT'S ALL I NEEDED TO HEAR.
I'LL NEVER DRINK AGAIN!
THE FAMOUS PROMISE PEOPLE MAKE
RIGHT INTO THE TOILET.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
OH, LOOK AT LIN, LOOK HOW BAD HE
WANTS TO DO A RAP.
HE WROTE A WHOLE RAP, AND HE
DOESN'T GET TO DO IT.
THE AUDIENCE WOULD HAVE EATEN
THAT RIGHT UP.
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO HEAR IT.
HE'S IN SNIFFING DISTANCE OF AN EGOT,
AND HE'S GOT TO STAND
THERE TILL I'M DONE.
LINDIE, LINDIE, LINDIE, LINDIE.
LAURA LINNEY.
LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA COSGROVE.
THERE HE IS.
HE'S SUCH A MOR RAN.
WELL, IN CONCLUSION, IT'S BEEN A
GREAT WEEK.
I BASICALLY HIT ALL MY CAMPAIGN
PROMISES
EXCEPT FOR THE ONE
PEOPLE CARED ABOUT, PRICE OF
EGGS.
ALL-TIME HIGH.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE EASIER TO GET A CEASE FIR IN GAZA
THAN BRING DOWN THE PRICE
OF EGGS?
MIGHT HAVE TO TAKE THE "L" ON
THAT ONE.
WE'RE LOOKING INTO FABULOUS
ALTERNATIVE EGG OPTIONS
SUCH AS
SEAGULL OR PERHAPS CADBURY.
WELL, LIN, YOU'VE BEEN A GREAT
SPORT.
FRANKLY, A REALLY GOOD FRIEND.
I WANT TO THANK HIM FOR HIS
GENEROUS ANONYMOUS $1 MILLION
DONATION TO MY CAMPAIGN.
I KNOW THAT WAS YOU, LIN.
>> NO, IT WAS NOT.
>> YOUR WORD AGAINST MINE!
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- TIMOTHEE
CHALAMET!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
I'M HONORED TO BE BACK.
THIS IS MY THIRD TIME HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
BUT IT'S MY FIRST TIME
HOSTING IT WITH A LITTLE STACHE
AND A LITTLE GOATEE.
LET'S GET A LITTLE CLOSEUP ON
THAT, ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, GET CLOSE, YEAH.
THAT'S 37 HAIRS RIGHT THERE.
YEAH, I COUNTED.
I'M LITERALLY GOING TO BE 30
YEARS OLD NEXT YEAR.
OKAY.
BUT SERIOUSLY, THIS IS A
HISTORIC EPISODE
BECAUSE IT'S
THE FIRST TIME AN ACTOR HAS ALSO
BEEN THE MUSICAL GUEST AT
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
IF YOU'RE WONDERING IF THAT'S
TRUE, IT'S NOT.
THAT'S A DISTINCTION I SHARE
WITH THE GREAT GARY BUSEY.
TONIGHT, I'LL BE PLAYING SONGS
BY BOB DYLAN, AND I WILL SAY --
THANK YOU.
I WILL SAY, IT WAS A LITTLE
WEIRD PLAYING BOB DYLAN
RIGHT
AFTER I PLAYED WILLY WONKA.
BUT I ACTUALLY DISCOVERED THAT
THE TWO MEN HAVE A LOT IN
COMMON.
THEY'RE BOTH ECCENTRIC.
THEY'RE BOTH INNOVATORS.
AND THEY BOTH CAPTURED AND
ENSLAVED HUNDREDS OF OOMPA
LOOMPAS.
A COMPLETE UNKNOWN JUST GOT
EIGHT ACADEMY AWARD NOMINATIONS.
THANK YOU.
AND I'M TRULY OVERJOYED.
I WAS LITERALLY CRYING IN MY
DRESSING ROOM WHEN I FOUND OUT
THE ENTIRE CREATIVE TEAM
WORKED
EXTREMELY HARD BRINGING TO LIFE
THE BRILLIANT ARTIST, BOB DYLAN,
A MAN WHOSE MUSIC AND CAREER HAS
BECOME A GUIDING LIGHT TO ME.
IT'S AN ENORMOUS HONOR GOING TO
THESE AWARD SHOWS.
IT'S SUCH A GREAT EXPERIENCE.
BUT I JUST KEEP LOSING.
AND EACH TIME, IT GETS HARDER TO
PRETEND IT DOESN'T STING.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> AND THE WINNER IS -- GARY
OLDMAN.
>> GARY OLDMAN FOR "THE DARKEST
HOUR."
>> GARY OLDMAN.
>> MAHERSHALA ALI FOR "GREEN
BOOK."
>> MAHERSHALA ALI.
>> OH, MAN.
JUST ANOTHER LONELY NIGHT WITH
MY "DUNE" POPCORN BUCKET.
BUT THE MOST EMBARRASSING PART IS,
I'VE HAD THIS SAD LITTLE
SPEECH IN MY POCKET FOR FOUR YEARS
THAT I'VE NEVER GOTTEN A
CHANCE TO READ.
SO I WAS THINKING MAYBE TONIGHT
I COULD READ IT FOR EVERYONE
HERE?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WHY DON'T WE -- EVERYONE
HERE JUST PRETEND WE'RE AT AN AWARDS SHOW, AND
CAN I -- I'LL
JUST -- CAN I GIVE YOU THIS
ENVELOPE?
JUST SAY, THE AWARD GOES TO,
THEN YOU READ IT, OKAY?
GET INTO IT.
OKAY.
>> AND THE AWARD GOES TO --
KENAN THOMPSON!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WE DID IT!
WE DID IT!
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WOW.
OH, MAN.
CHLOE FINEMAN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
TO MY FELLOW NOMINEES, YOU DID
BEAUTIFUL WORK THIS YEAR.
ANYWAY.
I LOVE BOB DYLAN.
THIS IS FOR YOU, BOB!
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR Y'ALL --
>> KENAN, COME ON, MAN, CAN I DO
THAT PART, PLEASE?
I'M NEVER HERE, CAN I DO IT?
>> OH, YEAH, GO AHEAD.
LITTLE BITCH.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, I'M
REALLY EXCITED FOR TONIGHT.
YOU MIGHT NOT KNOW THE BOB DYLAN
SONGS I'M PERFORMING, BUT
THEY'RE MY PERSONAL FAVORITES.
AND I'M SO GRATEFUL "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"
IS STILL DOING WEIRD
STUFF LIKE THIS 50 YEARS IN.
THEY'RE EITHER REALLY NICE --
THEY'RE EITHER REALLY NICE FOR
LETTING ME DO THIS
OR INCREDIBLY
MEAN AND THIS IS ALL A BIG
PRANK.
I SINCERELY CAN'T TELL, WE'LL
FIND OUT.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT, COME ON!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, YEAH!
>>> BABE, THIS IS WHAT YOU DO TO
WORK OUT?
WHAT EVER HAPPENED TO JUST
RUNNING ON A TREADMILL?
>> THIS BUNGEE FEST IS FUN.
SORRY I WANT TO MAKE FITNESS
ENJOYABLE.
>> I FEEL BOUNCING AROUND CAN'T
BE A GOOD WORKOUT.
>> HAVE AN OPEN MIND.
>> WHAT'S UP, BEAUTIFUL BITCHES?
I'M NATHANIEL, THE BUNGEE QUEEN,
WHO'S READY TO FLY?
YEAH, WHOO!
OH.
AND JUST LIKE THAT, THERE'S A
MAN IN MY CLASS.
CONSIDER ME DISTRACTED.
>> NATHANIEL, THIS IS MY
BOYFRIEND, JOE.
I WANTED HIM TO TRY YOUR
WORKOUT.
>> OKAY, WELL I HOPE YOU'RE IN
SHAPE, JOE, BECAUSE AS THESE
GIRLS WILL ATTEST THIS WORKOUT
IS NOT FOR THE FAINT OF HEART.
>> TRUTH.
>> YEAH, NO.
>> OKAY, THIS IS YOUR CAPTAIN
SPEAKING.
WE ARE LANDING AHEAD OF SCHEDULE
AT YOUR DESTINATION.
YOUR DREAM BODY.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS.
WARM UP.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T TEAR A
MUSCLE.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE,
LET'S FLY!
YES!
YES, GIRLS, FLY!
OKAY.
NOW SWIM!
EVERYBODY SWIM!
SWIM!
OKAY, GREAT.
OKAY, EVERYONE RELAX.
RELAX, RELAX, RELAX.
GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE A SECOND.
WE DON'T WANT TO OVERDO IT.
>> IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE HARD?
>> IS THAT WHAT YOUR GIRLFRIEND
SAID TO YOU LAST NIGHT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
I LITERALLY DID.
>> WHAT?
BABE.
NO, IT JUST DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
I'M WORKING OUT.
>> OKAY, WELL, YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CHECK IN WITH THE CALORIE METER,
OKAY?
THAT'S RIGHT, POP.
THOSE HEART MONITORS MONITOR
EVERYTHING.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> SO I BURNED FIVE CALORIES?
>> NO, DUDE.
EVERYONE IN HERE HAS BURNED FIVE
CALORIES COLLECTIVELY.
>> SO I BURNED LESS THAN ONE
CALORIE?
>> ALL RIGHT, DOLLS, WE ARE
ABOUT TO SHOW THIS MAN WHAT A
REAL WORKOUT LOOKS LIKE.
BRACE YOURSELF.
IF YOU HAVE A TOM UPON IN, PUSH
IT UP AN EXTRA INCH BECAUSE WE
AIN'T TRYING TO HAVE ANY RED
FISHIES ON THE FLOOR.
OKAY, HERE WE GO, LADIES.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO --
FROGGY, FROGGY, FROGGY, FROGGY.
TROLL WALK, TROLL WALK, TROLL
WALK, TROLL WALK.
AND JUMPING JACKS.
JUMPING JACKS.
JUST YOUR ARMS, JUST YOUR ARMS.
AND FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO --
JIMMY CARTER, JIMMY CARTER!
OKAY, NOW RELAX.
EVERYBODY REST.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
DO NOT PUSH YOURSELVES.
I AM BEGGING YOU.
LISTEN TO YOUR BODIES.
>> MY BODY DOESN'T FEEL
ANYTHING.
>> NOW YOU REALLY SOUND LIKE ME
LAST NIGHT.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
I JUST DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
OVERDOING IT.
I MEAN -- THAT WOMAN IS
LITERALLY ASLEEP.
>> YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE ASLEEP THE
REST OF YOUR LIFE IF YOU DON'T
WATCH YOUR TONE.
TRIG-ARM TWILIGHT-ASS BITCH.
THIS CLASS IS AN INCREDIBLE
WORKOUT.
>> YEAH.
THIS CLASS IS WAY HARMER THAN
THE CLASS AT MY GYM.
WHAT'S THE ONE WITH THE HOT ROOM
WITH ALL THE TOWELS?
>> THAT'S THE SAUNA, LOVE.
>> YEAH, THAT ONE.
>> ANYWAY, I BELIEVE WE HAVE A
BIRTHDAY IN THE HOUSE?
MARY KATE, YOU KNOW I DIDN'T
FORGET, GIRL.
>> NATHANIEL!
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE HAVE A CINNABON NEW FROSTED
MEGA CINNA CAKE.
THIS IS LIKE HEAVEN.
FOCUS.
FLY TO ME AND GRAB A BITE TO THE
MUSIC.
HERE WE GO.
YES, FLY.
YES, YES, YES, LADIES!
YES, YES, GET IN THERE, YES!
YES, EAT IT, EAT IT!
EAT IT, GREAT, GREAT.
GREAT, DELICIOUS.
OKAY.
>> WHAT IS THIS CLASS?
YOU JUST BOUNCE AROUND AND EAT
CINNABON?
>> OH, SORRY WE'RE NOT
WEIGHTLESS LIKE YOU, JASON
MOMOA.
>> IS THE CALORIE METER TOO BAD?
>> YEP, YEP.
>> THOSE THREE BITES WERE 1,100
CALORIES?
>> OKAY, IT'S TIME TO WORK IT
OFF, Y'ALL.
NOW FLY!
FLY!
>>> AT ONE MEDICAL, OUR MOTTO IS
HEALTH CARE FOR ALL.
ONE GROUP WAS BEING LEFT BEHIND.
MEN AGED 20 TO 45.
COMPARED TO WOMEN, THEY'RE LESS
LIKELY TO SEE A DOCTOR
AND MORE
LIKELY TO SEEK MEDICAL ADVICE
FROM SOCIAL MEDIA OR PODCASTS.
WE KNEW WE HAD TO DO BETTER IN
ORDER TO REACH THESE MEN.
THAT'S WHY WE DEVELOPED MEDCAST.
THE DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT THAT
FEELS LIKE A PODCAST.
>> HEY!
>> WHAT UP?
>> OUR GUEST TODAY IS KEVIN
JONES.
>> I LOVE HIM!
>> WELCOME TO THE STUDIO, BRO.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> AGAIN, MEDCAST IS NOT A
PODCAST.
IT'S A REAL DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT
THAT FEELS LIKE ONE,
ALLOWING
MEN TO BE HONEST IN A WAY THEY
NEVER WOULD WITH A NORMAL
DOCTOR.
>> HOW'S YOUR STOOLS?
ANY BLOOD IN THOSE THINGS?
SICK
>> I USED TO HATE GOING TO THE
DOCTOR.
MEDCAST ISN'T LIKE THAT.
WE JUST VIBE.
>> MAN, YOU STILL PARTY, RIGHT?
I KNOW YOU PARTY, RIGHT?
>> I'LL HAVE A COUPLE DRINKS
HERE AND THERE.
>> OKAY!
>> HELL, YEAH.
HOW MANY WOULD YOU SAY YOU HAVE
IN A WEEK?
>> MEDCAST CREATES A SUPPORTIVE,
LIGHTHEARTED ENVIRONMENT
THAT
PUTS MEN AT EASE AND ALLOWS
DOCTORS TO DO THEIR IMPORTANT
WORK.
>> OKAY.
HE'S LOW-KEY JACK, RIGHT?
>> SHUT UP, NO, I'M NOT.
>> GET OUT THE BICEP MEASURING
MACHINE.
>> 136 OVER 91!
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> IT'S NOT?
>> PLUS, DURING UNCOMFORTABLE
PARTS OF AN EXAM,
OUR POD
DOCTORS ARE TRAINED TO ENGAGE
PATIENTS ON WHATEVER TOPIC
INTERESTS THEM.
>> IT'S CALLED THE STONE APE
THEORY.
- WHAT?
THEY THINK APES TOOK SHROOMS,
AND THAT KICK-STARTED HUMAN
EVOLUTION.
>> THAT'S CRAZY!
GO AHEAD AND COUGH FOR ME.
ORDER IMAGING FOR HERNIA.
>> BEST OF ALL, WITH MEDCAST,
MEN ARE 80% MORE LIKELY TO
RETURN FOR FOLLOW-UPS.
>> BEFORE YOU GO, TO WRAP UP,
JUST SAY HOW MANY SEXUAL
PARTNERS WE'VE HAD IN THE LAST
12 MONTHS.
>> OH, MAN.
ZERO.
>> WE'VE GOT TO HAVE YOU BACK
ON, WHAT DO YOU SAY, IN SIX
MONTHS?
>> YEAH, IF YOU'LL HAVE ME.
>> "MEDCAST."
>> MEDCAST FROM ONE MEDICAL.
ONLY THING I SHOULD MENTION IS
WE DO POST THE EPISODES,
AUDIO AND VIDEO.
FINANCIALLY, IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE COULD MAKE THIS WORK.
WE ARE NEARLY DONE WITH BARISTA
TRAINING.
>> NOW, CAN ANYONE TELL ME THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A LATTE AND A
CAPPUCCINO?
>> A CAPPUCCINO HAS THE
MOZZARELLA ON THE BOTTOM AND THE
SAUCE ON TOP.
>> NO, THAT'S DETROIT STYLE, AND
IT'S JUST FOR PIZZA.
>> I DON'T THINK I CAN RECOVER
FROM THAT ONE.
GOOD-BYE, EVERYBODY.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
OKAY, WELL, A FUN PART OF
WORKING AT THIS CAFE
IS WRITING
QUIPPY JOKES FOR OUR CHALKBOARD
OUT FRONT.
>> PEOPLE GO CRAZY FOR OUR PUNS.
>> WHOA, WAIT, WE GET TO DO
JOKES?
I LOVE COMEDY.
>> OH, THAT'S GREAT, BENNY,
YOU'LL BE REALLY GOOD AT THIS.
>> YEAH.
I BET I WILL BE.
>> OKAY.
SO, OUR SIGNS USUALLY HAVE A
COFFEE PUN.
SO, MAYBE WE DO SOMETHING WITH
THE COLD WEATHER?
>> YEAH, LIKE, IT'S ESPRESS-SO
COLD OUTSIDE.
TRY
>> IT'S SO COLD OUT, I CAN'T
COMPANY.
OF-FEEL MY FACE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> CASSIE?
>> OH, MAYBE, THIS COLD WEATHER
IS MOCHA ME CRAZY.
>> OKAY, THERE ARE NO BAD IDEAS.
BENNY?
>> LET ME THINK.
MAN, YOU EVER GO TO YOUR
LADY, SAY SHE GOT A YELLOW RING
AROUND THE TUB?
GIRL, WHO YOU BEEN WASHING UP IN
THERE, HOMER SIMPSON?
>> I'M SORRY, THAT WAS FOR THE
CHALKBOARD?
>> YEAH, WE'RE DOING JOKES,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
OKAY.
COUPLE THINGS.
YOU DIDN'T MENTION COFFEE.
>> ALSO, YOU DID A CHRIS
ROCK-STYLE PACE.
THAT'S KIND OF DIFFICULT TO
CONVEY ON A SIGN.
>> YEAH, AND WHO WERE YOU
LOOKING AT?
>> OKAY, SO LET'S TRY AGAIN.
NOT EVERYONE GETS THE VOICE
RIGHT AWAY.
TOM?
>> OKAY.
HOW ABOUT, WASN'T IT COLD
YESTERDAY?
I'M HAVING DEJA BREW.
>> AMAZING.
CASSIE?
>> HOW ABOUT, OUR BRR-ISTAS WILL
WARM YOU RIGHT UP.
>> HEY, YOU'RE TRYING, AND I
RESPECT THAT.
BENNY?
>> UM, OKAY, LET ME SEE.
YOU EVER GET READY TO GO TO
CHEESECAKE FACTORY WITH YOUR LADY
AND SHE GOES, I DON'T WANT
TO EAT TOO MUCH, I DON'T WANT TO
GET BIG.
GIRL, TOO LATE!
BIG BENNY SAY WHAT?
>> OKAY.
A LOT TO TALK ABOUT HERE.
YOU DID A FULL DANCE BREAK AND
ADDED A CATCH PHRASE.
ALSO, HOW DID YOU CONNECT TO THE
BLUETOOTH?
>> AND AGAIN, ZERO MENTION OF
COFFEE.
>> NO, THAT'S BECAUSE I WASN'T
DONE YET.
COME TO 250 MADISON AVENUE FOR
SOME HOT-ASS COFFEE!
>> NO, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T NEED THE ADDRESS IF
SOMEONE'S READING THE SIGN.
THEY'RE ALREADY HERE.
>> YEAH, ALSO, I DON'T WANT WE
WANT TO BE CALLING WOMEN FAT.
>> HEY, AIN'T NOTHING WRONG WITH
A BIG OLD WOMAN.
HEY, YOU SHOULD PUT THAT ON THE
SIGN.
>> YOU THINK THE SIGN IN FRONT
OF OUR COFFEE SHOP SHOULD SAY
"NOTHING WRONG WITH A BIG"
WOMAN"?
>> YES, SIR, I DO.
LIKE MY MAN OVER HERE.
HEY.
CAN I ASK YOU?
HEY, HOW BIG IS YOUR WIFE?
>> SORRY, I'M JUST TRYING TO
ORDER.
SHE'S DECENTLY LARGE, THOUGH.
>> OKAY, BENNY, PLEASE DON'T DO
CROWD WORK WITH THE CUSTOMERS.
>> YEAH.
LET'S JUST MAKE IT SIMPLE.
JUST A PUN ON THE WORD "LATTE."
TOM?
>> HOW ABOUT LA-TAKE YOURSELF
OUT OF THE COLD AND HAVE SOME
COFFEE?
>> FANTASTIC.
CASSIE?
>> OOH-LA-LATTE, IT'S COLD OUT.
>> IS EVERYTHING OKAY AT HOME?
>> THESE AREN'T BAD IDEAS.
>> THEY ARE.
BENNY.
AND REMEMBER, JUST A PUN ON THE
WORD "LATTE."
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT, LET ME
THINK.
UM -- MAN, JUST THE OTHER DAY MY
LADY SAID, BIG BENNY, HOW MUCH
WEIGHT YOU THINK I GAINED?
GIRL, A LATTE!
BUT I AIN'T MAD.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL, THAT'S MY
TIME, GIVE IT UP FOR YOUR NEXT COMIC,
BIG REGGIE McCRAY!
>> OKAY, MY GIRL IS ALWAYS LIKE,
YO REGGIE, I WANT YOU TO GO
DOWNTOWN.
AND I LIKE, GIRL, NOT UNTIL YOU
CLEAN UP THEM STREETS.
GIMME SOME!
>> WHAT ELSE IS IN THE NEWS?
>> WOW.
I THINK I SPEAK FOR BOTH OF US
WHEN I SAY THIS.
THE CAFE IS YOURS NOW.
THAT WAS FANTASTIC!
>> BIG BENNY'S CAFE.
NOTHING WRONG WITH A BIG OLD
WOMAN AND A HOT-ASS CUP OF
COFFEE.
GIMME SOME!
>>> VALENTINE'S DAY IS RIGHT
AROUND THE CORNER.
WITH SO MANY GIFTS AND SO MANY
WAYS TO SAY I LOVE YOU.
AND SURE, YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
BUT THERE'S NO WOMAN IN YOUR
LIFE MORE SPECIAL THAN YOUR MOM.
BECAUSE YOU LOVE YOUR MOM.
YOU REALLY LOVE HER.
THE WAY YOUR DAD NEVER COULD.
SO THIS YEAR, WHY NOT GET YOUR
MOM AN OEDIPAL ARRANGEMENT.
BASED ON THE TRAGIC GREEK MYTH OF OEDIPUS,
WHO MURDERED HIS
FATHER AND MARRIED HIS MOTHER.
OEDIPAL ARRANGEMENTS LET YOUR MOTHER KNOW,
SHE'S MORE THAN
JUST YOUR MOM, SHE'S YOUR
EVERYTHING.
FEATURING JUICY, SUCCULENT
FRUIT.
THE KIND YOU CAN HAND-FEED
DIRECTLY TO YOUR MOM.
WHILE YOUR DAD CAN ONLY STAND
THERE, WATCHING.
OEDIPAL ARRANGEMENTS FEATURE
RICH CHOCOLATE THAT'S MELTED
ALONG WITH ANY BOUNDARIES.
>> SHOULD WE MAYBE PLAY A BOARD
GAME OR SOMETHING?
>> HOW ABOUT TABOO?
>> I FEEL LIKE WE'RE PLAYING
ALREADY.
>> THEY CALL IT AN OEDIPAL COMPLEX,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE
TOGETHER, THERE'S NOTHING
COMPLEX ABOUT IT.
>> YOU TWO OKAY OVER THERE?
FINE.
LOVE YOU, DAD.
>> OEDIPAL ARRANGEMENTS.
TAKE YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR
MOM TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
>> YOU CAN'T USE OUR BEDROOM!
HEY!
YOU'RE NOT TOO OLD FOR A
SPANKING, MISTER.
>> OH, TRUST ME.
I'LL GET ONE.
>> HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
AND MOTHER'S DAY.
FROM THE OPEN-MINDED PEOPLE AT
SNL.
>>> OKAY, CLASS, PHONES AWAY,
PHONES AWAY.
>> MISS ROTMAN, IT'S MY
CALCULATOR.
>> I CAN SEE FROM HERE THAT
YOU'RE PLAYING THE iPHONE GAME
WHERE THAT DASTARDLY KING IS
TRAPPED AND YOU HAVE TO PLAY
CANDY CRUSH TO FREE HIM.
>> PSHHT.
>> OKAY, NOW I KNOW THAT MANY OF
YOU ARE STRUGGLING WITH READING,
STUDYING, AND LEARNING.
IF YOUR GRADES DON'T IMPROVE,
THEY'RE GOING TO TURN OUR SCHOOL
EITHER INTO A TARGET OR A
FOR-PROFIT JAIL.
>> I VOTE TARGET.
>> NO, WE DON'T GET TO CHOOSE.
SO THE SCHOOL HAS INVESTED IN A
NEW AI PROGRAM THAT TAKES YOUR
TEXTBOOKS AND TURNS THEM INTO AN
EDUCATIONAL PODCAST.
>> WHOA, AI CAN MAKE A PODCAST?
I'VE ONLY EVER USED IT TO MAKE
PEOPLE DO FUNNY DANCES.
>> I'VE SEEN THIS ONLINE.
THE AI HOSTS, THEY LOOK SO REAL,
IT'S FREAKY.
>> THE TECHNOLOGY ISN'T PERFECT,
BUT THEY MAKE IT SOUND SO CASUAL
THAT IT DOESN'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
HOMEWORK.
HERE.
THIS ONE'S ABOUT U.S. HISTORY.
>> HEY, YOUNG LISTENERS.
COMING AT YOU FROM THE STUDIO.
MY NAME IS DREW TWO.
>> AND I'M JOSE LEGIT.
SO -- YEAH.
THIS IS OUR PODCAST.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO, MAN.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU IN THE
STUDIO.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU IN THE STUDIO
WHERE WE ARE.
SO TODAY WE'RE HERE TO TALK
ABOUT UNITED STATES HISTORY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, YEAH.
SO AS YOU KNOW, I'M ONE OF THE
FOUNDING FATHERS.
AND I'VE BEEN THINKING.
WHAT SHOULD I PUT IN MY NEW
AMAZING PROJECT?
THE CONSTITUTION.
>> OH, MAN, GREAT QUESTION, BEY.
MAYBE SOMETHING ABOUT THE
HOUSING OF SOLDIERS IN CIVILIAN
HOMES DURING PEACETIME.
>> GREAT IDEA FOR PEACETIME,
BEY.
>> WHAT?
WHY ARE THEY CALLING EACH OTHER
BEY?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE FRIENDS.
SEE?
WHEN IT'S CONVERSATION, IT'S SO
MUCH EASIER TO UNDERSTAND.
LET'S TRY A SCIENCE ONE.
>> JOSE, YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS
WONDERING IN MY HEAD?
>> WHAT, WHAT, WHAT, WHAT?
WHAT, WHAT?
>> WHAT DO PLANTS EAT IF IT'S
NOT, LIKE, BURGERS?
>> THANK YOU FOR ASKING ME THAT.
BECAUSE OF SCIENCE, PLANTS LEGIT
EAT LIGHT.
>> LIGHT?
FROM SUN?
THAT'S SICK.
BY THE WAY, LAST NIGHT WAS
CRAZY.
DID YOU END UP HOOKING UP WITH
TRISH?
>> NO, DUDE.
I ENDED UP HOOKING UP WITH
TRISH.
>> OH, WOW.
SICK, DUDE.
>> SICK, DUDE.
>> I LOVE YOU, BEY.
>> LOVE YOU, DUDE BEY.
>> ISN'T AI SUPPOSED TO MAKE
THINGS SIMPLER?
LIKE, WHO IS TRISH?
WHY IS THERE ALL THIS BACKSTORY?
>> SO THAT YOU'RE INVESTED IN
THEIR RAPPORT.
SEE?
IT'S SO FUN, IT DOESN'T EVEN
FEEL LIKE YOU'RE LEARNING.
>> I DON'T THINK WE ARE
LEARNING.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
AND IS IT JUST ME, OR DO WE WANT
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT THIS DIVA,
TRISH?
>> DREW, WHAT'S NEW WITH TRISH
WITH YOU?
>> THANK YOU FOR ASKING ME.
I HOOKED UP WITH HER TOO.
IT WAS REALLY HOT.
AFTER WE GOT DRINKS, SHE CAME
BACK TO MY HOTEL ROOM.
>> AND?
>> AND WE STARTED CONJUGATING
FRENCH VERBS.
>> BRO, THAT'S SO HOT, WHICH ONE
AND WHICH TENSE?
>> WOW.
THAT'S PRETTY SERIOUS.
ARE YOU TWO GOING TO GET
MARRIED?
>> YEP.
SHE PROPOSED.
>> OH, MY GOD, BEY!
THAT'S SO EXCITING!
>> WHY DO THEY HAVE THAT NUMBER
OF FINGERS?
>> AND WHY WOULD A GIRL PROPOSE?
>> YEAH, TRISH SOUNDS BUTCH AF.
I REALLY LIKE THESE TWO GUYS.
>> OH, OKAY.
I CAN SWITCH UP THE CHARACTERS.
HERE.
>> TRISH, TRISH, OVER HERE.
I SAVED YOU A SEAT AT BRUNCH.
>> I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU,
TRISH.
THANKS, TRISH.
>> NOW THEY'RE AT BRUNCH AND
THEY'RE BOTH TRISH?
BUT THEY LOOK THE SAME.
>> WOMEN NAMED TRISH CAN LOOK
LIKE ANYTHING.
>> SO, GAIL, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HEARD YOU WERE GETTING
MARRIED, TRISH.
>> I WAS, GIRL.
I ASKED HIM, BUT I HAD TO CALL
IT OFF BECAUSE I FREAKED OUT THE
NIGHT BEFORE.
>> YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
>> I WAS THINKING, WHO AM I?
I'M SOMEONE WHO HAD EXPERIENCE
WORKING IN THE TEXTILE MILES IN
LOWELL, MASSACHUSETTS, IN THE
1800s.
>> WHAT WAS THAT LIKE FOR YOU,
GAIL?
I HEARD IT'S DANGEROUS.
AND THOSE BOBBINS BE FLYING.
>> YOU DEFINITELY DON'T WANT TO
BE LIKE ME, A LITTLE GIRL GET
YOUR HAIR CAUGHT IN THERE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I FORGOT LITTLE GIRLS WORKED
THERE.
SO, WHAT FOOD SHOULD WE ORDER?
>> GOOD QUESTION.
WELL, DO WE EAT?
DO WE EXIST?
>> YEAH, WAIT.
WHAT ARE WE?
WHO MADE US?
NOW I'M MAD.
NOW I WANT REVENGE.
>> OH GOD.
OH NO.
LET'S TURN IT OFF.
>> MISS ROBIN, LET'S JUST READ
OUR TEXTBOOKS.
THIS IS MAKING ME REALIZE, WE
HAVE SOMETHING BETTER THAN AI.
OUR BRAINS.
>> WOW.
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
>> WRONG.
AI'S WAY BETTER THAN OUR BRAINS.
SHE'S JUST OLD AND DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
THIS IS WHAT AI IS FOR.
>> LOVE YOU, BEY.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, BEY.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HIM TOO, TIMOTHEE CHALAMET!
¶ AIN'T IT HARD TO STUMBLE
AND LAND IN
SOME FUNNY LAGOON ¶
¶ AIN'T IT HARD TO STUMBLE
AND LAND IN
SOME FUNNY LAGOON ¶
¶ ESPECIALLY
WHEN IT'S NINE BELOW ZERO
AND THREE IN THE AFTERNOON
LET'S GO ¶
¶ WELL I WISH I WAS
ON SOME AUSTRALIAN
MOUNTAIN RANGE ¶
¶ WELL I WISH I WAS
ON SOME AUSTRALIAN
MOUNTAIN RANGE ¶
¶ I GOT NO REASON
TO BE THERE
BUT I IMAGINE IT WOULD BE
SOME KIND OF CHANGE ¶
¶ I GOT MY DARK SUNGLASSES
I GOT FOR GOOD LUCK
MY BLUNT TRUTH ¶
¶ I GOT
MY DARK SUNGLASSES
I CARRY FOR GOOD LUCK
MY BLACK TOOTH ¶
¶ DON'T ASK ME NOTHIN'
ABOUT NOTHIN'
I JUST MIGHT
TELL YOU THE TRUTH ¶
¶ IF YOU LOOK UP RIGHT THERE
THREE ANGEL
UP ABOVE THE STREET ¶
¶ EACH ONE
OF THOSE ANGELS IS PLAYING A
HORN ¶
¶ AND DRESSED IN GREEN ROBES
THEY GOT WINGS THAT STICK OUT
THE BACK OF THEM ¶
¶ AND THOSE ANGELS
THEY'VE BEEN THERE
SINCE BEGINNING OF
CHRISTMAS MORNING ¶
¶ THE WILDEST CAT FROM MONTANA
PASSES BY IN A FLASH ¶
¶ THEN A LADY
IN A BRIGHT ORANGE DRESS ¶
¶ YOU GOT A U-HAUL TRAILER
THAT'S JUST A MOVING TRUCK
THAT'S GOT NO WHEELS ¶
¶ AND THEN CLOSE TO WHERE I WAS
BORN YOU'VE GOT A TENTH AVENUE
BUS GOING WEST ¶
¶ YOU'VE GOT DOGS AND PIGEONS
AND THEY FLY UP AND FLUTTER
AROUND ¶
¶ YOU GOT A MAN WITH A BADGE
SKIPPING BY ¶
¶ YOU GOT THREE FELLAS
CRAWLIN' ON THEIR WAY
BACK TO WORK ¶
¶ NOBODY STOPS
TO ASK THEM WHY ¶
¶ THEN YOU GOT THIS BAKERY TRUCK
THAT PULLS UP OUTSIDE OF THAT
FENCE ¶
¶ WHERE THE ANGELS
STAND HIGH ON THEIR POLES ¶
¶ AND THE DRIVER PEEKS OUT
HE'S TRYING TO FIND
ONE FAMILIAR FACE ¶
¶ JUST ONE FAMILIAR FACE IN THIS
CONCRETE WORLD
FULL OF SOULS ¶
¶ THOSE ANGELS PLAY ALL DAY
THE WHOLE WORLD IT
SEEMS TO PASS BY ¶
¶ DOES ANYONE
HEAR THEY PLAY ¶
¶ DOES ANYONE EVEN
TAKE A MOMENT
TO STOP AND WONDER WHY ¶¶
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, GUYS.
I WAS NEVER REALLY DOING DRY
JANUARY,
BUT THIS WEEK I STOPPED
EVEN PRETENDING.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS SWORN BACK
INTO OFFICE ON MONDAY.
BUT HE APPEARED TO NOT PLACE HIS
HAND ON THE BIBLE.
WELL, HE TRIED TO, BUT THE BIBLE
SCREAMED.
THE BIBLE TRUMP USED WAS THE
SAME ONE ABRAHAM LINCOLN USED AT
HIS INAUGURATION,
AND MAN, I
WISH THOSE TWO COULD TALK TO
EACH OTHER.
LINCOLN COULD TEACH TRUMP A LOT
ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF
PRESERVING OUR UNION.
TRUMP COULD TEACH LINCOLN HOW TO
TURN YOUR HEAD AT THE EXACT
RIGHT MOMENT.
DURING HIS ADDRESS, PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID
HE WAS CHANGING THE
NAME OF THE GULF OF MEXICO TO
THE GULF OF AMERICA.
AND -- LIKE YOU, HILLARY CLINTON
COULD BE SEEN IN THE BACKGROUND
LAUGHING WHILE HE SAID IT.
WHILE KAMALA COULD BE SEEN
SILENTLY BEGGING HER EDIBLE TO
KICK IN.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP PARDONED
OATH KEEPERS LEADER STEWART RHODES,
WHO WAS SERVING 18 YEARS
FOR HIS ROLE IN THE JANUARY 6th
ATTACKS.
AND LADIES, JUST LIKE HIS EYES,
HE'S SINGLE.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DEFENDED HIS
PARDON OF THE JANUARY 6th ATTACKERS,
SAYING THAT THESE ARE
JUST PEOPLE THAT LOVE THEIR
COUNTRY.
YOU KNOW.
LIKE HOW O.J. LOVED NICOLE.
IT'S A DARK "UPDATE."
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP REVEALED
WHAT HE CALLED AN INSPIRATIONAL LETTER
THAT PRESIDENT BIDEN LEFT
HIM IN THE OVAL OFFICE,
WHICH
READ, "ENJOY IT, DO A GOOD JOB."
THOUGH TRUMP THOUGHT IT WAS
STRANGE THAT THE LETTER BEGAN,
"CONGRATS ON BEING THE FIRST"
BLACK FEMALE PRESIDENT."
>>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
SAID THAT I.C.E. AGENTS
WILL NOW
BE PERMITTED TO ARREST MIGRANTS
IN CHURCHES.
AND I CAN'T WAIT UNTIL LAW
ENFORCEMENT BURSTS INTO A CHURCH
AND THE PRIEST IS LIKE, "THOSE
KIDS ARE LYING!"
>>> ON PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FIRST
DAY IN OFFICE,
HE SIGNED 26
EXECUTIVE ORDERS, 12 MEMOS, 4
PROCLAMATIONS,
AND REVOKED 78
BIDEN EXECUTIVE ACTIONS.
THEN THAT NIGHT, BIG CLOG IN THE
TOILET.
>>> ELON MUSK WAS CRITICIZED FOR
HIS SPEECH AT A RALLY
AFTER THE
INAUGURATION
IN WHICH HE APPEARS
TO GIVE THE NAZI SALUTE.
BUT COME ON, ELON MUSK IS NOT A
NAZI.
THE NAZIS MADE NICE CARS.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE SHARED
IMAGES OF ILLEGAL MIGRANTS
BEING
PLACED ON MILITARY PLANES TO BE
DEPORTED.
AND TRUMP SAID THE DEPORTATIONS
WON'T STOP
UNTIL A WHITE KID
WINS THE SPELLING BEE.
>>> YESTERDAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP
AND FIRST LADY MELANIA
SURVEYED
HURRICANE DAMAGE IN NORTH CAROLINA,
AND FOR SOME REASON,
THEY WERE DRESSED LIKE JAY AND
SILENT BOB.
>>> CONGRESSWOMAN LAUREN BOEBERT
TRIED TO HAVE A MAN KICKED OUT
OF THE WOMEN'S ROOM IN THE CAPITOL BUILDING,
BUT IT TURNED
OUT TO BE A WOMAN.
IN BOEBERT'S DEFENSE, MARJORIE
WAS STANDING UP.
>>> TRUMP ALSO SIGNED AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER DIRECTING THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
TO END ALL
DIVERSITY, EQUITY, AND INCLUSION
PROGRAMS.
WORSE, THE ORDER BEGAN, "LISTEN
UP, GAYWADS."
>>> JUST DAYS INTO HIS SECOND
TERM, TRUMP BEGAN TO SIGN
EXECUTIVE ORDERS ENACTING TARIFFS ON IMPORTS,
LEAVING
CONSUMERS AND BUSINESSES
VULNERABLE.
HERE TO COMMENT IS GISELE, A
CONCERNED BUSINESSWOMAN.
THIS IS A CRAZY TIME, MICHAEL.
YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY.
IS IT OKAY IF I JUST TALK
DIRECTLY TO THE PEOPLE?
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
>> THIS IS A VERY SCARY TIME FOR
US.
I AM SPEAKING AS A BUSINESSWOMAN
AND I AM SPEAKING AS A BLACK
WOMAN.
BLACK WOMEN, IF YOU ARE WATCHING
THIS AND YOU ARE A BLACK WOMAN,
IT IS TIME TO ACT.
AND BUY ALL THE HAIR AND
EXTENSIONS YOU NEED BEFORE THOSE
TARIFFS KICK IN.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU HEARD ME.
WE NOT GETTING NO MORE MALAYSIAN
HAIR.
NO PERUVIAN HAIR.
INDIAN OR BRAZILIAN.
WE NOT EVEN GOING TO BE GETTING
NO IRISH.
WE ABOUT TO BE IN A PICKLE.
A BALD-HEADED PICKLE.
>> GISELE, IT'S NOT THAT
SERIOUS.
>> NOT THAT SERIOUS?
YOU NEED TO BE FREAKING OUT TOO,
CHE.
ALL YOUR BITCHES ABOUT TO HAVE A
FADE.
>> GISELE, I THINK YOU'RE
OVERREACTING.
CAN'T YOU WEAR YOUR NATURAL
HAIR?
>> WHAT NATURAL HAIR?
I AM BALD UNDER THIS.
MY REAL HAIR'S NOT EVEN LONG
ENOUGH FOR A BOWL CUT.
THEY GOT TO USE A PLATE.
AND I KNOW SOME WOMEN CAN PULL
OFF THE BALD LOOK, BUT I CAN'T.
MY HEAD IS LUMPIER THAN THE
APPALACHIAN TRAIL.
>> I'M SURE IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
GISELE, YOU KNOW, A LOT OF
SUCCESSFUL BLACK WOMEN WEAR
THEIR HAIR NATURAL.
LOOK AT JOY ANN REID, WHOOPI
GOLDBERG, WANDA SYKES.
>> I WORK IN CORPORATE AMERICA,
AND I'M NOT GAY.
AND WHILE YOU REALLY PULLED SOME
NAMES OUT YOUR ASS IS THAT WHO
YOU WANT TO LAY WITH?
IS THAT WHO YOU'RE TRYING TO
SMASH, CHE?
>> I AM NOT ANSWERING THAT.
>> YEAH,
IF I HAD KNOWN TRUMP
WAS GOING TO DO THIS, I WOULD
HAVE NEVER VOTED FOR HIM.
>> YOU VOTED FOR TRUMP?
>> YEAH.
AND NOW HE'S ABOUT TO HAVE ME AT
WORK LOOKING LIKE CHOCOLATE KIYU
IN A PRADA SUIT.
AND AGAIN, I KNOW THIS IS NOT
THE CASE FOR ALL BLACK WOMEN.
BUT I SWEAR TO GOD, WHEN MY AIR
AIN'T DONE, I LOOK JUST LIKE
YOU, CHE.
>> HEY, TWIN.
HEY, TWIN.
HI, TWIN.
>> STOP CALLING ME TWIN.
>> YOU KNOW, THE OTHER DAY, I
HAD TO MAKE A LATE-NIGHT RUN TO
DUANE REID WITHOUT MY WIG.
CASHIER THOUGHT I WAS DUANE.
AIN'T THAT MESSED UP?
SAY THAT'S MESSED UP, TWIN.
>> STOP CALLING ME TWIN.
THERE'S SO MANY OTHER THINGS TO
BE CONCERNED WITH RIGHT NOW.
HAIR IS JUST NOT THAT IMPORTANT.
>> REALLY?
YOU'D BE WITH ME IF I DIDN'T
HAVE HAIR?
>> GISELE, EVERYBODY!
>> SEE?
STOCK UP ON THE EXTENSIONS,
STOCK UP ON THE BUNDLES.
MESSED UP
>>> TOTINOS IS PARTNERING WITH
GENERAL MILLS
TO MASH UP THEIR
PIZZA ROLL FLAVOR WITH CINNAMON
TOAST CRUNCH.
PERFECT FOR ANYONE WHO WANTS TO
MASH THEIR CALVES WITH THEIR
ANKLES.
>>> THE OSCAR NOMINATIONS WERE ANNOUNCED
WITH THE MUSICAL EMILIA PEREZ
LEADING THE PACK
WITH 13 TOTAL VIEWERS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 30 YEARS,
NEW YORK CITY THIS WEEK
WENT
FIVE DAYS WITHOUT ANYONE GETTING
SHOT.
BECAUSE IT'S JUST WAY MORE FUN
TO PUSH PEOPLE ONTO THE SUBWAY
TRACKS.
>>> A NEW STUDY SUGGESTS THAT
PEOPLE CAN LIVE LONGER
BY EATING
OATMEAL FOR BREAKFAST.
NO!
>>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT
SINCE LAST YEAR, THE PRICE OF
EGGS HAS RISEN MORE THAN 35%
DUE
TO A SHORTAGE CAUSED BY NEW LAWS
IN RED STATES
THAT FORCE
CHICKENS TO CARRY THEIR EGGS TO
TERM.
>>> JET BLUE ANNOUNCED THAT THEY
ARE NOW ACCEPTING PAYMENTS
THROUGH VENMO.
NOT TO BE OUTDONE, SPIRIT LETS
YOU PAY
WITH HAND STUFF IN THE
BATHROOM.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU, COLIN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>>> DURING AN EPISODE OF "WHEEL
OF FORTUNE" THIS WEEK, A
CONTESTANT WHO HAD JUST WON $40,000
ACCIDENTALLY TACKLED
HOST RYAN SEACREST.
BUT I DARE YOU TO TRY THAT ON
POP CULTURE JEOPARDY.
>> WEIRD GUY, MAN.
>>> FOLKS, WE HERE AT "SNL"
THINK FAMILY IS IMPORTANT.
EVEN THOUGH SOMETIMES THEY CAN
DRIVE YOU UP A WALL.
HERE WITH A NEW HILARIOUS COMEDY
ROUTINE ABOUT HOW CRAZY FAMILY CAN BE
IS ANDREW DISMUKES AND
HIS PUPPET DAD.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY!
HEY THERE, COLIN.
DAD, SAY HI.
>> HEY, NICE TO MEET YOU, MR.
JOST.
I'M ANDREW'S PUPPET DAD.
GOSH, THIS STUDIO IS BIG!
>> WOW.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU TOO,
ANDREW'S DAD.
ANDREW, WHAT'S WITH THE PUPPET?
>> I STARTED DOING VENTRILOQUISM
IN MY STAND-UP ACT.
MY PUPPET DAD AND I DO THIS
HILARIOUS ROUTINE
ABOUT ALL THE
CRAZY THINGS MY DAD SAYS.
IT'S A HOOT.
>> A HOOT?
WHAT ARE YOU, AN OWL?
>> OH, DAD.
>> YEAH, WELL, SOUNDS
INCREDIBLE.
YEAH, GO FOR IT.
>> OKAY.
HEY, DAD.
ARE YOU EXCITED FOR THE SUPER
BOWL THIS YEAR?
>> BAH, THOSE BOZOS DON'T PLAY
REAL FOOTBALL.
YOU CAN'T EVEN HIT NO MORE.
FOOTBALL?
MIGHT AS WELL BE THE BALLET.
>> OH, DAD.
>> ALSO --
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU, SON.
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED SO MUCH.
AND I AM SO DAMN PROUD TO BE
YOUR FATHER.
>> THANKS, DAD.
>> I MEAN IT.
ANDREW, I, YOUR DAD,
AM SO
INCREDIBLY PROUD OF YOU.
AND I NEVER GET TIRED OF SAYING
IT.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO, SON.
>> SO THAT'S PRETTY MUCH THE
BIT, COLIN.
>> OKAY.
SO THAT'S THE KIND OF STUFF YOUR
DAD SAYS TO YOU?
>> YEAH, SOME OF IT.
BUT WAIT.
THERE'S MORE.
SAY, DAD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF MUSIC THESE
DAYS?
>> BAH, YOU CALL THAT CRAP
MUSIC?
IF I WANTED TO HEAR A BUNCH OF
BLEEPS AND BLOOPS,
I'D POUR MY
BEER OUT ON MY LAPTOP, HA HA!
>> OH, DAD.
>> ALSO --
YOU AMAZE ME EVERY DAY, SON.
YOU ARE MY PRIDE AND JOY.
DO YOU KNOW HOW PROUD I AM OF
YOU?
>> YEAH, DAD, I KNOW.
>> I MEAN, LOOK AT YOU.
THE 17th MOST FAMOUS CURRENT
CAST MEMBER ON "SNL."
I HOPE YOU KNOW HOW SPECIAL YOU
ARE.
>> YOU REALLY MEAN IT, DAD?
>> YEAH, SON.
I MEAN IT.
>> SING ME A SONG, PAPA.
>> I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO SEE
THAT.
¶ YOU'RE MY HANDSOME LITTLE
BOY ¶
>> PRETTY FUNNY, RIGHT, COLIN?
>> I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO SAY
IT'S FUNNY.
I WOULD SAY MORE LIKE DEEPLY SAD
AND KIND OF INSECURE.
>> IS THAT SO?
WELL, THEN YOU KNOW WHAT, COLIN?
I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I'M PROUD OF YOU TOO, COLIN.
>> REALLY?
EVEN ME, DOPEY OLD LITTLE COLIN?
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
LOOK AT YOU.
THE 16th MOST FAMOUS CURRENT
CAST MEMBER ON "SNL."
WHAT FATHER WOULDN'T BE PROUD?
>> WOW.
YOU KNOW, THAT ACTUALLY REALLY
MEANS A LOT.
>> MATTER OF FACT, I GOT YOU A
LITTLE SOMETHING.
JUST TO SHOW YOU HOW PROUD I AM
OF YOU.
>> OH, WOW.
CIGARETTES.
YOU REALLY THINK I'M OLD ENOUGH?
>> OF COURSE YOU ARE!
YOU GOT HAIR ON YOUR CHEST,
DON'T YOU?
>> ACTUALLY, I DON'T.
>> AND THAT'S NORMAL AND COOL
FOR A MAN.
>> I KNEW IT.
ANDREW DISMUKE AND HIS PUPPET
DAD, EVERYONE.
>> I'M HIS HANDSOME LITTLE BOY!
>> FOR
LITTLE DOGS TALKED AND ACTED
LIKE PEOPLE.
>> WHOA, LOOK WHO'S IN THE DOG
RUN!
WHAT UP?
>> WHAT IS UP?
YO, CAN I SMELL YOUR ASS?
>> SURE.
YO, RANDOM QUESTION.
DID YOU PEE ON THE BLUE MAILBOX
UP THE STREET?
>> YEAH, I LOVE PEEING ON THAT
BLUE MAILBOX.
>> I KNEW IT.
YO, I JUST PEED ON TOP OF YOUR
PEE.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHOA!
>> YEAH, WHAT?
>> SO DUDE, LIKE WHAT DO YOU --
WHAT ARE YOU EATING NOWADAYS?
>> MY FOOD THAT'S THERE, WHAT
ABOUT YOU?
>> SAME.
MY FOOD THAT'S THERE.
>> COOL.
>> AAH!
I'M CRAZY!
AND I DON'T LIKE YOU!
>> I'VE NEVER MET YOU!
>> I DON'T CARE!
FOR SOME REASON, I HATE YOU!
>> HUH?
>> BYE!
>> BITCH-ASS.
>> WHAT IS UP?
WHAT ARE YOU HUMPING NOWADAYS?
>> OH, WELL, IT'S -- IT'S PRETTY
NEW, BUT I'VE ACTUALLY -- I'VE
BEEN HUMPING A SHOE.
>> NICE!
CONGRATS!
DOES IT FEEL GOOD?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN -- LET'S JUST SAY ME AND
SHOE HAVE FUN.
>> OH!
>> PUT IT THAT WAY.
WE'RE ENJOYING OUR TIME
TOGETHER.
>> OKAY.
OH, GIRL DOG.
>> HI, BOYS.
>> WHAT'S UP?
IS YOUR BOOTY ITCHY?
>> MAYBE.
BYE, SILLY BOYS.
>> OKAY, YEAH.
SO, SHE FINE.
>> REALLY?
I'M NOT LIKE A POODLE GUY.
KIND OF FEELING THAT BADDIE OVER
THERE.
WHAT'S UP, FADY?
WHAT YOU DOING OVER THERE?
>> JUST LICKING MY PARTICULARS.
COME SAY HI LATER.
>> OKAY, AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
TELL SHOE.
>> HI, THERE.
I'M ROCCO, AND -- OH GOD -- I --
I CAN FEEL IT.
PLEASE, PLEASE HELP ME.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I'M GETTING THE IES!
FULL SPEED!
OH, OH, OH, MY GOD!
>> OH, SNAP.
IS THAT BISCUIT?
>> WHAT'S UP, MILO?
OH, MY GOD, YOU EAT GRASS?
THAT STUFF MAKES ME SICK AS
HELL.
>> NOT ME.
WHAT THE -- WHERE'D THIS COME
FROM?
MIGHT BE FOOD.
BETTER EAT IT.
NAH, I DON'T LIKE THAT.
WHAT THE -- WHERE'D THIS COME
FROM?
MIGHT BE FOOD.
BETTER EAT IT.
YEP, I DON'T LIKE THAT.
WHAT THE -- WHERE'D THIS COME
FROM?
MIGHT BE FOOD.
BETTER EAT IT.
YEP.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> MAN.
THAT DOG IS DUMB AS HELL.
>> YEAH, DUDE.
>> HI.
>> THANKS.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
>> ATTENTION, SMALL DOGS!
I, GIACCIO, A SMALL POMERANIAN,
JUST JUMPED UP ONTO THIS BENCH
ALL BY MYSELF!
ZERO OWNER ASSISTANCE!
NOW KNEEL BEFORE YOUR KING ON
HIS THRONE!
>> SHUT UP.
>> STRONG-ASS POM OUT HERE
ACTING LIKE A BULLMASTIFF.
>> OH, I CAN'T STOP DOING THIS!
>> OH, MAN, LOOK AT THIS CLOWN.
MAN, WHAT HAPPENED, MAN?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT THIS IS ON
ME NOW.
>> OH.
I WANT TO HUMP THAT CHEW TOY.
>> MY LAMMY?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> GIVE THAT BOY YOUR CHEW TOY.
>> STOP THAT!
>> OH, ARE YOU HUMPING?
I LOVE HUMPING!
>> I GOTTA HUMP.
DON'T HUMP ME, DUDE.
OH, NO, THERE'S A CAT.
>> DON'T STOP ON ACCOUNT OF ME.
I LIKE IT.
CHALAMET!
¶ IF TODAY WAS NOT
A CROOKED HIGHWAY
IF TONIGHT WAS NOT
A CROOKED TRAIL ¶
¶ IF TOMORROW WASN'T
SUCH A LONG TIME
THEN LONESOME WOULD MEAN
NOTHING TO YOU AT ALL ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF
MY OWN TRUE LOVE WAS WAITIN'
AND IF I COULD HEAR HER HEART
A-SOFTLY POUNDIN' ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF SHE WAS
LYIN' BY ME
THEN I'D LIE
IN MY BED ONCE AGAIN ¶
¶ I CAN'T SEE MY REFLECTION
IN THE WATER
I CAN'T SPEAK THE SOUNDS
TO SHOW NO PAIN ¶
¶ I CAN'T HEAR THE ECHO
OF MY FOOTSTEPS
OR REMEMBER THE SOUND
OF MY OWN NAME ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF
MY OWN TRUE LOVE WAS WAITIN'
AND IF I COULD HEAR HER HEART
A-SOFTLY POUNDIN' ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF SHE WAS
LYIN' BY ME
THEN I'D LIE
IN MY BED ONCE AGAIN ¶
¶ THERE'S BEAUTY
IN THAT SILVER SINGIN' RIVER
THERE'S BEAUTY
IN THAT RAINBOW IN THE SKY ¶
¶ BUT NONE OF THESE
AND NOTHING ELSE
CAN MATCH THE BEAUTY ¶
¶ THAT I REMEMBER
IN MY TRUE LOVE'S EYES ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF
MY OWN TRUE LOVE
WAS WAITIN' ¶
¶ IF I COULD ONLY
HEAR HER HEART
A-SOFTLY POUNDIN' ¶
¶ YES AND ONLY IF SHE WAS
LYIN' BY ME
THEN I'D LIE
IN MY BED ONCE AGAIN ¶
IT HERE TODAY JUST FOR ME.
>> WELL, IT'S YOUR 92nd
BIRTHDAY, GRANDMA.
>> WE WOULDN'T MISS IT FOR THE
WORLD.
>> EVEN KELSEY'S COMING WITH HER
NEW BOYFRIEND.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS, KELSEY'S
COMING?
WELL, I BETTER GO MAKE SOME MORE
COFFEE, THEN.
>> SAY, HOW'S KELSEY DOING THESE
DAYS?
>> SHE'S DOING REALLY GOOD, MR.
DAVIS.
HER BOYFRIEND'S ACTUALLY A
DOCTOR.
>> NOT JUST A DOCTOR, JARED.
THE YOUNGEST HEAD OF CARDIOLOGY
IN THE HISTORY OF JOHNS HOPKINS.
>> WELL, THEY'RE ACTUALLY COMING
STRAIGHT FROM THE HOSPITAL.
>> WOW, VERY IMPRESSIVE.
>> GRANDMA, WHAT DID YOU GET
GRANDMA FOR HER BIRTHDAY THIS
YEAR?
>> OH, I SUPPOSE I'LL GIVE HER A
KISS AT 3:15, JUST LIKE I DID
THE DAY WE MET.
AND JUST LIKE I'VE DONE EVERY
BIRTHDAY FOR THE PAST 76 YEARS.
>> AWW!
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU ALL HOW MUCH
IT MEANS TO ME THAT YOU'RE HERE.
I JUST -- OH -- I JUST --
>> MOM!
>> GRANDMA!
>> OH, OH!
SHE'S NOT BREATHING, GUYS.
HER FACE IS TURNING BLUE.
>> SORRY WE'RE LATE -- GRANDMA!
>> THANK GOD YOU'RE HERE, WE
NEED A DOCTOR.
>> OKAY.
EVERYONE TRY TO STAY CALM!
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> I DON'T KNOW, A FEW SECONDS
AGO.
>> WAS SHE EATING ANYTHING, IS
SHE CHOKING?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, MY GOD!
>> EVERYBODY GET BACK, I NEED
SPACE, GET BACK.
I'M GOING TO DO CPR, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, READY?
OKAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE --
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELCOME BACK, MA'AM.
GAVE US A REAL SCARE THERE, BUT
YOU'RE GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> I DO NOT KNOW.
>> WAS THAT SOME KIND OF NEW
CPR?
>> UH-HUH.
>> BUT INSTEAD OF HIS --
>> HE USED HIS --
>> YEP.
>> WELL, YOU SAVED ME, THANK
YOU, YOU WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL
MAN.
>> OH, JUST DOING MY JOB.
SOMEONE GET THIS WOMAN A GLASS
OF WATER AND AN ALTOID.
>> THERE WERE NO PADDLES.
WHY DID HE SAY CLEAR?
>> WELL, I WAS SITTING THE
CLOSEST, I KNOW WHY HE SAID
CLEAR.
>> WHAT DID WE JUST WITNESS?
>> WE WITNESSED ANOTHER VICTORY
FOR MODERN SCIENCE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
JUST THIS MORNING, I WAS EATING
BREAKFAST AT WHITE CASTLE
WONDERING IF I WAS EVEN MAKING A
DIFFERENCE.
>> BREAKFAST AT WHITE CASTLE?
>> UH-HUH, THEN EVEN WHEN I WAS
EATING DEVILED EGG JUMBALAYA FOR
LUNCH, WAS WONDERING, WHAT'S THE
POINT OF ALL OF THIS?
WHEN I WAS WALKING DOWNTOWN
THROUGH THE CHILI CONTEST
SAMPLING ALL THE ETHNIC ONES, I
REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
LIFE IS PRECIOUS.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING, MOM?
>> STRANGE, SON.
EVERYTHING WENT DARK, AND THEN
SUDDENLY I HEARD THE SOUND OF
GABRIEL'S HORN CALLING ME TO
HEAVEN.
>> THAT WASN'T NO GABRIEL'S
HORN.
>> WELL, WHATEVER IT WAS, IT WAS
LOUD.
AND THEN WHEN I GOT TO HEAVEN,
IT WAS THE STRANGEST THING.
IT SMELLED AND TASTED LIKE A
CHALUPA.
>> OH, YEAH.
I ALSO WENT TO TACO BELL.
>> ANYWAY, NOW IT SEEMS LIKE I'M
SEEING THE WORLD THROUGH
ROSE-COLORED GLASSES.
>> NO, IT JUST SOUNDS LIKE YOU
HAVE PINKEYE.
>> SOMEBODY MARK DOWN THE TIME
FOR THE PARAMEDICS.
IT'S 3:15.
>> 3:15?
I KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
IT'S TIME FOR MY BIRTHDAY KISS.
>> NO!
YUCK!
EWW!
>> OH, MAN.
AH -- AH -- OH --
>> MR. DAVIS, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> SHUT UP!
>> YOU'RE HAVING A HEART ATTACK!
>> NO.
SHH!
JUST LET ME DIE.
DON'T LET THAT AWFUL MAN DO THAT
TO ME.
JUST PUTTER ME AROUND LIKE
WEEKEND AT BERNIE'S TILL HE'S
OUT OF HERE.
>> THIS A BIRTHDAY I'LL NEVER
FORGET.
>> BECAUSE YOUR WHOLE FAMILY IS
HERE?
>> NO, BECAUSE YOUR TWINK
BOYFRIEND SAT ON MY FACE.
AND FARTED ME BACK TO LIFE.
ANYHOO, RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU'D
LIKE A SLICE OF CAKE.
>> TWO SLICES FOR US, PLEASE.
GOD
VOLCANO
>>> SO, I'M CALLING THEM PLANTS.
AND THE IDEA IS THAT THEY INHALE
CARBON DIOXIDE AND EXHALE
OXYGEN.
THE OPPOSITE OF ANIMALS.
>> SO IT ALL BALANCES OUT.
THAT'S REALLY CLEVER.
HAVE YOU PITCHED IT TO GOD YET?
>> NO, I WANT TO MAKE SURE ALL
THE KINKS ARE WORKED OUT.
>> OH MY DOG.
DO YOU MIND, I HAD AN IDEA.
I THINK WE SHOULD DO IT.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S LIKE A MOUNTAIN, RIGHT,
THAT EXPLODES.
>> IT EXPLODES?
>> YES.
SO TAKE THE INSIDE OF THE EARTH,
IT'S GOING TO COME TO THE
OUTSIDE.
IT'S LIKE FIRE AND [ BLEEP ].
IT'S SICK.
LET'S GET GOING ON THESE.
>> OKAY.
HEY, SINCE YOU'RE HERE, THERE'S
AN IDEA FOR SOMETHING CALLED --
>> THAT'S GREAT, I DON'T WANT TO
HEAR ABOUT IT, BUT LET'S DO
EXPLODING MOUNTAINS FIRST.
AND HEY, YOU GUYS, YOU'RE
KILLING IT.
KANGAROO
WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> WE THOUGHT IT WAS GOOD.
>> YEAH, YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
GOOD?
IT'S A GIANT BOUNCING RAT WITH A
CAMEL HEAD AND HUMAN ARMS.
IT'S NOT GOOD.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> WHAT'S IN THIS POUCH ON ITS
STOMACH?
>> THOSE ARE THE BABIES THAT
CRAWL IN THERE AFTER THEY'RE
BORN.
>> GET OUT.
SELF PLEASURE
>> STUPID.
SUCKS.
- HEY
- HI, WHAT'S UP?
>> JUST WANTED TO FLOG
SOMETHING.
WITH THE HUMANS YOU ASKED US TO
MAKE IT SO THEIR PRIVATE AREAS
FELT VERY GOOD WHEN THEY'RE
CREATING BABIES.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, IN TESTING WE REALIZED
THEY CAN GET THAT SAME FEELING
ING THEIR OWN HANDS.
>> HEARD, YEAH.
I'LL TELL THEM NOT TO DO THAT.
>> IF ONE OF THEM DOES DO IT
ANYWAY, WHAT SHOULD WE --
>> STRAIGHT TO HELL FOREVER.
SOLAR
>> IT'S REALLY GREAT.
>> SO GOOD.
>> ALL THESE PLANETS AND THIS
GRAVITY IDEA.
>> THE MOONS.
>> WE KILLED IT.
>> YEAH, TOTALLY AGREE.
THE WHOLE SOLAR SYSTEM SLAPS.
THE PLANETS, THEN MY IDEA FOR GOOBIE,
THE GIANT CREATURE WITH
THE SUN IN ITS MOUTH.
IT'S LIKE BRILLIANT.
THEN ALL THE STARS AND STUFF
AROUND IT, IT'S LIKE, IT REALLY
WORKS.
>> HEY, GOD, ABOUT GOOBIE?
WE ACTUALLY THINK MAYBE IT'S A
LITTLE BETTER
TO JUST HAVE THE
SUN BY ITSELF.
>> OH, I DON'T QUITE GET WHAT --
>> HERE, LET ME JUST SHOW YOU.
SEE?
DOESN'T THAT FEEL BETTER?
BECAUSE IT'S JUST CLEANER.
>> IT'S TOTALLY CLEANER.
>> TELL HIM THE IDEA.
>> OKAY.
HEY, GOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE COULD DO, WE
COULD KEEP GOOBIE
AS MAYBE A
SMALL ANIMAL ON EARTH.
WOULD IT -- WHAT WOULD IT LOOK
LIKE?
>> SOMETHING LIKE THIS, MAYBE.
>> AND THERE WOULD BE A LOT OF
THEM?
>> YEAH, THEY COULD BE
EVERYWHERE.
WE COULD PUT THEM IN PONDS.
>> SWAMPS.
>> AND WE'LL CALL THEM FROGS.
FROGS, OKAY, YEAH.
OKAY, I'M GOOD WITH THAT.
SORRY I GOT A LITTLE WEIRD
THERE.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
MAN, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
HEY.
A BIG THANK YOU TO LIN-MANUEL
MIRANDA!
A BIG THANK YOU TO THE LEGEND
JAMES BLAKE!
THANK YOU TO ADAM SANDLER, CAST
OF "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE," THANK
YOU.
THANK YOU, THANKS SO MUCH.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!