>>> THIS WEEK, "THE NEW YORK
TIMES" BROKE THE STORY OF AN
EXPLOSIVE TRUMP CABINET MEETING
WHICH ENDED IN A SHOUTING MATCH
BETWEEN MARCO RUBIO AND ELON MUSK,
RUINING WHAT HAS BEEN AN
OTHERWISE REMARKABLY COOL
AND
SMOOTH START TO THE TRUMP
PRESIDENCY.
WE NOW TAKE YOU TO THE OVAL OFFICE
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP TRIES
TO BROKER A TRUCE.
>> MARCO, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
COMING.
I KNOW YOU'RE UNDER A LOT OF STRESS,
BUT I CAN'T HAVE YOU
FIGHTING WITH ELON, OKAY?
I NEED YOU TO BE MY GOOD LITTLE
MARCO.
>> MR. TRUMP, IF YOU THINK I'M
GOING TO STAND HERE AND LET YOU
CALL ME THAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> GOOD BOY.
WE LOVE TO SAY, MARCO RUBIO.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, I JUST MADE
ENGLISH THE OFFICIAL LANGUAGE.
SO NOW YOUR NAME IS MARK RUBY.
>> I ACCEPT THAT.
BUT WHAT I DON'T ACCEPT IS ELON
HAVING TOTAL ACCESS TO OUR
GOVERNMENT.
PLANES ARE CRASHING, AND HE
KEEPS TRYING TO FIRE AIR TRAFFIC
CONTROLLERS.
>> WELL, ELON KNOWS ABOUT LOT
ABOUT AIR TRAVEL.
HE RUNS SPACEX, WHICH IS DOING INCREDIBLE THINGS
IN TERMS OF
EXPLOSIONS.
AND WITH REGARD TO ROCKET
DEBRIS.
>> WELL, JUST BECAUSE ELON IS A
SUCCESSFUL BUSINESSMAN
DOESN'T
MEAN HE SHOULD RUN THE COUNTRY.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE TRIED THAT IN 2016, AND IT
DIDN'T WORK.
TRUMP 45, NOT A GREAT PRESIDENT.
BUT NOW WE'VE GOT TRUMP 47.
I'M OLDER.
WISER.
AND, FRANKLY, OLDER.
BUT ELON'S BEEN DOING GOOD JOB
WITH DOGE.
AND HE GAVE ME SOME GREAT STUFF
TO TALK ABOUT AT STATE OF THE
UNION.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE SPENDING $8
MILLION ON MAKING MICE
TRANSGENDER.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
PROBABLY NOT BECAUSE IT'S NOT
TRUE.
BUT I SAID IT, AND IT GOT A BIG
LAUGH, AND THAT IS ADDICTIVE.
BUT YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB
TOO, MARCO, OKAY?
YOU'RE DOING GREAT, YOU'RE THE
GOAT.
YOU'RE THE SCAPEGOAT.
BUT IT'S STILL A TYPE OF GOAD.
>> THAT IS AN HONOR, SIR.
BUT WHILE WE'VE BEEN CAUSING CHAOS,
I'VE BEEN WORKING BEHIND THE SCENES,
AND I AM VERY CLOSE
TO A DEAL WITH THE PANAMANIAN GOVERNMENT
TO RETAKE THE PANAMA
CANAL.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT IT
ANYMORE.
SEEMS LIKE A HASSLE.
WHAT I'D REALLY LOVE IS
THAILAND.
OKAY?
'CAUSE I'VE BEEN WATCHING "WHITE
LOTUS," AND IT LOOKS BEAUTIFUL,
RIGHT?
HOW ABOUT THE GIRL WITH THE
TEETH?
I DON'T MIND IT.
SO, THAILAND?
>> IF I MAY, SIR, AND THIS IS
VERY IMPORTANT,
AMERICA'S
FOREIGN POLICY HAS A LONG,
DELICATE HISTORY.
WE CANNOT AFFORD TO --
>> SO BORING.
THIS GUY CAN'T STOP TALKING.
I MEAN, WHO THE HELL DOES HE
THINK HE, ADRIEN BRODY?
WEIRD-LOOKING GUY, HE KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE LUIGI.
WE LIKE TO SAY WALA-LUIGI.
WHAT IS THIS?
I'M THINKING SOMETHING AND NOT
SAYING IT OUT LOUD.
WHOA, THIS IS A WHOLE NEW THING.
THIS IS CRAZY.
THIS CAN SAVE ME A LOT OF
TROUBLE.
I SHOULD DO THIS MORE OFTEN.
I WON'T, BUT I SHOULD.
>> AND MAINTAIN AMERICA'S
STANDING IN THE GLOBAL
COMMUNITY.
>> BAH.
WELL.
LET'S GET ELON IN HERE SO YOU
GUYS CAN WORK THINGS OUT.
ELON?
>> MY, IT'S ME, TECH SUPPORT.
HA HA HA, JUST KIDDING!
>> ELON, I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR
AT LEAST WEARING A SUIT THIS
TIME.
DOESN'T LOOK GREAT, RIGHT?
BILLIONAIRE, BUT HE SHOPS AT
JOSEPH A. BANK.
HE'S GIVING GROOMSMAN.
GOOD ONE
GLITCH!
BUFFERING!
HA HA, I'M BACK, I'M BACK, I'M
BACK.
>> NEVER GOING TO GET USED TO
THAT.
NOW, LOOK, I CAN'T HAVE YOU TWO
AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS, OKAY?
AFTER ALL, I HAVE A PERFECT
RECORD.
EVERYONE WHO'S EVER WORKED FOR
ME HAS LEFT ON GOOD TERMS.
AND THEN GONE ON TO WRITE A BOOK
CALLED, "THE MAN WHO RUINED
EVERYTHING."
SO YOU TWO NEED TO START ACTING
LIKE MATURE ADULTS, OKAY?
SO LET'S BEGIN WITH MARCO.
>> POLO.
>> NO, ELON.
I'M TRYING TO TALK TO MARCO.
>> POLO!
>> WHAT IS THAT, WHAT'S THIS,
WHAT'S THIS?
YOU DO THIS, WHAT'S THIS?
>> NOBODY KNOWS, OKAY?
LITTLE DANCE, WE LET HIM DO IT,
ALL RIGHT?
HE'S A BRIEF, UNSETTLING TRICK.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS THE
GUY YOU'VE GIVEN ACCESS TO THE
ENTIRE GOVERNMENT.
HE'S NOT AN ELECTED OFFICIAL.
>> I KNOW YOU ARE, BUT WHAT AM
I?
COME ON
THAT'S ENOUGH.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO INSULT EACH
OTHER, AT LEAST MAKE THEM GOOD.
SOMETHING LIKE --
ELON, HOW DO YOU HAVE 20 KIDS BUT I'VE NEVER
SEEN YOU WITH A CHICK?
JUST DUDES NAMED DONKEY DONG AND
BONER KING, STUFF LIKE THAT.
WATCH THIS.
MARCO.
SHORT AND GAY, CLASSY.
ELON, YOU'VE GOT TO LISTEN TO
ME.
MARCO IS A VERY IMPORTANT PART
OF THE TEAM.
AND WE ALL NEED TO --
>> PHASE ONE OF MY PLAN IS
COMPLETE.
INGRATIATE YOURSELF TO THE
PRESIDENT AND TAKE OVER THE
MEDIA.
BUT WAS TAKING THIS JOB A BAD
IDEA?
A LOT OF PEOPLE SEEM TO REALLY
HATE ME.
MY TESLA STOCK IS CRASHING,
AND MY PERSONAL NET WORTH JUST
DROPPED BY $100 BILLION.
ALL RIGHT?
>> SO, HEADLINES FROM THE
MEETING.
ONE, AMERICA'S DOING BAD GUY
NOW.
TWO, MARCO, GET YOUR BUDGET
UNDER CONTROL.
AND THREE, ELON, STAY IN YOUR
LANE.
YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS.
>> BUT I -- I PAID YOU $300
MILLION.
>> AND THAT'S WHY YOU'RE THE
BOSS.
SO, WE'LL GET OUT OF YOUR OFFICE
RIGHT AFTER WE SAY THIS.
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
HOST AND MUSICAL GUEST LADY
GAGA!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- LADY GAGA!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
I KNOW YOU MIGHT BE THINKING I'M
HERE TO PROMOTE MY ALBUM,
MAYHEM.
BUT I'M ACTUALLY HERE TO REMIND YOU THAT
I'M AN AMAZING ACTOR.
LAST TIME I HOSTED "SNL," I WAS
27.
I'M 38 NOW, WHICH IS
SCIENTIFICALLY THE BEST AGE
FOR
A FEMALE POP STAR TO BE.
MOST POP STARS ARE OVER 40.
CHAPPELL ROAN IS 58.
AND CHARLI XCX, SHE'S 75.
TATE McRAE IS MY BIOLOGICAL
GRANDMOTHER.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE BACK AT
SNL.
THE LAST TIME I HOSTED WAS IN
2013.
AND EVERY ASPECT OF MY
PERFORMANCE AGED AMAZINGLY.
'CAUSE THERE'S NO NEED TO GOOGLE SNL 2013,
LADY GAGA FEATURING
R. KELLY.
I WON'T BRING IT UP.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE BAD.
ANYWAY, I'M AN ACTOR NOW.
SELECTING FILMS
THAT WOULD
SHOWCASE MY CRAFT AS A SERIOUS
ACTOR.
FILMS SUCH AS "JOKER 2."
APPARENTLY PEOPLE THOUGHT IT WAS
AWESOME.
JOAQUIN AND I EVEN GOT NOMINATED
FOR A RAZZIE,
WHICH IS AN AWARD
FOR THE WORST FILM OF THE YEAR.
WE WON.
FOR WORST SCREEN DUO.
BUT JOKE'S ON THEM.
I LOVE WINNING THINGS!
AND MY RAZZIE BRINGS ME ONE STEP
CLOSER TO AN EGORT.
IT'S LIKE AN EGOT BUT IT'S
HURTFUL.
TONIGHT I'M THE HOST AND THE
MUSICAL GUEST --
WHICH MEANS SOMEONE MUST
INTRODUCE ME FOR MUSIC.
I ASKED BOWEN TO DO IT, BECAUSE
APPARENTLY HE'S A SUPERFAN.
BUT I THINK I MAKE HIM NERVOUS.
BOWEN, ARE YOU HAPPY I'M HERE?
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LADY
GAGA!
>> A LITTLE EARLY.
GREAT JOB, BOWEN, YAY!
BIG YEAR.
I GOT ENGAGED.
MY MOM SET US UP.
AND IT'S A TRUE STORY.
MY MOM CALLED ME ONE DAY AND SHE
GOES, "I MET YOUR HUSBAND."
WHAT DOES HE DO?
HE WORKS IN CANCER RESEARCH.
I WAS LITERALLY SMOKING A
CIGARETTE.
AND THEN WE WENT ON THREE DATES
AND I NEVER SMOKED AGAIN.
EXCEPT WHEN I'M DRUNK.
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS --
I'M FROM NEW YORK CITY,
SO HOSTING "SNL" IS SO EXISTENTIAL
TO ME.
I RESPECT EVERYONE HERE SO MUCH.
TONIGHT, I PROMISE TO ACT, TO SING,
AND TO NOT DO "JOKER 3."
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT. I'M HERE,
SO STICK AROUND, AND
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
JEREMY.
YOU CAN STILL COME.
I GET MY OWN ROOM IN CAS
YOU CAN STAY WITH ME
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
PARIS.
>> NO WAY. THE LAST THING YOU NEED
IS ME
DRAGGING YOU DOWN IN CAS
TRUST ME, BAILEY AND I WILL BE
FINE.
ALICIA, BEING A CHEF HAS ALWAYS
BEEN YOUR DREAM.
NOW GO GET IT.
BUT BEFORE YOU LEAVE FOR THE AIRPORT,
PROMISE ME JUST ONE
THING.
>> ANYTHING.
>> NEVER LOOK BACK.
NEVER.
GOT IT?
>> I LOVE YOU, JEREMY.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
NOW GO.
>> OKAY.
AND THANKS FOR THE RIDEABLE
LUGGAGE.
>> ALICIA, WAIT!
>> YES?
>> I JUST WANTED TO SAY --
I
HOPE YOU HAVE A DELICIOUS LIFE.
>> WHAT?
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE A CHEF.
THAT'S WHY I SAID THAT.
HAVE A DELICIOUS LIFE.
BECAUSE YOU'RE A CHEF?
>> YEAH.
OKAY.
>> I'M SORRY.
GO, ALICIA, GO, NEVER LOOK BACK!
>> BYE.
>> MY GOD.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I MAY HAVE MADE THE BIGGEST
MISTAKE OF MY LIFE
ALICIA, NO!
>> GO AROUND!
GO AROUND!
HEY, THERE, PRETTY LADY.
CUTE RIDE YOU'VE GOT THERE.
>> THANKS.
WHO ARE YOU GUYS?
>> THEY CALL US THE SONS OF
SAMSONITE.
LUGGAGE RIDING ALL OVER THIS
GREAT LAND FOR THE PAST THREE
YEARS.
>> YEAH, FROM NEW JERSEY ALL THE
WAY TO NEW YORK.
WHERE ARE YOU HEADING, LITTLE
MAMA?
>> TO THE AIRPORT.
I'M GOING TO CULINARY SCHOOL IN
PARIS.
MY DREAM.
>> OH, YEAH. TO
WHY SO SAD?
>> I'M JUST -- I HAVE TO LEAVE
SOMEBODY VERY SPECIAL BEHIND.
>> THAT'S A SHAME.
HEY, CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
HONEY, THERE'S FANCY CULINARY
SCHOOLS ALL OVER THE WORLD.
BUT LOVE?
GO AROUND!
LOVE IS RARE.
SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT.
>> BUT -- HE SAID TO NEVER LOOK
BACK.
>> WELL, WE TRIED.
LET'S RIDE, BOYS!
>> ALICIA!
I'M SORRY!
COME BACK!
OH, OH NO.
I'M OUT OF POWER!
I SHOULD HAVE HAD A FULL CHARGE.
GO AROUND!
BAILEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> OH, YOU BEAUTIFUL SON OF A
BITCH.
LET'S GO GET THAT GIRL.
I THINK WE'LL TAKE A SHORTCUT
THROUGH THE TUNNEL.
>> EXCUSE ME!
SORRY!
I'M HEADED TO
>> WHAT?
>> ALICIA, SLOW DOWN!
JEREMY --
>> BETTER SLOW DOWN, ALICIA!
SLOW DOWN!
TO
IT'S SO DANGEROUS!
>> MADE IT.
WHERE'S MY BAG?
RIGHT HERE.
>> ALICIA.
YOU CAN'T GET ON THAT PLANE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I CAN'T.
IT TOOK OFF OVER THREE HOURS
AGO.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD YOU MISSED IT,
BECAUSE THE NEXT FLIGHT YOU TAKE
IS GOING TO BE WITH ME.
>> YOU MEAN IT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE GOING TO PARIS, BABY.
>> PERFECT.
AND JEREMY?
>> YEAH?
>> LET'S HAVE A DELICIOUS LIFE.
GO AROUND!
>> GO AROUND!
PARENTS TO VOTE YES
ON THE REFERENDUM TO REPLACE THE SCHOOL
ROOF.
OKAY?
ONE LAST THING BEFORE CLASS.
AS YOU ALL KNOW, NEXT WEEK IS
THE ANNUAL
ATLAS HIGH
WEIGHTLIFTING COMPETITION.
I JUST WANT TO SAY, IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHO YOU ARE
OR WHAT YOU
LOOK LIKE.
ANY ONE OF YOU HAS A CHANCE TO
WIN IT.
>> YEAH.
EXCEPT PIP.
GOOD ONE
>> THAT IS GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY FUNNY.
OBVIOUSLY PIP DOESN'T HAVE A
CHANCE.
¶ PIP
YOU CAN BE ANYTHING YOU WANT ¶
¶ YOU CAN SHINE BRIGHTER THAN
THE BIGGEST AND BRIGHTEST STAR ¶
¶ THE OTHER KIDS MAY LAUGH AT YOU
AND TREAT YOU LIKE A FOOL ¶
¶ BUT I BELIEVE YOU CAN WIN
THE WEIGHTLIFTING CONTEST OUT AT
SCHOOL ¶
¶ PIP DON'T CRY
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TRY ¶
¶ YOU'VE GOT TO START OUT SMALL PIP
WITH JUST A LITTLE BIT OF
WEIGHT ¶
PUSH YOURSELF TO THE LIMIT
THAT'S HOW YOU GET FROM GOOD TO
GREAT ¶
¶ HIT A HEAVY BAG THAT'S JUST AN
OLD HOT DOG ¶
¶ NEVER USE STEROIDS
BECAUSE
GIVE A MOUSE A COOKIE AND HE'LL GET
LAZY ¶
¶ GIVE A MOUSE A CHALLENGE HE'LL
WORK LIKE CRAZY ¶
¶ PIP I BELIEVE IN YOU
IT'S TIME TO SHOW THE WORLD WHAT YOU CAN
DO ¶
LATER
>> THIS IS IT.
STUDENTS OF ATLAS HIGH,
START
YOUR MUSCLES!
200 POUNDS!
250 POUNDS!
500 POUNDS!
>> THAT'S MY HIGH SCHOOL
BOYFRIEND.
>> WELL, I THINK WE HAVE OUR
WINNER.
WAIT.
THERE'S ONE MORE NAME ON THE
LIST.
IT'S PIP.
PIP WILL BE STARTING AT 1 OUNCE.
>> HE'S GOING TO GO FROM 1 OUNCE
TO 500 POUNDS?
YEAH.
WE'RE GOING TO BE HERE ALL
FRIGGING DAY.
>> QUIET, BRAD.
HE LOOKS SERIOUS.
NEXT
DAMN
TWO
>> STOP LAUGHING AT HIM!
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELVES.
HE'S BETTER THAN ALL OF YOU.
>> NOT BETTER AT LIFTING
WEIGHTS.
>> THE ROOF!
LOOK OUT!
>> COME ON, MEN!
>> IT'S CRUSHING ME!
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> NOT -- STRONG -- ENOUGH.
>> OH, MAN.
I THINK THE ROOF IS --
2 OUNCES
TOO HEAVY.
>> SOMEBODY HELP!
OH, MY GOD, PIP.
>> EVERYBODY OUT, HURRY!
>> PIP.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
TRUTH IS -- MY DAD'S HARD ON ME,
SO I TOOK IT IT OUT ON PIP.
FROM NOW ON I PROMISE, I
NEVER --
>> IT JUST GOT TOO HEAVY, RIGHT,
PIP?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
RIGHT, PIP?
NO
BOTTLE, SIR?
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU'RE AWARE,
SINCE YOU
ORDERED THE BOTTLE AND I OPENED
IT, YOU STILL HAVE TO PAY FOR
IT.
>> FINE, BUT I WON'T HAVE MY
BEAUTIFUL DATE DRINKING THAT
SWILL.
BRING US A BOTTLE OF THE
ROMANEE-CONTI
1982.
>> A MAN OF FINE TASTES, I SEE.
>> YES.
IN WINE, NICHE ANIME,
AND WOMEN.
I LOVE THIS SONG.
>> THEN DANCE WITH ME TO IT.
>> DANCE?
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE RESTAURANT?
PEOPLE WILL STARE.
>> GOOD.
I WANT EVERYONE TO SEE ME
DANCING WITH THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN IN THE ROOM.
¶ IT'S LATE IN THE EVENING
SHE'S WONDERING WHAT CLOTHES TO
WEAR ¶
¶ SO I PUT ON MY MAKEUP
AND I BRUSH MY LONG BLOND HAIR ¶
¶ AND THEN SHE ASKS ME
DO I LOOK ALL RIGHT ¶
¶ AND I SAY YES
YOU LOOK WONDERFUL TONIGHT ¶
>> I'M JEAN FRANCO, BY THE WAY.
I DON'T THINK WE TOLD EACH OTHER
OUR NAMES.
>> JANELLE.
IF YOU'RE HOPING TO GET ME IN
BED TONIGHT, YOU'LL BE
DISAPPOINTED.
>> OH, YOU WON'T SLEEP WITH
SOMEONE ON THE FIRST DATE?
>> NO, I'LL SLEEP WITH YOU.
YOU'LL JUST BE DISAPPOINTED
BECAUSE I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT IT.
>> WHY DON'T YOU LET ME BE THE
JUDGE OF THAT?
AND I WILL JUDGE.
THEN WRITE A DETAILED PLAY BY
PLAY ON MY SUBSTACK.
>> I'D EXPECT NOTHING LESS.
>> IT'S LATER THAT EVENING
AND WE'RE WASTED IN TIMES SQUARE ¶
¶ SO I EAT A FULL BIG MAC
AND I SHAVE OFF MY BODY HAIR ¶
¶ AND THEN SHE BITES ME
ON BOTH MY NIPPLES LEFT AND RIGHT ¶
¶ AND I SAY BITCH
YOU LOOK WONDERFUL TONIGHT ¶
>> IF WE'RE TO GO ANY FARTHER,
YOU SHOULD KNOW
MY HEART BELONGS
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
>> OH.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
>> ORGAN DONOR 2685.
THANK GOD FOR MOTORCYCLES,
RIGHT?
>> INDEED.
YOU KNOW, I WORK IN MEDICINE.
>> A DOCTOR?
>> CLOSE.
I DO THE STAFF DISCLAIMERS IN
MEDICATION ADS.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR BEFORE STARTING.
STOP IMMEDIATELY IF YOUR
DIARRHEA LASTS LONGER THAN SIX
DAYS.
>> JUST LIKE ME, FALLING FOR AN
ACTOR.
¶ I FEEL WONDERFUL 'CAUSE I SEE
THE LOVE LIGHT IN YOUR EYES ¶
¶ AND THE BEAUTY OF IT ALL
IS THAT ¶
¶ YOU JUST DON'T REALIZE
ITALIANS AREN'T WHITES ¶
THANK
>> MY PLEASURE.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT PAYING.
I RECENTLY CAME INTO SOME MONEY.
>> YES, THERE WERE NO TISSUES
NEARBY.
I HAD TO BLAST IT SOMEWHERE, SO
WHY NOT 20s?
>> MAKES SENSE TO ME.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT ONE OF THOSE
FLY BY NIGHT TYPES.
>> WELL, I AM FLY AND BI.
- WHO
¶ WE GO TO A PARTY
AND EVERYONE SCREAMS AT ME ¶
¶ 'CAUSE IT'S A 5-YEAR-OLD'S PARTY
AND I'M SMOKING PCP ¶
¶ I EAT THE WHOLE BIRTHDAY CAKE
WHILE ALL THE CHILDREN CRY ¶
¶ I SHOUT GODDAMN
I FEEL WONDERFUL TONIGHT ¶
>> A BEAUTIFUL SONG.
>> A BEAUTIFUL SONG FOR A
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
>> ROMANEE-CONTI 1982, SIR.
>> PERFECT.
HOW MUCH IS THE BOTTLE?
>> $28,000.
>> RUN.
THANK
YOUR SUPPORT IS WONDERFUL.
>> AWW, YOUR FATHER RICKY
SOUNDED LIKE AN INCREDIBLE MAN.
>> AND HOW AMAZING OF A DAUGHTER WERE YOU,
GIVING HIM SUCH GOOD
CARE AT THE END.
TINA, WE KNOW THE GRIEVING
PROCESS HAS JUST BEGUN,
AND IT'S
HARD TO MAKE THESE TOUGH
DECISIONS.
BUT WE'RE HERE FOR YOU.
>> AND WE REALLY MEAN IT WHEN WE
SAY, HE'S PART OF OUR FAMILY
NOW.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL, THANKS, GUYS.
>> SO, TO START OFF FOR THE FUNERAL,
WHAT KIND OF A VIBE DID
YOU PICTURE?
>> VIBE?
HM, I GUESS I NEVER THOUGHT OF
THAT.
>> YEAH, I'M SURE.
IT COULD BE AS SIMPLE
AS A
CELEBRATION OF LIFE.
>> OR THE SECOND ONE THAT COMES
TO MIND IS, LIKE,
THE ROARING
'20s.
>> THAT SOUNDS KIND OF WEIRD FOR
ME.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO FEEL LIKE A
THEME PARTY.
>> OH, IT'S NOT A THEME PARTY.
>> NO THEME PARTY,
JUST A SUBTLE
NOD TO THE ROARING '20s.
>> UM -- OKAY, I GUESS IF IT'S
SUBTLE.
>> YEAH.
A FEW WORDS FROM FAMILY
MEMBERS.
AND A BURLESQUE PERFORMANCE BY
BIG MAMA AND THE FLAPPER GIRLS.
>> YOU KNOW, THEN WE COULD
OBVIOUSLY PASS OUT CHARACTER CARDS,
MAKE IT A MURDER MYSTERY
GAME.
>> OR SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS A
CELEBRATION OF LIFE.
>> YEAH -- A MURDER MYSTERY
PARLOR GAME WOULD BE VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE FOR ME.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE MY DAD WAS
MURDERED, AND IT'S STILL
UNSOLVED.
>> OKAY.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU GUYS JUST
TELL US WHAT YOU WERE
ENVISIONING.
>> I WAS THINKING MORE LIKE A
SLIDE SHOW OF PICTURES.
>> IMMEDIATELY NO.
>> NO.
>> WHY IMMEDIATELY NO?
THAT SEEMS LIKE THE EASIEST
THING TO DO.
>> UM, WELL, DID THEY HAVE HDMI
CABLES IN THE 1920s?
>> THEY DIDN'T.
>> OKAY.
YOU KNOW, THIS JUST ISN'T RIGHT
FOR US.
>> WELL, WAIT.
COULD I, LIKE, DRESS UP AS
GATSBY OR WHATEVER?
>> BABE, NO, I'M LEAVING.
WE ARE LEAVING, I'M SORRY.
>> NO, PLEASE, WE'RE SORRY.
BUT I SWEAR TO YOU, AND TO GOD,
AND ON MY CHILDREN'S LIVES,
THE
WORDS "ROARING '20s" WILL NOT
PASS THROUGH THESE LIPS AGAIN.
>> OKAY, I GUESS I CAN GIVE YOU
GUYS A SHOT, THEN.
SO, WILL YOU PROVIDE
REFRESHMENTS?
>> HEY, IT WOULDN'T BE A ROWING
'20s PARTY WITHOUT MOONSHINE.
>> WE HAVE A FULL-SERVICE
BARTENDER.
JACKSON?
>> WE MADE A SPECIALTY COCKTAIL
TO HONOR YOUR FATHER.
IT'S CALLED THE GIN RIP RICKY.
NO, BUT SERIOUSLY, I LISTENED TO
THE PODCAST ABOUT YOUR DAD'S
UNSOLVED MURDER,
AND HONESTLY,
BE CAREFUL WHO YOU TRUST.
>> I DIDN'T KILL HER DAD!
>> OH, YEP, AND AT THE END OF
THE FUNERAL THE GALS SHALL
DANCE.
HIT IT!
>> OR IT COULD BE AS SIMPLE AS A
CELEBRATION OF LIFE.
>> TINA, WOULD YOU MAKE ME THE
HAPPIEST MAN ON EARTH?
>> WHAT?
THIS IS THE WORST POSSIBLE TIME.
>> CONGRATULATIONS!
>> NO, NO, NO.
I'M LEAVING THIS PLACE.
I'M LEAVING YOU.
>> HIT IT!
>> WELL, LOOKS LIKE I'M SINGLE
NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
I'M BACK ON THE MARKET, DOLLS.
COME ON, DANCE FOR ME!
NUMBER ONE SELLING
LONG
MASCARA.
>> THE ONLY MASCARA THAT CAN
STAY ON ALL DAY,
NEVER SMUDGING
OR SMEARING.
>> IT NEVER RUNS, EVER.
>> BUT SOMETIMES DON'T YOU KIND
OF WANT IT TO?
>> YOU KNOW.
FOR ATTENTION.
>> SO DON'T HIDE YOUR FEELINGS.
FLAUNT THEM WITH L'OREAL EASY
RUN MASCARA.
>> YOU WANT MASCARA THAT SMEARS
ALL OVER YOUR FACE?
LETTING THE WORLD KNOW, YES, I
HAVE BEEN CRYING.
AND NO, I'M NOT OKAY.
>> MAKE A STATEMENT WHEN YOU
WALK IN THE ROOM,
AND THAT STATEMENT IS,
-  OH-OH,
- DON'T BLEND
IN. STAND OUT
>> WITH LASHES SO BOLD
AND A FACE SO STAINED,
YOU'LL HAVE EVERYONE ASKING,
HAVE YOU
TALKED TO MELISSA?
IT SEEMS LIKE SOMETHING'S REALLY
WRONG.
>> HEY, SORRY ABOUT THE
PROMOTION.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I'LL GET IT NEXT TIME.
>> L'OREAL EASY RUN,
RUNS EASY
THANKS TO A UNIQUE,
SCIENTIFICALLY PROVEN FORMULA
OF
JUST BEING REALLY, REALLY
LOW-QUALITY MASCARA.
AND ALSO A LITTLE PRINTER INK.
>> THIS MASCARA IS THE PERFECT WAY TO SAY,
NO, YOU GUYS GO
AHEAD, I'LL BE FINE.
>> YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MY ART SHOW
MEANT TO ME.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> MAKE EVERY DAY AN OCCASION
THAT'S ALL ABOUT YOU.
LIKE A FUNERAL FOR EVERYBODY.
WHY SHOULD THE WIDOW GET ALL THE
ATTENTION?
>> IF YOU REALLY WANT TO GO FULL
NUCLEAR, START LAUGHING TOO.
>> SO THIS YEAR, BE YOU.
>> BE BOLD.
- BE MESSY.
>> BE A COMPLETE AND TOTAL MESS.
>> WITH L'OREAL, BECAUSE YOU'RE
WORTH IT.
NO, SHUT UP, YOU ARE.
LADIES
ABRA
¶ PAY THE TOLL
TO THE ANGELS
DRAWIN' CIRCLES
IN THE CLOUDS ¶
¶ KEEP YOUR MIND
ON THE DISTANCE
WHEN THE DEVIL
TURNS AROUND ¶
¶ HOLD ME
IN YOUR HEART TONIGHT
IN THE MAGIC
OF THE DARK MOONLIGHT ¶
¶ SAVE ME FROM
THIS EMPTY FIGHT
IN THE GAME OF LIFE ¶
¶ LIKE A POEM SAID
BY A LADY IN RED
YOU HEAR THE LAST FEW WORDS
OF YOUR LIFE ¶
¶ WITH A HAUNTING DANCE
NOW YOU'RE BOTH IN A TRANCE
IT'S TIME TO CAST
YOUR SPELL ON THE NIGHT ¶
¶ ABRACADABRA AMOR-OO-NA-NA
ABRACADABRA MORTA-OO-GA-GA
ABRACADABRA ABRA-OO-NA-NA ¶
¶ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID
DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ¶
¶ ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA
ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA ¶
¶ FEEL THE BEAT
UNDER YOUR FEET
THE FLOOR'S ON FIRE
ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA ¶
¶ CHOOSE THE ROAD
ON THE WEST SIDE
AS THE DUST FLIES
WATCH IT BURN ¶
¶ DON'T WASTE TIME
ON A FEELIN'
USE YOUR PASSION
NO RETURN ¶
¶ HOLD ME
IN YOUR HEART TONIGHT
IN THE MAGIC
OF THE DARK MOONLIGHT ¶
¶ SAVE ME FROM
THIS EMPTY FIGHT
IN THE GAME OF LIFE ¶
¶ LIKE A POEM SAID
BY A LADY IN RED
YOU HEAR THE LAST FEW WORDS OF
YOUR LIFE ¶
¶ WITH A HAUNTING DANCE
NOW YOU'RE BOTH IN A TRANCE
IT'S TIME TO CAST
YOUR SPELL ON THE NIGHT ¶
¶ ABRACADABRA AMOR-OO-NA-NA
ABRACADABRA MORTA-OO-GA-GA
ABRACADABRA ABRA-OO-NA-NA ¶
¶ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID
DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ¶
¶ ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA
ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA ¶
¶ FEEL THE BEAT
UNDER YOUR FEET
THE FLOOR'S ON FIRE
ABRACADABRA ABRACADABRA ¶
¶ PHANTOM OF THE DANCE
FLOOR COME TO ME
SING FOR ME A SIN
FUL MELODY ¶
¶ ABRACADABRA AMOR-OO-NA-NA
ABRACADABRA MORTA-OO-GA-GA
ABRACADABRA ABRA-OO-NA-NA ¶
¶ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID
DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ¶¶
WEEKEND
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, TOMORROW MARKS THE START
OF DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME,
WHEN
WE SET OUR CLOCKS AHEAD.
IDEALLY FOUR YEARS.
AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP SPENT LAST
WEEK GEBDING OUR HISTORICAL BEST FRIEND, RUSSIA,
TRUMP DETERMINED
THIS WEEK TO ATTACKING OUR SWORN
ENEMY, CANADA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THOSE SYRUP-GUZZLING, POUTINE-MUNCHING,
MOOSE-HUMPING HOCKEY SLUTS
HAVE TAKEN
ADVANTAGE OF US FAR TOO LONG.
EVEN RIGHT HERE AT "SNL."
AMERICAN SKETCH COMEDY JOBS
ARE BEING STOLEN BY FILTHY
CANADIANS.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP ADDRESSED A
JOINT SESSION OF CONGRESS
AND
CLAIMED THAT NO PRESIDENT HAS
CHANGED GOVERNMENT FASTER THAN
HIM.
YEAH, AND NOBODY CHANGED AIRPORT
SECURITY FASTER THAN BIN LADEN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALSO SAID THAT
HE SIGNED AN EXECUTIVE ORDER
TO
BAN MEN FROM PLAYING IN WOMEN'S
SPORTS.
BUT IF MEN AREN'T ALLOWED TO
PLAY WOMEN'S SPORTS,
EXPLAIN
SOCCER.
>> LOT OF SOCCER FANS AT THE
GAGA SHOW.
>>> EDUCATION SECRETARY AND WWE
COFOUNDER LINDA McMAHON,
WHO'S
THE ONE ON THE RIGHT --
SAID THAT CLOSING THE DEPARTMENT
OF EDUCATION WOULD NOT HURT STUDENTS,
AND ACTUALLY, TEST
SCORES MIGHT GO UP.
MAYBE EVEN AS HIGH AS 69.
>>> AFTER IMPOSING TARIFFS ON
MEXICO AND CANADA ON TUESDAY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP REVERSED THEM ON
THURSDAY.
IT'S A CUNNING POLITICAL TACTIC
EXPERTS CALL
BIPOLAR DISORDER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID THE TARIFFS
ON GOODS FROM CANADA
IS TO STOP
THE FLOW OF FENTANYL,
EVEN
THOUGH LAST YEAR ONLY 40 POUNDS
OF THE DRUG WAS SEIZED AT THE
NORTHERN BORDER.
40 POUNDS, WHAT'S THAT, LIKE TWO
BUTTFULS?
TWO BUSTFULS?
I THOUGHT IT WAS SMART.
>>> EXPERTS SAY THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S TARIFFS
WILL RAISE THE
COST OF A NEW CAR BY AS MUCH AS
$12,000.
OR YOU CAN GET A FREE TESLA,
SINCE PEOPLE ARE THROWING THEM
AWAY.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, TESLA'S CEO
AND WHITE KANYE, ELON MUSK --
SUIT INSTEAD OF A
JACKET AND T-SHIRT TO THIS
WEEK'S CABINET MEETING
AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP MADE FUN OF HIS
CLOTHING.
IT'S A REFRESHING REMINDER THAT
BULLYING STILL WORKS.
>>> ON THURSDAY, ELON MUSK'S
SPACEX STARSHIP
EXPLODED JUST
MINUTES INTO ITS MISSION,
WHICH
IS HOW HE ENDED UP WITH ALL
THOSE KIDS.
IT WAS REPORTED THAT THE LEADERS
OF GREAT BRITAIN AND FRANCE
HAVE
BEEN COACHING VOLODYMYR
ZELENSKYY ON HOW TO DEAL WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
KIND OF LIKE HOW YOU NEED EXTRA
TRAINING TO BE A SPECIAL ED
TEACHER.
>>> AND THIS IS EXCITING.
DONALD TRUMP JR.
IS REPORTEDLY
CONSIDERING A RUN FOR PRESIDENT
IN 2028.
YEAH, YEAH.
IF YOU DON'T THINK HE COULD WIN,
YOU CLEARLY AREN'T FAMILIAR WITH
HOW THINGS WORK HERE IN HELL.
>>> THE NBA SEASON IS HEATING UP
NOW THAT WE'RE A MONTH AWAY FROM
THE PLAYOFFS.
HERE TO DISCUSS IS NBA CHAMPION
AND ESPN COMMENTATOR
AND ALWAYS
OUTSPOKEN KENDRICK PERKINS.
WHAT'S UP?
HEY.
HOW YOU DOING, MICHAEL?
I LIKE THAT JACKET, MAN.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOUR MAMA DRESSED
YOU UP TO GO APOLOGIZE TO THE
VICE PRINCIPAL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK SOME NBA.
THE CRAZIEST NEWS OF THE SEASON
IS THE DALLAS MAVERICKS TOOK ONE
OF THE LEAGUE'S BEST PLAYERS,
LUKA DONCIC, AND TRADED HIM TO
THE LAKERS.
WHY DID THEY DO THAT?
>> THERE'S A LOT OF QUESTIONS
ABOUT THIS HERE TRADE BUT FOLKS
ON THE INSIDE KNOW LUCKY DOOKIE
IS HURT.
I'M HEARING RUMORS HE GOT A
SMALL TEAR IN HIS IMPERIAL
CANCEROUS TATIOUS UTERUS.
I AIN'T NO DOCTOR, BUT BY MY
ESTIMATIONS, I BELIEVE HE GOING
TO BE DEAD BY APRIL.
>> WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
>> I JUST BE SAYING THINGS,
MICHAEL.
YOU KNOW, STEPHEN A. SMITH, HE
JUST GOT $100 MILLION TO GO ON
ESPN EVERY DAY AND TALK NOTHING
BUT NONSENSE, AND I WANT A PIECE
OF THAT TOO.
ALL I GOT TO SAY IS THINGS LIKE,
LARRY BIRD WAS CREATED BY
SCIENTISTS IN THE BACK OF A
CRACKER BARREL.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S RIGHT,
MAN.
>> MAYBE NOT.
BUT YOU GOT TO ADMIT, MAN, I
KNOW THE GAME.
I BE WATCHING FOUR, FIVE HOURS
OF TAPE EVERY NIGHT BEFORE I
TAKE MY BEARD OFF AND GO TO
SLEEP.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE MVP RACE.
WHO YOU GOT?
>> YOU CAN'T COUNT OUT THE
LEGENDARY LeBRON JAMES.
A MAN WHO, DESPITE BEING 55
YEARS OLD, JUST WON THE TOUR de
FRANCE.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THIS
FROM?
>> NOBODY KNOWS.
BUT IT'S AMAZING HOW LeBRON IS
STILL ABLE TO PLAY EVERY NIGHT.
HE'S 62 YEARS OLD.
>> YOU JUST SAID HE'S 55.
>> I KNOW!
THAT'S MY POINT.
LeBRON IS 71 YEARS OLD.
HAS ONE ARM, 12 KIDS, ONE OF
THEM IS BLACK.
>> NO.
>> THEN HE WORKS UNDERCOVER AS A
FRENCH SUPERSPY.
THE NAME IS LeBRON.
JAMES LeBRON.
>> JAMES LeBRON?
>> JAMES LeBRON, MY MAN.
MARK MY WORDS.
LUKA AND LeBRON ARE THE BEST
BLACK AND WHITE DUO SINCE THEM
JEWISH COOKIES.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
START, MAN.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS THE MAN IS
OLD, OKAY?
HELL, LeBRON AND I ARE THE SAME
EXACT AGE.
AND LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
GETTING OLDER AIN'T PRETTY.
MICHAEL, YOU EVER SNEEZED SO
HARD, AN OLD CHEERIO POPPED OUT
YOUR NOSE?
>> NO.
>> YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
THAT'S WHY I SOUND LIKE THIS.
>> YOU KNOW, I WASN'T GOING TO
BRING THIS UP.
BUT CHARLES BARKLEY CALLED YOU
AN IDIOT THIS WEEK.
>> OOH!
DO NOT GET ME STARTED ON THAT
CHARLES BARKLEY.
HE MAKES ME SO MAD.
WHOO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I FEEL A LITTLE HOT RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT BEARD'S NOT EVEN REAL?
>> I ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT,
MICHAEL.
I'M CRAZY, MAN.
I LOOK LIKE DAFFY DUCK WHEN HE
CHEWS HIS BEAK OFF.
>> KENDRICK, EVERYBODY.
>> HELL, OLD MAN.
>>> SCIENTISTS HOPING TO REVIVE
THE EXTINCT WOOLLY MAMMOTH HAVE
TAKEN A FIRST STEP BY
GENETICALLY ENGINEERING A
LONG-HAIRED WOOLLY MOUSE.
NOW IT'S ON TO STEP TWO, GETTING
IT DRUNK ENOUGH TO HAVE SEX WITH
AN ELEPHANT.
>>> THE MAKERS OF "SESAME
STREET" ANNOUNCED THAT THEY ARE
LAYING OFF MORE THAN 200
EMPLOYEES.
THE LAYOFFS WERE FIRST REPORTED
BY THIS SIGN.
>>> IN HONOR OF WOMEN'S HISTORY
MONTH, MATTEL IS RELEASING A
LINE OF BARBIE DOLLS THAT
CELEBRATES FEMALE FRIENDSHIPS.
AND MAYBE THEY'RE SUCH GOOD
FRIENDS THAT THEY KISS?
>>> AMAZON PRIME HAS LAUNCHED A
NEW TOOL THAT WILL USE AI TO DUB
MOVIES INTO ENGLISH FROM FOREIGN
LANGUAGES LIKE SPANISH, KOREAN,
AND SYLVESTER STALLONE.
>> NEW RESEARCH SUGGESTS MEN
WITH STRONGER SPERM MAY LIVE
LONGER THAN MEN WITH WEAKER
SPERM.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
DICK VAN DYKE BUSTS ROCKETS.
>>> AN AUSTRALIAN MAN WHO WAS
CREDITED WITH SAVING MORE THAN 2
MILLION BABIES BY REPEATEDLY
DONATING HIS BLOOD HAS DIED AT
THE AGE OF 88.
DOCTORS PRONOUNCED HIM DEAD WHEN
THEY HEARD THIS SOUND.
>> SO GROSS.
>> I COULD TELL YOU LIKED THAT.
>>> A FIRED STARBUCKS MANAGER IS
SUING THE COMPANY, CLAIMING HE
FACED EGREGIOUS DISCRIMINATION
FROM GAY CO-WORKERS FOR BEING
HETEROSEXUAL.
WHILE HIS GAY CO-WORKERS SAID HE
SHOULD SUE OLD NAVY FOR SELLING
HIM THOSE FRUMPY-ASS CHINOS.
>>> PLASTIC SURGEONS ARE SAYING
THAT A GROWING NUMBER OF WOMEN
ARE HAVING LABIA PUFF SURGERY ON
THEIR VAGINAS.
FUN FACT, LABIA PUFFS WAS ALSO
THE ORIGINAL NAME FOR HONEY
SMACKS.
>> WOMEN'S HISTORY MONTH.
>>> TONIGHT'S HOST AND MUSICAL
GUEST, AS YOU KNOW, IS OF COURSE
LADY GAGA.
HERE TO LEND HIS SUPPORT, MAKING
A RARE PUBLIC APPEARANCE, IS
LADY GAGA'S HUSBAND, LORD GAGA.
>> THANK YOU, COLIN.
HOW SPLENDID THAT MY WIFE'S
PERFORMING HER SONG.
I WISH SHE DRESSED LIKE THAT ON
THE ESTATE.
HA HA HA!
>> WOW.
THIS IS WILD.
YOU KNOW, I HAD NO IDEA THERE
WAS A LORD GAGA.
>> OF COURSE THERE IS.
HOW DO YOU THINK SHE BECAME A
LADY?
SHE MARRIED A LORD.
THAT'S HOW SHE BECAME A GAGA,
WHEREAS I WAS SIMPLY BORN THIS
WAY.
>> GREAT.
WHY HAVEN'T WE EVER SEN YOU WITH
HER?
>> WELL, I'M TERRIBLY WITH
BUSINESS, RUNNING THE GAGA
TEXTILE EMPIRE.
TRUTHFULLY, I DON'T WANT TO
OVERSHADOW MY WIFE.
>> I REALLY DON'T THINK THAT YOU
WOULD.
YOU MUST BE VERY PROUD OF ALL
HER ACCOMPLISHMENTS.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD SHE HAS A
HOBBY.
>> I THINK IT'S MORE THAN A
SHE'S ONE OF THE BEST-SELLING
MUSICIANS OF ALL-TIME.
>> IS SHE NOW?
THEY LIKE HER.
WELL, GOOD FOR HER.
>> YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT?
>> NO, I'M TERRIBLY BUSY WITH
BUSINESS.
BUT WE'RE VERY HAPPY.
IT'S CERTAINLY NOT A BAD
ROMANCE.
>> OKAY.
I'M -- I GUESS I'M CURIOUS, HOW
DID YOU TWO MEET?
>> SHE WAS PLAYING PIANO AT A
DEBUTANTE BALL.
YOU KNOW, WHERE TEENAGE GIRLS
ARE PRESENTED TO THEIR FATHERS'
WIDOWED FRIENDS TO MARRY.
YOU'VE BEEN TO THOSE.
>> I HAVEN'T.
>> YES, YOU HAVE.
YOU'RE LYING IF YOU SAY YOU
HAVEN'T, COLIN.
>> NO.
>> THAT YEAR'S OFFERINGS WERE
SUBPAR, BUT THE DAZZLING GIRL
BEHIND THE PIANO CAUGHT MY EYE.
SO I MADE HER MY WIFE.
NOW WE HAVE SEVEN GORGEOUS
CHILDREN.
>> YOU HAVE SEVEN KIDS?
>> YES, SEVEN LITTLE MONSTERS.
AND COLIN, AGAIN, THANK YOU FOR
INDULGING MY WIFE'S HOBBY AND
LETTING HER SING ON YOUR LITTLE
TALENT SHOW.
>> OKAY, ACTUALLY, SHE'S
INDULGING US.
YOUR WIFE IS VERY SUCCESSFUL,
SIR.
SHE HAS 14 GRAMMYS AND AN OSCAR.
>> YOU DON'T SAY, WOW.
WHAT A FEATHER IN HER CAP.
IF ONLY IT ALL PAID, EH?
>> I THINK IT DOES.
I THINK IT ACTUALLY PAYS A LOT.
>> WELL, IT CERTAINLY CAN'T BE
MORE THAN WHAT TEXTILES BRING
IN.
CAN YOU IMAGINE, COLIN?
A MAN WHOSE WIFE MAKES MORE
MONEY THAN HE?
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
OH, THE SHAME HE WOULD FEEL!
IMAGINE, COLIN.
IF I WAS SITTING HERE, ON
TELEVISION, BEHIND THIS DESK,
STARING AT THAT CAMERA, THE
WORLD STARING BACK AT ME,
KNOWING THAT MY WIFE'S INCOME
DWARVES MY OWN?
OH, OH!
OH, I WOULD DIE!
WHAT A LIVING NIGHTMARE.
WHAT A NIGHTMARE!
OH!
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH.
NOW TELL ME, WHAT DOES YOUR WIFE
DO?
>> LORD GAGA, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN!
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE.
>> FOR "WEEKEND
I HAVEN'T BEEN TO A FRIENDLY'S
SINCE I WAS A KID.
>> I KNOW, I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
FRIENDLY' WAS STILL IN BUSINESS.
>> ARE YOU AN IDIOT?
THEY HAVE 100 LOCATIONS
THROUGHOUT THE EAST COAST.
>> PLEASE DON'T CALL ME AN
IDIOT.
>> DON'T BE ONE.
YOU KNOW.
>> AND OH, IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
SOMEONE'S BIRTHDAY.
REMEMBER HOW THEY ALWAYS DO THE
BIRTHDAY SONG?
¶ FRIENDLY'S HAS A BIRTHDAY SONG
FRIENDLY'S HAS A BIRTHDAY SONG ¶
¶ IT'S NOT TOO SHORT AND NOT TOO
LONG ¶
¶ SOUND OFF HAPPY SOUND OFF
BIRTHDAY ¶
¶ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU POST.
>> THAT IS SO FUN.
>> GUESS WHAT, I TOLD HER IT WAS
YOUR BIRTHDAY, JENNY.
>> ME?
IT'S NOT MY BIRTHDAY.
ARE YOU AN IDIOT TOO?
I TOLD THEM IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY
SO WE CAN GET THE SONG AND THE
FREE SUNDAE.
>> I DON'T KNOW, IT FEELS REALLY
WRONG TO LIE AT FRIENDLY'S.
>> OH, IT'S FINE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, GET IN
TROUBLE?
>> HELLO.
>> WE UNDERSTAND THAT SOMEBODY
HAS A BIRTHDAY AT THIS TABLE.
>> YEAH, IT'S HER.
IT'S JENNY'S BIRTHDAY.
SHE'S TURNING 50.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> I'M KIDDING.
IT'S HER REAL BIRTHDAY FOR REAL,
RIGHT, JENNY?
>> YEAH.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
>> AND YOU SWEAR IT?
>> SWEAR IT?
>> YOU SWEAR TO ALL THE GODS IN
ALL THE HEAVENS THAT THIS DAY,
THE 8th OF MARCH, THIS IS INDEED
YOUR TRUE BIRTHDAY?
>> GUYS, I DON'T LIKE THIS.
>> RELAX, JENNY, IT IS YOUR
BIRTHDAY.
SO JUST SWEAR IT.
>> DO -- YOU -- SWEAR?
>> FINE -- I -- SWEAR.
>> VERY WELL.
YOUR PATH IS FIXED.
>> YOU HAD EVERY OPPORTUNITY TO
SPEAK THE TRUTH.
WE AT FRIENDLY'S WOULD LIKE TO
SAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY --
>> TO THE LIAR!
>> UH, WHAT THE HELL IS
HAPPENING?
>> I TOLD YOU, WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
LIED.
>> OKAY, HOW WOULD THEY KNOW
YOU'RE LYING?
IT'S PROBABLY JUST UNRELATED
TRIBAL DRUMMING AND A LIVE SING.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, MAN, THE
WAITERS, THEY KNOW!
>> WHEN YOU LIE ABOUT A BIRTHDAY
AT FRIENDLY'S, YOU MUST PAY THE
ULTIMATE PRICE.
>> SIN, SIN, SIN, SIN!
>> BEHOLD THE DEVIL!
BEHOLD LAMASHTU!
>> LAMASHTU!
LA MASHTU HAS SEEN THROUGH YOU!
>> GREAT, NOW THEY'VE SUMMONED
LAMASHTU.
>> DRINK, DRINK OF THE BLOOD OF
>> GUYS?
>> JUST DRINK THE BLOOD, JENNY.
IT'S FREE, RELAX.
>> DRINK, DRINK, DRINK!
>> NOW YOU ARE REBAPTIZED BY THE
MOTHER OF BEASTS.
THE MISTRESS OF INSANITY.
THE MAGICIAN PAZUZU CANNOT SAVE
YOU NOW, NEITHER THE DEMON DOG!
>> HOW DO THEY EVEN TRACK IF
IT'S SOMEONE'S BIRTHDAY?
>> WE SEND SOMEONE TO THE
HOSPITAL AND WITH OVER 100
LOCATIONS ON THE EAST COAST,
IT'S NOT HARD.
>> IS THERE A RESTROOM?
>> SURE.
BACK THERE AND TO THE LEFT.
>> OKAY, WELL, AT LEAST THE
BLOOD OF LAMASHTU DIDN'T AWAKE
ANYONE.
>> THE BLOOD OF LAMASHTU AWAKENS
MOLARUM!
COME, BASHNEAGLE, COME WITH
>> YOU GUYS, YOU CAN'T JUST LET
MOLARUM LEAD ME AWAY!
>> IT'S FRIENDLY'S, JENNY, BE
FRIENDLY.
>> BRING ME THE CAGE!
>> AT FRIENDLY'S, YOU HAVE
BETRAYED LAMASHTU.
YOU HAVE BETRAYED KALIMA.
>> YOU GUYS, HELP ME!
>> I WOULD, BUT I KIND OF WANT
TO SEE WHERE THIS GOES.
>> KALIMA, KALIMA!
>> GUYS, HE RIPPED MY HEART OUT
OF MY CHEST!
>> YOU ALWAYS FIND A WAY TO MAKE
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU.
>> NOW WE WILL EAT THE REST OF
YOUR FRIEND.
BUT HER HEART -- IS ON THE
HOUSE.
>> OH, LOOK, THEY PUT AN ICE
CREAM CONE ON JENNY'S HEART.
THEY ARE FRIENDLY.
YAY!
¶ STANDIN' ON THE CORNER
SMOKIN' THAT GRASS
AND THE BOYS
ALL PASS ME BY ¶
¶ TALKIN' SOME SMACK
WITH YOUR HAND ON MY ASS
I'M A MURDERER IN DISGUISE ¶
¶ YEAH YOU WANNA BE COOL
BUT YOU'RE MAKIN' ME MAD
BITE MY LIP
IT STARTS TO BLEED ¶
¶ YEAH IT TASTES SO GOOD
BUT IT GOTTA BE BAD
IF I'M GONNA GET YOU HOME ¶
¶ GONNA MAKE
THE CURTAINS SCREAM
BELIEVE IT ¶
¶ GONNA MAKE THE CEILIN'
SHAKE FOR ME
I'MA BE YOUR FULL-TIME
BEDROOM DEMON ¶
¶ I'M GONNA MAKE YOU SCREAM
THAT'S A MATTER OF FACT
I'LL BE YOUR FANTASY ¶
¶ I'M A KILLAH
AND BOY
YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT ¶
¶ OH KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH KILLAH ¶
¶ I'M A KILLAH
AND BOY
YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT ¶
¶ OH KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH ¶
¶ LIGHTIN' UP
MY FINAL CIGARETTE
I'LL BURN A HOLE
RIGHT THROUGH YOUR EYES ¶
¶ LOOKIN' AT YOU
LIKE A ZOMBIE KILLER
HUNGRY FOR A HOMICIDE ¶
¶ IF I GET YOU ALONE
UNDER YOUR SKIN AND BONE
I'MA TRY YOU ON FOR SIZE ¶
¶ I'M 'BOUT TO WEAR YOU OUT
LIKE MY FAVORITE SUIT
WOOLS PARALYZED ¶
¶ GONNA MAKE
THE CURTAINS CREAM
BELIEVE IT ¶
¶ GONNA MAKE THE CEILING
SHAKE FOR ME
I'MA BE A FULL-TIME
BEDROOM DEMON ¶
¶ I'M GONNA MAKE YOU SCREAM
THAT'S A MATTER OF FACT
I'LL BE YOUR FANTASY ¶
¶ I'M A KILLAH
AND BOY
YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT ¶
¶ OH KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH KILLAH ¶
¶ I'M A KILLAH
AND BOY
YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT ¶
¶ OH KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH KILLAH
KILLAH ¶
¶ I'M A KILLAH
AND BOY
YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT ¶
¶ KILLAH ¶¶
OR IS IN SEVERAL BOOK CLUBS?
YOU'RE GETTING OLDER, BUT YOU
STILL WANT TO HAVE FUN.
>> I WANT MY STYLE TO MATCH HOW
I AM ON THE INSIDE.
SPUNKY AND A LITTLE BIT FUNKY.
>> I WANT PEOPLE TO SEE ME AND
THINK, YOU'VE GOT IT GOING ON.
>> I'M NO SPRING CHICKEN, BUT
THIS HEN STILL KNOWS HOW TO
CLUCK.
>> THAT'S WHY WE WEAR --
>> LITTLE RED GLASSES.
>> THEY'RE THE ONLY GLASSES THAT
SAY, I TEACH PHILOSOPHY AND EAT
POPPERS EVERY NIGHT.
>> COME ON, WE'RE GETTING
POPPERS, LET'S GO.
>> LITTLE RED GLASSES ARE
FASHIONABLE, FUN, AND SEXY.
JUST KIDDING.
BUT THEY DO MAGNIFY TEXT.
>> I NEED THESE BABIES.
I GOT AFRICAN DRUMMING TONIGHT,
AND I GOT TO SEE MY CONGAS.
>> I GOT TO BE ABLE TO READ.
EVERY MORNING, I READ "THE KITE
RUNNER" IN FULL ON THE TOILET.
>> LITTLE RED GLASSES.
THEY ARE THE BEST IN THE ORANGE.
THIS IS A HAIKU.
>> COME ON, WE'RE GETTING
PIEROGIS, LET'S GET IN THE CAR,
LET'S GO.
>> WITH LITTLE RED GLASSES --
>> ARE WE 50 OR 25?
>> THE ANSWER IS 57.
>> THEY'RE FOR WOMEN WITH NAMES
LIKE BITSY, PIPSY, AND RAHEL.
HERE'S RAHEL NOW.
>> HOW RED ARE MY GLASSES?
I HAVE A CELESTIAL SEASONINGS
CREDIT CARD.
AND HOW LITTLE ARE THEY?
I'M THE MOST UPTIGHT BUDDHIST
YOU'VE EVER MET IN YOUR LIFE.
>> HOW RED ARE MY GLASSES?
I LIKE MY PEANUT BUTTER LIKE I
LIKE MY DOGS.
HOMEMADE, CHUNKY, AND TERRIBLE.
HOW LITTLE ARE THEY?
I ONCE WENT DOWN ON LEONARD
COHEN.
>> WE -- WE ALL DID.
>> LITTLE RED GLASSES HAVE THE
EYE-CATCHING QUALITIES OF A STOP
SIGN, AND THEY PAIR PERFECTLY
WITH THINGS THAT MAKE ME MEAN.
LIKE IF I'M IN THE SAUNA, YOU
KNOW YOU'RE SEEING EVERYTHING.
>> ALL MY DRESS-UP CLOTHES ARE A
LITTLE BIT ASIAN.
>> EVERY THREE WEEKS, I GO TO
POMPEII.
>> I WAS AHEAD OF THE CURVE ON
GAY MARRIAGE, AND THAT'S WHERE
IT STOPPED.
>> ME TOO!
>> COME ON, WE'RE GETTING
ETHIOPIAN.
EVERYBODY WASH YOUR HANDS, LET'S
GO.
>> DON'T JUST TAKE US FROM US.
ASK YOUR CELEBRITY SPOKESWOMAN,
GREAT "BRITISH BAKING SHOW"
JUDGE COOLEY.
>> HELLO.
AND I'M NOT BEING DISAPPOINTED
IN CAKE.
I'M WEARING LITTLE RED GLASSES,
AND YOU CAN TOO.
THEY COME IN ALL SORTS OF STYLES
LIKE OUTDOORSY, INDOORSY, THE
MOM FROM BOB'S BURGERS,
PROFESSOR TRELAWNY, AND CHUCK
SCHUMER.
NOW, HE'S A TENDER SPONGE.
>> ARE YOU WONDERING IF LITTLE
RED GLASSES ARE RIGHT FOR YOU?
ASK YOURSELF THIS.
DO YOU LOVE DANCING AT A WEDDING
WITH YOUR SHOES OFF?
>> DO YOU SEND YOUR FOOD BACK
EVERY TIME?
>> IS YOUR PROFESSION VERY BAD
THERAPIST?
>> GIRLS, I HAVE A CONFESSION.
I DON'T EVEN NEED GLASSES.
I'M DESTROYING MY EYES.
BUT I LOVE THE LOOK.
>> BITSY!
>> COME ON, WE'RE GOING ON A
">>> HEY, EVERYONE.
HOPE YOU'RE ENJOYING YOUR MEAL."
SINCE YOU'RE MY FAVORITE TABLE,
MIMOSAS ARE ON THE HOUSE.
>> OH, SLAY, THANK YOU!
>> THIS WHOLE PLACE IS SUCH A
SLAY.
HOW ARE YOUR EGGS, ROSA?
>>> THEY'RE ACTUALLY A SLAY.
>> THESE MIMOSAS ARE BLOWING
SLAY SHOTS AND VOMITING INTO THE
MOTHER BAG.
>> RIGHT!
>> THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH, CAN WE NOT?
>> WHAT, NO, XANDER, PIA, ARE
YOU GUYS OKAY?
WHY AREN'T YOU QUEENING OUT WITH
US?
>> I HAVE TO TELL YOU GUYS
SOMETHING.
SO IMPORTANT THAT WE HAVE TO
SING IT TO YOU.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> YOU'RE SCARING US, I'M KIND
OF GAG.
¶ YOU CAN'T JUST REPEAT ONE WORD
WHEN THERE'S SO MANY MORE TO
USE ¶
¶ SO WE'VE MADE A BIG DECISION
FOR ALL OF US AND YOU ¶
¶ NO MORE SLAY NO 94 SLAY ¶
¶ WE KNOW IT SOUNDS IMPOSSIBLE
BUT THERE'S OTHER WORDS TO SAY ¶
¶ FROM NOW ON WHEN SOMETHING
ROCKS WE'LL JUST SAY WOW I LIKE
THAT ¶
¶ AND THEN WE'LL STOP ¶
>> WHAT?
NO MORE SLAY?
BUT WHAT IF A WOMAN WE LOVE IS
WEARING AN OUTFIT THAT'S
AMAZING?
>> GREAT QUESTION.
WE'LL JUST SAY, "HEATHER, YOUR
DRESS LOOKS NICE."
>> "IT'S BLUE AND I LIKE THAT,
GOOD-BYE, HEATHER."
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT US TO
SAY?
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS, BUT YOUR
SOUL WAS KIND OF A BUST.
>> THANKS, BUT ALSO --
¶ NO MORE BUST NO MORE FLEX ¶
¶ NO MORE FLINGING THE MUD ON
THE TOILET NO MORE FEET ON
PEOPLE'S NECKS ¶
¶ I'M CONFUSED THAT LIVING MEANS
THE SAME THING AS DEATH ¶
¶ JUST SAY GOOD OR BAD INSTEAD ¶
¶ AND NO MORE REHEATING NACHOS
THAT'S ONE'S ACTUALLY NEW ¶
¶ NIP IT IN THE BUD BEFORE THE
ENDLESSNESS ¶
¶ ON THE DAY THE WORLD ENDS WE
DON'T WANT THE LAST THING THAT
YOU SAY ¶
¶ TO BE, THIS IS NOT A SLAY ¶
>> BUT PEOPLE LOVE SLAY.
IT'S COOL.
>> IF IT WERE COOL, IT WOULDN'T
BE ON AN OLIPOP CAN.
>> BUT WAIT.
I WANT THINGS SLAY.
I DON'T WANT TO CHANGE THE WAY I
TALK.
AM I DELULU?
>> LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
¶ NO YOU'RE NOT DELULU YOU'RE
ACTUALLY 32 ¶
¶ YOU'RE A STRAIGHT WHITE WOMAN
WHO'S HONESTLY 42 PLUS 2 ¶
¶ YOU'RE 44 GIRL ¶
>> I THINK I SEE WHAT YOU TWO
MEAN.
THE OTHER DAY MY THERAPIST ASKED
ME HOW I WAS DOING, AND ALL I
COULD THINK TO SAY WAS VIVA
DOWN.
>> I GOT HIT BY A CAR AND THE
FIRST THING I SAID WAS NOT ME
GETTING HIT BY A CAR.
>> I SAW A BILLBOARD TODAY FOR
CHIPS AHOY! THAT SAID, WE AIN'T
NO CRUMBS.
YOU'RE A COOKIE, THERE IS
CRUMBS.
>> I NAMED MY SON MOTHER.
>> SEE?
COME ON.
>> COME ON, EVERYBODY.
¶ NO MORE SLAY NO MORE SLAY ¶
¶ THAT'S NOT OOMFIE SIS OR HUNTY
IT'S JUST ANOTHER GAY GUY ¶
¶ NO MORE SLAY NO MORE SLAY ¶
¶ WE STOLE WORDS FROM OTHER
PEOPLE AND WE'RE GIVING THEM
BACK TODAY ¶
FEEL LIKE SUCH A PART OF THIS
COMMUNITY.
EVERYONE WAS SO KIND ALL WEEK.
THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU, GOOD NIGHT!