>>> YOU'RE WATCHING CNN.
>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M ABBY PHILLIP.
IF YOU'RE JUST JOINING US,
PRESIDENT BIDEN HAS FINISHED
DELIVERING HIS STATE OF THE
UNION ADDRESS.
BIDEN NEEDED TO SHOW ENERGY
TONIGHT, AND HE DIDN'T
DISAPPOINT.
AFTER A BRIEF 45 MINUTES OF
SELFFIES ON THE WAY TO THE PODIUM,
BIDEN BEGAN HIS SPEECH
WITH A BANG.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I JUST POUNDED A CELSIUS.
LET'S DO THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
MR. SPEAKER,
TOO SLOW.
LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY. FOLKS,
TONIGHT, I'M GOING TO
COVER A LOT.
THERE'S GOING TO BE A LOT OF
APPLAUSE.
SO KAMALA, I HOPE YOU DIDN'T
SKIP LEG DAY, GIRL.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE UP AND DOWN
ALL NIGHT.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT!
LET'S GO!
NOW TONIGHT, I'M ALSO GOING TO
BE TALKING ABOUT MY PREDECESSOR,
MAINLY BECAUSE EVERY TIME I SAY
PREDECESSOR,
MIKE JOHNSON SHAKES HIS HEAD
LIKE HE JUST
ACCIDENTALLY CUT 30 SECONDS OF
THE SHOW EUPHORIA.
LOOK AT THAT WEIRDO.
I ACTUALLY TRIED TO FIX THE
BORDER CRISIS,
BUT THE BILL WAS
TANKED BY MY PREDECESSOR.
OH, OH, OH, YOU DON'T LIKE THAT?
OH, YOU DON'T LIKE THAT?
ANYBODY WANT TO SAY SOMETHING TO
ME?
>> I DO.
BOO!
LIAR.
>> DAMN IT.
WHOA.
MARGERY,
YEAH, THANKS FOR
DRESSING UP TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I WOULD STAY HERE AND
TALK TO Y'ALL MORE,
BUT I SAW A
GLIMPSE OF THE REPUBLICAN
SENATOR'S RESPONSE TO MY SPEECH,
AND I THINK SHE'S GOING TO HELP
ME MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE I CAN
SAY HERE.
ENJOY.
>> ALL IN ALL, A STRONG SPEECH
FROM PRESIDENT BIDEN.
BUT LET'S FOLLOW HIS ADVICE AND
TAKE A LOOK AT THE REPUBLICAN RESPONSE
FROM ALABAMA JUNIOR
SENATOR, KATIE BRITT.
>> GOOD EVENING, AMERICA.
MY NAME IS KATIE BRITT.
AND I HAVE THE HONOR OF
SERVING THE GREAT PEOPLE OF ALABAMA.
BUT TONIGHT, I'LL BE AUDITIONING
FOR THE PART OF SCARY MOM.
AND I'LL BE PERFORMING AN
ORIGINAL MONOLOGUE
CALLED THIS
COUNTRY IS HELL.
YOU SEE, I'M NOT JUST A SENATOR,
I'M A WIFE, A MOTHER,
AND THE
CRAZIEST BITCH IN THE TARGET
PARKING LOT.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE FUTURE OF
OUR CHILDREN,
AND THIS IS WHY
I'VE INVITED YOU INTO THIS
STRANGE, EMPTY KITCHEN.
BECAUSE REPUBLICANS WANTED ME TO
APPEAL TO WOMAN VOTERS,
AND
WOMEN LOVE KITCHEN.
BUT SERIOUSLY, MY HUSBAND WESLEY AND I
JUST WATCHED PRESIDENT
BIDEN'S SPEECH,
AND WHAT I SAW
WAS THE PERFORMANCE OF A
PERMANENT POLITICIAN.
BUT ME, I'M NOT PERFORMING.
I'M NOT.
BUT FIRST AND FOREMOST, I'M A
MOM.
AND LIKE ANY MOM, I'M GOING TO
DO A PIVOT OUT OF NOWHERE
INTO A
SHOCKINGLY VIOLENT STORY ABOUT
SEX TRAFFICKING.
AND REST ASSURED, EVERY DETAIL
ABOUT IT IS REAL,
EXCEPT THE YEAR, WHERE IT TOOK PLACE,
AND
WHO WAS PRESIDENT WHEN IT
HAPPENED.
AND TONIGHT, I AM NOT JUST
RESPONDING TO THE STATE OF THE
UNION.
I AM ALSO SELLING THESE GORGEOUS
BEJEWELED CROSS QUICK LASSES FOR
QVC.
THIS AFINTY DIAMOND NECKLACE
GOES WITH ANYTHING,
AND YOU CAN
WEAR IT FROM DA CHURCH TO DA
CLUB.
AND NOW I'M GOING TO GET REALLY
SEDUCTIVE FOR NO APPARENT
REASON.
AS I WAS SAYING,
THE AMERICAN DREAM HAS TURNED INTO A
NIGHTMARE.
YOU KNOW, MY HUSBAND WESLEY AND I
SPEND A LOT OF TIME IN THIS
KITCHEN WORRYING.
KITCHENS ARE WHERE FAMILIES HAVE
THE HARD CONVERSATIONS.
LIKE THE ONE WE'LL HAVE TOMORROW
ABOUT HOW MOMMY FREAKED OUT THE
ENTIRE COUNTRY.
BUT, Y'ALL, BIDEN'S THE ONE WHO
IS DESTROYING OUR COUNTRY.
JUST ASK YOURSELF,
ARE YOU BETTER OFF TODAY THAN YOU WERE
FOUR YEARS AGO?
BACK IN THE GOOD OLD DAYS OF 2020,
THE YEAR THAT NOTHING BAD
HAPPENED.
♪ AND IT CAN BE THAT WAY AGAIN ♪
OH, GOSH, I GUESS I CAN SING.
THAT'S SO GREAT.
BUT OUR COUNTRY IS NOT.
IT'S LIKE I TELL MY KIDS EVERY
NIGHT.
WE ARE STEEPED IN THE BLOOD OF
PATRIOTS IN A CASTLE MADE OF
BONES.
GOOD NIGHT, KIDS.
AND SPEAKING OF TEA, MY TEA IS
READY.
BUT TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WHO
ARE STRUGGLING RIGHT NOW,
KNOW
THIS.
WE HEAR YOU.
WE SEE YOU.
WE SMELL YOU.
WE'RE INSIDE YOUR KITCHEN RIGHT NOW
LOOKING THROUGH YOUR FRIDGE.
AND WHAT'S THAT ON THE TOP
SHELF?
MIGRANTS.
I THINK THAT ANALOGY WENT WELL.
IN CONCLUSION, TO THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES,
I'LL JUST
SAY THIS, MR. BIDEN,
THIS ISN'T
THE LAST YOU'LL SEE OF KATIE
BRITT.
MAYBE NOT IN POLITICS,
BUT WHEN YOU CLOSE YOUR EYES,
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, JOSH
BROLIN!
THANK
I LOVE BEING HERE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN 12 YEARS
SINCE I LAST HOSTED.
AND I'VE MISSED THIS PLACE.
I MEAN, SO MUCH HAS CHANGED.
NOT REALLY.
IT'S THE SAME.
BUT THE BAND -- I MEAN, A COUPLE
GUYS, BUT IT'S ALL --
ANYWAY, IT
ALL SEEMS DIFFERENT, BUT IT'S
THE SAME.
THE FIRST TIME I HOSTED WAS IN 2008,
MUSICAL GUEST WAS SOMEONE
I HAD NEVER HEARD OF BEFORE,
ADELE.
NOW SHE'S A GLOBAL SUPERSTAR.
THE SECOND TIME I HOSTED, THE
MUSICAL GUEST WAS GOTIER,
AND
NOW HE'S JUST SOMEONE THAT I
USED TO KNOW.
12 YEARS.
WHERE DOES IT GO?
I MEAN, LOOK AT THE MILESTONES
THAT WE'VE EXPERIENCED.
MARTHA STEWART AND SNOOP DOGG
RIPPING BONG HITS TOGETHER.
CARDI B'S HIT SONG WET ASS
PASTRAMI.
I WAS A PURPLE DUDE, THANOS WITH
A SCROTUM CHIN
THAT SNAPPED ALL
THE POPULATION INTO DUST.
IT'S BEEN A GOOD 12 YEARS.
I'VE BEEN DIRECTING, I'VE BEEN
WRITING A LOT.
I WROTE AN APPARENTLY SUPER
CREEPY POEM ABOUT TIMOTHEE
CHALAMET.
I DON'T THINK IT'S CREEPY, BUT
YOU BE THE JUDGE.
LIGHTS.
YOUR FACE IS ETCHED BY
ADOLESCENCE.
YOUR CHEEKBONES JUT TOWARD
WHAT ARE YOUTH EYES THAT SLIDE DOWN A
PROMINENT NOSE
AND ON TO LIPS OF
A CERTAIN POETRY.
I MEAN, IT'S WEIRD, YEAH.
BUT I --
NO, I DON'T WANT TO
SLEEP WITH HIM.
BUT THAT'S WHAT I DO.
I WRITE POEMS ABOUT EVERYONE I
WORK WITH.
LIKE THIS WEEK, I WROTE A POEM
ABOUT KENAN.
>> WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY NOW?
>> REMEMBER?
WE WERE REHEARSING,
AND I WAS
LOOKING AT YOU, YOUR FACE, AND I
JUST GOT INSPIRED.
LIGHTS.
I LOOK AT YOU WITH YOUR AGELESS FACE
AND SLIDE DOWN FURROWED
BROW UNTO SULTRY EYES.
THEN JUMPING OFF UNDER YOUR
SUGAR COOKIE CHEEKS
INTO THE
DIVETS OF YOUR LAUGH LINES
AWAKENS IN ME A SYMPHONY OF DESIRE,
TO WHICH I CAN ONLY
SAY -- WHAT UP WITH THAT?
>> COOL, COOL, COOL, COOL, COOL,
COOL.
>> LOVE YOU.
ANY WHO, I WRITE A LOT.
I MEAN HAVE A BOOK COMING OUT
LATER THIS YEAR
CALLED "FROM
UNDER THE TRUCK."
THAT WHOLE BOOK IS ABOUT KENAN.
SO THIS IS MY THIRD TIME
HOSTING, AND, MAN, THERE'S JUST
NOTHING LIKE IT.
YOU KNOW I'VE BEEN DOING COLD
PLUNGES FOR 20 YEARS, RIGHT?
AND THE ONLY THING I CAN COMPARE
THIS SHOW TO IS THAT.
HOSTING IS LIKE JUMPING INTO AN
ICE BATH, YOU KNOW.
SCARY, IT'S EXHILARATING,
YOUR PENIS IS IN YOUR STOMACH.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY TO PREPARE
FOR IT.
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO IS JUST
JUMP RIGHT IN.
SURRENDER TO THE DISCOMFORT.
YOU READY FOR THIS?
I AM INEVITABLE!
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
ARIANA GRANDE IS HERE,
SO STICK
AROUND.
>>> WELL, CONGRATULATIONS, MS. POPLY,
YOUR BUSINESS ACCOUNT
IS OFFICIALLY OPEN.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, CHELSEA.
OH, THIS IS SO GREAT.
>> SHE'S A BUSINESS OWNER.
MEANWHILE, WE'RE MAKING CHECK
DEPOSITS LIKE IT'S 1995.
>> BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY,
HON.
LAST TIME WE TRIED E THE DEPOSITING
I ACCIDENTALLY POSTED
BY SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER ON
ZILLOW.
>> THIS IS A ROBBERY!
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO TO
US?
HANDS
>> SLIDE YOUR PHONES ACROSS THE
FLOOR.
>> MOVE.
COME ON!
>> DON'T YOU DARE TOUCH ME.
DO NOT.
>> BE QUIET AND NO ONE GETS
HURT, OKAY?
>> NO ONE GETS HURT?
YEAH RIGHT.
I'VE SEEN ENOUGH MOVIES TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS TO A CHICK LIKE ME.
TAKE ME TO THE VAULT AND GET IT
OVER WITH YOU NASTY BOYS.
>> WHAT?
LADY, SHUT UP.
>> WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
JUST WATCH?
>> WATCH WHAT?
>> WATCH HELPLESS AS YOU HAVE
YOUR WAY WITH MY SUPPLE WIFE?
>> THIS IS SO MESSED UP.
>> AND WHO'S GOING TO FILM IT?
HIM?
>> FILM IT?
>> I'M SO MAD I CAN'T SEE
STRAIGHT RIGHT NOW.
>> SHUT UP!
NO ONE'S FILMING ANYTHING.
>> WHO HERE IS THE BANK MANAGER?
>> I AM.
I'M THE MANAGER.
>> ALL RIGHT, GLASSES.
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO THE VAULT
AND PUT IN THE COMBINATION.
GOT
>> AND YOU BETTER NOT TRIP THE
DISTRESS ALARM.
>> DON'T TOUCH HIM.
TOUCH ME!
HE PROBABLY HAS SOME FAMILY, AND
I'M JUST SOME CHICK.
>> MOVE, LADY.
>> WHY ARE YOUR HANDS TIED UP?
>> WE TIED OURSELVES
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE YOU SICKOS
THE SATISFACTION.
YOU PROBABLY ARE GOING TO TAKE
MY CHICK IN THE BACK
AND LAY HER
ON A BED OF QUARTERS AND MAKE A
SMUT FILM IN THE VAULT.
YOU MAKE ME SICK.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THE FILM?
ROBIN ROBIN OR STICKUP AT
ROBIN'S?
>> HER NAME IS ROBIN, OKAY?
>> YOU GUYS SHUT UP.
NO ONE WANTS TO OR IS GOING TO
DO ANYTHING WITH YOUR WIFE.
>> OH, I GET IT.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE YOUR WAY
WITH ME INSTEAD?
YOU KNOW THIS, IF YOU TRY ANY
FUNNY BUSINESS, I WILL JUST
SCREAM, AND I WILL SCREAM LIKE
THIS, EHHHHH!
>> THAT'S YOUR SCREAM?
>> ISN'T IT YOUR LUCKY DAY?
WE JUST OPENED UP OUR MARRIAGE.
>> AND WE WERE BOTH PRETTY
NERVOUS ABOUT OPENING THINGS UP,
SO WE MADE A LOT OF RULES.
>> AND EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THE
RULES ALLOWS ME TO BE WITH MEN.
>> Y'ALL ARE NASTY.
CAN YOU JUST SHUT UP SO THEY CAN
ROB US IN PEACE?
>> GUYS, WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
I'VE BEEN IN THE VAN FOR TEN
MINUTES.
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT, A BARELY
LEGAL LATINO.
THAT'S COOL, RIGHT?
>> A BARELY LEGAL LATINO IS
MUCHO COOL.
>> OKAY.
I'M NOT BARELY LEGAL.
I'M 31.
EWW.
WHAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
>> THIS WEIRD COUPLE IS TRYING
TO HOOK UP WITH US.
>> AND THIS PERVERT WANTS TO
FILM IT.
>> I DO NOT WANT TO FILM IT.
THAT WAS THEIR SUGGESTION.
>> WELL, THERE'S ANOTHER BANK ON
THE EAST SIDE.
SHOULD WE JUST GO THERE?
>> NO, YOU IDIOT.
WE'RE ALREADY HERE.
OKAY?
YOU NEED TO MAN UP, OKAY?
AND THEN LET'S FINISH WHAT WE
STARTED HERE, ALL RIGHT?
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
>> REMEMBER US?
>> YEAH!
YOU SICKOS.
>> WHY ARE YOU HAND CUFFED AND
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR?
>> BECAUSE I'VE SEEN ENOUGH
MOVIES TO KNOW WHAT'S COMING
NEXT FOR A CHICK LIKE ME.
>> BUT KNOW THIS, I DO PILATES,
OKAY?
IT'S GOING TO HURT WAY MORE THAN
IT'S GOING TO HURT ME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> THE COPS!
>> LET'S GO.
LET'S GO!
STOP IT!
>> OH, THE BOYS IN BLUE!
I HOPE THOSE BEEFY PIGS DON'T
TRY TO JOIN IN.
>> BUT IF THEY DO, HE'S GOING TO
FILM IT.
>> KEEP ME OUT OF IT!
>> HEADPHONES, SIR?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> THAT'LL BE 29.99.
>> WHAT?
NO.
NEVER MIND, THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHTY, SIR.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG
FLIGHT.
♪ I'M ON THIS FLIGHT TO PHOENIX,
AND MY PHONE'S GOT NO POWER, I
GOT NO DAMN ENTERTAINMENT FOR
THREE WHOLE HOURS ♪
♪ WHEN OUT THE CORNER OF MY EYE,
I AM SAFE FROM DISASTER, THE MAN
TO MY RIGHT IS WATCHING BRAD
PITT IN AD ASTRA, AND NOW I AM
THE MAN WHO WATCHES THE MAN WHO
WATCHES THE MOVIE CATTY CORNER
TO ME ♪
♪ MY KINDLE IS DEAD, I AM RAW
DOGGING THIS FLIGHT, SO I WILL
WATCH WHAT HE WATCHES, THE MAN
TO MY RIGHT ♪
♪ I GOT MY KINDLE AND SOME
HEADPHONES, LIFE COULDN'T BE
BETTER AND WHEN I LOOK UP I SEE
THEY GOT MY FAVORITE MOVIE
EVER ♪
♪ I'M WATCHING AD ASTRA, BRAD
PITT'S IN THE ZONE, I LOOK OVER
MY SHOULDER AND REALIZED I AM
NOT ALONE ♪
♪ BECAUSE BACK THERE IS A MAN,
HE'S WATCHING ME, MAN, HE'S
WATCHING MY MOVIE, CATTY CORNER
TO ME ♪
♪ HIS BREATH IS ON MY NECK, I
CAN'T KEEP WATCHING LIKE THIS, I
GO TO TURN OFF THE MOVIE, HIS
HAND GRABS MY WRIST ♪
♪ DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING, I
GOT NOTHING TO DO, MY KINDLE IS
DEAD, SO I AM LIVING THROUGH
YOU ♪
♪ HOW CAN YOU EVEN WATCH IT,
THERE'S NO CAPTIONS, I'LL KEEP
IT ON IF YOU CAN TELL ME WHAT
JUST HAPPENED ♪
♪ PROBABLY BRAD IS AD ASTRA, NO
THAT'S NOT HIS NAME ♪
♪ THEN WHO THE HELL IS AD ASTRA,
YOU SOUND TOTALLY INSANE.
HERE JUST PLAY MY SUDOKU ♪
♪ I DO NOT KNOW HOW, I NEVER
LEARNED THE RULES, AND I AM NOT
STARTING NOW ♪
>> WOULD YOU TWO SHUT UP?
♪ THIS POUR SOUL HAS NOTHING,
HIS KINDLE IS DEAD, ONE DAY IT
COULD BE YOU WITH NOTHING TO DO
BUT STARE AHEAD ♪
♪ I AM THE AIR MARSHALL, ON MY
PLANE THERE'S ONE RULE, YOU MUST
DO UNTO OTHERS AS YOU WOULD HAVE
THEM DO TO YOU ♪
♪ BECAUSE ONE DAY YOU'LL BE THE
MAN WHO WATCHES THE MAN WHO
WATCHES THE MOVIE CATTY CORNER
TO ME ♪
♪ IF YOUR KINDLE IS DEAD AND
YOU'RE RAW DOGGING THIS FLIGHT,
THEN YOU WILL WATCH WHAT HE
WATCHES, THE MAN TO YOUR RIGHT ♪
♪ YEAHHHHH ♪
>> ENJOY YOUR FLIGHT.
I HATE IT.
IT LOOKS STUPID ON ME.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING TO SAY.
I LOVE IT BUT IT'S STUPID.
>> OKAY.
LET'S GET STARTED THEN.
EVERYONE, WELCOME BACK TO THE
PEOPLE PLEASERS SUPPORT GROUP.
>> IT'S SO GOOD TO BE HERE.
>> YEA, WE'RE BACK.
>> AND NOT EVERYONE NEEDS TO
TALK AT ONCE.
>> TOTALLY.
>> NOT EVERYONE CAN HEAR.
>> WE SHOULDN'T ALL BE TALKING.
>> YOU'RE ALL HERE BECAUSE
YOU'RE TERRIFIED OF CONFLICT, SO
YOU AGREE WITH LITERALLY
EVERYTHING EVERYONE SAYS.
BUT WE'RE HERE TO HEAL.
WHO WANTS TO SHARE FIRST TODAY?
>> I'LL GO.
THIS WEEK, MY BOYFRIEND WANTED
TO GO OUT TO DINNER, BUT I
ALREADY ATE.
>> SO WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> I SAID, SOUNDS GREAT.
I'M HUNGRY.
I'LL DRIVE, UNLESS YOU WANT TO.
NO WORRIES AT ALL.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WOULD HAVE
DONE.
>> IT'S FINE TO HAVE TWO
DINNERS.
>> LIKE WE SAID LAST WEEK,
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO BE
ASSERTIVE AND SAY NO.
>> TOTALLY.
THAT'S ACTUALLY WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
>> BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU DID.
>> YOU'RE SO RIGHT.
I DID NOT DO THAT BECAUSE I
COULD NOT DO THAT.
I'M DUMB.
>> DON'T CALL YOURSELF DUMB.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO, THEN NO
WORRIES.
>> NO, MIKE, IT'S NOT NO
THAT'S A PHRASE WE TRY TO AVOID
ALONG WITH ALL GOOD EITHER WAY,
NO TOTALLY, AND I'M FINE WITH
WHATEVER, ANGEL.
MIKE, WHY DON'T YOU SHARE?
>> OKAY.
I'VE BEEN REALLY WANTING TO
BREAK UP WITH MY GIRLFRIEND.
>> YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THAT FOR A
LONG TIME.
YOU NEED TO DUMP HER.
>> BUT WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SO
LONG, AND SHE REALLY UNDERSTANDS
ME.
>> YOU CAN'T BREAK UP NOW, LOVE
IS SO IMPORTANT.
>> I DECIDED BREAKING UP WAS THE
RIGHT THING TO DO, SO I SAT HER
DOWN TO DO IT.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
HOW DID IT GO?
>> WENT REALLY WELL.
I PROPOSED, AND WE'RE GETTING
MARRIED.
IS THAT GOOD?
>> NO.
I THINK WE ALL KNOW THAT'S NOT
GOOD.
OKAY.
WHO'S NEXT?
HEY, SAM, BUDDY, DO YOU WANT TO
MAYBE TELL US ABOUT YOUR NEW
HAIR?
DID YOU GO TO THE BARBER AND
THEY SAID THEY HAD AN IDEA?
AND YOU KNEW IT WAS BAD
IMMEDIATELY, BUT YOU JUST
WATCHED THEM DO IT AND THEN YOU
SAID I LOVE IT, THANK YOU.
>> BUT CAN I SAY SOMETHING IN MY
DEFENSE?
I GAVE THEM A HUGE TIP.
>> OKAY.
WHO'S NEXT?
WHERE IS SERAFINA?
>> HEY, EVERYONE.
SORRY I'M LATE.
I GOT HIT BY A CAR, AND I WAS
LIKE, OH, MY GOD, I'M SO SORRY,
CAR, I HOPE YOU'RE OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, SERAFINA, WHY
DON'T YOU SHARE?
>> OKAY.
WELL, I HATE MY JOB, SO I NEED
TO QUIT.
BUT THEY GIVE ME GREAT HEALTH
INSURANCE, AND IT'S SO NICE OF
THEM TO PAY ME.
>> SHE HAS TO STAY FOR THE
HEALTH INSURANCE.
>> OF COURSE.
WHAT IF SHE GETS SICK.
>> HOW ABOUT WE TRY A ROLE PLAY
EXERCISE?
CHARLIE, CAN YOU PLAY HER BOSS?
>> YES.
UNLESS SOMEONE ELSE WANTS TO.
WHATEVER IS FINE.
>> SO CHARLIE IS YOUR BOSS.
TRY ASKING HIM FOR A RAISE.
>> OKAY.
I NEED A RAISE.
>> NO, TOTALLY.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT RAISE.
SORRY.
I'M SUCH A BAD BOSS.
YOU CAN HAVE MY JOB.
>> NO, YOU'RE GREAT.
I'M DOING BAD AS AN EMPLOYEE.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY FIRE ME.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> I'M DUMB, YOU'RE SMART.
>> WE ARE BOTH SMART AND STUPID.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> I'M THE COMPANY'S CEO, AND
YOU'RE BOTH SO AMAZING, YOU
SHOULD HAVE MY JOB.
I DON'T DESERVE IT.
I'M RESIGNING.
>> STOP.
WHAT HAPPENED THERE WAS BAD.
IN THAT EXERCISE, EVERYONE LOST
THEIR JOBS.
>> WELL, I THINK THEY DID THEIR
BEST.
>> YEAH.
AND I AGREE -- IF THAT'S OKAY
WITH YOU.
>> I THINK OUR WORK IS DONE
HERE.
LET'S ALL SAY THE PEOPLE
PLEASERS PRAYER OF DEFERENCE.
>> GOD, GRANT ME THE SERENITY TO
SAY NO, BUT IF YOU'RE TOO BUSY
WITH HEAVEN, THEN NO WORRIES.
AMEN.
OR A-MEN, WHATEVER YOU PREFER.
I LIKE THAT ONE.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT'S THE CABERNET, AND THE
BOOK SAYS TO PAIR THAT WITH THE
AGED GOUDA.
>> MM.
THAT'S GOOD.
YEAH.
>> GOSH, RICK AND MELISSA, THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING US OVER.
>> YEAH.
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A WINE AND
CHEESE NIGHT BEFORE.
>> WELL, WE HAVE A PASSION FOR
WINE AND A PASSION FOR FINE
CHEESE.
WE'RE SO HAPPY TO GET TO SHARE
IT WITH ALL OF YOU.
>> OH, MY GOSH, BABE, LOOK WHO
DECIDED TO JOIN US.
TIGER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> AWW, SHE LOVES YOU.
>> THE LITTLE GUY JUST WALKED
RIGHT UP AND CURLED UP IN MY
LAP.
>> WELL, THAT IS SPECIAL.
TIGER NEVER COMES OUT WHEN WE
HAVE COMPANY, AND HE NEVER
SNUGGLES UP TO ANYONE LIKE THAT.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> NOT THAT I CAN REMEMBER.
CHRIS, YOU MUST HAVE GOOD
ENERGY.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, I HOPE YOU GUYS ARE
READY FOR A TRIP TO ESPANIA
BECAUSE UP NEXT WE HAVE A ROIJA.
>> THE CAT NEVER DOES THIS?
>> NOT REALLY.
LIKE MELISSA SAID, YOU MUST HAVE
GOOD ENERGY.
>> I HOPE SO.
I MEAN, THE CAT CHOSE ME, RIGHT?
MUST BE BECAUSE OF MY ENERGY.
>> YEAH.
>> SO, GUYS FOR THE RIOJA,
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO GET A
GOOD NOSE, SO REALLY GET IN
THERE.
>> CAT COULD'VE CHOSE ANYONE.
BUT HE CHOSE ME, SO I GUESS I
GOT GOOD ENERGY.
>> YEAH, CHRIS, ARE YOU OKAY,
MAN?
SEEMS LIKE THIS CAT THING IS
REALLY SIGNIFICANT TO YOU.
>> WELL, IT IS.
I WORRY I DON'T HAVE GOOD
ENERGY, SO IT'S GOOD TO KNOW
THAT I DO.
THAT'S AWESOME.
>> IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
ANYTHING GOING ON AT WORK OR?
>> NO, JUST SAME OLD, SAME OLD,
CLOSING DOWN NURSING HOMES AND
TURNING THEM INTO TOP GOLFS.
SAME AS IT EVER WAS.
>> GOD, I FORGET THAT'S WHAT YOU
DO.
>> BY THE WAY, WHAT HAPPENS TO
THE OLD FOLKS AFTER YOU SHUT
DOWN THE HOMES?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
PROBABLY SLEEP IN THE STREET.
I'M SORRY.
SO YOU'RE SAYING HE NEVER DOES
THIS?
>> I MEAN, WITH US HE DOES,
BUT -- ANYWAY, GUYS, WITH THE
RIOJA, YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO
TAKE A BITE OF THE MANCEGO.
>> LOOK, TIGER'S CUDDLED UP WITH
RANDALL NOW.
>> YEAH.
LITTLE GUY CRAWLED OVER AND
CURLED UP ON MY LAP.
>> THIS IS CRAP.
>> WELL, YOU MUST HAVE GOOD
ENERGY TOO, RANDALL.
>> OH, MUST HE?
MUST HE HAVE GOOD ENERGY?
OR IS IT JUST YOUR CAT IS ONE
BIG DAMN SLUT?
>> HEY, NOW, CHRIS, THERE'S NO
NEED TO CALL MY CAT THAT.
>> HEY, I JUST CALLS THEM LIKE I
SEES THEM.
YOUR CAT'S A SLUT, BUSSING IT
OPEN FOR EVERY LAP AT THIS
LAME-ASS WINE AND CHEESE NIGHT.
>> YOU TAKE THAT BACK!
>> WHATEVER.
THIS PARTY SUCKS.
ZERO SINGLE CHICKS.
DUDES ARE ALL MID.
BY THE WAY, YOUR HOUSE SMELLS
LIKE A FART.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S BEEN
PARTING ALL NIGHT, CHRIS.
>> I'M EATING CHEESE AND WINE,
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO RIP A LITTLE
ASS?
YOU WANT ME TO DIE?
>> NONE OF US HAVE BEEN RIPPING
ASS ALL NIGHT, CHRIS.
>> BS.
YOU REALLY EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN BLOWING CHEESE
SMOKE INTO THAT CUSHION ALL
NIGHT?
>> MAYBE ONCE, BUT THAT'S IT.
>> SO YOU HAVE?
SO YOU KNOWINGLY HAVE?
SO YOU KNOWINGLY HAVE AND YET
ACTED LIKE I WAS THE ONLY ONE
RIPPING IT UP.
F THIS!
>> YOU'RE SCARING MY LADY!
OKAY?
NOW, I'M SORRY THAT TIGER IS
WITH RANDALL, BUT YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A CHILD!
>> OW!
>> RICK, LOOK, TIGER'S BACK WITH
CHRIS.
>> YEAH.
LITTLE GUY JUST CRAWLED UP AND
CURLED UP IN MY LAP.
>> HE GRABBED HIM OFF MY LAP,
AND TIGER BIT HIS ARM.
>> LIAR.
>> CHRIS, YOU'RE BLEEDING A LOT.
YOU SHOULD GO TO A HOSPITAL.
>> NEVER.
I'LL DIE HERE.
I'LL DIE HERE HAPPY, AND IF YOU
GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT, THEN
I'LL JUST TAKE YOU OUT WITH ME.
>> GO AHEAD.
MAKE MY DAY!
VIENNA
OUTDONE YOURSELF THIS TIME.
>> YES, THIS IS TRULY QUITE THE
AFFAIR.
>> GENTLEMEN, YOU FLATTER ME.
>> THE ARCH DUCHESS WILL BE HERE
SHORTLY.
MAY I REMIND YOU THAT A MARRIAGE
WOULD NOT ONLY INCREASE YOUR RANK
BUT STABILIZE THE FAMILY
FOR YEARS TO COME.
>> YES, BUT I HEAR SHE'S A
DIFFICULT WOMAN TO IMPRESS.
>> INDEED, SHE'S SEEN MANY OF
THE WORLD'S GREAT SPLENDORS,
BUT
SHE HAS NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS.
>> WHAT IS IT, KINSKY?
>> I CALL IT THE SHRIMP TOWER.
I JUST THOUGHT OF IT LAST NIGHT.
>> I DO FEEL I'VE SEEN SHRIMP AT
A PARTY BEFORE.
I DON'T THINK SO
AND IT'S ALL SHRIMP?
>> INDEED, FROM TOP TO BOTTOM,
NOTHING BUT SHRIMP.
SHRIMP, SHRIMP, SHRIMP, OR AS I
LIKE TO CALL THEM,
THE SINKING
MAN'S MOZZARELLA SHRIMP.
QUITE
>> I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE IT
DOES SEMIPRECARIOUSLY PLACED.
>> THAT'S PART OF ITS CHARM.
IF ANYTHING WERE TO HAPPEN TO MY
SHRIMP TOWER,
I WOULD OBVIOUSLY
KILL MYSELF.
>> WAIT.
SHE'S HERE.
>> THE ARCH DUCHESS,
KLAUSTENBERG.
>> MY GOD, SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> COUNT KINSKY, THANK YOU FOR
INVITING ME TO YOUR PALACE.
I MUST SAY, IT FEELS LIKE HOME,
AND PERHAPS ONE DAY, IT WILL BE.
>> I THINK THE SHRIMP TOWER IS
WORKING.
>> I MEAN, I SUPPOSE SO.
>> OH, LOOK, HE'S GOING TO DANCE
WITH HER.
>> KINSKY!
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
>> WHAT?
I THOUGHT SHE WAS GOING TO KNOCK
OVER THE SHRIMP TOWER.
>> GOOD GOD, MAN, WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING?
>> SO I'M INSANE.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO THOUGHT SHE
WAS GOING TO KNOCK OVER THE
SHRIMP TOWER.
SHOW OF HANDS, WHO ELSE THOUGHT
SHE WAS GOING TO KNOCK OVER THE
SHRIMP TOWER?
ONE PERSON, THANK YOU.
>> BUT KINSKY, YOU KILLED THE
POOR GIRL.
>> OH, GOD.
PERHAPS I OVERREACTED IN THE
HEAT OF THE MOMENT.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
>> I'M OKAY.
I WASN'T EVEN TRYING TO KNOCK
OVER THE SHRIMP TOWER.
>> KNOCK OVER THE SHRIMP TOWER?
>> KINSKY, YOU'VE DONE IT AGAIN.
>> LOOK, WE ALL AGREE THAT THE
NIGHT HAD TO BE SPECIAL,
AND THE
THING THAT MADE THE NIGHT
SPECIAL WAS THE SHRIMP TOWER.
WE MUST PROTECT THE SHRIMP TOWER
AT ALL COSTS.
YOU ARE PROFESSOR OF LOGIC, DO
YOU DETECT ANY ERROR IN MY
THINKING?
>> THE MAN'S LOGIC IS SOUND.
>> WELL, IF HE SAYS HE'S RIGHT.
>> THAT IS ALL I'M SAYING.
NOW, COULD I HAVE PERHAPS
HANDLED IT BETTER?
SURE.
BUT I'M HUMAN.
WHICH IS UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE I
WISH I WERE A SHRIMP.
>> GOOD HEAVENS, MAN, YOU'VE GOT
SHRIMP ON THE BRAIN!
>> KINSKY, I HAVE SOMETHING I
WANT TO SAY!
I'VE SEEN THE WAY YOU
PASSIONATELY PROTECT THE THINGS YOU LOVE,
AND IF YOU CAN LOVE ME
AS MUCH AS YOU LOVE THAT SHRIMP TOWER,
WELL, THEN I WOULD BE THE
LUCKIEST GIRL IN EUROPE.
>> WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE KINSKY
HAS FOUND A BRIDE.
AND NOW LET US CELEBRATE BY
EATING THE SHRIMP.
>> YOU EAT IT BY THE TAIL?
>> HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO EAT IT?
BY THE HEAD?
>> KINSKY, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW, IN A WAY, I'M
RELIEVED.
ACTUALLY KIND OF LIBERATING, YOU
KNOW?
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I MUST SAY THE NIGHT
WAS A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
>> INDEED.
TO KINSKY, THE HAPPIEST MAN IN
THE WORLD.
>> TO KINSKY!
OUR TOPIC TODAY IS HE CHEAT OR
NAH?
PLEASE WELCOME JASMINE WHO SAYS
SHE'S FED UP WITH HER HUSBAND
JERRY AND SUSPECTS HE MAY BE
STEPPING OUT.
SO TELL US WHAT'S GOING ON,
JASMINE.
>> HEY, SHONDA.
I'M JUST FED UP, GIRL.
I DO EVERYTHING FOR THIS MAN.
I COOK FOR HIM, I CLEAN, I TAKE
CARE OF THE KIDS.
I EVEN WASH HIS FUNKY DIRTY
DRAWERS.
>> GIRL, HE SOUNDS LIKE A D-O-G,
GOING DOG, DUMP HIS ASS.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING HE DOESN'T
APPRECIATE YOU, JASMINE?
>> NOT AT ALL.
ALL HE DOES IS SIT IN FRONT OF
THE TV LIKE A DANG ZOMBIE.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, YOU ARE
BEAUTIFUL.
AND IF YOU WAS MY LADY, WE
WOULDN'T NEED NO TV.
>> THANK YOU.
THERE ARE STILL GENTLEMEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO JASMINE, WHY ARE YOU STILL
WITH THIS BUM?
>> BECAUSE HE WASN'T ALWAYS LIKE
THIS, SHONDA.
HE USED TO TAKE MY DANCING,
HIKING, AND WE HAD SEX ALL THE
TIME.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT NOW?
>> NOW HE'S ALWAYS TIRED, AND HE
DOESN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING, SO HE
MUST BE GETTING IT FROM SOMEBODY
ELSE.
>> AND WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SAY,
MA'AM?
>> HONEY, THERE IS NO EXCUSE.
THAT MAN IS NO GOOD, AND YOU
NEED TO DUMP HIS ASS QUICK.
>> WELL, GIRL, YOU KNOW OUR
AUDIENCE IS ALWAYS GOING TO TELL
IT LIKE IT IS.
SO WHAT DO YOU HOPE TO FIND OUT
TODAY?
>> SHONDA, I DO EVERYTHING FOR
THIS MAN, AND HE GIVES ME
NOTHING, SO I JUST WANT TO KNOW
IS HE CHEATING OR NAH.
>> WELL, LET'S BRING THAT DIRTY
CHEATER OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO AHEAD AND BRING OUT
JERRY.
>> BOO!
>> BOO.
>> NOPE.
I AIN'T FOOLING WITH THIS.
>> OKAY.
SO, JERRY, JASMINE SAYS YOU TWO
ARE NOT INTIMATE ANYMORE.
>> SHE BROKE MY DAMN NECK.
>> RIGHT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, THAT'S REALLY
COOL, YEAH.
>> NO.
NO.
IT'S NOT COOL.
I STILL HAVE NEEDS.
MAYBE YOU CAN'T HUMP, BUT YOU
CAN STILL GO DOWNTOWN LIKE YOU
USED TO.
>> THAT'S HOW I BROKE MY DAMN
NECK, YOU SLAMMED DOWN ON ME.
>> BECAUSE I LIKED IT.
TAKE THE COMPLIMENT.
>> OH, WOW.
DO YOU WANT TO ADD SOMETHING,
MA'AM?
>> NO, I DO NOT.
>> OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S OUR SHOW, FOLKS.
>> NO.
I STILL HAVE QUESTIONS.
IF YOU'RE NOT CHEATING ON ME,
WHO ARE YOU LOSING ALL THAT
WEIGHT FOR?
>> YOU STOPPED FEEDING ME.
>> YEAH.
THIS IS MESSED UP.
I'M GOING TO GO PRAY IN SPANISH.
>> OKAY.
THEN WHY WERE YOU OUT ALL NIGHT
LAST WEEK?
>> CHAIR BATTERY DIED.
>> HUH-HUH.
GOD GON' GET Y'ALL FOR THIS
MESS.
EXCUSE ME.
>> WELL, JASMINE DOESN'T KNOW
THIS, BUT JERRY HAS ASKED THE
SHOW FOR A PATERNITY TEST ON
THEIR 2-YEAR-OLD SON, JERRY JR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
>> AIN'T MY KID.
>> NOW, WHY DO YOU SUSPECT JERRY
JR. MIGHT NOT BE YOURS?
>> HE'S BLACK.
>> BECAUSE MY GRANDFATHER'S
ITALIAN.
>> ALSO, I AIN'T GOT IT UP IN
FIVE YEARS.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE HARD TO
MAKE A BABY, RIGHT, Y'ALL?
>> YOU GO GIRL.
>> REALLY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I TRIED.
>> SHOOT.
WELL, WE HAVE THE TEST RESULTS
IF YOU WANT TO HEAR THEM.
>> I DO.
>> YES, PLEASE, READ THEM.
>> OKAY.
WHEN IT COMES TO 2-YEAR-OLD
JERRY JR., JERRY, YOU ARE NOT
THE FATHER.
>> OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?
>> I KNEW IT!
I KNEW IT!
I'M FREE.
>> YOU KNOW, LET'S TAKE A BREAK,
AND WHEN WE COME BACK -- YOU
KNOW WHAT?
WE NOT COMING BACK.
♪♪
♪ I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D UNDERSTAND ME
HOW COULD YOU
EVER EVEN TRY ♪
♪ I DON'T WANNA TIPTOE
BUT I DON'T WANNA HIDE
BUT I DON'T WANNA FEED
THIS MONSTROUS FIRE ♪
♪ JUST WANNA LET
THIS STORY DIE
AND I'LL BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WE CAN'T BE FRIENDS
BUT I'D LIKE TO
JUST PRETEND ♪
♪ YOU CLING TO YOUR
PAPERS AND PENS
WAIT UNTIL YOU
LIKE ME AGAIN ♪
♪ WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
MY LOVE
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ ME AND MY TRUTH
WE SIT IN SILENCE
MMM, BABY GIRL
IT'S JUST ME AND YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA ARGUE
BUT I DON'T WANNA BITE
MY TONGUE, YEAH
I THINK I'D RATHER DIE ♪
♪ YOU GOT ME MISUNDERSTOOD
BUT AT LEAST
I LOOK THIS GOOD ♪
♪ WE CAN'T BE FRIENDS
BUT I'D LIKE TO
JUST PRETEND ♪
♪ YOU CLING TO YOUR
PAPERS AND PENS
WAIT UNTIL YOU
LIKE ME AGAIN ♪
♪ WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
MY LOVE
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
MY LOVE
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ KNOW THAT YOU MADE ME
I DON'T LIKE HOW
YOU PAINT ME
YET I'M STILL HERE HANGING ♪
♪ NOT WHAT YOU MADE ME
IT'S SOMETHING
LIKE A DAYDREAM ♪
♪ BUT I FEEL SO SEEN
IN THE NIGHT
SO FOR NOW, IT'S ONLY ME ♪
♪ AND MAYBE THAT'S
ALL I NEED ♪
♪ WE CAN'T BE FRIENDS
BUT I'D LIKE TO
JUST PRETEND ♪
♪ YOU CLING TO YOUR
PAPERS AND PENS
WAIT UNTIL YOU
LIKE ME AGAIN ♪
♪ WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
MY LOVE
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
MY LOVE
I'LL WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE
♪ WAIT FOR YOU, WAIT FOR YOUR
LOVE, WAIT FOR YOUR LOVE, I KNOW
I ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, ON THURSDAY, SLEEPY JOE
FINALLY WOKE THE HELL UP.
PRESIDENT BIDEN DELIVERED THE
STATE OF THE UNION, AND HE
HONESTLY CRUSHED IT,
EVEN
TRUMP'S HOUSE ELF LINDSEY GRAHAM
WAS LAUGHING AND ENJOYING IT.
NORMALLY HE'S ONLY THAT HAPPY
WHEN WATCHING RUE PAUL'S DRAG
RACE.
SPEECH GREAT.
YOU COULD TELL THE BAR WAS LOW.
THE NEW YORK POST'S HEADLINE WAS
JUST, HE'S ALIVE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S LIKE A HEADLINE YOU SEE
ABOUT BIG FOOT.
BIDEN ALSO GOT A BIG RESPONSE
WHILE ADDRESSING THE ISSUE OF
ABORTION WHEN HE SAID WE'RE
ABOUT TO FIND OUT HOW MUCH
POLITICAL POWER WOMEN HAVE, THEN
HE TURNED TO KAMALA AND SAID,
EXCEPT YOU.
FORMER PRESIDENT AND CURRENT
REVERSE MORTGAGE APPLICANT
DONALD TRUMP CRITICIZED BIDEN'S
SPEECH SAYING THE WORDS ARE NOT
FLOWING SMOOTHLY OUT OF HIS
MOUTH.
WELL, WE CAN'T ALL SPEAK WITH
THE SAME EFFORTLESS GRACE AS
DONALD J. TRUMP.
>> JUST RECENTLY HEARD THAT
SAUDI ARABIA AND RUSSIA WILL --
UH --
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE JUST
INSERTED A COLONOSCOPY CAMERA.
>> SOME DEMOCRATS CRITERIA VISED
PRESIDENT BIDEN BY TALKING ABOUT
MIGRANTS BY USING THE WORD
ILLEGALS.
COME ON, HE'S 81 YEARS OLD.
HE MEANS WELL.
LIKE WHEN MY MOM PUT UP THAT
SIGN TO STOP ORIENTAL HATE.
COLIN, YOU GO.
>> BIDEN ALSO TOOK TIME TO SAY
SHRINKFLATION IS AFFECTING
SNICKERS BARS AND PEOPLE PAY THE
SAME AMOUNT FOR 10% FEWER
SNICKERS.
IT'S PRETTY RISKY FOR A WHITE
GUY WITH A STUTTER TO KEEP
SAYING THE WORD SNICKERS.
THE REPUBLICAN RESPONSE WAS
DELIVERED BY ALABAMA SENATOR
KATIE BRITT, WHO MADE SOME
CHOICES.
>> AS A MOM, I CAN'T QUIT
THINKING ABOUT THIS.
MR. PRESIDENT, ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
WE SEE YOU.
WE HEAR YOU.
AND WE STAND WITH YOU.
>> THANKS.
THOSE ARE ALL SCENES FROM HER
ONE-WOMAN SHOW, A BRITT MUCH.
IT'S THE PLAY CRITICS ARE
CALLING, IS SHE OKAY?
THAT WAS HONESTLY SOME OF THE
WORST ACTING I'VE EVER SEEN, AND
I'VE SEEN ME.
>> MITCH McCONNELL OFFICIALLY
ENDORSED DONALD TRUMP FOR
PRESIDENT BECAUSE DESPITE THEIR
DIFFERENCES, THEY ACTUALLY GO
WAY BACK.
DONALD TRUMP ENDORSED MARK
ROBINSON FOR NORTH CAROLINA
GOVERNOR CALLING ROBINSON MARTIN
LUTHER KING ON STEROIDS.
NOT TO BE CONFUSED WITH MARTIN
LUTHER KING ON OZEMPIC.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GO AGAIN, COLIN.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T HAVE IT TODAY.
>> I'M GLAD YOU TOLD IT.
MARJORIE TAYLOR GREEN, SEEN HERE
DRESSED FOR HER SHIFT AT TGI
CRAZIES WAS QUESTIONED BY A
REPORTER ABOUT HER JEWISH SPACE
LASERS CONSPIRACY THEORY, AND
GREEN RESPONDED LIKE THIS.
>> WHY DON'T YOU GO TALK ABOUT
JEWISH SPACE LASERS, AND REALLY
WHY DON'T YOU [ BLEEP ] OFF?
>> WOW.
EVEN MORE SHOCKING, LOOK WHAT
HAPPENS A LITTLE LATER IN THE
VIDEO.
>> REALLY, WHY DON'T YOU
[ BLEEP ] OFF.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> ARIZONA SENATOR KIRSTEN
CINEMA, WHO LOOKS LIKE ALL THE
FLINTSTONES AT ONCE, ANNOUNCED
THAT SHE IS RETIRING FROM THE
SENATE.
BUT I DOUBT ANY OF US WILL EVER
FORGET THE NAME OF SENATOR
CRYSTAL SALMONELLA ALL RIGHT.
>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT NBC
STUDIOS AND 30 ROCK HAVE BEEN
INFESTED WITH BED BUGS.
EVERYBODY LOOK UNDER YOUR SEATS.
>> NETFLIX ANNOUNCED IN JULY IT
WILL LIVE STREAM A FIGHT BETWEEN
MIKE TYSON AND JAKE PAUL.
BUT THE REAL FIGHT WILL BE MIKE
TYSON TRYING TO ANNOUNCE
NETFLIX.
>> IT'S HARD TO DO, SEE?
JET BLUE AND SPIRIT AIRLINES
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE CANCELING
THEIR PLANNED MERGER AFTER A
FEDERAL JUDGE TOLD JET BLUE,
GIRL, DON'T.
>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT
92-YEAR-OLD RUPERT MURDOCH IS
SET TO MARRY HIS 67-YEAR-OLD
GIRLFRIEND.
THE COUPLE ASKED IN LIEU OF
WEDDING GIFTS, SEND LUBE.
>> OH, GOOD, ANOTHER ONE.
>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT
92-YEAR-OLD RUPERT MURDOCH IS
SET TO MARRY HIS 67-YEAR-OLD
GIRLFRIEND.
THE COUPLE IS REGISTERED AT
CAMPBELL'S FUNERAL HOME.
OH, BOY, THIS IS A ROUGH DAY FOR
ME, MAN.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER, TWO
MALE HUMPBACK WHALES WERE
PHOTOGRAPHED HAVING SEX.
LEARN MORE ABOUT IT IN THE
HEARTBREAKING DRAMA HUMPBACK
MOUNTAIN.
>> A SOCIAL MEDIA INFLUENCER WAS
ARRESTED FOR ALLEGEDLY THROWING
A TAMPON AT BOUNCERS WHO WERE
REMOVING HER FROM A CLUB.
WELL, AT LEAST WE KNOW WHY SHE
WAS ACTING THAT WAY.
SHOULD I JUST GO HOME?
I'M GOING TO GO HOME.
>> A PENNSYLVANIA MAN HAS BEEN
SENTENCED TO TWO YEARS PROBATION
FOR SELLING BODY PARTS FOR THE
MORTUARIES, BUT STILL NO
PUNISHMENT FOR THE BUYER,
ARBY'S.
>> ARBY'S, WE HAVE YOUR GRANDPA.
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE"
>> WELCOME BACK TO MOVIE MUSICAL
MASTERPIECES.
I'M YOUR HOST, KEN BURNT.
WELL, IT'S OSCAR WEEKEND, AND
TONIGHT WE'RE LOOKING BACK AT
ONE OF THE FEW MOVIE MUSICALS
EVER NOMINATED FOR BEST PICTURE.
IT'S THE 2001 BAZ LUHRMANN FILM,
MOULIN ROUGE.
THE FILM'S CROWN JEWEL IS THE
ELEPHANT LOVE MEDIALLY, WHICH
STRUNG TOGETHER TEN POPULAR LOVE
SONGS LIKE ALL YOU NEED IS LOVE
AND I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
BUT WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW IS THAT
THE ORIGINAL MEDIALLY WAS MUCH,
MUCH LONGER SINCE THEY DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT SONGS THEY COULD GET
THE RIGHTS TO, JUST TO BE SAFE,
THEY TRIED MANY MORE THAT HAVE
NEVER BEEN SEEN.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SATIN, I WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
YOU KNOW I CANNOT FALL IN LOVE
WITH YOU.
>> WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A PROSTITUTE?
>> NO.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE SICK?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE ACTUALLY
AUSTRALIAN.
>> NO.
>> LOVE IS A SPLENDID THING.
ALL YOU NEED IS LOVE.
♪ SOME PEOPLE WANT TO FILL THE
WORLD WITH SILLY LOVE SONGS ♪
♪ WELL, WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT,
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW BECAUSE
HERE I GO AGAIN ♪
♪ LOVE LIFT US UP WHERE WE
BELONG, YOU BELONG WITH ME, YOU
BELONG WITH ME, A NAME, I CALL
MYSELF, FA, A LONG, LONG, WAY TO
RUN, SO I CREEP, YEAH, JUST KEEP
IT ON THE DOWN LOW, 'CUZ NOBODY
ELSE SUPPOSED TO KNOW ♪
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
>> THEY KNEW THEY COULD GET THE
RIGHTS TO HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SO
THEY FELL BACK ON THAT A LOT.
LET'S SEE SOME MORE.
♪ IN THE NAME OF LOVE, ONE NIGHT
IN THE NAME OF LOVE, WAITING FOR
TONIGHT, WHOA, WHEN YOU WILL BE
HERE IN MY ARMS ♪
♪ WAITING FOR TONIGHT, OH, I'VE
DREAMED OF THIS LOVE FOR SO
LONG, IT'S BEEN ONE -- DERWALL.
>> OH, NO!
YOU JUST COUGHED BLOOD INTO A
NAPKIN.
THAT'S MOVIE FOR DYING.
♪ JESUS TAKE THE WHEEL -- ON THE
BUS GO ROUND AND ROUND, SHE'LL
BE -- COME SAIL AWAY, COME SAIL
AWAY, SAIL AWAY WITH ME ♪
♪ THE ONLY MAN WHO COULD EVER
REACH ME WAS THE SON OF A
PREACHER MAN, THE ONLY MAN WHO
COULD EVER TEACH ME WAS THE SON
OF A PREACHER MAN ♪
♪ I FEEL LIKE A WOMAN, BOW, BOW,
BOW, HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪
>> BAZ LUHRMANN ALSO TRIED TO
TIE THE SONG LADY MARMALADE INTO
THE DIALOGUE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SATIN, WE NEED YOU ON STAGE.
IT'S SHOW TIME!
AND AS WE SAY AT THE MOULIN
ROUGE, HAY SISTER, SOUL SISTER,
BETTER GET THAT DOUGH, SISTER.
>> DO WE SAY THAT?
I'M NOT SURE I'VE EVER HEARD
THAT.
>> DID I TELL YOU, I FINALLY
LEARNED FRENCH.
>> TELL US A LITTLE.
>> IT GOES KITCHY KITCHY YA-YA
DA DA.
KITCHY KITCHY YA-YA HERE.
IT MEANS MOCHA CHOCO LA LA.
>> OH, SATIN, YOU'RE FAINTING.
>> I'M DYING.
>> OH, BUT CAN YOU SING A LITTLE
BIT MORE?
>> JUST A LITTLE.
>> ME TOO.
♪ 'CUZ I III WILL ALWAYS LOVE
YOU, IIII CAN'T HELP LOVING --
HOW WONDERFUL LIFE IS NOW YOU'RE
IN -- HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO -- OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
HISTORY.
>> FOUR HOURS WITHOUT A BREAK.
RIDICULOUS.
>> I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT I'M
HATING THIS JOB TODAY.
>> I KNOW.
CAN WE ALL JUST GO HOME?
>> UH-OH, SOUNDS LIKE SOME DUDES
HAVE THE MID-DAY BLUES.
WHO WANTS A SUB FROM TOMMY
FLING, THE SANDWICH KING?
YUM, YUM, COME AND GET IT.
>> OH, THANKS, TOMMY, BUT WE'RE
ACTUALLY ALL SET TODAY.
>> OH, ALL SET?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HOW ABOUT THE GIRLS?
I MADE THEM EXTRA MEATY FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU?
>> ACTUALLY, TOMMY, WE ALREADY
ORDERED PIZZA.
>> HOW?
BY GOING ON THE DOMINO'S PIZZA
APP AND ORDERING PIZZA.
>> OKAY.
WHAT'S THIS BITCH TALKING ABOUT?
>> TOMMY, DON'T CALL HIM THAT.
YOUR SUBS ARE GREAT.
WE'VE JUST BEEN BRANCHING OUT,
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, WE USED TO EAT YOUR
SUBS EVERY DAY, BUT NOW WE'RE
TRYING SOMETHING ELSE.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
I GOT IT.
GUESS YOU DON'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
♪ I USED TO FLY, NOW I JUST FALL
DOWN, I WHAT I WAS MADE FOR ♪
>> TOMMY, YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
YOU KIND OF JUST STOOD THERE IN
SILENCE FOR A WHILE.
>> YEAH.
YOU LOOKED PRETTY SAD.
>> SAD?
I'M NOT SAD.
YOU'RE SAD FOR MISSING OUT ON
THESE EPIC SUBS.
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO TAKE
THEM BACK TO MY BROS IN
ACCOUNTING.
>> NO, NO.
THEY SAID IN THE MEETING THEY
WERE GOING TO ORDER FROM
PAV BAJI.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
>> IT'S INDIAN.
A NEW PLACE THEY WANTED TO TRY.
>> OH, SOMETHING NEW.
I GOT IT.
GUESS YOU DON'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
♪♪
♪ JUST SOMETHING YOU GAVE
FOR -- ♪
♪ WHAT WAS I MADE FOR ♪
>> SHOULD WE DO SOMETHING?
HE'S BEEN SINGING THAT "BARBIE"
SONG FOR LIKE TEN MINUTES?
>> TOMMY, YOU OKAY?
>> MORE THAN OKAY.
YOU GUYS ARE THE ONES WHO SUCK
DONG AND THINK YOU'RE BETTER
THAN MY SUBS.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> LOOK, I'VE BEEN DOING THIS
FOR 15 YEARS AND YOU WON'T EVEN
BUY A SODA?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WELL, TOMMY, KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE YOU FILLED THE BOTTLES
YOURSELVES BECAUSE THEY DON'T
HAVE CAPS, JUSTIN FOIL ON TOP.
>> AND THE COLORS DON'T SEEM
RIGHT.
COKE ISN'T BRIGHT BLUE.
>> BUY A PICKLE AT LEAST.
>> WELL, NOT OUT OF A LISTERINE
BOTTLE.
>> GOD FORBID I RECYCLE.
JUST FORGET IT.
WHAT DO I KNOW?
I'M JUST SOME SUB GUY.
>> COME ON.
WE DON'T JUST LIKE YOU FOR YOUR
FOOD.
WE LIKE YOU FOR WHO YOU ARE AS A
PERSON.
>> HOW?
>> WELL, LIKE YOU'RE FUNNY.
>> YEAH?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I KNOW A JOKE.
OKAY.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
>> WHO'S THERE?
>> TWO ITALIAN QUEERS.
>> NO!
♪♪
>> TOMMY, YOU GOT GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
>> YOU WERE ALWAYS MY FAVORITE
CUSTOMERS.
THAT'S ALL.
LOOK, I TELL YOU WHAT, WHY DON'T
YOU TAKE THESE SUBS.
THEY'RE ON THE HOUSE, OKAY?
TAKE THEM.
>> TOMMY, THAT'S VERY NICE OF
YOU.
YOU EVEN WROTE MY NAME ON IT.
TURKEY FOR TRISH.
>> VEJ FOR DEB.
>> LIKE I SAID, YOU'RE MY FAVES.
>> WELL, THERE'S NO SIGN OF THE
PIZZA.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
>> UGH.
>> THEY'RE COVERED IN MOLD.
>> I NEED A NEW FRIDGE.
>> THESE SMELL TERRIBLE!
>> MINE LOOKS OKAY.
♪♪
>> YOU OWE ME 200 BUCKS.
COME TAKE MY HAND
THROW YOUR GUITAR AND YOUR
CLOTHES IN THE BACK SEAT ♪
♪ MY LOVE
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND
BUT I'LL HOLD YOUR HURT
IN THE BOX HERE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ HOW COULD WE KNOW
WE'D REARRANGE
ALL THE COSMOS, MMM
WE CRASHED AND WE BURNED ♪
♪ NOW I JUST CAN'T GO
WHERE YOU DON'T GO
AND USUALLY I'M
#ИМЯ?
♪ ANXIOUS
TOO MUCH
BUT I'LL LOVE YOU
LIKE YOU NEED ME TO ♪
♪ IMPERFECT FOR YOU
MESSY
COMPLETELY
DISTRESSED ♪
♪ BUT I'M NOT LIKE THAT
SINCE I MET YOU
IMPERFECT FOR YOU ♪
♪ LET'S GO TONIGHT
'CAUSE THERE'S JUST A FEW
SECONDS LEFT TILL TOMORROW ♪
♪ WE HAVE
ALL THAT WE NEED
LET'S LEAVE OUR BAGGAGE
AND WINE AT THE TABLE ♪
♪ MMM, HOW COULD WE KNOW
THAT THIS WAS A
HAPPY DISASTER, MMM ♪
♪ I'M GLAD WE
CRASHED AND BURNED
I'LL NEVER FORGET
WHEN YOU TOLD ME ♪
♪ YOU SAID, USUALLY I'M
#ИМЯ?
ANXIOUS
TOO MUCH ♪
♪ BUT I'LL LOVE YOU
LIKE YOU NEED ME TO
IMPERFECT FOR YOU ♪
♪ MESSY
COMPLETELY
DISTRESSED
BUT I'M NOT LIKE THAT ♪
♪ SINCE I MET YOU
MMM, HOW COULD WE KNOW
WE'D MAKE THE BAD
STUFF DELIGHTFUL, MMM ♪
♪ I'M GLAD WE
CRASHED AND BURNED
I KNOW WE'LL BE THERE
FOR EACH OTHER ♪
♪ WHEN WE'RE FEELING
#ИМЯ?
ANXIOUS
TOO MUCH ♪
♪ BUT I'LL LOVE YOU
LIKE YOU NEED ME TO
IMPERFECT FOR YOU
MESSY ♪
♪ COMPLETELY
DISTRESSED
BUT I'M NOT LIKE THAT
SINCE I MET YOU ♪
♪ IMPERFECT FOR YOU
MMM, MMM, MMM
IMPERFECT FOR YOU ♪
♪ YOU, YOU, YOU
YOU, YOU
IMPERFECT FOR YOU ♪♪
SEASON.
>> I'VE KNOWN YOU SINCE YOU WERE
MY INTERN.
HOW DID I NOT KNOW YOU WERE A
KNICKS FAN.
>> ARE YOU FROM NEW YORK.
>> I MOVED HERE IN COLLEGE, SO I
ADOPTED THE TEAM, BUT I'M
ACTUALLY FROM TEMECULA.
>> TEMECULA, I KNOW THAT'S
RIGHT.
Y'ALL BEEN IN THE BATHROOMS
HERE?
THEY GOT THAT GOOD SOAP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND HERE YOU GO, MISS.
>> OH, LISA, DID YOU SNEAK OFF
AND PAY FOR THE WHOLE TABLE?
>> OH, THANK YOU.
THAT'S SO NICE.
>> LISA, I'M YOUR SISTER'S BOSS.
I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT.
>> BUT I INSIST.
I PAY MY WAY.
I GOT MONEY TOO.
I JUST GOT BROKE OFF IN COURT.
>> I WOULD PAY MONEY TO WATCH
YOU IN COURT.
>> WHAT YOU WANT?
YOU TRYING TO GET RODE TO DEATH
OR SOMETHING?
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO BE KIND.
>> PLEASE IGNORE HER.
SHE'S JUST JOKING AROUND.
>> HOLD UP.
THIS AIN'T RIGHT.
THEY ADDED GRATUEY.
I WROTE IT IN MY TIP, BUT THEY
ALREADY ADDED GRATUEY.
>> NORMALLY RESTAURANTS ADD
GRATUITY FOR LARGER PARTIES.
>> SO A FREE LOADER CORRECTING
ME.
THEY ONLY SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
FOR PARTIES OF SIX OR MORE.
I AIN'T GETTING TRICKED INTO
TIPPING TWICE.
I'M GOING TO FIX THIS.
>> GUYS, I ALMOST FORGOT TO TELL
YOU ABOUT THIS, SO I'VE RECENTLY
BEEN TAKING FLUTE LESSONS.
>> ERASABLE PENS FOR THE WIN, AM
I RIGHT?
>> I STARTED PLAYING IN MY
LIVING ROOM --
>> 18%?
I WAS GOING TO GIVE Y'ALL 20.
Y'ALL BLOCKING Y'ALL BLESSINGS.
IT'S ALL ABOUT REFILLS THAT'S
FREE, YET I SEE TEN PINA COLADAS
ON THE BILL.
DAMN!
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> THIS IS THE CUSTOMER COPY.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO ERASE IT.
CAN'T YOU JUST SCRATCH IT OUT?
>> THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
>> LISA, COULD YOU CUT IT OUT?
MARK WAS JUST TALKING.
>> I HEARD EVERY WORD.
MR. TARZAN TRYING TO LURE ME
OVER TO HIS HOUSE TALKING ABOUT
HE GOT A BIG SNAKE.
SIR, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I JUST ATE 37 HABANERO WINGS.
I'M NOT RIDING YOU.
>> EXCUSE ME, MISS.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS TO LEAVE.
YOU HAVE MADE A COMPLETE MESS,
AND OUR HOST SAID SHE SAW
SOMEBODY STEALING SOAP FROM THE
BATHROOM.
>> I BOUGHT THIS FROM WALL
GROOMS.
>> ONCE AGAIN, PLEASE LEAVE.
>> WHY WE GOT TO LEAVE?
BECAUSE OF OUR DISABILITY?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A DISABILITY.
>> SIR, I WILL HAVE YOU KNOW, HE
IS NEGRO DIVERGENT.
>> GET OUT!
>> DON'T TALK TO MY SISTER LIKE
THAT.
>> I GOT THIS.
.
WHEN I LOOK AT LISA, I SEE A
VERY LAYERED WOMAN WHO ISN'T
ALWAYS AWARE OF HER
SURROUNDINGS.
>> SAY THAT.
>> LISA HAS DETERMINATION,
PERSISTENCE, MIGHT EVEN BE A
KLEPTO.
WHEN IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE,
LISA ONLY HEARS WHAT SHE WANTED
TO HEAR.
>> SAY THAT.
>> AND WE CANNOT LOSE WHAT'S
IMPORTANT TONIGHT, LISA FED US
ALL.
>> I PAID MY WAY.
HOLD UP.
THIS WING AIN'T DONE.
THAT'S IT.
I'M SUING.
I TOLD THEM TO COOK MY MEAT.
THANK YOU TO LORNE MICHAELS FOR
MAKING SNL THE GREATEST SHOW ON
EARTH!
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.