FROM PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN.
>> HI.
GOOD EVENING, AMERICA.
IT'S ALMOST HALLOWEEN.
I'M NOT OUT OF BREATH.
I'M JUST EXCITED
BECAUSE
HALLOWEEN IS THE GREATEST
HOLIDAY IN THE WORLD.
THE WORLD.
BUT LOOK, BOTTOM LINE,
WORLD IS
A PRETTY SCARY PLACE RIGHT NOW,
WARS, SHOOTINGS, CLIMATE CHANGE,
EVERYTHING IN THE NEW BRITNEY
BOOK.
I WANT TO PUT EVERYONE AT EASE.
NOTHING PUTS PEOPLE AT EASE LIKE
AN 80-YEAR-OLD MAN
HANGING
HALLOWEEN DECORATIONS.
SO COME ON, JOIN ME.
WE'LL WALK OVER HERE TO THE
LADDER.
HERE WE GO.
YOUR OLD BOY JOE IS GOING TO
CLIMB A LADDER.
HERE YOU GO, JOE.
OH, YEAH, BABY.
DOING ALL RIGHT.
STEP TWO.
YEAH.
RELAX.
I'M NOT GOING TO FALL.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO FOR THREE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHOO, WHAT A MAN, WHAT A MAN,
WHAT A MAN, WHAT A MIGHTY FINE
MAN.
LITTLE SHAKY.
WE CAN DO THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
RELAX.
THAT NEEDS TO GO WAY UP THERE.
ON SECOND THOUGHT, LET'S DO THAT
LATER.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT, SEE, LADDERS ARE FUN,
THOUGH.
SEE, WHEN I WAS A KID, LADDERS
DOES CUTTING-EDGE TECHNOLOGY.
THIS WAS LIKE AN iPAD.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK AT THIS OVER HERE.
LOOK AT THIS SPOOKY DECORATION.
THAT'S A SEVERED ARM.
OH, SHOOT.
OH, NO.
THAT'S NOT A DECORATION.
THAT'S AN ARM OUR DOG COMMANDER
RIPPED OFF A SECRET SERVICE
AGENT.
OH WELL.
WHERE WAS I?
OH, RIGHT.
IT'S HALLOWEEN.
I LOVE HALLOWEEN.
IN FACT, A LOT OF MY CLOSEST
FRIENDS ARE GHOSTS.
THAT'S WHY I GOT TO PLAN FOR
HALLOWEEN.
IT'S CALLED BOO BACK BOOER.
IT'S WITH ALL THE CLASSICS,
GOBLINS, GHOULS,
AND OF COURSE
THE GRIM REAPER,
WHO I
PHYSICALLY FIGHT EVERY SINGLE
DAY.
BECAUSE WE GOT TO STAY POSITIVE,
FOLKS.
CRIME IS DOWN, UNEMPLOYMENT IS DOWN,
STOCK MARKET IS DOWN.
WELL, TWO OUT OF THREE AIN'T
BAD.
HEY, IT'S RIGHT ON TIME,
A WHITE HOUSE AIDE TO HELP ME PUT UP THE
COBWEBS.
>> ME?
NO, I'M NOT AN AIDE.
I'M NEW SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE,
MIKE JOHNSON.
>> OH, I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO?
>> MIKE JOHNSON.
I WAS JUST ELECTED SPEAKER OF
THE HOUSE.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
AND YOUR NAME IS WHAT?
>> MIKE JOHNSON.
NO ONE'S GOING TO FORGET THAT.
ANYWAY, I'M NOW SECOND IN LINE
TO REPLACE YOU,
SO I'M EXCITED
TO SEE MORE OF THIS WHOLE LADDER
THING.
COOL
>> SO HOW DID YOU END UP
SPEAKER?
>> NO ONE KNOWS.
AND THIS IS MY ADULT BLACK SON.
ALSO NAMED MICHAEL.
>> HEY, GUYS.
I'M HIS ADULT BLACK SON.
I'M ONLY 11 YEARS YOUNGER THAN
HIM, AND I'M KIND OF A SECRET.
IT'S NORMAL.
DON'T LOOK INTO THAT AT ALL.
>> WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
HIS NAME IS ALSO MIKE JOHNSON?
>> NO ONE KNOWS HIS LAST NAME.
IT'S NORMAL.
>> YEAH.
HE OFTEN COMPARES OUR SITUATION
TO THE MOVIE THE BLIND SIDE,
AND
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT STORY HELD
UP GREAT.
ANYWAY, LET'S GO, WHITE DAD.
>> SOUNDS GOOD, ADULT BLACK SON.
AND REMEMBER MY NAME, AMERICA.
JOHN MIKESON.
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT THAT
WAS, BUT, HEY, IT'S A CONFUSING
TIME.
I JUST WISH SOMEONE COULD HELP ME EXPLAIN
THE TRUE MEANING OF
HALLOWEEN.
>> MAYBE --
MAYBE --
MAYBE I CAN HELP.
>> I'M SORRY.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> I'M THE SPIRIT OF HALLOWEEN.
THE GHOST OF ALL HALLOWS PAST.
IN SOUTH AMERICA, THEY CALL ME
PAPA PUMPKIN.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
I NEVER BEEN.
>> HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE?
DID YOU COME IN THROUGH THE
CHIMNEY?
>> CLOSE.
THE TOILET.
IT'S THE HALLOWEEN WAY.
IT'S WHAT THE HOLIDAY IS ALL
ABOUT.
SURE, THERE'S SPOOKY GOBLINS,
CREEPY CRAWLERS, HOCUS POCUS,
BUT IT'S ABOUT COMRADERY REALLY.
MEET THE NEIGHBORS YOU DON'T
WANT TO SEE AGAIN ON ANY OTHER
DAY.
AFTER ALL, YOU CAN'T SPELL
HALLOWEEN WITHOUT HELLO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS I NEVER REALIZED THAT.
IS THAT REALLY HOW YOU SPELL IT?
>> PRETTY MUCH.
NOW, I HAVE A POEM I WOULD LIKE
TO RECITE.
TRICK OR TREAT,
SMELL MY FEET,
GIVE ME SOMETHING GOOD TO EAT.
>> OH, WOW, OKAY.
YEAH.
THAT'S VERY NICE.
>> I'M NOT DONE.
>> IF YOU DON'T, I DON'T CARE,
I'LL PULL DOWN YOUR UNDERWEAR.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I THINK THAT'S JUST A
CRIME.
>> NOT ON HALLOWEEN.
NOT WHEN PAPA PUMPKIN'S IN TOWN.
NOW, COME ON.
LET ME SMELL THOSE FEET.
FOR AMERICA.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, NATE
BARGATZE!
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S VERY EXCITING.
IT'S CRAZY.
I'M AS -- LOOK, IF YOU'RE AT
HOME, I'M AS SHOCKED AS YOU ARE
THAT I'M HERE.
I'VE COME TO THIS BUILDING FOR A LONG TIME,
SO IT'S UNREAL TO BE
HERE AT "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT THERE.
MY NAME IS NATE BARGATZE.
I'M FROM TENNESSEE.
I'M ALSO FROM THE 1900s.
AND --
I JUST THINK YOU GOT TO SAY IT.
LIKE THE WORLD IS SO FUTURE NOW.
AND I FEEL IN THE WAY OF IT.
HOTELS, HOTELS ARE FUTURISTIC.
YOU TAKE A SHOWER, THE SHOWER'S
ENCLOSED.
BUT NOW A LOT OF HOTELS HAVE
HALF A GLASS, AND WATER GETS ON
THE FLOOR.
AND THAT'S THE FUTURE.
THAT'S WHAT THE FUTURE --
THAT'S
WHAT THEY WANT.
AND, YOU KNOW, I WOULD LIKE A
WHOLE --
THEY DO HALF A GLASS
BECAUSE I'M STILL ALIVE, SO
THEY'RE LIKE --
THEY DON'T WANT
TO HEAR ME GOING WHERE'S THE
GLASS AT,
SO THEY DO HALF A
GLASS.
IN THE FUTURE, THE FLOOR IS
ALWAYS WET, EVERY FLOOR.
I MEAN, I THINK -- I'M 44.
MY DAUGHTER'S 11.
WHEN SHE'S MY AGE, IT'LL BE
2057.
I DON'T EVEN BELIEVE THAT'S A
REAL YEAR.
MY MOVIES DIDN'T GO THAT HIGH IN
FAKE YEARS.
HOW AM I GOING TO TALK TO
SOMEONE FROM 2057?
I HAVE MORE IN COMMON WITH A
PILGRIM.
I SAW TOO MUCH OLD-TIMEY STUFF.
I'M PRE-INTERNET.
WE GO TO A COUNTY FAIR, WILSON
COUNTY FAIR --
THIS IS IN
TENNESSEE IF YOU'RE WONDERING,
AND WE WOULD GO THERE -- FAIRS,
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY'RE STILL
OPEN.
I DON'T THINK THE GOVERNMENT
KNOWS ABOUT THEM.
WE RIDE THESE RIDES THAT WERE ON
THE INTERSTATE AN HOUR AGO.
SO, MY DAD IS A MAGICIAN IF YOU DON'T KNOW,
AND WE WOULD GO
WATCH HIM PERFORM.
THIS IS THE '80s.
SO WE GO WATCH HIM, MY DAD'S
DOING MAGIC.
RIGHT NEXT TO HIM, THEY HAD
DONKEYS
JUMPING OFF A HIGH DIVE
INTO A POOL.
SO PRETTY TOUGH TO KEEP PEOPLE'S
ATTENTION
WHEN MY DAD IS LIKE,
IS THIS YOUR CARD?
AND EVERYBODY'S LIKE, HOLD ON,
THIS DONKEY'S ABOUT TO JUMP OFF
THIS HIGH DIVE.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU DON'T THINK
YOU WANT TO SEE UNTIL IT'S UP
THERE.
I USUALLY -- LOOK, I USE THE
WORD JUMP VERY LOOSELY.
YEAH.
THESE DONKEYS ARE FALLING OFF
THIS HIGH DIVE.
BUT CAN'T PUT THAT ON THE SIGN.
YOU KNOW.
WANT TO WATCH A DONKEY FALL OFF
A HIGH DIVE?
LIKE, NO.
WHAT IF HE JUMPED?
WELL, AT LEAST HE'S INTO IT.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, PETA SHUT THAT
DOWN.
THAT WAS ONE EVERYBODY WAS LIKE,
WE GET THAT ONE.
THERE WAS ANOTHER ONE THEY HAD
TO SHUT DOWN,
SO THIS IS ALSO IN
THE '80s, PRE-INTERNET.
YOU COULD FIGHT AN ORANGUTAN.
YOU COULD FIST FIGHT AN
ORANGUTAN.
THIS WAS OFFERED.
WE DIDN'T HAVE A LOT GOING ON.
THIS IS WHAT WE HAD TO DO.
SO AN ORANGUTAN WOULD BE IN A
BOXING RING WITH BOXING GLOVES ON,
AND IT WOULD STAND LIKE THIS,
AND A GUY WOULD PAY $5 --
IT WASN'T FOR FREE.
YOU WOULD PAY, AND YOU WOULD GO IN THERE
AND THIS ORANGUTAN
WOULD JUST KNOCK THIS DUDE OUT
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T HAVE THE
INTERNET TO LOOK UP HOW STRONG
IS AN ORANGUTAN, SO --
IT WAS ALL WORD OF MOUTH BACK
THEN.
YOU HAD TO MEET A GUY THAT JUST
FOUGHT AN ORANGUTAN.
AND YOU'RE LIKE, ARE THEY
STRONG?
YEAH, DUDE.
BUT THE ARMS ARE SKINNY.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT AS WELL.
THAT STRENGTH COMES FROM
SOMEWHERE.
LOOK, YOU THINK I'M OLD.
THERE'S PEOPLE OLDER THAN ME
STILL AROUND.
THAT'S CRAZY.
IT'S CRAZY.
WALKING AROUND, PEOPLE FROM THE
'30s.
MY GREAT AUNT HELEN, FROM THE
'30s, SHE'S DEAF.
THEY DIDN'T KNOW SHE WAS DEAF
UNTIL SHE WAS 9 YEARS OLD.
THAT'S HOW LONG IT TOOK FOR THEM TO FIGURE --
DEAF IS ONE OF THE
EASIER ONES TO FIGURE OUT.
AND THE DOCTORS WERE BAFFLED,
AS THEY SMOKED IN HER FACE.
AND THEY WERE LIKE, I DON'T
KNOW.
SHE'S RUDE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
MY MOM -- MY PARENTS ARE GETTING OLDER,
SO WE HAD MY MOM GO PICK
UP OUR DAUGHTER RECENTLY AT A
FRIEND'S HOUSE.
I TEXTED HER THE ADDRESS.
SHE WENT TO THE WRONG HOUSE.
SHE KNOCKED ON THE DOOR, AND
ANOTHER GRANDMOTHER ANSWERED.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
THIS IS LIKE TWO DOGS SEEING
EACH OTHER THROUGH A FENCE.
THEY'RE GONNA BE THERE FOR A
WHILE, YOU KNOW?
SO MY MOM, SHE KNOCKED ON THE
DOOR.
ANOTHER
MY MOM GOES, IS MY GRANDDAUGHTER
IN THERE,
AND THAT LADY GOES, I
HAVE THREE GRANDSONS.
SO, NO SOLUTION.
JUST TWO GRANDMOTHERS JUST, DO
YOU HAVE STUFF?
I HAVE STUFF TOO.
THEY TALKED FOR 30 MINUTES.
IT'S A WRONG DOOR.
I HAD TO GO GET MY DAUGHTER THEN
FIND MY MOM.
MY DAD TOO.
MY DAD HAS SURGERY EIGHT TIMES A
YEAR PROBABLY.
AND HE LOVES IT.
HE LOVES IT.
HE HAD SURGERY BECAUSE HE WAS
ADDICTED TO AFRIN, THE NOSE
SPRAY.
LOOK, I HAVE BEEN ADDICTED TO
AFRIN THE NOSE SPRAY.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS, I
WOULD HONESTLY TELL YOU NOT TO
GET INVOLVED.
IT'S ONE OF THE BEST THINGS I'VE
EVER BEEN A PART OF.
SOLVES EVERYTHING IMMEDIATELY.
WHEN I WAS ON IT TOO, MY WIFE
WAS -- SHE WOULD BE LIKE WHAT'S
THAT NOISE?
SHE WOULD HEAR ONE PUFF, WHAT'S
THAT?
I GO, I AIN'T GOING TO LIVE LIKE
THIS.
I DIDN'T WORK THIS HARD NOT TO
DO AFRIN IN MY OWN HOME.
SO MY DAD GOES TO THE DOCTOR,
AND THEY WERE LIKE, DO YOU USE
AFRIN, AND HE GOES, NO.
AND THE DOCTOR WAS LIKE, LIKE I
CAN SEE THAT YOU USE IT.
I WAS JUST SAYING THAT.
AND HE GOES, HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN USING IT, AND MY DAD SAID FIVE YEARS,
WHICH IS A LIE.
BUT MY MOM WAS THERE, AND SHE
GOES, HOW ABOUT 45 YEARS.
THAT'S HOW LONG HE'S USED IT.
THE BACK OF THE BOX SAYS NO MORE
THAN THREE DAYS.
THERE'S NOT A MEDICINE ON EARTH
THAT TELLS YOU TO GIVE IT A GOOD
45-YEAR RUN.
THAT'S WHY I GET NERVOUS AS I
GET OLDER
BECAUSE I AM ALREADY
NOT SMART.
AND I'M IN MY PRIME RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T READ ANY BOOKS.
I DON'T DO IT.
AND I THINK THAT MATTERS.
I DO THINK THAT MATTERS.
READING, I BELIEVE, IS THE KEY
TO SMART.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE ALWAYS SAID.
AND I DON'T DO IT BECAUSE EVERY
BOOK IS JUST THE MOST WORDS.
IT DOESN'T LET UP.
I MEAN, EVERY PAGE IS MORE WORDS --
IT'S LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
PUT SOME BLANK PAGES IN THERE.
LET ME GET MY HEAD ABOVE WATER
FOR TWO SECONDS.
THANK YOU.
I'M LIKE, I WANT TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT HISTORY BECAUSE I DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING.
SO I'M TRYING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
AND I CAN TELL I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HISTORY BECAUSE
EVERY HISTORY MOVIE I WATCH,
I WATCH ON THE EDGE OF MY SEAT
JUST LIKE WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
I DON'T KNOW.
I WATCHED THE MOVIE PEARL
HARBOR, AND I WAS AS SURPRISED
AS THEY WERE.
JUST CRAZY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT!
FOO FIGHTERS ARE HERE,
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL IG
>>> TWO CHEFS, ONE CUISINE,
ONE WINNER, CHEF SHOWDOWN.
>> CHEFS, IT'S BEEN AN EMOTIONAL
WEEK HERE AT CHEF SHOWDOWN.
WE VISITED THE OLDEST BLACK
CHURCH IN GEORGIA
WHERE WE
LEARNED ABOUT THE ORIGINS OF SOUL FOOD
IN PREPARATION FOR OUR
SOUL FOOD CHALLENGE.
WHAT WAS THAT EXPERIENCE LIKE
FOR YOU BOTH?
>> AMAZING.
I FELT CONNECTED TO MY CULTURE,
TO MY ROOTS.
IT WAS REALLY AN HONOR.
>> AND YOU, DOUGIE?
>> HECK YEAH.
THUMBS UP.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS GREAT.
>> NOW FOR THE CHALLENGE, YOU
EACH WERE ASKED TO PREPARE A
SOUL FOOD FEAST FOR OUR GUEST
JUDGES.
THE REVEREND JEREMIAH FIELDS.
>> BLESSINGS.
>> AND THE QUEEN OF SOUL FOOD
HERSELF, OWNER OF SWEET MADDIE'S KITCHEN,
MS. MADDIE JOHNSON.
CHEFS, THE JUDGES TASTED YOUR
PLATES BLIND, AND THEY'RE READY
TO WEIGH IN.
JUDGES, WHAT DID YOU THINK OF
PLATE NUMBER ONE?
>> WELL, PLATE NUMBER ONE WAS
PERFECT.
OKAY?
I COULD FEEL THE SOUL.
THE BRISKET, JOHN,
THE COLLARDS.
THIS PLATE RIGHT HERE IS THE
CULTURE.
>> YES, I AGREE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHO COOKED WHAT,
BUT WHOEVER COOKED PLATE ONE
KNEW EXACTLY WHAT SHE WAS DOING.
>> YES.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT PLATE TWO?
>> PLATE TWO FRANKLY PISSED ME
OFF.
I MEAN, WHAT IS THIS?
OKRA FOAM,
CORNBREAD ICE CREAM,
HUSH PUPPY JELLY?
THIS AIN'T NO SOUL FOOD.
>> THIS PLATE HAS NO SOUL AND NO
FOOD.
>> YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
LOOK HERE, MY MAN, RESPECT FOR
THROWING YOUR HAT IN THE RING,
BUT THIS AIN'T IT.
>> JUDGES, TODAY'S WINNING PLATE
IS --
>> PLATE ONE.
>> YES, PLATE ONE BY A MILE.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, DOUGIE.
>> DOUGIE?
DOUGIE COOKED THAT?
>> YES.
I'M SORRY.
>> HOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW. I JUST DID MY BEST,
AND, AGAIN,
SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
>> HAVE YOU COOKED THIS KIND OF
FOOD BEFORE?
>> NO, SIR.
I'M SORRY.
>> BUT YOU MUST HAVE GROWN UP
AROUND IT, RIGHT?
I MEAN, WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> RHODE ISLAND.
>> RHODE ISLAND?
NAH.
>> I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
YOUR PARENTS THE BLACK SOMEHOW.
>> NO.
MY PARENTS ARE WHITE.
I'M SORRY.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD BE.
>> KELLY, WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I LIVE IN FRANCE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY EACH HAD A HELPER, THOUGH,
RIGHT?
FROM THE ELIMINATOR CHEF.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
THAT COULD BE IT.
>> YES.
SOUS CHEFS, COME ON OUT.
>> OH, OKAY.
WHAT IN THE -- NO!
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU WERE HIS SOUS CHEF?
>> YES, SIR.
I'M SO SORRY.
I MADE THE COLLARDS.
>> OKAY.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I MADE THE DECONSTRUCTED
BLACK EYED PEAS.
>> YOU NEED TO KILL YOURSELF.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE, THE BOTH OF
YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME TRY PLATE TWO AGAIN.
MAYBE I MISSED SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE SOUS VIDE CATFISH IS PRETTY --
NO IT IS NOT.
I'M LYING.
I HATE THIS.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO THIS, GIRL?
>> IT'S ACTUALLY IMPOSSIBLE
CATFISH.
IT'S MADE FROM SOY PROTEIN.
>> THE JUDGES --
THE JUDGES HAVE SPOKEN.
HERE TO PRESENT THE PRIZE IS CULINARY ICON
PADMA LAKSHMI.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, KELLY.
AS PART OF YOUR PRIZE --
>> THE WHITE BOY WON.
>> REALLY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DID NOT MEAN TO.
>> OKAY.
DOUGIE, AS PART OF YOUR PRIZE TODAY,
YOU'LL BE A GUEST ON
MS. MADDIE'S YOUTUBE SERIES,
THE BLACK KITCHEN.
>> THAT'S SO COOL.
I'M SORRY.
>> AND YOU'LL BE AN HONORED
GUEST AT THIS YEAR'S
ESSENCE
FEST.
>> WOW.
NO THANK YOU.
>> AND YOU'LL BE MADE A CULTURAL
AMBASSADOR BY
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
>> I'M HONORED, BUT PLEASE TAKE
THIS OFF ME.
>> CONGRATS, DOUGIE FOR PUTTING
THE SOUL IN SOUL FOOD.
>> OH, COME ON, PADMA.
DON'T SAY IT LIKE THAT.
FALL
DAD?
ANYBODY HOME.
>> -- COMES A CHILLING NEW
VISION OF HORROR.
PIZZA
>> IF YOU'RE CALLING TO ASK IF I
WANT PEPPERONI, DAD, YOU ALREADY
KNOW THE ANSWER.
>> TURN AROUND.
>> WHAT?
WHO IS THIS?
>> JUST TURN AROUND.
HELLO.
KELSEY?
>> WAIT, MARK?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK IN
AUTUMN HOLLOW?
>> FROM THE HALL MARK CHANNEL,
THE LAST THING KELSEY EXPECTED
WAS TO BE REUNITED
WITH HER HIGH SCHOOL CRUSH
TURNED HOMETOWN KILLER,
BUT SOMETIMES LIFE COMES
UP WITH OTHER PLANS
IN A STAB AT
LOVE.
>> I DIDN'T COME TO AUTUMN
HOLLOW TO BE STALKED BY A SERE
YELL KILLER.
I HAVE A CAREER IN NEW YORK TO
GET BACK TO.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S
WHAT HE HAS IN MIND.
>> WITH TWO ALMOST ATTRACTIVE
ACTORS WITH ALMOST HUMAN
SOUNDING NAMES.
STARRING GASHELY GREIGERT AND
BREN CLOBORG.
GET OUT
TRY NEW
>> NO. THESE ARE MY ROOTS.
I GUESS I LIKE KILLING PEOPLE I
KNOW.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> FROM THE PRODUCERS OF THE
CHRISTMAS PRINCE AND MAMA.
>> I HAVE TO GO.
I HAVE A 3,000-WORD ARTICLE ON
THE TRUE MEANING OF HALLOWEEN,
AND IT'S DUE TOMORROW.
>> CAN I SHOW YOU SOMETHING
FIRST?
>> WOW.
DID YOU MAKE ALL THESE KNIVES?
YOU HAVE A REAL TALENT.
>> LOOK, I HAVE TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
>> NO, ME FIRST.
>> LET'S DO IT AT THE SAME TIME.
>> I'M FALLING FOR YOU.
>> I WANT TO KILL YOU AND YOUR
WHOLE FAMILY.
>> WE CORNERED THE MARKET ON
CHRISTMAS, WHY NOT HALLOWEEN?
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING FEMALE
VIEWERS LIKE MORE THAN ROMANCE
IS MURDER.
>> WHAT AM I DOING?
I'M SCARED.
>> OF THE MURDERS?
>> NO, OF LOVE.
>> ALL Y'ALL WHITE GIRLS IS --
Y'ALL STUPID.
>> AND LIKE FALLING AUTUMN
LEAVES, THE MAGIC ENDS ALL TOO
SOON.
>> KELSEY, YOU WEREN'T AT THE
AIRPORT.
DID YOU FORGET I WAS COMING?
WHO IS THIS GUY?
>> MARK, THIS IS MY FRIEND JAKE.
>> FRIEND?
I'M YOUR FIANCE.
>> WAIT.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I WANT
TO KILL YOU ANYMORE.
>> DON'T SAY THAT.
>> JUST GO BACK TO NEW YORK.
THERE'S PLENTY OF PEOPLE TO KILL
YOU THERE.
>> MARK!
>> BABE, WE'RE LEAVING.
LIMO'S OUTSIDE.
MARK
>> A MOVIE FOR THE WHOLE FAMILY
SHOT ENTIRELY ON A SAMSUNG
GALAXY.
>> KELSEY?
YOU STAYED?
>> I'M NEVER LEAVING AGAIN.
>> THEN I'VE GOT SOMETHING FOR
YOU.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> YES!
>> HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, NO.
HUH-HUH.
>> ONLY ON HALLMARK, WHERE BOO
MEANS BOYFRIEND.
CAMP
BRITISH
>> HOW WILL WE EVER WIN THIS
WAR?
>> BY REMEMBERING WHAT WE FIGHT
FOR.
>> GENERAL WASHINGTON.
>> SIT, PLEASE.
WE NEED YOUR STRENGTH FOR THE
FIGHT AHEAD.
WE FIGHT FOR A COUNTRY OF OUR OWN,
A NEW NATION WHERE WE
CHOOSE OUR OWN LAWS.
>> HERE, HERE.
>> CHOOSE OUR OWN LEADERS.
>> YES, SIR!
>> AND CHOOSE OUR OWN SYSTEMS OF
WEIGHTS AND MEASURES.
>> WEIGHTS AND MEASURES, SIR?
>> YES.
YES, I DREAM OF THAT ONE DAY OUR
PROUD NATION
WILL MEASURE
WEIGHTS IN POUNDS AND THAT 2,000
POUNDS SHALL BE CALLED A TON.
>> AND WHAT WILL 1,000 POUNDS BE
CALLED, SIR?
>> NOTHING.
BECAUSE WE WILL HAVE NO WORD FOR
THAT.
>> SEEMS LIKE WE SHOULD HAVE A
WORD FOR 1,000 POUNDS, SIR.
>> AND YET, WE WON'T.
BECAUSE WE ARE FREE MEN.
AND WE WILL BE FREE TO MEASURE
LIQUIDS IN LITERS AND MILLILITERS,
BUT NOT ALL
LIQUIDS.
ONLY SODA, WINE, AND ALCOHOL.
>> ONLY THOSE, SIR?
>> YES.
BECAUSE FOR MILK AND PAINT, WE
WILL USE GALLONS, PINTS, AND
QUARTS GOD WILLING.
>> HOW MANY LITERS ARE IN A
GALLON, SIR?
>> NOBODY KNOWS.
>> AND, SIR, IN THIS NEW COUNTRY,
WHAT PLANS ARE THERE
FOR MEN OF COLOR SUCH AS I?
>> DISTANCE WILL BE MEASURED IN
INCHES, FEET, YARD, AND MILE.
SO 12 INCHES TO A FOOT.
>> 12 FEET TO A YARD.
>> IF IT WERE ONLY SO SIMPLE.
3 FEET TO A YARD.
>> AND HOW MANY YARDS TO A MILE?
>> NOBODY KNOWS.
>> OKAY.
WELL, HOW MANY FEET TO A MILE?
>> 5,280, OF COURSE.
IT'S A SIMPLE NUMBER THAT
EVERYONE WILL REMEMBER.
>> I MUST CONFESS, IT FEELS A
LITTLE COMPLICATED, SIR.
WHY NOT USE METERS AND
KILOMETERS.
>> WE WILL, SOLDIER.
BUT ONLY IN CERTAIN UNPOPULAR
SPORTS LIKE TRACK AND SWIMMING.
FOR POPULAR SPORTS LIKE
FOOTBALL, WE WILL USE YARDS.
>> FOOTBALL, SIR?
>> YES.
IT'S A SPORT WHERE YOU THROW A
BALL WITH YOUR HANDS.
>> SO IN FOOTBALL, THERE IS NO
KICKING?
>> THERE'S A LITTLE KICKING.
YOU KICK THE BALL TO GET POINTS.
>> HOW MANY POINTS, SIR?
>> SOMETIMES ONE AND SOMETIMES
THREE.
>> I'M VERY CONFUSED, SIR.
>> DO NOT WORRY FOR OUR NEW
NATION, WE WILL HAVE RULERS WITH
TWO SETS OF NUMBERS,
INCHES ON
ONE SIDE, CENTIMETERS ON THE
OTHER.
>> SO WE CAN SEE WHERE THEY LINE
UP?
>> YES, EXCEPT THAT THEY DON'T
LINE UP, AND THEY NEVER WILL.
>> WHY?
>> LIBERTY, SON.
LIBERTY.
>> AND THE SLAVES, SIR, WHAT OF
THEM?
>> YOU ASKED ABOUT THE
TEMPERATURE.
>> I DID NOT.
>> WE SHALL HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
UNRELATED SCALES OF TEMPERATURE.
ONE OF THEM WILL MAKE SENSE TO
THE ENTIRE WORLD, AND THE OTHER
WILL BE SUPER RANDOM.
OUR GREAT NATION WILL USE THE
RANDOM ONE.
>> WHAT IS THE SCALE CALLED,
SIR?
>> FAHRENHEIT.
>> SPELL THAT FOR ME.
>> IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT ONE DAY, IF WE ARE BRAVE, WE
WILL GET RID OF THE U
IN A LOT
OF BRITISH WORDS LIKE COLOR AND
ARMOR.
BUT BY GOD WE WILL KEEP THE
BRITISH U IN THE WORD GLAMOUR.
>> ONLY GLAMOUR, SIR?
>> ONLY GLAMOUR.
THIS IS MY DREAM FOR OUR
COUNTRY, MEN,
A MELTS POT OF
DIFFERENT MEASUREMENTS
THAT WILL
MAKE EUROPEAN MEN THROW
TANTRUMS.
IN SHORT, A LAND OF LIBERTY.
>> WHERE ALL MEN ARE FREE.
WHERE ALL MEN ARE FREE, RIGHT?
MUDPUDDLE
♪ LATELY IT'S BEEN GETTIN' A
LITTLE COLD UP NORTH ♪
♪ BUT FURTHER SOUTH IT'S STILL
LIKE 90 DEGREES ♪
♪ NOW IN THESE PARTS WE MAY NOT
HAVE THE BIGGEST CITIES ♪
♪ AND WE MAY NOT HAVE THE OCEANS
BUT WE'VE FOUND SOMETHING EVEN
BETTER TO DO ♪
♪ DRINKIN' ON A LAKE BEACH
HANGIN' ON A LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ ICE COLD BEERS, WITH FRIENDS
WE'VE HAD FOR YEARS
DOWN ON LAKE
BEACH ♪
♪ BUTT-BROWN WATER ONLY UP TO MY
KNEES ♪
♪ DOWN AT THE BOTTOM THERE'S
THREE FEET OF LEAVES ♪
♪ GOT POISON IVY FROM WHIZZIN'
IN THE TREES ♪
♪ DOWN ON LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ SLIPPIN' ON SLIMY ROCKS ALL DAY LONG,
OFF-DUTY COP IS
SMOKIN' A BONG ♪
♪ BIG SNAPPIN' TURTLE JUST BIT
ME ON THE DONG ♪
♪ DOWN ON LAKE BEACH
HANGIN' ON
A LAKE BEACH,
KIDS SNEAKIN' A SIP,
LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS DIP,
MY
BEST FRIEND'S WIFE JUST KISSED
ME ON THE LIPS ♪
♪ DOWN AT THE LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ FIVE PEOPLE I KNOW,
40 THAT I DON'T KNOW,
EVERYBODY'S PHONES
AT 7% ♪
♪ FOUR PRETTY GIRLS ALL GOT THE
SAME HAIRCUT,
DOWN ON A LAKE
BEACH ♪
♪ DRAGGED MY YETI DOWN A
TWO-MILE ROAD,
EVERY STEP I TAKE
I MAYBE SQUASH A BABY TOAD ♪
♪ DIAPER IN THE WATER WITH A
HEAVY-ASS LOAD,
DOWN ON THE LAKE
BEACH ♪
♪ MY GIRLFRIEND DIDN'T SHOW UP,
BUT MY UNCLE DID,
AND HE'S NOT
FUN TO PLAY CORNHOLE WITH ♪
♪ HE'S GOT WEIRD GEAR AND HE
KNOWS ALL THE RULES ♪
♪ AND HE CAN'T TELL THAT THAT'S
NOT THE VIBE ♪
>>> THAT ONE BOUNCED OFF THE
GROUND.
THAT DOES NOT COUNT!
>> RELAX, MAN.
HE'S JUST A KID.
>> IF HE'S OLD ENOUGH TO PLAY,
HE'S OLD ENOUGH TO KNOW THE
RULES.
TAKE THE BAG OFF THE BOARD.
THAT'S HOW THE PROS PLAY!
♪ WHISKEY --
SHOT!
♪ TEQUILA --
SHOT! ♪
♪ WISH I --
GOT A TETANUS --
SHOT! ♪
♪ FAT GUY IN A TANK WITH A
T-SHIRT TANLINE ♪
♪ GRANNY'S BIG YAMS GETTING
FRIED IN THE SUNSHINE ♪
♪ RACCOON IN THE WATER, DIDN'T
KNOW THEY CAN SWIM ♪
♪ BROUGHT A WHOLE LOT OF BREAD,
NOT A LOT OF SANDWICH STUFF ♪
♪ THREE LOAFS OF WHITE BREAD,
BUT NOT ANY HAM ♪
♪ ONE DIRTY TODDLER, NO ONE'S
CLAIMIN' HIM ♪
♪ SCREAMIN' AT KIDS NOT TO SWIM
THAT WAY CAUSE THAT'S WHERE THE
BATS ARE ♪
♪ THAT'S WHERE THE BATS ARE,
STAY AWAY FROM THE RATS ♪
♪ DON'T GO OVER THERE,
HALF OF
THE LAKE BELONGS TO THE BATS ♪
♪ ON A LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ I THINK I BLEW OFF MY HAND ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE AMBULANCE,
ROLLING DOWN THE HILL, SUN IN
THE SAND,
CLAIMED BY THE LAKE BEACH ♪
♪ ON THE LAKE BEACH, TURN A BOY
INTO A MAN,
LAKE BEACH
NO ONE PICKS UP THE CANS ♪
♪ WHOLE LOT OF LAKE, NOT A LOT
OF LAND ♪
Down on a lake beach
♪ AND THE NEXT DAY WE ALL SEE
EACH OTHER AT CHURCH ♪
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
>> DON'T YOU ALL LOOK SO CUTE!
>> I THINK WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO BREAK OUT THE KING SIZED BARS
FOR THIS BUNCH.
>> KIDS, WAIT!
YOU'RE ABOUT TO MAKE A TERRIBLE
MISTAKE!
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> I'M FRAN DRESCHER, S.A.G.
PRESIDENT!
>> WOW, FRAN DRESCHER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I'M HERE TO TEACH YOU HOW TO
DO HALLOWEEN DURING A STRIKE.
>> OH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SINCE THE ACTORS ARE ON STRIKE,
THE GUILD ASKS MEMBERS NOT TO
WEAR COSTUMES BASED ON MOVIE OR
TV CHARACTERS.
>> EXACTLY.
BECAUSE THEN WE WOULD BE
PROMOTING THE COMPANIES WE'RE
STRIKING AGAINST, WHICH MAKES
ALL OF THESE CHILDREN A BUNCH OF
ADORABLE SCABS.
RUN HOME AND CHANGE, KIDS,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
>> THANKS, FRAN.
>> WOW.
NOW, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
>> IS IT REALLY THAT BIG A DEAL?
>> WELL, YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF
NERVE TALKING TO ME LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE DRESSED UP AT SLOTH
FROM THE GOONIES.
>> I'M NOT DRESSED AS SLOTH.
I'M HOLDING A BABY RUTH.
>> ARE THERE ANY COSTUMES THAT
ARE OKAY?
>> I'M GLAD YOU ASKED.
THERE ARE MANY GREAT CHARACTERS
YOU CAN STILL BE FOR HALLOWEEN.
FOR EXAMPLE, HARRY POTTER AS
DESCRIBED ONLY IN THE BOOK.
>> I LOOK JUST A LITTLE BIT OFF,
AND THAT'S A GOOD THING.
>> OR HOW ABOUT MINOR CHARACTERS
FROM THE BIBLE, WHO HAVE NOT
APPEARED IN ANY FILM ADAPTATION.
>> I'M ZOHETH, SON OF ISHI WHO
BEGET BEN ZOHETH.
>> SEE.
WHO NEEDS IRON MAN WHEN YOU HAVE
ZOHETH'S SON ISHI WHO CAN BEGET
BEN ZOHETH?
>> THESE KIDS DON'T LOOK HAPPY.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S SCARY WHAT THE MOVIE
STUDIOS ARE DOING TO OUR
CHILDREN, ISN'T IT?
THAT'S WHY WE'VE BEEN PICKETING
FOR 100 DAYS.
>> THAT MUST BE EXHAUSTING.
>> HEY, DID YOU JUST CALL ME
EXHAUSTING?
>> NO.
>> WELL, A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE.
OKAY.
BACK TO COSTUMES.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS YEAR, YOU
CAN'T BE YODA, BUT YOU CAN BE
HODA.
>> THE WIG IS FAKE, BUT THE WINE
THE REAL!
>> WAIT.
WHY IS THAT ONE OKAY?
ISN'T SHE ON TV?
>> WELL, DAYTIME AND REALITY TV
ARE OKAY, WHICH MEANS THAT
YOU'RE DRESSED FINE, BECAUSE
YOU'RE DRESSED AS ONE OF THE
PERVERTS FROM TO CATCH A
PREDATOR.
>> THIS IS JUST MY REGULAR
OUTFIT.
>> WHAT IF PEOPLE ALREADY BOUGHT
A COSTUME BEFORE THE STRIKE?
>> GOOD QUESTION.
WITH SMALL ADJUSTMENTS, MANY
COSTUMES CAN BE STRIKE FRIENDLY.
FOR EXAMPLE, SAY YOU'RE DRESSED
AS WOLVERINE.
JUST DROP THE CLAWS, AND
WAH-LAH, NOW YOU'RE ANY GAY GUY
OVER 50.
>> THANKS, FRANNY.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
OR SAY YOU'RE DRESSED AS MARIO.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS PUT ON A
CHEF'S HAT, AND NOW YOU'RE THE
GUY FROM THE PIZZA BOX.
>> IT'S A-ME, THE GUY FROM THE
PIZZA BOX.
>> MS. DRESCHER, HOW CAN I HOPE
TO UNDERSTAND SOMETHING SO
COMPLICATED?
I'M JUST A LITTLE KID.
>> WELL, HODA, I THINK I CAN
EXPLAIN IN TERMS EVEN A DRUNK
CHILD CAN UNDERSTAND.
NEGOTIATING WITH THE STUDIOS IS
A LOT LIKE TRICK OR TREATING.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU GO TO THE
BIGGEST HOUSE ON THE BLOCK, AND
ALL THE LIGHTS ARE OFF, AND
THEY'RE PRETENDING THEY'RE NOT
HOME?
BUT YOU CAN SEE THEM THROUGH THE
WINDOW EATING KITKAT BARS,
DOZENS OF KITKAT BARS, BILLIONS
OF KITKAT BARS, RECORD NUMBERS
OF KITKAT BARS, ALL US ACTORS
ARE SAYING IS BREAK ME OFF A
PIECE OF THAT KITKAT BAR.
>> WOW.
WHEN YOU PUT IT LIKE THAT, IT
MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
>> THANK YOU.
LOVE YOUR COSTUME, BY THE WAY.
KEVIN BACON'S PEDEPHILE
CHARACTER.
>> I'M NOT WALTER.
>> YOU KNOW HIS NAME?
>> I HAVE ONE MORE COSTUME IDEA.
SHE'S A STRONG, CONFIDENT WOMAN
WHO DOMINATED THE SUMMER AND IS
AN INSPIRATION TO GIRLS
EVERYWHERE.
>> BARBIE.
>> NOPE, THE NANNY.
>> BUT ISN'T THE NANNY
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OWNED BY
THE STUDIOS?
>> OH, I WOULDN'T CALL HER
INTELLECTUAL.
LADIES
RESCUED
♪ IT CAME IN A FLASH
IT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE
IT HAPPENED SO FAST
AND THEN IT WAS OVER ♪
ARE YOU THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING
IS THIS HAPPENING NOW ♪
♪ OH ARE YOU FEELING
WHAT I'M FEELING
THIS IS HAPPENING NOW ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL FREE TO SOME DEGREE
TO DANCE UNDER THE LIGHTS
I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ BRING ME BACK TO LIFE
KINGS AND QUEENS AND IN-BETWEENS
WE ALL DESERVE
THE RIGHT ♪
♪ I'M JUST WAITING TO BE
RESCUED I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED TONIGHT ♪
♪ I FELL IN A TRAP
MY HEART'S GETTING COLDER
IT'S COMING ON FAST
IT'S OVER MY SHOULDER ♪
♪ OH ARE YOU THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING
IS THIS HAPPENING NOW ♪
♪ OH ARE YOU FEELING
WHAT I'M FEELING
THIS IS HAPPENING NOW ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL FREE TO SOME DEGREE
TO DANCE UNDER THE LIGHTS
I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ BRING ME BACK TO LIFE
KINGS AND QUEENS AND IN-BETWEENS
WE ALL DESERVE
THE RIGHT ♪
♪ I'M JUST WAITING TO BE
RESCUED I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED TONIGHT ♪
♪ TO BE RESCUED TONIGHT
RESCUE ME TONIGHT
RESCUE ME TONIGHT ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL FREE TO SOME DEGREE
TO DANCE UNDER THE LIGHTS
I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ BRING ME BACK TO LIFE
KINGS AND QUEENS AND
IN-BETWEENS
WE ALL DESERVE
THE RIGHT ♪
♪ I'M JUST WAITING TO BE
RESCUED I'M JUST WAITING TO
BE RESCUED ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL JUST WAITING
TO BE RESCUED TONIGHT ♪
♪ TO BE RESCUED TONIGHT
RESCUE ME TONIGHT
RESCUE ME TONIGHT ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WELL, AFTER WEEKS OF STRUGGLING
TO ELECT A NEW SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE,
REPUBLICANS GAVE UP AND
JUST GENERATED ONE WITH AI.
THERE'S NO WAY MIKE JOHNSON IS A
REAL PERSON.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE A
CONSERVATIVE REPUBLICAN,
YET HE
LOOKS LIKE EVERY MSNBC HOST
COMBINED.
I FEEL LIKE THE WAY MIKE JOHNSON
GOT ELECTED IS AFTER WEEKS OF VOTING,
REPUBLICANS ARE BORED AND ALL WROTE IN
THE SAME FAKE NAME,
AND THEN
THEY WERE LIKE, WAIT, THAT'S A
REAL GUY?
>> SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON HAS ALSO
BEEN CALLED HOMOPHOBIC
FOR
SUPPORTING ANTI-LBGTQ LEGISLATION
AND SAYING IT'S
BIZARRE AND DEVIANT,
WHICH ARE
TWO FANTASTIC GAY CLUBS ON THE
WEST SIDE.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT AND CURRENT COURTROOM SKETCH
MODEL DONALD TRUMP
TESTIFIED ON
THE STAND FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
OVER TEN YEARS,
AND IT'S FUN
THAT NOBODY IS 100% SURE WHICH
TRIAL THIS SKETCH IS FROM.
TURNS OUT IT WAS FROM HIS CIVIL
FRAUD TRIAL
WHERE MICHAEL COHEN
TESTIFIED AGAINST DONALD TRUMP
WHILE TRUMP WAS IN THE
COURTROOM.
AND I BELIEVE WE HAVE VIDEO.
>> MICHAEL COHEN TESTIFIED THAT
DONALD TRUMP'S THREE OLDEST CHILDREN
WERE INVOLVED IN
PUTTING TOGETHER FINANCIAL
STATEMENTS FOR HIS COMPANY.
IVANKA WROTE THE SUMMARIES, DON
JR. PUT TOGETHER THE NUMBERS
AND ERIC
LICKED THE ENVELOPE.
TRUMP ASSESTS AND SAY
NOT 4 BUT 6
MELANIA
>> AND EARLIER TODAY, MIKE PENCE
OFFICIALLY ENDED HIS
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
HE MADE THE DECISION AFTER HE
CONSULTED WITH GOD,
AND GOD
SAID, DUDE, YOU'RE EMBARRASSING
BOTH OF US.
>> A NEW POLL SHOWS PRESIDENT
BIDEN AND DONALD TRUMP
ARE TIED
IN A HYPOTHETICAL 2024 REMATCH,
THOUGH THEY'RE BOTH RUNNING 50
POINTS BEHIND KILL ME.
KING CHARLES WILL VISIT KENYA NEXT WEEK
WHERE HE IS EXPECTED
TO ACKNOWLEDGE BRITAIN'S ROLE IN
THE SAVE TRADE.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, ATTEMPT TO
RETURN MEGHAN.
I JUST REPORT THE NEWS, GUYS.
>> I'M GLAD I DIDN'T TELL IT.
MITCH McCONNELL, SEEN HERE WATCHING
THE BANK FORECLOSE ON A
SINGLE MOTHER --
SAYS THAT HE HAS COMPLETELY
RECOVERED AFTER TWO INCIDENTS
WHERE HE APPEARED TO FREEZE UP
AND BECOME UNRESPONSIVE.
BUT SUSPICIOUSLY, HE MADE THE COMMENTS
WHILE BEING HELD UP BY
TWO GUYS IN BEACHWEAR.
WITH THE ACTORS STRIKE RECENTLY
PASSING THE 100 DAY MARK, MANY
ACTORS HAVE BEEN OUT OF WORK FOR
MONTHS.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT ACTORS NOT
BEING ABLE TO FIND WORK IS MY
AGENT, J.J. GORDON.
>> HEY, JOSTY, BABY, HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU SINCE MIAMI, BUD.
HOW'S MY FAVORITE CLIENT.
>> HEY, J.J.
SO NICE TO SEE YOU.
WHAT'S IT LIKE BEING MY AGENT
DURING THE LONGEST STRIKE IN
S.A.G. HISTORY.
>> WELL, I HAVEN'T BEEN GETTING
MANY CALLS ABOUT YOU, SO PRETTY
MUCH BUSINESS AS USUAL.
BUT DON'T WORRY, I GOT A LOT OF
IDEAS FOR YOU ONCE THIS THING
WRAPS UP.
>> OH, REALLY?
LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE THE OPPORTUNITY OF A
LIFETIME.
BIG NEW NETFLIX MOVIE ASKING FOR
A COLIN JOST TYPE.
>> PERFECT.
WHAT'S THE MOVIE?
>> IT'S CALLED NOT ALL HEROES
ARE SANDWICHES, THE JARED FOGLE
STORY.
>> I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
RESPECT, RESPECT.
>> RESPECT?
>> YES, I RESPECT THAT DECISION.
>> SURE.
>> HOW ABOUT THIS?
WHAT ABOUT JURASSIC PARK?
>> GREAT.
>> PORN VERSION.
IT'S CALLED JURASSIC PORK, AND
YEP, THEY'RE LOOKING FOR A MOFO
WITH SHORT ARMS TO PLAY A HORNY
T-REX.
I SAID YOU WOULD DO IT FOR FREE.
>> J.J., I'M NOT DOING DINOSAUR
PORN FOR FREE, MAN.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU SAID DOWN
IN MIAMI, MAN.
MAN!
WE WERE GETTING TWISTED IN
MIAMI.
YOU WERE THROWING ASS LIKE IT
WAS YOUR QUINCEANERA.
>> MY QUINCEANERA?
LOOK, ARE THERE ANY ROLES FOR ME
THAT AREN'T PORN?
>> YEAH.
I HEAR YOU.
WELL, THERE'S THIS NEW DISNEY
MOVIE YOU WOULD BE PERFECT FOR.
COULD BE A BLOCKBUSTER.
IT'S A LIVE ACTION POCAHONTAS
REBOOT CALLED JOHN SMITH'S
REVENGE, THE STORY OF A MAN WHO
HIT IT, QUIT IT, AND THEN
REMEMBERED WHAT TEAM HE'S ON.
FEELS RIGHT UP YOUR ALLY, JOSTY.
RIGHT UP YOUR ALLY.
>> THAT IS NOT RIGHT UP MY ALLY.
>> OKAY.
HOW ABOUT A COMMERCIAL THEN?
THAT'S A BIG PAY CHECK.
>> WELL, I SUPPOSE I HAVE BEEN
EYEING ANOTHER HELICOPTER.
>> OKAY.
HOW ABOUT THIS, OKAY, JERSEY
MIKE'S LOOKING FOR A NEW
SPOKESMAN.
>> PERFECT.
I LOVE THEIR SANDWICHES.
>> NO, SORRY.
IT'S JERSEY MIKE.
HE RUNS A KILL SHELTER IN
NEWARK.
>> I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
>> COLIN, HELP ME OUT, MAN!
HELP ME OUT!
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
I GOT NOTHING TO WORK WITH OVER
HERE.
OKAY?
YOU GOT A BAD BODY, YOU GOT A
BAD VIBE, AND YOUR FACE IS
GIVING THOMAS THE TANK ENGINE.
IT'S JUST A FLAT GRAY CIRCLE.
>> YOU'RE MY AGENT!
>> GIVE ME SOMETHING, C.J.!
I MEAN, CAN YOU SING?
>>.
♪ NOT REALLY ♪
>> CAN YOU DANCE?
>> A LITTLE.
>> CAN YOU DO IMPRESSIONS?
>> HEY, HEY, HEY!
>> YOU CAN ONLY DO FAT ALBERT.
I MEAN, OUR OPTIONS ARE LIMITED,
BUD!
REMEMBER WHEN YOU AUDITIONED FOR
DAHMER ON NETFLIX?
THEY SAID NO BECAUSE THEY NEEDED
SOMEONE WITH THE SLIGHTEST
GLIMMER OF HUMANITY.
>> J.J., THEN WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO DO?
>> COLIN, I WANT YOU TO GET OUT
THERE BECAUSE PEOPLE LOVE YOU,
THE REAL YOU, OKAY?
THEY WANT YOU TO JUST BE COLIN
JOST, OKAY?
WHICH IS WHY I THINK YOUR
DOCUMENTARY IS GOING TO BE HUGE
FOR US.
>> WHAT DOCUMENTARY?
>> JOST THE TWO OF US, MY SUMMER
WITH EPSTEIN.
>> MY AGENT, J.J. GORDON,
EVERYONE.
>> YOU LOOKING FOR
REPRESENTATION, CHE?
>> I'M GOOD.
I'M GOOD.
>> HE'S THE BEST.
>> NOPE.
ACCORDING TO A NEW POLL, 57% OF
NEW YORKERS AGREE WITH MAYOR ADAMS' CLAIM
THAT THE MIGRANT
CRISIS COULD DEFINITELY DESTROY
THE CITY.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
IN MY BUILDING, THE MIGRANTS FIX
EVERYTHING.
YOU GUYS NOT LIVE IN --
>> MICHIGAN STATE APOLOGIZED
AFTER AN IMAGE OF ADOLF HITLER
APPEARED ON A VIDEO BOARD AT A
FOOTBALL GAME.
EVEN MORE UPSETTING, IT WAS
DURING THE KISS CAM.
SOUTHWEST AIRLINES HAS
INTRODUCED A NEW FEATURE ON ITS APP
THAT LETS PASSENGERS TRACK
THEIR BAGS.
SOUTHWEST, WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
WHERE YOUR BAG IS.
>> AFTER DWAYNE JOHNSON COMPLAINED
THAT A WAX FIGURE OF
HIM AT A MUSEUM IN FRANCE HAD
THE WRONG SKIN TONE,
THE MUSEUM
HAS ATTEMPTED TO DARKEN THE
STATUE.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT MELTED IN THE
TANNING BED.
A MAN IN UTAH WAS ORDERED TO REMOVE
A HALLOWEEN DECORATION OF
A SKELETON POLL DANCING.
THAT LOOKS LIKE EVERY WHITE
STRIP CLUB TO ME.
>> THE WORLD'S OLDEST DOG EVER
HAS DIED AT THE AGE OF 31.
AND SOME EXPERTS BELIEVE IT
COULD HAVE LIVED EVEN LONGER
IF
I HAD LOOKED BEFORE BACKING OUT
OF THE DRIVEWAY.
AND A NEW REPORT FINDS THAT
VERMONT IS THE SAFEST STATE IN
AMERICA.
FOR LIKE, YOU KNOW, US.
>> NEW RESEARCH SUGGESTS THAT VIAGRA
CAN HELP LOWER A MAN'S
CHANCES OF DEVELOPING ALZHEIMER'S BY 50%
THANKS TO EFFECT
POSTNUT CLARITY.
>> WHITE CASTLE HAS REPLACED FRY
COOKS WITH ROBOTS.
BUT ONE THING THEY CAN'T REPLACE
IS JUMPING OVER THE COUNTER TO
CHOKE A CUSTOMER.
>> OLIVE OIL PRICES HAVE DOUBLED
EXTRENE WEATHER
WHICH SADLY HAS FORCED MANY
NEW JERSEY RESIDENTS TO BATHE IN
WATER.
FOR
CLEAR SKIES AHEAD.
WE SHOULD BE LANDING IN NEWARK
IN THREE HOURS.
>> YOU OKAY, BABE?
>> BABE, I THINK THE BABY'S
COMING.
>> OH, MY GOD!
EXCUSE ME, EVERYONE.
MY WIFE IS IN LABOR.
IS THERE A DOCTOR ON BOARD?
PLEASE, WE NEED A DOCTOR.
IS ANYONE A DOCTOR?
>> I'M A LAWYER.
>> WHAT?
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE NEED.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, PRETTY GOOD
JOB, YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT A DOCTOR, SECOND BEST
JOB IS A LAWYER.
>> WHO CARES IF LAWYER'S THE
SECOND BEST JOB?
IS ANYONE IN HERE A DOCTOR?
OH, THANK GOD.
>> OH, I'M NOT A DOCTOR.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY, I DON'T
THINK LAWYER IS THE SECOND BEST
JOB.
>> NOBODY CARES RIGHT NOW.
>> I CARE.
IF LAWYER'S NOT NUMBER TWO, THEN
WHAT IS?
>> I MEAN, GOT TO BE ENGINEER.
>> OKAY.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE AN ENGINEER?
>> NO, I'M A LAWYER.
I JUST GENUINELY BELIEVE
ENGINEER IS NUMBER TWO.
>> HOLD ON.
HOLD ON.
HOW IS ENGINEER NUMBER TWO?
>> HOW IS LAWYER NUMBER TWO?
>> WELL, BEING A LAWYER IS HARD.
SOMETIMES AN INNOCENT MAN GOES
TO JAIL, AND THEN YOU DON'T GET
PAID.
>> I AGREE.
LAWYER SOUNDS HARD.
AND I SHOULD KNOW, I ALSO HAVE A
HARD JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M A TEACHER.
SO I TEACH FUTURE LAWYERS AND
DOCTORS.
>> BOO!
>> OKAY.
I'M BEGGING YOU, WE'LL TAKE ANY
DOCTOR, ANY KIND OF DOCTOR.
>> I'M A KIND OF DOCTOR.
>> NO, NO, NO.
NOT YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO A QUICK POLL.
SO WE ALL AGREE DOCTOR IS NUMBER
ONE, NO DOUBT.
>> FOR SURE.
>> THEN FOR NUMBER TWO, IT'S
BETWEEN LAWYER AND ENGINEER.
>> WELL, I THINK I HAVE THE
HARDEST JOB OF ALL.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I AM A MOTHER.
>> OKAY.
BUT IN TERMS OF REAL STUFF, LIKE
JOBS THAT ACTUALLY PAY MONEY.
>> WELL, I'M A PILOT.
I FERRY HUNDREDS OF SOULS
THROUGH THE SKIES, AND I THINK
THAT'S THE SECOND BEST JOB.
>> WAIT.
IF YOU'VE BEEN IN THE BATHROOM,
WHO'S FLYING THE PLANE?
>> OH, NO!
THE AUTOPILOT, DUMB-ASS.
I GUESS PILOT IS PRETTY EASY.
BUT NOT AS EASY AS TEACHER.
>> BOO!
>> WHOO, WHOO.
>> PLEASE, CAN WE GET A DOCTOR?
>> THERE IS NO DOCTOR, OKAY?
SO THE BEST THING FOR YOUR WIFE
RIGHT NOW IS WE FIGURE OUT WHAT
THE SECOND BEST JOB IS.
>> DID SOMEONE ASK FOR A DOCTOR?
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
THANK GOD.
>> BECAUSE THAT'S MY HALLOWEEN
COSTUME.
>> COME ON, MAN.
♪ I HAD A VISION OF YOU
AND JUST LIKE THAT
I WAS LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT
LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ I FOUND A VERSION OF LOVE
AND JUST LIKE THAT I WAS LEFT
TO LIVE WITHOUT IT
LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ WAITING FOR THIS STORM TO
PASS WAITING ON THIS SIDE OF
THE GLASS ♪
♪ BUT I SEE MY REFLECTION IN
YOU SEE YOUR REFLECTION IN ME
HOW COULD IT BE
HOW COULD IT BE ♪
♪ THERE IS SOMETHING BETWEEN
US BETWEEN ME AND YOU
THERE IS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US ♪
♪ I SEE RIGHT THROUGH
I SEE RIGHT THROUGH ♪
♪ I HAD A VERSION OF HOME
AND JUST LIKE THAT
I WAS LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT
LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ I HAD A PERSON I LOVED
AND JUST LIKE THAT I WAS LEFT
TO LIVE WITHOUT IT
LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ WAITING FOR THIS STORM TO
PASS WAITING ON THIS SIDE OF
THE GLASS ♪
♪ BUT I SEE MY REFLECTION IN
YOU SEE YOUR REFLECTION IN ME
HOW COULD IT BE
HOW COULD IT BE ♪
♪ THERE IS SOMETHING BETWEEN
US BETWEEN ME AND YOU
THERE IS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US ♪
♪ I SEE RIGHT THROUGH
I SEE RIGHT THROUGH ♪
♪
♪ THERE IS SOMETHING BETWEEN
US BETWEEN ME AND YOU
THERE IS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US ♪
♪ I SEE RIGHT THROUGH
I SEE RIGHT THROUGH ♪
♪ I HAD A VISION OF YOU
AND JUST LIKE THAT
I WAS LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT
LEFT TO LIVE WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ WAITING ON THIS SIDE
OF THE GLASS ♪
FOOD
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M ACTUALLY
OKAY.
I'M DOING THIS MEAL SERVICE
THING.
>> COOL.
HELLO FRESH?
>> NO.
THAT ONE WAS TOUGH.
I'M ON THIS NEW ONE THAT SIMPLE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COOK AT ALL.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S IT CALLED?
>> DAWG FOOD.
>> LIKE DOG FOOD?
>> YEAH. FOR
GRAB YOUR BOWL, YOUR DAWG FOOD,
AND BAM, YOU GOT LUNCH.
>> MART, ARE YOU HEARING THIS?
YOU'RE ALSO DOING IT?
>> MY NEW MEAL PREP SERVICE.
>> YOU GUYS ARE JUST EATING DOG
FOOD.
>> IT'S ALL WE EAT.
>> SOMETIMES I ORDER A SALAD
WHEN I'M BEING BAD.
>> DOES IT TASTE GOOD?
>> NOT REALLY.
IT'S DOG FOOD.
>> YOU CAN'T BE EATING DOG FOOD.
>> IT'S NOT DOG FOOD. IT'S DAWG FOOD,
WHICH IS DOG
FOOD, BUT THE BAG SAYS IT'S
OKAY.
BAWLS
>> MINE WAS A GIFT FROM MY
GIRLFRIEND.
>> SHE'S OKAY WITH THIS?
>> NO.
SHE HATES IT.
>> NOW WE CAN'T EAT STUFF
BECAUSE AN ANIMAL EATS IT?
>> IF I PIGEON BITES MY FOOD, I
HAVE TO THROW THE WHOLE THING
AWAY?
>> YES!
>> I GUESS WE JUST GREW UP
DIFFERENT.
SEE
>> BAD DOG!
>> I AM SO SORRY.
PEELE
>> WHOSE DOG IS THAT?
>> HE'S HERE FOR DINNER.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
>> WHAT'S THE LASH T?IS THIS BED
I NEVER CALLED YOU.
>> WE NEVER HOOKED UP.
>> OH, THAT WAS A DREAM WE HAD.
>> IS THIS TOO GROSS FOR YOU?
I'LL SWITCH TO WET.
>> DON'T EAT WET DOG FOOD.
>> IT'S NOT JUST WET DOG FOOD.
I'M PUTTING KETCHUP ON IT.
DON'T
>> OH, MY GOD, DUDE.
NO.
DUDE
RIP
LUCKSMY.
THANK YOU LAUREN, "SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE," THE CAST IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
EVERYBODY THAT WORKS HERE, IT'S
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HARPER, WE LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU.