MONDAY
>>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
I'M PEYTON MANNING.
>> AM, YEAH, AND I'M ELI
MANNING, HIS BROTHER.
>> YEAH, I THINK THEY KNOW WE'RE
BROTHERS BECAUSE OF THE SAME
LAST NAME.
YEAH
CAST
WHERE WE DO LIVE
ANALYSIS OF WHAT'S ALREADY
PLAYING ON TV.
NORMALLY WE DO IT DURING THE
MONDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL.
>> BUT TONIGHT'S NOT MONDAY.
IT'S SATURDAY.
>> GREAT INCITE, ELI.
>> YEAH.
SO INSTEAD OF FOOTBALL, WE
DECIDED TO CHECK OUT THE SEASON
PREMIER OF SNL.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF CHANGES AT
THE SHOW, WHICH COULD BE
EXCITING.
LET'S SEE WHAT THEY SPENT THE
ENTIRE SUMMER COMING UP WITH.
>> OKAY, WE GOT AN ESTABLISHING
SHOT OF MAR-A-LAGO.
>> OH, GOOD.
TRUMP SKETCH.
WAY TO MIX IT UP.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, AS YOUR LAWYER,
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
BE HIDING DURING A HURRICANE.
>> ACTUALLY, IT'S THE SAFEST
PLACE I HAVE BEEN IN TWO YEARS.
THERE'S NO LAWYERS, NO FBI.
I'M IN MY HAPPY PLACE.
OKAY.
>> A FEW GUESTS WANTED TO SAY
HELLO, MR. PRESIDENT.
>> PLEASE, CALL ME CURRENT
PRESIDENT.
>> WHY ARE GUESTS VISITING
DURING A HURRICANE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT A ROOKIE
LEADING A SENIOR CAST MEMBER
INTO THE ROOM.
PROBABLY GOING TO RUN A SIMPLE,
RIGHT THIS WAY, MA'AM.
>> RIGHT THIS WAY, MA'AM.
>> TELEGRAPHED IT.
>> AND HE DOESN'T CLOSE THE DOOR
BEHIND HIM.
NOW HE'S TRYING TO FIX IT.
THE NEW GUY IS FULLY PANICKING.
HE'S JUST STARING IN THE CAMERA.
GOD. AND THAT MIGHT BE THE ONLY
TIME WE SEE HIM TONIGHT.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT HEIDI'S GOT.
SHE'S NEVER LET ME DOWN.
>> SIR, THE GOVERNOR OF SOUTH
DAKOTA IS HERE.
>> HELLO.
I'M GOVERNOR CHRISTY NULL
AND I
WANT TO TAKE YOUR ABORTION
RIGHTS.
>> AND SHE LET ME DOWN.
>> OKAY.
TIME OUT.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
>> THE GOVERNOR OF SOUTH DAKOTA,
A POLITICAL IMPRESSION THAT NO
ONE ASKED FOR.
WHAT ABOUT FUN IMPRESSION LIKE
ANTHONY FAUCI OR LINDSEY GRAHAM
OR RUDY GIULIANI?
>> THOSE WERE ALL KATE McKINNEN.
>> DAMN.
>> I ALSO WANT TO SAY HAPPY
EARLY COLUMBUS DAY, SIR.
>> WE LOVE COLUMBUS.
SAILED RIGHT OFF THE EDGE OF THE
WORLD BUT LANDED IN HAITI AND
GOT TO WORK.
>> I GOT TO POINT OUT, WHERE'S
THE BALANCE POLITICALLY?
THEY'RE MAKING TRUMP-COLUMBUS JOKES,
MEANWHILE, JOE BIDEN'S LOST HIS
MARBLES.
EVEN
>> HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
DONALD JUNIOR IS COMING IN.
DAD. I HATE TO CUT THE PARTY SHORT,
BUT WE GOT TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
THE PRESIDENT OF CHINA CAN ONLY
HOLD SO MANY NUCLEAR SECRETS.
>> LET'S JUST SAY I'M HAPPIER
THAN WHEN THE QUEEN'S CORGIS
FOUND OUT THEY WEREN'T GOING
WITH PRINCE ANDREW.
>> THAT CONFUSED ME, AND DID
BOWEN SAY CORGI,
DOES HE NOT
KNOW IT'S PRONOUNCED ARE CORDY?
>> IT'S A SURPRISE FUMBLE FROM
THE VETERAN YANG.
STEP UP
YOU CAN TELL THE PRESSURE IS
GETTING TO HIM.
>> MEANWHILE, LOOKS LIKE SARA SHERMAN
IS PEEKING IN THE WINDOW
TRYING TO WATCH THE SKIT.
>> NOW SHE REALIZES SHE'S CAUGHT
AND TRIES TO MAKE A SMOOTH EXIT.
WOW.
THEY'RE ALL PROFESSIONALS, BUT
SO ARE THE NEW YORK JETS.
>> THE SHOWS HAVE REBUILDING FOR
SURE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE STATS
SO FAR.
14 ATTEMPTED JOKES THIS EPISODE.
ONLY ONE MILD LAUGH AND THREE
CHUCKLES.
>> I HEARD THEY STAY UP UNTIL
5:00 A.M. WRITING THE SHOW.
>> WHEN DO THEY START WRITING
THE SHOW?
4:30
THANK GOD THEY'VE GOT KENDRICK
LAMAR BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY
REASON ANYONE IS TUNING IN.
>> LET'S CHECK BACK IN ON THE
SKIT.
>> NOW, PRESIDENT XI, YOU'RE NOT
HELPING OUT VLADIMIR PUTIN, ARE
YOU?
BECAUSE AS BRANDY TOLD MONICA,
THE BOY IS MINE.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS, AM I RIGHT?
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> WAIT.
IS HE TRYING TO MAKE THAT A
CATCH PHRASE?
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> OH, GOD, LOOK, HE'S SAYING IT
TO CAMERA NOW.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> DESPERATE STUFF.
ANYWAY, JOINING US NOW IS THE
THREE-TIME HOST OF SNL
DURING
WHAT NOW SEEMS LIKE A GOLDEN
ERA.
JOHN HAMM.
JOHN, WHAT HAVE YOU SEEN SO FAR
TONIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S NOT
COMEDY.
THEY HAVEN'T EVEN USED KEY
UNANIMOUS YET.
THAT'S LIKE PUTTING A WHOLE TEAM
OF ELIS ON THE FIELD,
AND YOU'VE
GOT THE PEYTON SITTING ON THE
SIDELINES.
>> I AGREE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE NEW CATS?
ANYONE YOU'RE EXCITED ABOUT?
>> I HAVE BEEN SCOUTING DEVON
WALKER AT BAR SHOWS FOR YEARS
NOW.
KID
COMES
>> SIR, THAT CORN KID IS HERE TO
SEE YOU.
>> IT'S CORN.
IT'S GOT THE JUICE.
>> OH, HELL NO.
CORN KID?
DEVON WALKER'S FIRST APPEARANCE
ON NATIONAL TV,
AND THEY GOT HIM
DOING CORN KID?
HEY
>> IT COULD BE WORSE.
LOOKS LIKE THEY GOT MOLLY AND
MARCELLO DOING THE GRITTY.
ATTEMP
MAYBE THIS IS STRATEGIC LIKE
WHEN A SPORTS TEAM TANKS TO GET
A BETTER DRAFT PICK NEXT YEAR.
>> AND SIR, THE SPECIAL MASTER
IS HERE.
HE FINISHED REVIEWING YOUR
DOCUMENTS.
>> I'VE DECIDED, THEY'RE ALL
AWESOME.
SEAN WHITE?
that is just gratuitous stunt casting
WELL, YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES THEY
NEED TO BRING IN A REAL
CELEBRITY
WHEN THE HOST ISN'T
THAT FAMOUS.
>> RIGHT.
>> I MEAN, THEY COULDN'T GET THE
STAR OF THE SUMMER MOVIE
OR TOM
CRUISE OR JOHN HAMM, THEY HAD TO
GET THE COSTAR.
>> WELL, I HEARD THEY RARELY PUT
THE HOSTS IN COLD OPEN,
SO WHEN
THEY DO, IT IS SPECIAL.
>> SPECIAL OR SIT DESPERATE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANKS FOR STOPPING BY, JOHN.
I KNOW JOHN'S GOT TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> NO.
I'M GOING TO STICK AROUND AND
SEE WHAT THE HELL THIS SHOW IS
GOING TO BE.
>> AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MILES
TELLER.
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HERE
HOSTING THE SEASON PREMIER OF
SNL.
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME HOSTING,
AND I KNOW THEY LIKE WHEN YOU DO
IMPRESSIONS, AND PLAY DIFFERENT CELEBRITIES,
AND I WANTED TO
COME PREPARED.
SO I ASKED MY FRIENDS, WHAT
CELEBRITY DO I LOOK LIKE,
AND I
WAS THINKING A YOUNG DENIRO,
MAYBE A PAUL NEW MAN,
AND THEY
WERE LIKE, NOPE, RACHEL MADAU.
I DIDN'T SEE IT, BUT ONE OF THEM
SENT ME THIS.
THIS YEAR, I WAS IN A MOVIE
CALLED "TOP GUN, MAVERICK",
AND
ONE OF THE THINGS I LOVED ABOUT THE MOVIE
IS IT REALLY SEEMED TO
BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY YOU GET A MOVIE
THAT'S LOVED BOTH BY THE
MILITARY COMMUNITY AND THE GAY
COMMUNITY.
THAT WORKED OUT.
IT WAS ALSO AMAZING GETTING TO
WORK WITH TOM CRUISE.
THAT GUY IS LEGEND.
WE BOTH PUSHING OURSELVES TO THE
ABSOLUTE LIMIT FOR THIS MOVIE.
HE DID HIS OWN STUNTS, AND I
GREW MY OWN MUSTACHE.
IN THE MOVIE, THERE'S A SCENE
WHERE MY CHARACTER ROOSTER
SINGS
AND PLAYS GREAT BALLS OF FIRE ON
THE PIANO.
PLAY
I TOLD THEM, I DON'T NEED A
DOUBLE, GUYS.
I'LL DO IT MYSELF, I'LL DO IT
LIVE.
SO I LEARNED THIS SONG, A
PRACTICED IT A BUNCH.
I EVEN TOOK PIANO LESSONS.
MY INSTRUCTOR WAS JK SIMMONS,
WHO WAS SURPRISINGLY NICE.
AND ON SET, I PLAYED THE ENTIRE
SONG, BEGINNING TO END,
AND THEN
WHEN I SAW THE MOVIE, THIS IS
WHAT THEY ENDED UP USING.
I GOT TO SAY, I'M SO HONORED TO
BE HERE.
GROWING UP, ME AND MY FAMILY
WOULD WATCH "SNL" EVERY WEEK,
AND MY SISTERS AND I WOULD
REENACT SOME OF THE SKETCHES,
AND MY MOM WOULD VIDEO TAPE
THEM.
ONE OF OUR FAVORITES WAS THE
SPAR TAN CHEERLEADERS.
FERRELL
I PLAYED SHERRY OTERRY
BECAUSE I WAS EIGHT AND I HAD THE FRAME
FOR IT.
NOW, I THOUGHT THAT VIDEO WAS
LOST.
BUT MY MOM FOUND IT, AND SHE'S
HERE TONIGHT,
AND SHE BROUGHT
IT.
HERE IT IS.
THAT'S ME IN THE TANK TOP.
MY SISTER ERIN IS PLAYING WILL
FERRELL.
OH, YEAH.
AND IF YOU LOOK IN THE
BACKGROUND, THAT'S MY OTHER
SISTER, DANA.
PRETTY SURE SHE'S PLAYING LAUREN
MICHAELS.
AND THEN WE FINISH OUR ROUTINE
WITH THE CLASSIC,
WHO'S THAT
SPARTAN IN MY TP.
>> WHO'S THAT SPARTAN IN MY TP?
>> IT'S ME, IT'S ME.
NAILED IT.
BUT SERIOUSLY, HOW CRAZY IS
THAT?
MY PARENTS USED TO WATCH ME DO
SKITS IN MY LIVING ROOM,
AND NOW
THEY'RE HERE WATCHING ME HOST
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
STICK
>>> IT'S TIME TO PLAY AMERICA'S
EASIEST GAME SHOW,
SEND
SOMETHING NORMAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, AMERICA.
WELCOME TO SEND SOMETHING
NORMAL.
I'M YOUR HOST, HALEN HARDY.
THE GAME IS VERY SIMPLE.
WE HAVE FOUR MALE CELEBRITY CONTESTANTS,
AND ALL THEY HAVE
TO DO IS REPLY TO A WOMAN'S DM
ON INSTAGRAM
IN A WAY THAT IS
NORMAL.
AND FELLOWS, IF YOU SEND A NORMAL DM,
YOU WIN $100 MILLION.
AGAIN, THE GAME IS SEND A WOMAN
A NORMAL DM
AND YOU WIN
$100 MILLION.
NOW, LET'S MEET OUR FIRST
CONTESTANT, ADAM LEVINE.
NOW, WE ALL KNOW WHY YOU'RE
HERE, ADAM.
>> I WAS BAD.
>> YES, YOU WERE, ADAM.
NEXT UP, COMING TO US ALL THE
WAY FROM HIS INVOLUNTARY CAREER CHANGE,
ARMY HAMMER.
>> YEAH, HI.
CAN I GET A BIG WELCOME BACK TO
HOLLYWOOD ROUND OF APPLAUSE?
>> NO, YOU MAY NOT.
NEXT UP, NEIL DEGRASS TYSON.
>> WELL, THANK YOU FOR HAVING
ME.
WHAT A PLEASURE.
WHY AM I HERE?
>> WELL, NEIL, YOU HAVEN'T HAD A
DM SCANDAL YET, BUT YOU NEVER
KNOW.
>> OH, PLEASE, IN MY CIRCLE, DM
STANDS, DIVALENT MAGNESIUM.
BUT I SUPPOSE IN OUR ALTERNATE
REALITIES, ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
>> AND OUR FINAL CONTESTANT,
IT'S "SNL" CAST MEMBER, BOWEN
YANG.
>> WOW.
>> NOW, BOWEN IS OUR RETURNING
CHAMPION.
LAST WEEK, WE RACKED OVER
$1.4 BILLION.
BOWEN, WHAT DO YOU ATTRIBUTE YOUR
SUCCESS TO?
>> OH, BEING GAY.
>> MAKES SENSE TO ME.
ALL RIGHT.
ADAM LEVINE, HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO RESPOND TO THIS WOMAN'S DM?
HEY, ADAM, HUGE FAN.
LOVE YOUR MUSIC.
>> OKAY.
TOUGH CALL.
CAN I SEE HER MOST LIKED
VACATION PHOTO?
>> SEEMS LIKE THAT COULDN'T
POSSIBLY HELP, BUT SURE.
GOT TO SAY, ADAM, DON'T LOVE
THAT HAND MOTION.
OKAY.
I HAVE MY ANSWER.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOING TO KICK THINGS OFF
WITH A
HOLY MOLY!
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
BUT I GOT THREE MORE, THOUGH.
HOLY MOLY!
HOLY CRAP!
YOUR BODY IS MAKING MY PENIS
SMILE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SORRY, ADAM.
YOU ALMOST HAD IT THERE.
>> OH, OKAY.
I DID?
>> NO.
ARMY, IT'S YOUR TURN TO RESPOND.
YOUR MESSAGE IS, HEY, ARMY, HOPE
YOU'RE DOING OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOK.
I KNOW THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
TALK ABOUT ME IN THE PRESS,
BUT
I'VE DONE A LOT OF WORK ON
MYSELF, AND I'VE CHANGED.
SO I HAVE MY MESSAGE.
>> WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
>> I WANT TO BREAK OPEN YOUR
BONES AND SUCK OUT THE MARROW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO TO NEIL.
YOUR MESSAGE IS, HEY, NEIL, I
LOVE YOUR PODCAST.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT A KIND MESSAGE.
WHAT A NICE WOMAN.
DESERVES A WELL-RESEARCHED
RESPONSE.
PLEASE SHOW ME HER MOST LIKED
VACATION PHOTO.
>> YOU TOO, NEIL?
ALL RIGHT.
>> UH-HUH.
OKAY.
CALCULATING.
>> NOW, NEIL, LET ME HELP YOU
OUT HERE.
YOU WILL WIN IF YOU JUST SAY,
THANK YOU.
>> I HAVE AN ALTERNATE RESPONSE.
SALUTATIONS.
PERHAPS IF THE STARS DO ALIGN,
YOU WOULD LIKE TO COME OVER AND
PEER INTO MY TELESCOPE,
METAPHORICALLY SPEAKING.
>> NOW, NEIL, ARE YOU ASKING
THAT WOMAN TO LOOK INTO YOUR
PENIS?
>> I SUPPOSE I WAS.
IS THAT NOT NORMAL?
>> NO.
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT UP IS BOWEN YANG.
BOWEN, GOT A GOOD FEELING YOU'RE
GOING TO WIN THIS ROUND.
>> ME TOO.
>> YOUR MESSAGE IS, HEY, I'M A
HUGE FAN.
I WOULD LOVE TON YOUR FRIEND.
>> THAT'S SO NICE.
I'LL JUST SAY --
>> JUST BEFORE YOU START.
THIS MESSAGE IS FROM DUA LIPA.
>> OH, NO!
>> GOT A RESPONSE, BOWEN?
>> HOLY MOLY!
HOLY CRAP!
YOUR MUSIC MAKES MY PENIS SMILE.
>> BOWEN, COME ON, MAN.
HORRIBLE.
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A QUICK
BREAK, BUT WHEN WE COME BACK,
WE'LL SEE IF ANY OF THESE GUYS
CAN JUST SAY NOTHING AT ALL.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU A HINT, I'M
GOING TO SAY, A MIGHT NEED TO
SEE THAT BOOTY!
>>> EVERYBODY ON THE GROUND!
>> OH, NO, NO, NO.
>> YOU, WE NEED EVERYTHING FROM
THE VAULT IN THE BAG.
>> DO WHAT WE SAY, AND NO ONE
HAS TO GET HURT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OPEN THE VAULT, LADY.
>> I'M GOING AS FAST AS I CAN.
>> WELL, PICK IT UP!
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I'M SORE ARE I.
I'M NOT CALLING THE POLICE, I
SWEAR.
>> SLIDE IT OVER NOW, OR WE KILL
YOU.
>> I WANT TO, BUT I CAN'T.
THE BECAUSE IT'S --
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IT'S TIME TO BE REAL.
>> TIME TO BE WHAT?
>> TIME TO BE REAL.
>> WAIT.
WAIT, IT IS?
>> YEP.
I JUST GOT THE NOTIFICATION.
TIME TO BE REAL.
>> EVERYBODY SHUT UP.
YEAH. OR TELL US WHAT BE REAL IS.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
IT'S THIS APP, IT'S THE ONLY
HONEST SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> YOU THINK I'M AN IDIOT?
HONEST SOCIAL MEDIA DOESN'T
EXIST.
>> WITH BE REAL, YOU CAN ONLY
POST ONCE A DAY WHENEVER THE APP
SENDS OUT A NOTIFICATION.
>> SO EVERYONE POSTS WHEREVER
THEY ARE WHATEVER THEY'RE DOING.
>> IT'S NOT STATUS ORIENTED, AND
THAT'S WHY IT'S CALLED BE REAL?
>> YES, YOU'RE GETTING IT.
>> EVERYBODY NEEDS TO -- WHAT
ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> TWO MINUTES TO POST.
QUICK, QUICK, POSE.
>> WAIT, WAIT, SO IS IT A
PICTURE OF YOU OR ME?
>> THAT'S THE THING.
IT TAKE AS I FRONT AND BACK
PHOTO AT THE SAME TIME.
>> THAT IS CRAZY.
>> DO YOU GUYS ALL WORK FOR BE
REAL OR ANYTHING?
>> NO.
WE'RE JUST SO ALIGNED WITH THE
MISSION OF THE PLATFORM.
>> YOU, DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
IT.
>> WHERE THE HELL IS SECURITY?
>> COME ON, YOU DON'T WANT TO
POST LATE.
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU POST
LATE?
>> IT TELLS PEOPLE SO THAT
EVERYONE KNOW THAT IS YOUR BE
REAL WASN'T BEING REAL.
>> OKAY.
I DOWNLOADED IT, AND I'M GOING
TO BE REAL ABOUT EXACTLY WHAT
I'M DOING.
>> NO!
DON'T POST THIS ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> NO.
NO MORE CUE RATION.
I DON'T CARE WHO KNOWS WHAT I'M
DOING RIGHT NOW.
I'M GOING TO BE REAL.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> DOWNLOAD BE REAL TODAY.
>>> HE'S BEEN IN THERE FOR 17
MINUTES.
HE'S GOING TO BE LATE FOR WORK.
>> HONEY, EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> NO ITCHES, NO SCRATCH, MY
BOOTY FEELS SO SNATCHED.
THANK YOU, CHARMIN.
WE FINALLY CHEEK TO CHEEK.
YEAH, WE FINALLY CHEEK TO CHEEK.
THANK YOU, CHARMIN.
>> I WAS SO WORRIED FOR A SECOND
THERE, DAD.
>> DON'T WORRY, SWEETIE.
IT'S NOT MY FIRST TIME, AND IT
WON'T BE MY LAST TODAY.
>> AMEN.
>> WAIT, WHERE'S TOBY?
WHY DIDN'T HE JOIN IN?
>> SORE ARE I.
I'M OVER HERE.
I DIDN'T HEAR YOU SINGING.
>> WHAT'S WRONG, SON?
ARE YOU STOPPED UP?
>> YEAH, TOBY, YOU OKAY?
WAIT.
WHAT YOU READING HERE?
WHAT IS THIS?
IS THIS?
IT'S AN ACCEPTANCE LETTER, TO
TOILET PAPER COLLEGE.
MY SON IS GOING TO TPC.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M ABOUT TO CRY.
TOILET PAPER COLLEGE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS
HAPPENING.
>> I'M SORRY, DAD.
IT'S NOT.
I'M NOT GOING.
>> WAIT.
HANG ON NOW.
I DON'T THINK I HEARD YOU RIGHT.
>> THEN TAKE THE CHARMIN OUT OF
YOUR EARS, DAD.
I CHANGED MY MIND.
>> NOW, LISTEN TO ME, BOY.
YOU ARE THE FIRST MEMBER OF THIS
FAMILY TO GO TO COLLEGE, AND YOU
ARE GETTING THAT BFA.
>> I DON'T WANT A BACHELOR OF
FLUSHING ARTS.
>> WELL, I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU
WANT.
>> KEITH, RELAX.
>> NO, NO.
I WORKED IN THAT TOILET PAPER
MINE FOR 40 YEAR.
40 YEARS.
>> IT'S TRUE, TOBY.
HE'S DOWN THERE WITH HIS PICK AX
ALL DAY JUST GATHERING UP THOSE
ROLLS.
>> AND I DID NOT WORK MY PAWS TO
THE BONE JUST TO SEE YOU THROW
THIS AWAY.
YOU GETTING THAT DEGREE IN
STUDIES.
>> WHY DOES EVERYTHING IN OUR
LIFE HAVE TO REVOLVE AROUND
GOING TO THE BATHROOM?
>> BECAUSE, SWEETIE, WE'RE
BEARS.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
WE DO TWO THINGS.
WE EAT HONEY, AND WE SHOOT IT
OUT.
>> WELL, I WANT MORE, MOM.
I WANT MORE THAN JUST EATING
HONEY AND SHOOTING IT OUT.
>> YOU ARE NOT MY SON.
>> DAD!
DON'T SAY THAT!
>> NOW, GO UPSTAIRS IN YOUR
ROOM, STACEY.
I'M GOING TO MALL YOUR BROTHER
NOW.
>> TOBY, CAN YOU JUST PLEASE DO
WHAT HE WANTS?
>> WHAT ABOUT WHAT I WANT?
>> WELL, WHAT IS IT?
>> I WANT TO DANCE, MAMA.
I WANT TO DANCE.
>> WE DANCED AT THE BEGINNING.
>> NOT TOILET DANCING, NOT
TWERKING BECAUSE OUR ASSS ARE
CLEAN.
I'M TALKING ABOUT ART.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
>> NO, I DON'T GET THIS DAY AT
ALL.
>> THEN LET ME SHOW YOU.
WILLIAM, CAN YOU COME IN?
>> HELLO.
I APOLOGIZE FOR BEING LATE.
I WAS USING YOUR BATHROOM.
>> THAT'S OUR KITCHEN.
>> THEN YOU HAVE MY APOLOGIES.
>> WHO IS THIS?
>> I MET HIM IN DANCE CLASS.
>> WHAT?
>> I CAN TELL BY YOUR REACTION
THAT THIS IS SHOCKING NEWS, BUT
I HAVE MORE.
YOUR SON IS GOOD.
>> PLEASE, DAD, JUST GIVE ME A
CHANCE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M DOING
THIS, BUT ALL RIGHT.
BUT IF I'M NOT IMPRESSED, YOU
ARE GOING TO THAT DOO DOO
COLLEGE.
>> DEAL.
I'M SO SCARED.
>> HEY, DON'T BE.
♪
>> HONEY, YOU'RE CRYING.
>> YES, MY SON IS A DANCER.
>>> HELL, YEAH.
CLOUD BAR IS HOPPING TONIGHT.
>> HELL YEAH IT IS.
GOING TO BE A GOOD NIGHT.
>> DAMN RIGHT.
DESERVE IT.
I CRUSHED WORK TODAY.
GOD DAMN DAY TRADING, I LIVE FOR
IT.
>> I STAND DAY TRADING, BRO.
>> NOT GOING TO LIE.
GIRLS IN HERE TONIGHT, DECENT.
>> LOT OF COUNTING IN THE ROOM
THIS EVE.
GOING TO GET MY FLIRT ON THEN MY
SQUIRT ON.
YOU FEEL ME?
>> YES, DUDE.
>> LATELY I HAVE BEEN INTO THE
FLAT ASS, FLAT CHEST, TINY
TEETS.
>> NOT SO MUCH INTO THE TINY
TEETS, BUT I'M LOOKING FOR A
HONEY TO MAKE A MESS WITH.
OH, YEAH.
HOT ALERT.
LET'S FLIRT WITH THESE TOO.
>> OH, YEAH.
CHARM NEVER DID NO HARM.
>> GETTING DRUNK?
>> SORRY?
>> YOU GUYS GETTING DRINKUS?
>> OH, DRINKS, YEAH.
>> COOL, COOL.
ALCOHOL!
BOOP, BOOP, SORRY.
YEAH, I LOVE ALCOHOL.
>> I WORK IN FINANCE.
>> OKAY.
COOL.
EXCUSE ME, BARTENDER?
>> YEAH, WHAT DO YOU NEED,
SWEETIE?
>> CAN I GET A STELLA?
>> STELLA.
>> AND CAN I GET A VODKA CRAN?
>> OH, CRANBERRY, UH-OH, UTI?
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> YOP.
THAT WAS WEIRD.
WHY AM I TALKING LIKE THIS.
PUT THESE FAIR MAIDS DRINKS ON
MY TAB.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> YES, WITH YOUR FINEST TOP
SHELF LIQUOR.
>> OKAY.
TOP SHELF HAS A $90 UPCHARGE.
IS THAT OKAY?
>> OH, NOT SO MUCH.
WHY SO SERIOUS?
BATMAN.
NOW NO.
WE CHILLING, NO.
HOW MUCH IS THE LICK TORE THREE
SHELVES DOWN FROM THE TOP?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S JUST DO STOILY.
YOU GOT A TAB?
>> MY NAME IS NICK CHODECORK.
IT'S A BVA DEBIT.
>> SO YOU GUYS ARE FRIENDS?
>> YEAH.
>> BLACK AND WHITE, HELL YEAH.
I'LL CLAP FOR THAT.
>> YEAH.
SO LET'S CHAT.
DID YOU GUYS BUY YOUR CLOTHES AT
A STORE OR ONLINE?
>> STORE.
>> STORE AS WELL.
>> Y'ALL LIKE STORES.
YEAH.
>> I MEAN, IT DEPENDS ON WHICH
ONE.
IS SHE ALMOST BACK WITH THE
DRINKS.
>> DEPENDS ON WHICH ONE, OKAY,
VERY COOL.
SOME STORES YOU LIKE.
OTHER STORES, YOU'RE LIKE, I
DON'T KNOW.
I MIGHT NOT GO IN THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, YEAH.
THAT'S INTERESTING.
VERY COOL.
STORES.
HEY.
WHOO.
>> CHODECORK, YOUR CARD WAS
DECLINED.
>> PLEASE RUN IT AGAIN.
>> WHAT Y'ALL STREAMING?
Y'ALL WATCH STRANGER THINGS?
>> IF YOU'RE ASKING IF I WATCH
STRANGER THINGS, THEN, YES, I
DO.
>> YES.
♪ I'M RUNNING UP THAT HILL ♪
>> VECNA.
BOOBIES!
I'M SORRY.
WHY DID I DO THAT?
>> I WORK IN FINANCE.
>> YES, YOU SAID THAT.
>> HAHA -- YOU GUYS WANT TO COME
OVER TO OUR APARTMENT?
>> YOU'RE ROOMMATES?
YOU GUYS ARE LIKE 40.
>> YEAH, GOOD ONE.
>> LET'S JUST GO TO THE PATIO
BAR.
>> NICE TALKING.
BYE.
>> YEAH.
YO, HOW DID THAT HAPPEN, BRO?
YOUR GAME WAS ON POINT.
>> I KNOW, DUDE, RIGHT?
LIKE I'M IN A MAD DRY SPELL
RIGHT NOW.
NO JOKE, IT'S BEEN 11 YEARS
SINCE I DID IT, BUT LIKE ON
PURPOSE, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I'VE NEVER DONE
IT.
SO I MEAN, I GUESS THE LAST TIME
WAS LIKE I HAVE BEEN WAITING MY
WHOLE LIFE, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHOULD I JUST LIKE GIVE UP?
>> NAH.
LET'S DO A LAP.
>> YEAH, MOST DEF, DOG.
MOST DEF.
>>> WE COME TO THIS PLACE FOR
MAGIC.
WE COME TO AMC THEATERS TO
LAUGH, TO CRY, TO CARE.
BECAUSE WE NEED THAT, ALL OF US.
THAT INDESCRIBABLE FEELING WE
GET WHEN THE LIGHTS BEGIN TO
DIM.
OH, I CAN'T DESCRIBE IT.
AND WE GO PLACES WE'VE NEVER
BEEN BEFORE, NOT JUST ENTERTAIN,
BUT SOMEHOW REBORN TOGETHER.
DAZZLING IMAMGS ON A HUGE SILVER
SCREEN.
SOMEHOW HEART BREAK FEELS GOOD
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
>> HEARTBREAK FEELS GOOD IN A
PLACE LIKE THIS.
HEARTBREAK FEELS GOOD IN A PLACE
LIKE THIS.
>> AND I CAN FEEL.
OUR HEROES FEEL LIKE THE BEST
PART OF US, AND OUR STORIES FEEL
PERFECT.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> WE ARE HERE!
AMC, WE MAKE MOVIES BETTER.
>> WHAT THE [ BLEEP ] JUST
HAPPENED?
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
"Rich Spirit" and "N95"
Takin' my baby to school, then I pray for her
'Cause you bitches ain't never been cool, writin' testament
Paintin' pictures, put me in the Louvre, that's a definite
Universal shift, I'm in a groove and celebrity do not mean integrity, you fool
WITH THE EYE PATCH
TAKE OFF THE UNLOYAL
TAKE OFF THE UNSURE ♪
♪ TAKE OFF DECISIONS I LACK
TAKE OFF THE FAKE DEEP
TAKE OFF THE FAKE WOKE
TAKE OFF THE I'M BROKE ♪
HUH, TWO ATMS ♪
♪ YOU STEPPIN' OR WHAT
YOU OUT OF POCKET, HUH
WHO YOU THINK THEY TALK 'BOUT
TALK ABOUT US ♪
♪ YOU OUT OF POCKET
SHOOT, SHOOT, SHOOT
WHO YOU THINK THEY COPY OFF
COPY OFF US ♪
♪ GET BACK IN POCKET
SERVIN' UP A LOOK
DANCIN' IN THE DROUGHT
HELLO TO THE BIG STEPPER ♪
♪ NEVER LOSIN' COUNT
VENTIN' IN THE SAFE HOUSE
VENTIN' IN THE SA-, AHH
CAN I VENT ALL MY TRUTH ♪
♪ I GOT NOTHIN' TO LOSE
I GOT PROBLEMS AND POOLS
I CAN SWIM IN MY FAITH
CAMERA'S MOVIN' ♪
♪ WHENEVER I'M MOVIN'
THE FAMILY SUIN'
WHATEVER I MAKE
MURDER IS STACKIN' ♪
♪ THE PRESIDENT ACTIN'
THE GOVERNMENT TAXIN'
MY FUNDS IN THE BANK
HOMIES ATTRACTIN' THE FEDS ♪
♪ WHEN I'M BRACKIN'
LOOK AT MY REACTION
MY PUPILS ON SKATES
LET'S THINK ABOUT THIS ♪
♪ FOR A SECOND
TELL ME WHAT YOU WOULD DO
FOR AESTHETIC
WOULD YOU SELL YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ ON CREDIT
WOULD YOU SELL YOUR BRO
FOR LEVERAGE
WHERE THE HYPOCRITES AT ♪
♪ WHAT COMMUNITY FEEL
THEY THE ONLY ONES RELEVANT
WHERE THE HYPOCRITES AT
WHAT COMMUNITY FEEL ♪
♪ THEY THE ONLY
ONES RELEVANT
YOU OUTTA POCKET
YEAH, YOU OUTTA POCKET ♪
♪ YOU ENTERTAIN THE MEDIOCRE
NEED TO STOP IT
YOU ENTERTAININ' OLD FRIENDS
WHEN THEY TOXIC ♪
♪ WHAT'S YOUR LIFE LIKE
AND GOSSIP
WHAT IS CANCEL CULTURE, DAWG
SAY WHAT I WANT ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ I'M LIKE OPRAH, DAWG
I TREAT YOU LIKE I'M WATCH
I OWN IT ALL
OH ♪
♪ YOU WORRIED 'BOUT A CRITIC
THAT AIN'T PROTOCOL ♪
♪ YOU'RE OUT OF POCKET ♪
♪ YOU ENTERTAINER MEDIA NEED TO
STOP IT ♪
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> HEY, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> IN A SPEECH AFTER ANNEXING
SECTIONS OF UKRAINE,
VLADIMIR
PUTIN ATTACKED THE U.S. FOR SATANISM
AND DENOUNCED THE MANY
GENDERS IN FASHION IN THE U.S.
IT WAS A HATEFUL, UNHINGED SPEECH
WHICH HAS MANY AMERICANS
CALLING HIM ELECTABLE.
>>> THE KREMLIN CELEBRATED THE
ILLEGAL ANNEXATION OF UKRAINE
WITH ENTERTAINMENT IN THE RED
SQUARE.
SAY WHAT YOU WILL, BUT A GIG IS
A GIG.
>> MOSCOW URGING ALL SIDS IN
RUSSIA TO LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
OH, COOL, I'LL TRY TO DO THAT,
SAID BRITTNEY GRINER.
>> HURRICANE IAN HIT FLORIDA THIS WEEK,
AND GOVERNOR RON
DeSANTIS CALLED T IT A 500 YEAR
FLOODING EVENT.
IT'S SUCH A TRAGEDY THAT
DeSANTIS WON'T LET THEM
TEACH
ABOUT IT IN FLORIDA SCHOOLS.
>> AND AT A WHITE HOUSE EVENT,
PRESIDENT BIDEN
IN AUDIENCE
ASKED, WHERE'S JACKIE,
APPARENTLY FORGETTING
SHE DIED LAST MONTH.
WORSE, HE KEEPS FORGETTING THAT
THIS WOMAN IS STILL ALIVE.
>> THE ELECTORAL COUNT REFORM
ACT WAS APPROVED BY ALL MEMBERS
OF A SENATE COMMITTEE
EXCEPT FOR
TED CRUZ.
COINCIDENTALLY, EVERYONE EXCEPT
FOR TED CRUZ IS ALSO WHO JESUS
LOVED.
>> JENNY THOMAS, WHO'S BEGGING
YOU TO NOTICE THE SCARF,
SO SHE
CAN SAY, OH, THIS OLD THING --
REPORTEDLY TOLD THE COMMITTEE
HER HUSBAND WAS UNAWARE
IN HER
INVOLVEMENT TO CHALLENGES IN THE 2020 ELECTION,
AND THEY NEVER
DISCUSSED ANY CASE BEFORE THE
COURT.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I BELIEVE,
IT'S THAT THIS GUY DOESN'T TALK
TO HIS WIFE.
>>> REPRESENTATIVE MARJORIE
TAYLOR GREEN REVEALED
HER
HUSBAND HAS FILED FOR DIVORCE
AFTER 27 YEARS OF MARRIAGE.
HE BLAMED IRRECONCILABLE
DIFFERENCES FOR THE SPLIT
WHILE
SHE BLAMED THE JEWS.
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN ON FRIDAY
ATTENDED A FORMAL CEREMONY
WELCOMING JUSTICE KETANJI BROWN
JACKSON TO THE SUPREME COURT.
SAID PRESIDENT BIDEN, AND
WHERE'S JUSTICE GINSBURG?
RUTH, COME UP HERE?
>>> LAST MONTH, MITCH McCONNELL
EXPRESSED CONCERN ABOUT
REPUBLICANS CHANCES IN THE
MIDTERM.
HERE TO EXPLAIN IS MITCH
McCONNELL AND HERSCHEL WALKER.
>> PLEASURE, PLEASURE.
>> YEAH, LET'S GO TEAM.
ALL RIGHT.
>> SO HERSCHEL, YOU'RE A FORMER
NFL PLAYER.
>> YES.
>> WITH NO FORMER EXPERIENCE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> AND YOU WERE CAUGHT LYING
ABOUT HAVING THREE SECRET
CHILDREN.
>> YES, SIR.
>> SO SENATOR McCONNELL, DO YOU
REALLY THINK THIS GUY IS READY
TO BE A SENATOR?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT I SAY,
AND I SAY, GO HERSCHEL WALKER.
>> WELL, I LOVE YOU TOO, MITCH
McCONIC.
ME AND MITCH ARE LIKE TWO PEAS
IN A BAG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU'VE ALREADY SAID SOME
THINGS THAT HAVE REPUBLICANS
WORRIED.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU SAID, QUOTE,
OUR GOOD AIR DECIDED TO FLOAT
OVER TO CHINA'S BAD AIR, SO WHEN
CHINA GETS OUR GOOD AIR, THE BAD
AIR GOT TO MOVE OUT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> I'LL SLOW DOWN SO YOU CAN
UNDERSTAND.
WE ALL KNOW AIR, RIGHT?
AIR BUD.
>> UH-HUH, YEP.
>> AIR JORDAN.
>> SURE.
>> ERIN BROKOVICH.
>> YOU SEE, SCIENTISTS DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
EVERYBODY TALK ABOUT CLIELT.
BUT WHAT WE REALLY SHOULD BE
FOCUSED ON IS PULLING HAWAII
CLOSER.
BRING THAT CLIMATE OVER HERE.
>> I LIKE THAT IDEA.
>> THEY DON'T NEED IT.
THEY LITTLE.
THAT'S SOMETHING WE NEED TO LOOK
AT VERY CLOSELY, RIGHT, DISH?
>> IT'S MITCH.
>> EXACTLY.
>> SENATOR McCONNELL, I GOT TO
ASK, WHAT QUALIFICATIONS DOES
THIS GUY ACTUALLY HAVE TO BE IN
THE SENATE?
>> THERE'S TOO MANY TO NAME.
FIRST OF ALL, HE PLAYED
FOOTBALL, AND GEORGIA LOVES
FOOTBALL.
>> EVERYBODY LOVES FOOTBALL.
BASEBALL.
IN FACT, MAN, CATCHING BALLS IS
WHAT MAKES US DIFFERENT FROM
APES.
AND LISTEN, IF WE COME FROM
APES, WHY ARE THERE STILL APES
OUT THERE?
RIDDLE ME THAT, OBAMA MICHELLE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY REAL POLICY
PROPOSALS?
>> OF COURSE I DO.
I WROTE DOWN A FEW FOR MITCH ON
THE WAY DOWN HERE.
GO AHEAD AND READ THAT THERE,
MITCH.
>> PROPOSAL NUMBER ONE, BARBECUE
TUESDAY.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> NUMBER TWO, LET'S GET A
DAYTIME MOON, THAT WAY, NO MORE
RAIN.
>> BOOM.
>> AND NUMBER THREE, CREATE A
DEPARTMENT OF INSTAGRAM BOOTY,
TOO MANY GIRLS OUT HERE FAKING
THEIR CAKE.
>> IT AIN'T RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TELL THEM ABOUT YOURSELF.
>> THANK YOU, STITCH.
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
WHERE'S MY CAMERA?
IS IT DOWN HERE?
>> NO.
IT'S RIGHT THERE, MAN.
IT'S THERE.
>> OH, OKAY.
HI, OF AMERICA.
MY NAME IS HERSCHEL BERSHEL,
WHENEVER I'M IN HARD TIME, I
THINK ABOUT THE STRENGTH OF THE
FOUNDING FATHERS, GEORGE CARVER
WASHINGTON, THE JEFFERSONS, AND
BENJAMIN FRANKENSTEIN.
THEY CHANGED THE WORLD WHEN THEY
GOT TOGETHER AND WROTE THE
BIBLE, AND WHEN I'M THE
GOVERNMENT, WE GOING TO SEE.
>> MITCH McCONNELL AND HERSCHEL
WALKER, EVERYBODY.
>> BRITISH OFFICIALS HAVE
UNVEILED KING CHARLES III'S NEW
ROYAL MONOGRAM.
THE C STANDS FOR CHARLES, THE R
IS FOR REX, AND THE THREE IS HOW
MANY HUNDREDS OF YARDS BRINS
ANDREW HAS TO STAY FROM SCHOOLS.
>> WHILE PERFORMING IN
WASHINGTON, LIZZO PLAYED A
CRYSTAL FLUTE ON STAGE THAT WAS
ONCE OWNED BY JAMES MADISON.
SO WE HAVE HAD A GAY PRESIDENT.
THE DEA IS WARNING THAT DRUG
CARTELS ARE USING RAINBOW
COLORED FENTANYL TO TARGET YOUNG
PEOPLE.
FOR CONCERNED PARENTS, HERE'S
WHAT RAINBOW FENTANYL LOOKS
LIKE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
INTRODUCED A NEW PLAN TO PUT
NUTRITION LABELS ON THE FRONT
INSTEAD OF THE BACK.
SO TO GIVE YOU AN IDEA OF THE
OVERALL HEALTH OF AMERICANS,
WE'RE TOO LAZY TO DO THIS --
>> THAT'S A LOT.
THAT'S A LOT.
>> IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT BY
2025, NEW YORK WILL INSTALL
CAMERAS IN EVERY SUBWAY CAR.
HUH, I THOUGHT IT WAS ILLEGAL TO
PUT CAMERAS IN BATHROOMS.
>> POLICE IN FLORIDA SAY THAT
MULTIPLE SHOTS WERE FIRED DURING
A FIGHT OUTSIDE A CHUCKY CHEESE,
BUT THERE WERE NO VICTIMS
LOCATED.
HMM, MAYBE CHECK THE PIZZA.
>> EUPHORIA STAR SYDNEY SWEENEY
RECEIVED BACKLASH WHEN INSTAGRAM
PHOTOS FROM A FAMILY EVENT
SUGGEST HER PARENTS MIGHT BE
TRUMP SUPPORTERS.
HERE TO COMMENT IS ONE OF OUR
CAST NEWEST MEMBERS, MICHAEL
LONGFELLOW.
>> HELLO.
THANK YOU.
HEY, COLIN.
>> HEY, MICHAEL.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK OF SYDNEY
SWEENEY GETTING ALL THIS
BACKLASH FOR HAVING CONSERVATIVE
PARENTS?
>> WELL, MY FAMILY IS FROM
ARIZONA, SO IF YOU CAN GET IN
TROUBLE FOR WHAT YOUR PARENTS
THINK, IT'S BEEN A GOOD RUN.
>> THEY'RE CONSERVATIVE?
>> WELL, MY DAD IS ANTI-COVID
VACCINE.
HE DOESN'T REALLY BELIEVE IN THE
VIRUS.
WHICH IS CRAZY BECAUSE EVERY
ANTIVAX ARTICLE HE SENDS ME
GIVES ME TEN OF THEM.
>> DO YOU READ THE ARTICLE?
>> I TRY, BUT THERE'S SO MUCH
CENSUS PORN ON THE SIDE.
>> YOU DON'T FEEL THE NEED TO
DISTANCE YOURSELF FROM YOUR DAD?
>> NO.
THEY COULD BE DEAD TOMORROW.
YOU SHOULDN'T CUT THEM OUT OF
YOUR LIVES.
SPEND TIME WITH THEM.
CALL THEM, GET IN THE WILL.
>> RIGHT.
BUT THE SYDNEY SWEENEY THING
WASN'T JUST ABOUT THE VACCINE.
IT WAS ALSO HER PARENTS WERE
TRUMP SUPPORTERS, RIGHT?
>> WELL, MY DAD DOESN'T HATE
THAT GUY.
HE'S NOT ONE OF THOSE ANTIVAX
ARIZONA LIBERALS YOU'RE ALWAYS
READING ABOUT.
YOU GOT TO STAND UP TO YOUR
PARENTS.
I SAT HIM DOWN, AND I TOLD HIM,
YOU KEEP GOING DOWN THIS PATH, I
MIGHT HAVE TO PAY FOR MY OWN CAR
INSURANCE NEXT YEAR.
THEN HE TOLD ME HOW MUCH IT WAS,
AND I SAID, WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT WHEN I SAID THAT.
I'M SORRY.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF
YOUR FAMILY?
>> DO YOU CONSIDER STEP MOMS
FAMILY?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO.
>> AH, SHOOT.
LISTEN.
FAMILY DYNAMICS ARE COMPLICATED.
YOU GET IT.
I IMAGINE A LOT OF PEOPLE IN
YOUR FAMILY ARE REPUBLICAN.
>> WELL, NOT REALLY.
>> NO, JUST YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WOULD SAY I'M MORE LIKE A BILL
MA ARE, R LIBERAL, YOU KNOW?
>> RIGHT.
A REPUBLICAN.
LISTEN.
JUST TO MAKE IT SUPER CLEAR, I'M
VERY LIBERAL.
I'M NOT A REPUBLICAN.
I MEAN, UNLESS I GET BOARDING
GROUP A AT THE AIRPORT, THEN
I'LL BE ONE FOR LIKE FOUR
MINUTES.
USUALLY I'M LIKE ANARCHY, CHAOS.
DON'T TOUCH ME, GET OFF MANY E.
THAT'S HOW RICH PEOPLE SAY GET
OFF ME.
YOU HAVE TO SAY IT LIKE ONE 1/2
TIMES.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF -- I SAID GET
YOUR HANDS OFF ME.
>> MIKE LONGFELLOW, EVERYBODY.
>> THANKS, COLIN.
>>> THE CIA IS MARKING ITS 75th
ANNIVERSARY BY LAUNCHING A
PODCAST, AND BECAUSE IT'S THE
CIA, THEY'RE LAUNCHING IT
DIRECTLY INTO AN AFGHANI
WEDDING.
>> NEW ITALIAN PRIME MINISTER
GEORGIA MELONI HAS BEEN ACCUSE
OFFED OF SPREADING WHITE
SUPREMACIST IDEAS, WHICH IS
CRAZY.
WE'RE NOW COUNTING ITALIANS AS
WHITE?
>> ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR NEW
VIDEO GAMES IS TROMBONE CHAMP,
WHICH IS A GUITAR HERO STALE
GAME FOR THE TROMBONE.
TROMBONE CHAMP IS ALSO THE
NICKNAME OF A VERY POPULAR LADY
IN MY NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> A NEW STUDY SAYS THE COMBINED
MASS OF EVERY ANT ON EARTH IS
GREATER THAN THE MASS OF EVERY
MAMMAL AND BIRD COMBINED, THANKS
MOSTLY TO THIS JUICY BITCH.
>> THIS SUMMER, AN INVASIVE
SPECIES, THE SPOTTED LANTERN FLY
HAS SPREAD THROUGHOUT THE
NORTHEAST DESTROYING LOCAL
VEGETATION.
EXPERTS ARE SO CONCERNED,
THEY'RE URGING PEOPLE TO KILL
THEM ON SIGHT.
IF YOU'VE SEEN ONE, YOU MIGHT
AGREE.
>> I'M A SPOTTED LANTERN FLY.
I DON'T CARE WHAT EXPERTS SAY,
I'M GOING TO EAT YOUR CROPS.
SCIENTISTS ARE WORRIED ABOUT MY
HIGHLY REPRODUCTIVE CAPACITY
BECAUSE I'M A PLAYER.
MY GOALS ARE TO LAY EGGS, BE ON
JUDGE JUDY, AND EAT EVERY CROP.
AND YOU CAN'T CHANGE MY MIND.
>> WELL, LET'S BRING HIM OUT.
A SPOTTED LANTERN FLY, EVERYONE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S RIGHT.
BOO ME, BOO ME.
Y'ALL DON'T EVEN KNOW ME.
BOO ME, HATERS.
Y'ALL HATERS CAN KISS MY ASS,
AKA MY SECRETION HOUSE.
>> YOU'RE COMING IN A LITTLE
AGGRESSIVE.
>> OH, I'M AGGRESSIVE.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S DOING THE
AGGRESSIVE MICHAEL CHE?
PEOPLE ARE TELLING THEIR
CHILDREN TO STOMP ME TO DO.
WHAT IS THIS MONSTER GERMANY?
>> I THINK YOU MEAN NAZI
GERMANY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I'M A BUG.
I'M TRYING TO LIVE MY LIFE, FIND
A MATE, AND HAVE 3 TO 4,000
BABIES.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF BABIES.
>> HEY, THEY HATING, I'M MATING.
WHO WOULD WANT TO SIT ON THIS.
LOOK AT THAT UNDERWING.
YEAH.
THIS WHAT Y'ALL LOOK LIKE TRYING
TO STOMP ME.
KEEP STOMPING.
I EVEN LOOK GORGEOUS DEAD,
BITCH.
>> RELAX.
WHAT DO YOU SAY OF THE PEOPLE
ACCUSING YOU OF BEING AN
INVASIVE SPECIES?
>> INVASIVE, MY FAMILY HAS BEEN
IN THIS COUNTRY FOR GENERATIONS.
>> HOW LONG IS THAT?
>> ABOUT FOUR MONTHS.
>> OOUF ALSO BEEN THREATENING
THE LOCAL VEGETATION.
>> HOW?
BECAUSE I JUMP ON A LOCAL TREE
AND STICK MY MOUTH ON IT AND
SUCK THE SAP OUT UNTIL IT'S
DEAD.
Y'ALL GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT?
OH, I'M HERE NOW, CATCH ME
OUTSIDE, SUCKING ALL YOUR TREES
TO DEATH.
>> PEOPLE RELY ON THE CROPS
YOU'RE DESTROYING.
>> I DON'T CARE.
CROPS NOWS WHAT THEY DID.
IF I SEE CROPS, I'M SUCKING THEM
ON SITE.
>> WELL, LANTERN FLY, WE GOT A
LITTLE SURPRISE FOR YOU.
CROPS IS ACTUALLY HERE TONIGHT.
>> OH, HELL NO!
>> LET'S BRING CROPS OUT.
>> DON'T SUCK ME TO DEATH!
TRY!
YOU CAN'T EVEN FLY!
>> I CAN.
>> YOU DOING A LOT OF TALKING,
BUT YOU AIN'T DOING A LOT OF
SUCKING.
>> KEEP STOMPING, BITCH, KEEP
STOMPING.
>> I'M
>>> WOW, IT'S SO GREAT
McDONALD'S IS GETTING THE GANG
BACK TOGETHER FOR A NEW AD
CAMPAIGN.
>> OH, TOTALLY.
THIS IS GONNA BE SO FUN.
HEY, HAS ANYONE SEEN GRIMACE?
>> NO, BUT IF I KNOW HIM, HE'S
SCARFING DOWN A COUPLE PREGAME
BURGERS.
>> HEY, PROBABLY MORE THAN A
COUPLE, HUH?
>> HI, EVERYONE.
>> WHAT THE --
>> HEY, FELLAS, HOW ARE WE?
>> GRIMACE?
OH, MY GOD.
DID YOU --
>> LOSE 300 POUNDS THIS SUMMER?
YEAH.
>> MAN, YOU LOOK INCREDIBLE.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT --
>> LOST 300 POUNDS AND GOT
TOTALLY YOKED UP?
YEAH.
>> COOL.
SO THEN, HOW DID YOU --
>> DROP THREE HUNDO AND GET
STACKED TO THE HEAVENS?
WELL, I STARTED WALKING TO WORK,
DRANK A LOT OF WATER, AND -- OH,
I STOPPED EATING McDONALD'S FOR
EVERY MEAL.
>> WELL, I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
PAULA MUST BE THRILLED.
>> OH, WELL, YES, SHE'S HAPPY
FOR ME, BUT, UH, YEAH, WE GOT
DIVORCED.
>> NO!
YOU GUYS WERE SO SOLID!
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELL, I GOT THIS NEW BODY,
AND --
LOOK, I HATE TO SAY IT, FELLAS,
BUT I WAS SWERVING THIS SUMMER.
>> WAIT.
SWERVING?
>> WHAT IS "SWERVING"?
>> CHEATING CONSTANTLY ON MY
WIFE.
>> WELL, MAYBE WE SHOOT THAT
COMMERCIAL.
>> ABSOLUTELY, MAN, IT'S YOUR
WORLD.
IT'S BEEN A LONG SUMMER OF SELF
DISCOVERY, AND I WANT YOU TO
KNOW, IF YOU DO THE WORK AND DIG
REALLY DEEP, I PROMISE YOU
YOU'LL FIND SOME SURPRISES.
MYWAY, LET'S DO THIS, BROTHER.
I'M EXCITED.
>> OKAY.
GREAT.
EVERYONE READY?
>> YEAH!
>> AND ACTION.
>> I WANT A McDOUBLE.
>> I WANT TO STEAL YOUR
HAMBURGERS.
>> I WANT TO GET THE WHOLE WORLD
A HAPPY MEAL.
>> AND I -- WELL, I'M A BISEXUAL
MAN.
>> AND CUT.
CUT.
>> WOW.
FELT REALLY GOOD TO SAY THAT.
>> GRIMACE, YOU'RE BISEXUAL?
>> YEAH.
I LIKE BOTH.
THIS SUMMER, I REALIZED THAT.
I WAS GETTING OFF A PLANE, AND
WHEN I SAID BYE TO THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANTS, ONE OF THEM SHOOK MY
HAND AND KISSED IT, AND I
REALIZED, EHH, I LIKE BOTH.
>> OKAY.
CONGRATS, GRIMACE.
>> AND I WOULD LIKE TO SAY THAT
I'M BI IN THE COMMERCIAL.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO ME, AND
I DON'T REALLY EAT McDONALD'S
ANYMORE.
>> LET ME THINK ABOUT THAT.
>> HEY, IF YOU'RE HAPPY, WE'RE
HAPPY.
>> HAPPY, YEAH.
AM I HAPPY?
YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I AM HAPPY.
GUYS, I HAVE SOME PRETTY BIG
NEWS.
I'M BISEXUAL.
>> YEAH, YOU SAID THAT ALREADY.
>> WELL, IT'S JUST LIBERATING TO
LET GO OF A SECRET.
BUT I GUESS YOU GUYS WOULDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
>> WELL, I GOT A SECRET.
>> OH, MY GOD, MAYOR McCHEESE.
I FORGOT YOU WERE THERE.
YOU LITERALLY HAVEN'T SAID A
THING SINCE WE HAVE BEEN HERE.
>> WELL, THE THING IS I DIDN'T
ALWAYS HAVE A CHEESE BURGER FOR
A HEAD.
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG MAN, I WAS A
HUMAN PRINCE.
ONE DAY I WENT TO McDONALD'S.
OUTSIDE ON THE STREET WAS THE
UGLIEST WOMAN I'VE EVER SEEN.
SHE WAS BUMPY.
ASKING ME TO BUY HER A BURGER.
LONG STORY, I THREW A BUNCH OF
BRAND NEW BURGERS IN THE TRASH.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, SHE SPOOKED
ME, THAT'S WHY I GOT THIS CHEESE
BURGER HEAD.
ALSO, I'M BISEXUAL.
>> WE'RE BI TOO!
>> HOW ABOUT YOU, RONALD?
YOU BI?
>> SURE, I'M BI -- BUYING A
PELOTON SO I CAN START SWERVING
LIKE GRIMACE.
>> BADABABABA, I'M LONG BOTH.VI
>>> ONCE AGAIN, KENDRICK LAMAR.
♪ I COME FROM A GENERATION
OF HOME INVASIONS
AND I GOT DADDY ISSUES
THAT'S ON ME ♪
♪ EVERYTHING THEM FOUR WALLS
HAD TAUGHT ME
MADE HABITS BURY DEEP
THAT MAN KNEW A LOT ♪
♪ BUT NOT ENOUGH TO KEEP ME
PAST THEM STREETS
MY LIFE IS A PLOT
TWISTED FROM DIRECTIONS ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T SEE
DADDY ISSUES RUN ACROSS
MY HEAD TOLD ME
FUMBLE FOUL ♪
♪ I'M TEARY-EYED
WANNA THROW MY HANDS
I WON'T THINK OUT LOUD
A FOOLISH PRIDE ♪
♪ IF I LOSE AGAIN
WON'T GO IN THE HOUSE
I STAYED OUTSIDE
LAUGHIN' WITH MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ THEY DON'T KNOW MY LIFE
DADDY ISSUES MADE ME
LEARN LOSSES
I DON'T TAKE THOSE WELL ♪
♪ MAMA SAID
THAT BOY IS EXHAUSTED
HE SAID, GO
IF HE GIVE UP NOW ♪
♪ THAT'S GON COST HIM
LIFE'S A
YOU COULD BE A OR STEP
OUT THE MARGIN ♪
♪ I GOT UP QUICK
I'M CHARGIN' BASKETS
AND FALLING BACKWARDS
TRYNA KEEP BALANCE ♪
OH, THIS THE PART WHERE
MENTAL STABILITY MEETS TALENT
OH, THIS THE PART
HE BREAKS MY HUMILITY ♪
♪ JUST FOR PRACTICE
TACTICS WE LEARNED TOGETHER
SORE LOSERS FOREVER
DADDY ISSUES ♪
♪ EARLY MORNIN' WAKE UPS
PRACTICIN' ON DAY-OFFS
TOUGH LOVE BOTTLED UP
NO CHASER ♪
♪ NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASE ♪
♪ EARLY MORNIN' WAKE UPS
PRACTICIN' ON DAY-OFFS
TOUGH LOVE BOTTLED UP
NO CHASER ♪
♪ NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASER ♪
♪ I GOT DADDY ISSUES
THAT'S ON ME
LOOKIN' FOR, I LOVE YOU
RARELY EMPATHIZIN' ♪
♪ FOR MY RELIEF
A CHILD THAT GREW ACCUSTOMED
JUMPING UP WHEN
I SCRAPED MY KNEE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF I CRIED ABOUT IT
HE'D SURELY TELL ME
NOT TO BE WEAK
DADDY ISSUES ♪
♪ HID MY EMOTIONS
NEVER EXPRESSED MYSELF
MAN SHOULD NEVER
SHOW FEELINGS ♪
♪ BEING SENSITIVE
NEVER HELPED
HIS MAMA DIED
I ASKED HIM WHY HE GOIN' ♪
♪ BACK TO WORK SO SOON
HIS FIRST REPLY WAS
SON, THAT'S LIFE AND BILLS
GOT NO SILVER SPOON ♪
♪ DADDY ISSUES GO GET
YOUR MONEY, SON
PROTECT YOURSELF
TRUST NOBODY ♪
♪ ONLY YOUR MAMA'N'EM
THIS MADE RELATIONSHIPS
SEEM CLOUDY
NEVER ATTACHED TO NONE ♪
♪ SO IF YOU TOOK
SOME LIKINGS AROUND ME
I MIGHT REJECT THE LOVE
DADDY ISSUES ♪
♪ KEPT ME COMPETITIVE
THAT'S A FACT
I DON'T GIVE A WHAT'S
THE NARRATIVE, I AM THAT ♪
♪ WHEN KANYE GOT BACK
WITH DRAKE
I WAS SLIGHTLY CONFUSED
GUESS I'M NOT MATURE ♪
♪ AS I THINK
GOT SOME HEALIN' TO DO
EGOTISTIC ZERO-GIVEN
AND TO BE SPECIFIC ♪
♪ NEED ASSISTANCE
WITH THE WAY
I WAS BROUGHT UP
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR HEART
IS MADE OF STONE
AND YOUR MIND
IS MADE OF GOLD ♪
♪ AND YOUR TONGUE
IS MADE OF SWORD
BUT IT MAY WEAKEN
YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ MY HOMIES AIN'T GOT
NO DADDY
GROW UP OVERCOMPENSATIN'
LEARN 'BOUT BEIN' A MAN ♪
♪ AND DISGUISE IT
AS BEIN' GANGSTA
I LOVE MY FATHER
FOR TELLIN' ME TO ♪
♪ TAKE OFF THE GLOVES
'CAUSE EVERYTHING HE DIDN'T
WANT WAS EVERYTHING I WAS
AND TO MY PARTNERS THAT ♪
♪ FIGURED IT OUT
WITHOUT A FATHER
I SALUTE YOU
MAY YOUR BLESSINGS ♪
♪ BE NEUTRAL
TO YOUR TODDLERS
IT'S CRUCIAL
THEY CAN'T STOP US ♪
♪ IF WE SEE THE MISTAKES
'TIL THEN
LET'S GIVE THE WOMEN A BREAK
GROWN MEN ♪
♪ WITH DADDY ISSUES ♪
♪
♪ EARLY MORNIN' WAKE UPS
PRACTICIN' ON DAY-OFFS
TOUGH LOVE BOTTLED UP
NO CHASER ♪
♪ NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASER
NEAT, NO CHASER ♪
♪
>>> HELLO.
>> HELLO.
>> OOH!
♪ WE'RE MOVING
WE'RE MOVING
WE'RE MOVING ♪
>> WE'RE MOVING!
>> OH, WE'RE MOVING!
AND WELCOME TO "CARIBBEAN
QUEENS."
>> MY NAME IS TRINITY SUMMERS.
>> AND I AM DESIREE WINGO.
AND WE ARE COMING TO YOU LIVE --
>> AND HUNGOVER.
>> FROM GRAVER'S RESORT AND SPA,
WHERE THE PARTY NEVER STOPS, AND
>> WE MET ON A SPIRIT AIRLINES
FLIGHT ON THE WAY OVER.
YEAH, WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
HERE FOR A WEEK, BUT WE NEVER
#ИМЯ?
MONTHS.
WE'RE DOING A WHOLE LOT OF
LOVING.
>> IT'S OFF PEAK, WHICH MEANS
THERE'S NO SUN, BUT THERE'S ALSO
NO WOMEN YOUNGER THAN US.
>> YEAH, WE'RE BRAGGING.
>> YES, WE ARE.
>> NOW PLAY OUR SONG.
>> OUR THEME SONG IS OF COURSE
BY THE GREATEST MUSICIAN OF THE
LAST 200 YEARS, MR. BILLY OCEAN.
>> THE MAN SINGS SO GOOD, THEY
NAMED THE OCEAN AFTER HIM.
WHICH BRINGS US TO THE FIRST
SEGMENT OF EVERY SHOW, "GOOGLE
IF BILLY OCEAN IS STILL
MARRIED".
>> HE IS.
>> STILL?
>> THAT BITCH.
>> WELL, BLESS THEIR LOVE, AND
THAT MEANS I NEED A DRINK.
PLEASE WELCOME OUR FAVORITE
BARTENDER, LISA.
>> MY NAME IS LEAH, BUT THAT'S
OKAY.
>> WE LOVE HER.
>> WE'RE SO CLOSE.
>> WE'RE LIKE FAMILY.
>> WE DON'T EVEN TIP HER.
>> BUT YOU COULD.
>> NOW, OUR NEXT SEGMENT IS
WHAT WE GOT UP TO THIS WEEK.
>> WE WENT PA ARE, ASAILING,
SHORTS FELL OFF.
>> JET SKIING, SHORTS FELL OFF.
>> BREAKFAST BAR, YOU KNOW OUR
SHORTS FELL OFF.
>> WELL, OUR GUESTS TODAY AS
ALWAYS ARE SOME HUHKY GUYS WE
MET LAST NIGHT THAT WE'RE NOW
GOING TO SEE IN THE LIGHT OF
DAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SEE IF THE
SPARKS ARE STILL SPARKING.
COME ON OUT, GORDY AND BARACK.
>> HEY, LADIES, LOOKING GOOD.
>> YEAH, LOOKING WELL HP LIT,
BUT STILL GOOD.
>> OH, OKAY.
SO YOU REMEMBER US?
>> OH, YEAH, WE DO.
I JUST DON'T REMEMBER IF IT WAS
LIKE FUN OR LIKE UH-OH.
>> IT WAS BOTH.
SO WE WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT
YOU.
YOU SAID LAST NIGHT YOU WERE A
SPORTS AGENT?
>> I SELL CATHETERS.
>> WELL, HOOK A GIRL UP.
>> I'M TRYING TO REMEMBER WHAT
YOU SAID YOUR JOB WAS, LAWYER?
>> WHITE RAPPER.
>> OH, OKAY.
I LOVE WHITE RAP.
>> WELL, I DO RAP AND REGGAE
TOO.
I GO BY SWAGGY.
THAT'S WHITE SWAGGY.
♪ LIFE IS ONE BIG PARTY WHEN
YOU'RE STILL YOUNG ♪
>> I'M GOOD TO GO.
>> I'M POPPING, OKAY.
IT'S TIME FOR THE FINAL VIBE
CHECK.
>> LET'S SEE IF THOSE VIBES ARE
STILL VIBING.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> OKAY.
THIS IS NICE.
>> GET A LITTLE CLOSER TO ME.
TRINITY, MY GUY'S GOT A HARDY.
>> NO, NO, I DON'T.
>> LET ME JUST CHECK MINE.
OKAY.
HE'S GROWING, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S GETTING THERE.
>> MY BAD.
>> NO, BABY, IT'S A GOOD THING.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK WE BETTER WRAP THIS
SHOW UP BEFORE OUR SHORTS FALL
OFF.
>> OH, YEAH.
GET IT, LADIES.
YOU TWO ARE THE PROUDEST,
OLDEST, SKANKS I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> AND BILLY'S LITTLE BROTHER
FRANK OCEAN IS HERE.
>> GIVE IT TO US, FRANK.
>> I KEEP TELLING YOU, WE ARE
NOT RELATED.
>> JUST GET OVER HERE AND SING
US THE DAMN SONG.
♪ CARIBBEAN QUEENS, NOW WE
SHARING THE SAME EAM ♪DR
>>> THANK YOU TO KENDRICK LAMAR,
JOHN HAMM, SEAN WHITE.
TO MY FAMILY, KELLY, MY WIFE AND
MY FRIENDS, YOU KNOW WHO YOU
ARE.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU LAUREN, THE CAST AND
CREW, THE BAND, THIS IS A DREAM
COME TRUE TO ME, AND I'M JUST SO
APPRECIATE TIF.
SO THANK YOU ALL FOR SPENDING
THIS NIGHT WITH ME, AND EVERYONE
AT HOME, JUST PLEASE BE SAFE.