PENTAGON
>>> HELLO ONCE AGAIN.
NSA
AND THIS IS SPECIAL AGENT
FITZSIMMONS.
>> YOU TWO ARE A GREAT INTEREST
ABDUCTIONS
WILD
>> WE WERE JUST THREE GALS AT A
HOT SAUCE EXTO
AND NOW WE'RE VIP
AT THE PENTAGON.
>> I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SAY FOR THE RECORD,
PENTAGON HAS ALWAYS
BEEN MY FAVORITE SHAPE,
SO THIS
IS A REAL TREAT FOR ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, GOOD TO HEAR.
NOW, LET'S START WITH HOW YOU
WERE ALL BROUGHT INTO THE
SPACECRAFT.
>> WELL, WE HAD PULLED OVER ON
THE SIDE OF THE HIGHWAY JUST TO STRETCH OUR LEGS
AND SUDDENLY I
WAS ENVELOPED BY THIS WARM BLUE
LIGHT.
>> AND IT GENTLY LIFTED US ON TO
THE SHIP LIKE WE WAS FLOATING.
THEN WE MET ALIENS MADE OF PURE
ENERGY.
ALMOST LIKE ANGELS, SIR.
I ALMOST CRIED.
AND YOU, MS. RAFFERTY?
>> YEAH, SAME.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> NO, OBVIOUSLY NOT.
YEAH, I WASN'T SO MUCH GENTLY LIFTED
AS I WAS YANKED SKYWARD
BY SOME SORT OF CLAW MACHINE DEVICE,
AND MIND YOU, I'M
POPPING A SQUAT ON THE MEDIAN AT THE TIME
SO I SLIDE RIGHT OUT OF
MY SLACKS AND I'M BECOME
ROCKETED UP TO THE SHIP.
CUCKOO
I BARELY MANAGED TO PULL MY
WONDER WEAR BACK UP.
>> I'M SORRY, YOUR WONDER WEAR?
>> YEAH, I CALL THEM THAT
BECAUSE IF YOU SAW THEM, YOU'D
WONDER WHERE THEY'D BEEN.
ANYWAY, I GET DUMPED ON BOARD
THE BOTTOM OF THE SHIP,
AND I
SEE MY LITTLE PALS, THE LITTLE
GRAY ALIENS WITH THE BIG DUMB
EYES.
AND IT HITS ME, COLLEEN,
THIS MAY BE THE MOST STABLE
RELATIONSHIP YOU'VE EVER HAD.
>> THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
NOW, ONCE YOU WERE ON BOARD,
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELL, THE ALIENS SHOWED US,
LIKE, THE FIVE ELEMENTAL FORCES
THAT KNIT THE FABRIC OF REALITY
TOGETHER.
AND Y'ALL WILL NEVER BELIEVE THIS,
BUT THOSE PHI FORCES WERE
ARRANGE IN THE A PENTAGON.
>> LIKE, THERE IS A UNIVERSAL
LANGUAGE THAT BONDS THE UNIVERSE TOGETHER,
AND THE CLOSEST WORD
WE HAVE TO DESCRIBE IT IS LOVE.
>> AND YOU, MS. RAFFERTY?
>> YEAH, A LITTLE DIFFERENT DOWN
IN THIRD CLASS.
I GET ON BOARD AND THE GRAY ALIENS, GOD BLESS THEM,
THEY'RE
ALREADY STANDING IN LINE TO BAT
MY KNOCKERS AROUND,
I THINK,
WHAT THE HELL, PLAY THE HITS.
SO I START UNBUTTONING MY BLOUSE,
BUT I'M IN MY SKIF VIS,
WHICH ARE REAL LOOSE.
SO, MY ITSY AND BITSY ARE
FULL VIEW
NOT TO GET TOO GRAPHIC, BUT
PUBICALLY SPEAKING,
IT'S A
JUNGLE DOWN THERE.
I'VE GOT MORE HAIR POKING OUT THE SIDE
THAN A HIPSTER'S BEARD
STUFFED INTO AN N-95.
LOOK, I'M NOT PROUD OF IT, BUT,
HEY, WHY CLEAN THE HOUSE IF
NOBODY'S COMING OVER, RIGHT?
>> THANK YOU, MS. RAFFERTY FOR
THAT DETAILED ACCOUNT.
NOW, WHAT HAPPENED NEXT WITH THE
ENERGY BEINGS?
>> WELL, THE ALIENS SHOWED US
HOW AN INFINITE NUMBER OF REALITIES
CAN COEXIST AT ONCE.
>> YEAH, AND, LIKE, HOW THE
DIFFERENT REALITIES CONVERGING IN ONE SPOT
WHERE
FOREVER
KIND OF
WHAT WE WOULD CALL HEAVEN.
>> WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, NO.
SO, THESE TWO ARE HANGING WITH
DOCTOR STRANGE AND THE MULTIVERSE,
MEANWHILE, I'M STUCK
WITH THE MADNESS.
BACK IN ECONOMY, WORD IS OUT
ABOUT MY HARRY FODDER.
GRAYS
THESE ARE POINTING AT MY DOWN
THERE HAIR, AND THEY'RE LIKE --
ELBOWING EACH OTHER LIKE,
ARE
YOU GUYS SEEING THIS?
>> SO, THE GROUP'S REACTION WAS
ONE OF EXCITEMENT?
>> YEAH, LIKE WHEN A DOG -- LIKE
A DOG WHEN ITS OWNER COMES HOME
FROM WORK.
IT WAS BEDLAM, OKAY?
THEY'RE RUNNING AROUND,
THEY'RE
WAVING THEIR ARMS LIKE KERMIT THE FROG
MAKING WEIRD LITTLE
NOISES LIKE --
AND THEN ONE OF THESE LITTLE
BASTARDS RUNS UP AND --
I'M SORRY, CARLA, I GOT TO USE
YOU HERE.
PLUCKS ONE RIGHT OUT,
STARTS SHOWING IT OFF.
NOW, SUDDENLY MY CURLIES HAVE
BECOME THE MUST-HAVE ITEM OF THE SEASON,
AND THEY'RE FLYING OFF
THE SHELF.
THEY'RE GRABBING AND PLUCKING
AND GRABBING AND PLUCKING,
CLIMBING ALL OVER EACH OTHER
LIKE MY BUSH
IS THE LAST
LIFEBOAT ON THE "TITANIC."
>> AND WERE YOU UNSETTLED BY
THIS AT ALL?
>> NO.
HONESTLY THE ENTIRE TIME, ALL I
COULD THINK WAS,
DAMN, THAT
FORTUNE TELLER WAS DEAD ON.
DID YOU GUYS GET ANY OF THAT
PUBE STUFF?
>> NO, NO PUBE STUFF.
SORRY.
>> HEY, DON'T APOLOGIZE.
FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE I'M READY
FOR BIKINI SEASON.
>> WOW.
AGAIN, VERY DETAILED.
WELL, HOW WERE YOU RETURNED TO
EARTH?
>> THERE WAS ANOTHER SOFT LIGHT
THAT JUST WASHED OVER ME,
AND I
WAS INSTANTLY BACK TO WHERE I
WAS BEFORE.
>> OH, IT WAS LIKE WAKING UP
FROM AN AMAZING DREAM.
>> OKAY, SEE, NOW, THAT REALLY
RIPS MY NIPS.
BECAUSE I HAD TO CLIMB DOWN A GD
ROPE LADDER THAT WAS TOO SHORT, RIGHT
SO I DROPPED 20 FEET AND
LAND ASS UP
WITH MY DONG HOLE
AND WRONG HOLE OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF A FIELD.
>> AND WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
>> THE UMPIRE CALLED TIMEOUT
AND THE METS SECURITY STAFF TOOK ME
OUT OF THE STAND.
NOT THE MOST EMBARRASSING THING
I'VE DONE ON A JUMBOTRON.
>> WELL, THAT WAS A RIVETING TESTIMONY,
BUT THERE IS
SOMETHING YOU SHOULD ALL KNOW.
WE HAVE BEEN IN CONTACT WITH THE
BEINGS.
>> THEY HAVE OFFERED THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT ACCESS TO SOME OF THEIR TECHNOLOGY
IF ONE OF YOU
AGREES TO GO WITH THEM
PERMANENTLY.
>> WELL, I CAN READ THE ROOM.
IT'S ME, RIGHT?
SURE.
WHY NOT?
I ALWAYS KIND OF FELT LIKE AN
ALIEN ON THIS PLANET ANYWAY.
WELL, EARTH, I LOVE YOU.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME STAY A
WHILE.
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN --
NATASHA LYONNE!
THANK
MY NAME IS NATASHA LYONNE,
AND I ALSO WISH I WAS HARRY STYLES.
GOSH.
WILL YOU LOOK AT THIS?
I'M HOSTING THE SEASON FINALE OF
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
FOR A REAL NEW YORKER LIKE ME,
THAT'S BIG.
I HAVE A SHOW CALLED "RUSSIAN
DOLL".
THE SECOND SEASON OF "RUSSIAN
DOLL" JUST PREMIERED ON NETFLIX,
AND TWO THINGS YOU DEFINITELY
WANT TO BE ASSOCIATED WITH RIGHT NOW
ARE RUSSIA AND NETFLIX.
YOU KNOW, IT'S MY FIRST TIME
HOSTING AND I'M GENUINELY
HUMBLED TO BE HERE.
THE TRUTH IS, I FEEL A COSMIC
CONNECTION TO "SNL."
THE PEOPLE HERE ARE MY REAL-LIFE
CHOSEN FAMILY.
I HAVE BEEN COMING HERE SINCE I
WAS A TEENAGER.
I COCREATED "RUSSIAN DOLL" WITH
AMY POEHLER.
AND I HAVE GREAT FRIENDS --
FRED
HEY.
HEY, ARE YOU BUSY?
>> RIGHT NOW?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> I THOUGHT WE COULD DO OUR
NATASHA LYONNE IMPRESSIONS FOR
YOU.
>> WE DO GOOD IMPRESSIONS OF YOU
WHEN YOU'RE NOT AROUND.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
IPSO FACTO.
GOOD
>> HOW ARE YOU?
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A DYNAMITE SWEATER.
COCKAROACH.
BYE
>> FREDDY AND I DATED FOR SEVEN
YEARS.
WE'RE THE ONLY COUPLE WHO HAD A
SEX TAPE NOBODY WANTED TO BUY.
GOD, I LOVE THIS PLACE.
SNL COMBINES EVERYTHING I LIKE --
NEW YORK CITY, SHOW BUSINESS,
PEOPLE WHO HAVE DONE
THE SAME THING SINCE THE '70s,
AND DIFFERENT UNIONS FIGHTING.
YEAH, I LOVE IT.
I MEAN, I'M A NEW YORK CITY KID
AND A SHOWBIZ BABY.
WEIRD STORY, BUT WHILE I HAVE
YOU, LISTEN TO THIS.
SO, I'M BORN IN NEW YORK.
DOESN'T MATTER WHAT YEAR.
EARLY '80s PROBABLY.
EVERYTHING IS BROWN.
MOST AUTOMOBILES ARE LONG AND
BANANA COLORED.
MY PARENTS GET THIS BIG IDEA
THAT I HAVE A FUTURE IN SHOW BUSINESS,
SO I START
AUDITIONING.
A LOT OF CASTING MANAGERS ARE
LOOKING FOR A LITTLE ORPHAN ANNIE TYPE
WHO TALKS LIKE
DEDERAMON.
HERE'S A CLIP FROM ONE OF MY
EARLIEST ROLES.
>> HI.
>> HI, PEE WEE.
>> WE'VE GOT A NEW MEMBER.
- HER NAME IS --
>> HI.
>> YEAH.
I GOT TO SAY, MY BEST WORK TO
DATE.
SO, I DO SOME TV.
MY MOM AND MOVED TO THE UPPER
EAST SIDE.
SUDDENLY I'M IN THE MOVIES.
I WAS IN ALL THOSE '90s MOVIES,
AMERICAN PIE, "AMERICAN PIE
2."
AMERICAN
AND CULT FAVORITE "BUT I'M A
CHEERLEADER."
SO, THINGS ARE GOING GREAT AND
KNOCK KNOCK, WHO'S THERE?
MULTIPLE ARRESTS AND DRUG
ADDICTION.
OH, YEAH, I WENT TO HELL AND
BACK.
LIFE WAS ROUGH.
BUT JUST LIKE WHEN FABIO WAS ON
THAT ROLLER COASTER
AND THE BIRD FLEW INTO HIS FACE --
HEY, DO WE
HAVE A PHOTO OF THAT?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
JUST LIKE WHEN FABIO, WHEN THAT HAPPENED,
I BRUSHED MYSELF OFF
AND I GOT BACK ON THE RIDE.
AND NOW I'M HERE.
ALL RIGHT?
SURE, I'M CONFLATING EVENTS,
GLOSSING OVER ENTIRE DECADES,
BUT I'M HERE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I FOUND.
THERE'S ALWAYS HOPE IN THIS AND DESPAIR
AND THERE'S ALWAYS A
REASON TO GET BACK IN THE RING
AND FIGHT ANOTHER DAY.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW.
JAPANESE BREAKFAST IS HERE.
STICK AROUND AND WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
STUPID.
>> HI.
I'M JOANN.
AND FOR AS LONG AS I CAN
REMEMBER, I'VE BEEN A STUPID
PERSON.
>> I'M TIM, AND MY PARENTS ARE
BOTH STUPID.
I'M STUPID, AND MY GRANDSON IS
STUPID.
>> NEARLY 1 IN 5 U.S. ADULTS
LIVE WITH A MENTAL ILLNESS OR
LEARNING DISABILITY.
>> AND WE ARE NOT THAT.
BELIEVE ME.
THEY CHECKED.
>> I'M JUST PLAIN STUPID.
>> I ALWAYS KNEW I WAS
DIFFERENT.
THINGS THAT WERE OBVIOUS TO
EVERYONE ELSE WERE ALWAYS VERY
COMPLICATED FOR ME.
>> JOKES HAVE TO BE EXPLAINED.
MOVIES HAVE TO BE EXPLAINED.
FOODS HAVE TO BE EXPLAINED.
SLOWLY.
>> I DON'T NEED THIS THING.
I JUST THOUGHT IT SOUNDED COOL.
I GUESS THAT'S STUPID.
>> MOST PEOPLE, LIKE ME, GO
THEIR WHOLE LIVES WITHOUT EVER
KNOWING THEY'RE STUPID, BUT
WE'RE EVERYWHERE.
WE DRIVE YOUR BUSES.
WE RUN COMPANIES.
>> I WRITE LAWS.
>> AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
I DO.
>> I FOUND OUT I WAS STUPID
WALKING FULL SPEED INTO A GLASS
WINDOW.
A STAINED GLASS WINDOW.
>> SARCASM JUST SOUNDS LIKE LIES
TO ME.
>> BEING STUPID IS NOT A CHOICE.
>> IT'S NOT A CHOICE.
>> IT'S A CHOICE.
>> JUST BECAUSE YOU ARE A STUPID
PERSON DOESN'T MEAN YOU DON'T
HAVE A VOICE.
SO, GET OUT THERE.
>> GET OUT THERE.
>> AND VOTE.
>> LET YOUR VOICE BE HEARD.
>> VOTE.
>> I'M STUPID, AND I VOTED.
>> I VOTE.
AND I AM VERY STUPID.
>> WAIT.
THIS AIN'T MY GRANDSON.
>> MY STUPID VOTE COUNTS AS MUCH
AS ANYBODY ELSE.
>> AND SOMETIMES WAY MORE, LIKE
IN MY COUNTY.
>> SO DON'T LET THEM STOP YOU.
>> DON'T LET THEM CONFUSE YOU.
>> SOMEBODY WILL SAY SOMETHING,
AND THEN SOMEBODY WILL SAY
SOMETHING ELSE.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH.
>> YOU CAN VOTE.
YOU CAN BUY A GUN.
>> YOU CAN BUY ALL THE GUNS.
>> I WATCH ONE CHANNEL, AND I
GET SO MAD.
>> MY SON'S WIFE IS A SMART
PERSON.
SHE'S TEARING US APART.
>> VOTE.
>> GET OUT THERE.
>> VOTE EVERY DAY IF YOU HAVE
TO.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE THEY ASK IF
YOU'RE STUPID.
>> NOBODY SHOULD HAVE TO LEARN
THINGS THAT THEY DON'T WANT TO.
>> I VOTE FOR DONKEYS.
BUT SOMETIMES I LIKE ELEPHANTS.
>> I WANT A CANDIDATE THAT
SMILES AT ME.
>> THE COMPUTER SCREEN SAYS
PROVE YOU'RE NOT A ROBOT, SO I
CUT MYSELF.
>> SOMEBODY SAID -- AND I'M
LIKE, IS THAT REAL?
>> MY SCREEN TIME IS 14 HOURS A
DAY.
BUT THEY DON'T KNOW I HAVE
ANOTHER PHONE.
>> VOTE.
>> DANCE.
>> FOR A TALL MAN.
>> VOTE.
BECAUSE THEY GIVE YOU A STICKER
AND YOU CAN PUT IT ANYWHERE.
>> WAIT, THIS IS MY GRANDSON.
>>> NO SCORE AS WE HEAD INTO THE
BOTTOM OF THE THIRD,
YANKEES/WHITE SOX.
LYLE O'RILEY ALONGSIDE HALL OF
FAMER BIZ NEWSOM.
>> GORGEOUS DAY FOR A BALL GAME!
>> IT IS.
BEFORE WE GET BACK TO THE ACTION
ON THE FIELD, LET'S GO TO WALT
HALL FOR A WORD FROM OUR
SPONSORS.
WALT?
>> WNYX YANKEES COVERAGE IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY SMACKMAN'S
DEPARTMENT STORE.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT PLAIN
BROWN SUIT AND PLAIN BROWN HAT?
WELL, SMACKMAN'S OF COURSE.
BACK TO THE BALL GAME.
>> THANK YOU.
GLAD YOU MADE IT IN TODAY.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WERE FEELING A
LITTLE UNDER THE WEATHER THIS
MORNING?
>> OH, YEAH.
STUFFY HEAD, SORE THROAT, THE
WORKS.
LUCKILY, MY DOCTOR PRESCRIBED ME
THIS NEW COLD MEDICINE CALLED
METHAMPHETAMINE.
YEAH, IT JUST KNOCKS MY COLD
RIGHT OUT.
>> WELL, GLAD YOU'RE FEELING
BETTER.
>> I'M EXCITED.
I AM FEELING VERY CHATTY.
AND I FEEL LIKE I WANT TO TALK
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> OKAY.
SOUNDS LIKE THIS METHAMPHETAMINE
MEDICINE DID THE TRICK.
AND GENE WOODLING COMES TO THE
PLATE.
15 FOR 25 THIS SEASON AGAINST
LEFTY PITCHERS.
>> NOT BAD FOR AN ALCOHOLIC.
>> DON'T SAY, THAT BIZ.
>> HEY, YOU SEE -- 22 YEARS OLD,
THE PUSH ON THAT WOMAN.
I AM LIKE A SOLDIER'S HAIRCUT,
HIGH AND TIGHT.
>> LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT ANOTHER
MAN'S WIFE LIKE THAT.
HERE'S THE PITCH.
>> IT'S OUT OF HERE!
>> EXCEPT IT'S NOT.
POP FLY DIRECTLY OVER HOME
PLATE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TAKE ANOTHER COLD PILL
SO I DON'T GET STUFFY.
>> OKAY, SOUNDS GOOD, BIZ.
JOLTIN' JOE DiMAGGIO IS HEADED
TO THE PLATE.
OR SHOULD I SAY, MR. MARILYN
MONROE?
>> HOW THE HELD DID JOE
DiMAGGIO, THE UGLIEST SON OF A
BITCH IN BASEBALL SNAG THAT
BROAD?
>> WATCH THE LANGUAGE, BIZ.
>> YOU KNOW HE'S ITALIAN, RIGHT?
ITALIANS AREN'T EVEN WHITE.
>> DO NOT SAY THAT.
LINE DRIVE AT THIRD.
>> AND IT'S OUT OF HERE!
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
IT IS NOT.
BUT DI MAGGIO EASILY MAKES IT TO
FIRST.
>> OH, YEAH.
QUESTION -- HOW MUCH MONEY WOULD
YOU PAY TO SNIFF MARILYN
MONROE'S BED SHEETS?
>> OKAY, I'M NOT GOING TO
ANSWER, THAT BECAUSE THAT IS
INAPPROPRIATE.
>> OH, NO, IT'S NOT.
INAPPROPRIATE WOULD BE LIKE, HOW
DO YOU FIT FOUR HOOKERS ONTO A
CHAIR?
TURN IT UPSIDE-DOWN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
NO, BIZ.
HOW ABOUT A SPONSOR I.D.?
WALT?
>> TODAY'S COVERAGE IS BROUGHT
TO YOU BY MITCHUM, THE
BUSINESSMAN'S SCOTCH.
>> THANK YOU, WALT.
ONE OUT, RUNNER ON FIRST.
ROOKIE MICKEY MANTLE COMING TO
THE PLATE.
A LOT OF FOLKS SAY THIS KID'S
POWER ARE REMINDS THEM ABOUT A
YOUNG BABE RUTH.
>> YOU HEARD THE STORY ABOUT
BABE RUTH IN CLEVELAND, RIGHT?
HELLO.
OF COURSE.
WELL, TOLD ME NOT TO TELL THE
STORY ABOUT BABE RUTH.
IT'S A REAL SHAME, BECAUSE
IT'S --
>> MAYBE LAY OFF THAT COLD
MEDICINE.
MAN MANTLE SQUARING UP AT THE
PLATE.
>> WHAT THE HELL.
WE'RE IN CLEVELAND.
IT'S MIDNIGHT AFTER THE GAME.
BABE IS DRUNK AS A SKUNK,
LOOKING FOR WHAT ELSE?
>> PLEASE STOP.
WINDS UP.
>> BABE SEES A KID, ABOUT 10
YEARS OLD, AND BABE HIT HIM.
>> NO, HE DID NOT.
>> BABE RUTH WAS SO HUNGRY --
>> NO.
>> -- THAT HE EIGHT A CHILD --
>> NO, HE DIDN'T.
>> HE DID.
CLOTHES AND ALL.
>> BABE RUTH WAS FAMOUSLY KIND
TO CHILDREN.
3-0'S IS COUNT.
>> WELL, HE ATE ONE.
IF YOU'RE LISTENING TO THIS AND
YOU'RE IN YOUR CAR AND STUCK IN
TRAFFIC, I HAVE AN IDEA.
JUST GUN IT.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
>> SLAM THE GAS AND SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> NO.
HE'S JOKING.
DON'T DO THAT.
>> I'M NOT!
>> BALL FOUR.
BASES LOADED.
>> I HAVE SOME OBSERVATIONS ON
DIFFERENT RACES J NO, NO, NO.
LET'S HEAR FROM OUR SPONSOR.
>> I KIND OF WANT TO HEAR THIS.
* **
AND I SAID I'LL SEE YOU AT
WORK *
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, KINGSTON RESIDENCE
INN.
ONCE AGAIN, WE ARE THE
TREECE HENDERSON TRIO.
SO GLAD YOU JOINED OUR BIG
KICKOFF TO SUMMER CELEBRATION.
WE GOT A HOT SHOW TO GET BACK
TO, BUT BEFORE WE DO, MY
ALLERGIES ARE EXPLODING.
CAN I ASK IF ANYONE HAS NASONEX?
IT WOULD REALLY GET ME THROUGH
THIS EXPERIENCE.
I'LL PUT A CONDOM ON THE
NASAL -- CAN I GET THAT SQUIRT?
AM I SPEAKING CLEARLY?
I HAVE ASKED FOR NASONEX AT
LEAST 11 TIMES.
NO?
>> NOBODY HAS IT, TREECE.
>> OKAY, FINE.
* TWEEDLE DEE ROLL
TWEEDLE DEE BUN
SOON WE'LL EACH HAVE
BURGERS IN THE SUMMER SUN *
**
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MEET THE BAND.
ON KEYBOARD, IT'S BRAD DATES.
AND HIS LAST NAME IS DATES, BUT
HE HASN'T HAD ONE IN SIX YEARS.
>> I'VE BEEN MARRIED FOR TEN,
TREECE.
>> HEY, THIS IS JUST SHOW
PATTER.
I DON'T KNOW.
ALSO HERE TONIGHT, IT'S HELEN.
>> I'M HELEN.
I DON'T PLAY AN INSTRUMENT.
I'M JUST HERE TO DANCE.
>> WELL, WE LOVE HELEN HELPING
OUT THE BAND.
AND FINALLY, ON HARMONICA, IT'S
MY ROOMMATE AND LANDLORD, CASSIE
MARIE.
>> WATCH ME BLOW THIS.
**
>> YEAH!
CASSIE, YES!
>> THAT WAS FIRE, CASSIE MARIE.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE PHONING
IT IN TONIGHT CONSIDERING THE
STATE I FOUND YOU IN THIS
MORNING.
>> OH, NO.
THAT'S BETWEEN US, TREECE.
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING IS FINE.
>> WELL, YOU WERE CRYING PRETTY
HARD IN THE CAR.
>> OKAY, TREECE, I DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT THAT HERE.
MY TEARS ARE MY BUSINESS.
>> YEAH, BOUNDARIES, TREECE.
>> BUT I CARE ABOUT HER
EMOTIONAL STATE.
>> TREECE, ZIP IT.
>> OKAY, FINE!
**
S.
SUMMER *
* PUT ON A SPREAD AND SAUCE UP
YOUR SUMMER SASS *
**
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOW IS EVERYBODY DOING TONIGHT?
HOW ABOUT YOU, LOVELY COUPLE?
>> OH, WE'RE NOT A COUPLE.
I'M GAY AND SHE'S MY PSYCHIC.
>> WHOA!
>> YEAH, AND THE SPIRIT WORLD IS
TELLING ME THAT YOUR
HARMONICA PLAYER IS HIDING
SOMETHING FROM YOU.
>> I KNEW IT.
SPILL THE BEANS, CASSIE MARIE.
>> OH, HO!
THERE IS NOTHING TO SPILL, AND
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS
PSYCHICS.
>> IT'S SOMEONE WITH AN "R"
NAME.
>> WHAT?
SO THERE'S A "R" IN YOUR LIFE?
IS IT R. KELLY?
STEER CLEAR.
>> THERE'S NO R. KELLY.
>> THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
* TWEEDLE DEE HOT
NO KIDS IN SCHOOL *
* I WANT TO MAKE FRIENDS WITH
SOMEBODY WHO HAS A POOL *
**
>> TREECE, I'M SORRY TO
INTERRUPT, BUT CASSIE IS ABOUT
TO RECEIVE A NEST CAM ALERT.
>> WHAT?
PULL OUT YOUR PHONE.
>> TREECE, YOU'RE KILLING THE
VIBE.
>> JUST DO IT.
IT'S YOUR NEST CAM.
THERE'S SOMEONE IN YOUR FRONT
YARD.
SHE WAS RIGHT AGAIN.
>> YOU TWO!
GET OUT OF HERE WITH YOUR DEVIL
BUSINESS!
>> OH, NO, I PAID $4 FOR BOTH OF
THESE SEATS.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE, HONEY.
>> WHO IS THAT IN YOUR YARD?
HE'S WEARING A T-SHIRT THAT SAYS
RONALD.
>> THAT'S AN "R" NAME!
>> YES, IT'S MY EX, RONALD.
>> WELL, THAT EXPLAINS THE TEE.
WAIT, WHAT'S HE DOING NOW?
>> HE'S IN THE CLOSET BEDROOM.
>> WHAT?
BUT THAT'S MY CLOSET BEDROOM.
THAT'S WHERE I PUT MY
FASHIONWARE.
>> HE MUST THINK THEY'RE MINE.
HE'S GOING TO BURN THEM TO GET
ME BACK FOR DUMPING HIM.
>> OH, NO, HE HAS MY BOTTEGA
VENETA FANNY PACK.
YOU CAN'T BURN THAT!
THAT'S MY BOTTEGA VENETA.
>> BUT IT'S A KNOCKOFF, TREECE.
>> OH, YOU SHUT UP!
>> TREECE, THEY'RE JUST CLOTHES.
>> YOU'RE JUST CLOTHES.
AND HER EX-BOYFRIEND IS ABOUT TO
ANGELA BASSETT MY BOTTEGA VENETA
AND SET IT ON FIRE AND WALK AWAY
AND SNAP.
NOW, CALL HIM AND TELL HIM TO
STOP.
>> OKAY, JUST FOR YOU, TREECE.
HELLO, RONALD.
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ME?
NO, YOU'RE GARBAGE!
I DON'T CARE.
BURN EVERY PIECE OF CLOTHING IN
THAT ROOM IF YOU WANT!
>> NO!
THAT WAS NOT THE PLAN.
>> I'M SORRY, TREECE.
I'LL BUY YOU ALL NEW STUFF
TOMORROW.
>> YOU CAN'T.
YOU'RE POORER THAN ME.
* TWEEDLEDEE HOT *
* I'M CUTTING YOU OFF OF ALL OF
MY SONGS *
>> NO!
>> YES!
**
>>> WELL, ALL GOOD THINGS MUST
COME TO AN END, INCLUDING THIS
PROM.
BUT WE'VE GOT A COUPLE SONGS
LEFT.
SO LET'S MAKE THEM COUNT.
CLASS OF 2002, HOW Y'ALL
FEELING?
**
>> HARD TO BELIEVE IT'S BEEN
20 YEARS SINCE THAT NIGHT.
AFTER GRADUATION, WE ALL WENT
OUR SEPARATE WAYS, BUT I STILL
LIKE TO THINK ABOUT MY OLD
FRIENDS AND SMILE.
SHELLY HINES GRADUATED FIRST IN
OUR CLASS, THEN WENT TO HARVARD,
WHERE SHE GRADUATED DEAD LAST.
I GUESS OUR HIGH SCHOOL JUST
WASN'T THAT GOOD.
TESSA WHITE GOT MARRIED AND HAD
TWO BEAUTIFUL DAUGHTERS.
AND ONE FAT UGLY SON.
AS FOR RACHEL FINSTER, WELL, THE
LESS SAID ABOUT HER THE BETTER.
DANA MIGUEL MADE GOOD ON HER
PROMISE TO HIKE THE APPALACHIAN
TRAIL.
SHE REMAINS MISSING TO THIS DAY.
TRENA DASH PLAYED D-1 SOCCER IN
COLLEGE AND WON A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
SHE SHOULD HAVE BEEN HAPPY, BUT
SHE NEVER GOT OVER RACHEL
FINSTER SLEEPING WITH HER DAD.
DARIUS CALDWELL EVENTUALLY MADE
IT TO THE PROS --
PROFESSIONAL PORNOGRAPHY.
HE'S WORKED WITH ALL THE GREATS,
EVEN RACHEL FINSTER.
>> AS FOR CARLY HILL, SHE MOVED
TO WEST VIRGINIA AFTER HIGH
SCHOOL AND MARRY A MINER, A COAL
MINER WHO WAS 16 YEARS OLD.
BILLY MANDEL FOLLOWED HIS
DREAMS.
UNFORTUNATELY, HE ONLY DREAMED
ABOUT KILLING HIS GRANDPARENTS.
DOUGIE FINNEGAN NEVER STOPPED
INVENTING THINGS, AND EVENTUALLY
ONE OF THOSE INVENTIONS MADE HIM
RICH.
FENTANYL.
MAYBE YOU HEARD OF IT?
RACHEL FINSTER SURE HAS.
CLASS SWEETHEARTS BECCA AND
ROBBIE MADE A VOW TO LOSE THEIR
VIRGINITY THAT NIGHT.
AND THEY BOTH DID.
TO THE DEEJAY.
SOME PEOPLE HAD HAPPIER STORIES,
LIKE NATALIE TURNER, WHO WAS
GRANTED THE FIRST GAY MARRIAGE
LICENSE IN THE STATE.
WE ALL WENT TO THE WEDDING, EVEN
RACHEL FINSTER, WHO WAS THERE
PROTESTING WITH HER HATEFUL
CHURCH.
SEVEN YEARS LATER, JEFF AHMED
REACHED OUT TO RACHEL TO TRY TO
TALK SENSE AND HER, AND IT
WORKED.
THEY STARTED DATING AND MOVED IN
TOGETHER.
HIS BODY WAS NEVER FOUND.
SOME OF OUR FRIENDS SURPRISED
US.
CARLA ANDRETTI FOLLOWED HER
MOTHER'S FOOTSTEPS ALL THE WAY
TO THE CAPITOL BUILDING, ON
JANUARY 6th.
HOW CAN WE FORGET AMY FULTON?
I'M NOT SURE HOW, BUT WE ALL
DID.
JUST COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT HER
LIKE SHE DIDN'T EXIST.
THEN THERE'S PETER LIU, WHO LEFT
A HUGE MARK ON BROADWAY AFTER HE
THREW HIMSELF OFF THE ROOF
OF THE WINTER GARDEN THEATER
PROTESTING.
HERSCHEL WILLIAMS, HE BECAME A
WRITER.
HIS FIRST BROOK, "FRIEND OF THE
DEVIL, GROWING UP WITH THE
RACHEL FINSTER," WAS A BEST
SELLER.
TIME TOOK US ALL IN DIFFERENT
DIRECTIONS.
FOR A BRIEF MOMENT, WE WERE
ALL THERE TOGETHER DANCING THE
NIGHT AWAY WITH OUR WHOLE LIVES
AHEAD OF US.
EXCEPT FOR ME.
I WAS MURDERED BY RACHEL
FINSTER, AND MY SOUL CANNOT
CROSS OVER UNTIL SHE IS BROUGHT
TO JUSTICE.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
JAPANESE BREAKFAST.
**
* TELL THE MEN I'M COMING
TELL THEM COUNT THE DAYS *
* I CAN FEEL THE NIGHT
PASSING BY LIKE A MISTAKE
WAITING FOR ME *
* CAUGHT UP IN MY FEELINGS *
* OVERTHINK THE TRUTH *
* FANTASIZE YOU'VE LEFT ME
BEHIND AND I'M TURNED BACK
RUNNING FOR YOU *
* MAKE IT UP TO ME
YOU KNOW IT'S BETTER *
* BE SWEET TO ME BABY
I WANNA BELIEVE IN YOU *
* I WANNA BELIEVE
* BE SWEET TO ME BABY
I WANNA BELIEVE IN YOU
I WANNA BELIEVE IN SOMETHING *
**
* SO COME AND GET YOUR WOMAN *
* COME AND GET YOUR WOMAN *
* PACIFY HER RAGE *
* TAKE THE TIME TO UNDO YOUR
LIES MAKE IT UP ONCE MORE WITH
FEELING *
* RECOGNIZE YOUR MISTAKES *
* AND I'LL LET YOU BACK IN *
* REALIZE NOT TOO LATE *
* LIKE YOU ALWAYS *
* MAKE IT UP TO ME
YOU KNOW IT'S BETTER *
* BE SWEET TO ME BABY
I WANNA BELIEVE IN YOU *
* I WANNA BELIEVE *
* BE SWEET TO ME BABY
I WANNA BELIEVE IN YOU *
* I WANNA BELIEVE
IN SOMETHING *
* BE SWEET TO ME BABY
* I WANNA BELIEVE IN YOU
I WANNA BELIEVE *
**
>> It's "Weekend Update" with
Colin Jost and Michael Che.
Good evening, everyone.
>> Welcome to "Weekend Update."
I'm Michael Che.
>> I'm Colin Jost.
COVID
HORNIEST
MONKEY
THINGS GONE
STOCK
WAR
THIS IS US
CROCK
FUTURE BLEAK
CRAZY
CHILD
I JUST DID
BABY FORMULA
TUCKER
BRAGGING
PUSHED THEORIES
REPLACE WHITE PEOPLE WITH MINORITIES.
EXIST
TURN
UNLESS IT'S HALLOWEEN.
TUCKER CARLSON'S GOT A LOT OF
NERVE PUSHING THESE WILD CONSPIRACY THEORIES,
BECAUSE IF
HE THINKS THE GOVERNMENT HAS A
SECRET PLOT TO HELP THE MINORITIES
HE MUST BE SMOKING
THAT CRACK THEY SECRETLY PUT IN
NEIGHBORHOODS.
LIZ CHENEY
ATTACK HOUSE GOP LEADERSHIP
ENABLED WHITE SUPREMACY AND ANTISEMIT
REJECTED THE ATTACKS
CALLING THEM CHEAPER
THAN A BLACK RABBI.
>> DOUG MASTRIANO,
WHOSE FACE APPEARS TO BE PHOTOSHOPPED ON TO
A HOT DOG
WON THE PENNSYLVANIA
REPUBLICAN PRIMARY FOR GOVERNOR
AND SAID IF HE'S ELECTED HE'D BE
SO FAR TO THE RIGHT HE'D MAKE
DeSANTIS LOOK LIKE A CENTRIST.
SANTIS
SCHOOL MUSICAL
>> ELON MUSK DEFENDED HIMSELF
FROM ALLEGATIONS
THAT HE
REPORTEDLY EXPOSED HIMSELF TO A
FLIGHT ATTENDANT ON HIS PRIVATE JET,
SAYING, QUOTE,
IF I WERE
INCLINED TO ENGAGE IN SEXUAL
HARASSMENT,
THIS IS UNLIKELY TO
BE THE FIRST TIME IN MY ENTIRE
30-YEAR CAREER THAT IT COMES TO
LIGHT.
OOH, SORRY, WE WERE LOOKING FOR
A SIMPLE "DID NOT DO IT".
THE ANSWER WAS, DID NOT DO IT.
>>> REPUBLICANS IN GEORGIA ARE CONCERNED
DOMINIC THIEM ENDORSED
CANDIDATES IN THE PRIMARIES WHO
ARE NOT QUALIFIED.
FOR INSTANCE, HIS PICK FOR
ATTORNEY GENERAL IS LITERALLY
'90s ACTION STAR STEVEN SEGAL.
NOW, THAT'S NOT TRUE,
BUT WHAT DOES IT SAY ABOUT TRUMP THAT YOU
DIDN'T DOUBT IT FOR A SECOND?
>> RICH PARENTS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY ARE REPORTEDLY STOCKING
UP ON BLACK MARKET BABY FORMULA,
WHICH I ASSUME IS FORMULA THAT
WAS SUPPOSED TO GO TO BLACK
MARKETS.
>> TAYLOR SWIFT GAVE A
COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS AT NYU'S
GRADUATION CEREMONY THIS WEEK,
BECAUSE COLLEGE IS A LOT LIKE
BREAKING ONE TAYLOR SWIFT.
YOU'RE STILL GOING TO BE PAYING
FOR IT DECADES LATER.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
WRITING A BOOK,
IT WILL CONTAIN
8,000 COMMAS AND NO PERIODS.
PLANNING TO TRAVEL ABROAD.
HERE WITH HIS TIP FOR
INTERNATIONAL ROMANTIC GO
AHEADAWAYS IS A GUY WHO JUST
BOUGHT A BOAT.
>> MWAH!
GUESS WHO'S GOT TWO TICKETS TO
BUMPING THIGHS?
YES!
>> I'M ALREADY REGRETTING THIS.
BUT LET'S HERE SOME OF YOUR
TRAVEL TIPS.
>> YOU GOT IT.
LET'S TALK BEST PLACE TO GET THE
BEST LAYS ON VACAY.
HEAD DOWN TO THE FRENCH RIVIERA
TO SEE CANS.
SOON SHE'LL WANT YOU TO BE LIKE
NAPOLEON AND BONE HER PART.
I HAVE A SMALL PENIS.
DON'T JUST SAY IN FRANCE, AS
MANY WOMEN TOLD YOU, YOU'VE GOT
TO MOVE AROUND DOWN THERE.
EURO TRAIL IS YOUR TICKET TO
EURO TAIL.
MAYBE TRY BERLIN TO REEL HER IN.
YOU'LL BE IN HER BLACK FOREST
AND SHE'LL BE MOANING AND YOUR
EAR, THIS IS THE WORST THING TO
HAPPEN IN GERMANY.
>> COME ON, MAN.
>> OH, YEAH.
COME ON, I SHALL.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE A UGLO
AMERICANO, GRAB A GUIDE BOOK.
RICK STEVES LEADS TO SLICK
BEAVIS.
AND THERE'S NOTHING SCARIER THAN
A LANGUAGE BEARER.
A LITTLE DUO LINGO AND YOU'LL
ANDB DOING LINGUS.
>> YOUR HAM IS TINY?
>> SI.
SPEAKING OF SMALL SERVINGS, HEAD
TO BARCELONA FROM THE AMALFI
COAST.
TO GET YOUR BOLOGNA INTO SOME --
DON'T FORGET ABOUT HER NAPLES IF
YOU WANT HER TO GOBBLE GOO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
PEOPLE ARE LIKE VISIBLY SICK.
WHY WOULD ANY WOMAN WANT TO BE
WITH YOU?
>> I HAVE TO ADMIT, I HAVE
DRIVEN MANY A LADY TO THE ISLE
OF LESBOS
IN MY BOAT.
>> GUY WHO JUST BOUGHT A BOAT,
>>> PARAMOUNT PLUS ANNOUNCED
THEY ARE MAKING A NEW
YELLOWSTONE PRE-QUEL SERIES WITH
HARRISON FORD AND HELEN MIRIN.
>>> THE NEWEST STATE WITH THE
HIGHEST OBESITY IN THE COUNTRY
IS MIKE "THE SITUATION"
SORRENTINO.
IT'S GOTTEN SO BAD, DOCTORS HAD
TO REMOVE ITS FOOT.
>>> AN ATTENDANT ON A FRONTIER
AIRLINES FLIGHT HELPED DELIVER A
BABY, BECAUSE ON FRONTIER IT'S
NOT WORTH ASKING IF ANYONE'S A
DOCTOR.
>>> QUEEN ELIZABETH MADE A
SURPRISE PUBLIC APPEARANCE THIS
WEEK AT THE OPENING OF A NEW
TRAIN LINE IN LONDON AFTER
PRINCE CHARLES TIED HER TO THE
TRACKS.
IT'S NOT REAL.
>>> A PAINTING BY PABLO PICASSO
PORTRAYING HIS LOVER AS A SEA
CREATURE WAS SOLD AT AUCTION FOR
$67 MILLION.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL ABSTRACT
EXPRESSION OF HIS LOVE AND
ADMIRATION THAT HE NAMED "TITTY
SQUID."
>> THERE ARE A GROWING NUMBER OF
NUNS JOINING TIKTOK TO SHOW WHAT
LIFE IN A CONVENT IS REALLY
LIKE.
BECAUSE WHEN THE CATHOLIC CHURCH
TRIES TO CONNECT WITH YOUNG
PEOPLE, IT ALWAYS GOES WELL.
>>> THIS WILL GET YOU BACK.
A SCHOOL DISTRICT IN FLORIDA IS
INVESTIGATING A PICTURE POSTED
ONLINE OF STUDENTS SPELLING OUT
THE "N" WORD.
IT'S A SHOCKING INSTANCE OF
FLORIDA STUDENTS BEING ABLE TO
SPELL.
>>> WELL, IT'S ALMOST SUMMER AND
AS THE WEATHER CHANGES, SO DO
STYLES AND TRENDS.
HERE TO COMMENT ON WHAT'S IN FOR
SUMMER ARE TWO TREND
FORECASTERS.
WELL, THANKS FOR COMING BACK.
I CAN SEE YOU'RE READY FOR THE
WARM WEATHER.
>> YES.
WE HAD A MEETING THIS MORNING
WITH THE SUN.
>> WE TYPED WHAT IT TOLD US INTO
A BIG, THROBBING COMPUTER.
HERE IS --
>> THE REPORT.
>> OUR FIRST CATEGORY IS SUMMER
FRUIT TRENDS.
>> IN, GRAPES WITH SEEDS.
>> IN, TYING CHERRY STEM WITH
TONGUE TO IMPRESS FOR SEX.
>> IN, "WATERMELON SUGAR" SONG.
>> AND OUT --
>> NAVEL ORANGE!
>> NAVEL ORANGE, EW.
I HAVE BELLY BUTTON.
YOU'RE FRUIT!
>> WHAT'S NEXT?
HONEYDEWS WITH C-SECTION SCARS?
>> HIT IT NAVAL ORANGE, GO TO
BED, BITCH!
>> WHY DO YOU GUYS ALWAYS HAVE
TO YELL?
>> BECAUSE IF WE WHISPER, NO ONE
LISTENS!
OUR NEXT CATEGORY IS --
>> GREETING TRENDS.
>> IN, "HEY!"
>> IN, "KATHERINE?"
>> IN, "COME ON IN, GUYS,
WELCOME TO HOOTERS."
>> AND OUT --
>> THIS IS YOUR CAPTAIN
SPEAKING.
>> HUH?
>> NO, YOU'RE FLYING A PLANE,
NOT HOSTING A PODCAST.
>> YOU'RE A PILOT.
CAPTAINS ARE FOR BOATS, YOU SKY
BITCH!
>> BY THE WAY, YOUR GIRL WORKERS
ARE GIVING ME VODKA BACK HERE.
WE'RE HAVING AN AMAZING TIME
WITHOUT YOU.
GO TO BED, BITCH!
>> ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
>> HMM?
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> NO!
WE'RE TERRIFIED!
BECAUSE THE NEXT CATEGORY IS
HERE.
>> TIME TRENDS.
>> IN, 3:25 P.M.
>> IN, ABOUT 10 TO 15 MINUTES.
>> IN, MIDNIGHT WHEN YOU TURN TO
PUMPKIN.
>> AND OUT --
>> WHEN THE KITCHEN IS CLOSED!
>> WHEN THE KITCHEN'S CLOSED,
HOW INTERESTING.
I CAN SEE PEOPLE MOVING AROUND
BACK THERE.
>> ALL I WANT IS A COMPLICATED
DISH THAT'S NOT ON THE MENU, AND
I'M ALLERGIC TO EVERYTHING!
>> THE KITCHEN'S CLOSED?
>> GO TO BED, BITCH!
>> I LOVE WHEN YOU COME, BUT I
NEVER UNDERSTAND ANYTHING YOU'RE
SAYING.
>> GOOD, ENJOY THE VIEW.
>> AND PAY ATTENTION TO --
>> FUTURE TRENDS!
>> IN, 10 NICE YEARS.
>> IN, A FRIEND I REALLY
COULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS WITHOUT.
>> AND WHOA, LOOK WHO'S BACK
IN --
>> IT'S NAVEL ORANGE.
WE LOVE YOU, GIRL.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, NAVEL
ORANGE.
>> WHAT'S GOING TO BE OUT IN THE
FUTURE?
>> WELL, MICHAEL, THE COMPUTER
HAS OUSTED THREE TRENDS.
>> AND YOU KNOW THEY HAVE TO BE
EVICTED TO HELL.
>> OUT IS PRETTILE LITTLE
BOUQUET.
>> EXPENSIVE TIARA.
>> AND MICHAEL CHE!
>> NO!
>> BUT I'M JUST HEARING
SOMETHING NEW IS IN.
IN, MY BEST GUYS KISSING ME.
>> WELL, THEN, WE MUST.
>> MWAH!
>> TREND FORECASTERS, EVERYBODY.
>> LOVE YOU!
>> AIDY BRYANT.
>>> A MANAGER OF AN ARBY'S --
THIS IS A TERRIBLE TRANSITION.
A MANAGER OF AN ARBY'S IN
WASHINGTON HAS BEEN ARREST FOR
DISTRIBUTING CHILD PORN.
IF FOUND GUILTY HE COULD FACE TO
YEARS AT SUBWAY.
THE MAN TOLD POLICE HE URINATED
IN MILK SHAKES
FOR HIS OWN
SEXUAL GRATIFICATION.
AUTHORITIES NOTICED THE MILK
SHAKES TASTED BETTER.
>> ARBY'S.
WE HAVE THE PEEPEE SHAKES.
>>> A CALIFORNIA HIKER WHO WAS
ATTACKED BY A MOUNTAIN LION
SAID
HER DOG SAVED HER LIFE BY JUMPING TO HER DEFENSE
BECAUSE
AFTER THE DOG, THE MOUNTAIN LION
WAS WAY TOO FULL TO EAT ANYTHING
ELSE.
>> IT'S NOT REAL!
>> A BRITISH WOMAN DISCOVERED
WHEN SHE GOT PREGNANT THAT SHE
HAD A SECOND TINY VAGINA.
UH, YEAH, THE BUTT.
>>> A WOMAN IN MARYLAND
GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE A DAY
AFTER HER 82nd BIRTHDAY.
APPARENTLY IT TOOK HER SO LONG
BECAUSE SHE'S VERY, VERY DUMB.
I DON'T KNOW.
A WOMAN IN MARYLAND GRADUATED
FROM COLLEGE A DAY AFTER HER
82nd BIRTHDAY.
BUT I HEARD THEY ONLY PASSED HER
BECAUSE HER ROOMMATE DIED.
EPISODE OF THE SEASON.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS PETE
DAVIDSON.
THANK YOU.
HELLO.
THANKS.
HELLO, COLIN AND CHE
AND MILLIONS OF PEOPLE ONLY WATCHING
TO SEE IF I BRING UP KANYE.
>> YEAH, YOU HAD A WEIRD YEAR.
>> YEAH.
I JUST -- I NEVER IMAGINED THIS
WOULD BE MY LIFE.
LOOK AT ME WHEN I STARTED HERE.
BACK THEN I WAS JUST LIKE A
SKINNY KID AND NO ONE KNEW WHAT
RACE I WAS.
LIKE NOW, EVERYONE KNOWS I'M WHITE
BECAUSE I BECAME HUGELY
SUCCESSFUL WHILE BARELY SHOWING
UP TO WORK.
AND LIKE, LOOK AT ME NOW.
I'M AGING LIKE AN OLD BANANA,
AND COLIN STILL LOOKS LIKE THE
ONLY KENNEDY WHO DOESN'T DRINK.
>> THANKS, PETE.
SO, ARE YOU OFFICIALLY LEAVING?
>> YEAH, MAN, LORNE ACCIDENTALLY
GIFTED ME A SOCK, SO I'M FREE.
>> HAS A LOT CHANGED SINCE YOU
STARTED HERE?
>> A LOT HAS CHANGED.
IN THREE YEARS
FOX NEWS WENT
FROM CALLING ME A MONSTER FOR
MAKING FUN OF CONGRESSMAN DAN
CRENSHAW'S EYE PATCH
TO ALSO
MAKING FUN OF HIS EYE PATCH.
TUCKER CARLSON CALLED HIM EYE
PATCH McCAIN.
THAT'S TWO VETERAN INSULTS IN
ONE.
YOUR DAD'S A DICK.
>> I'M NOT RELATED TO TUCKER
CARLSON.
>> LEARN SOMETHING EVERY DAY.
IN FAIRNESS, WHAT I SAID,
BECAUSE IT STILL BOTHERS ME,
I WAS MAKING A JOKE ABOUT
SOMEONE'S EXPERIENCE
WITHOUT
REALIZING THE MEDICAL CONDITION
BEHIND IT WAS A SENSITIVE ISSUE,
WHICH IS A "SNL" TRADITION.
ON ONE HAND I DON'T LIKE A GUY
RUNS UP ON STAGE.
MY CHOSE WILL BE SOLD OUT.
>> IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'RE
GOING TO MISS?
>> LORNE FOR SURE.
HE'S LED US THROUGH THE COVID
ERA.
THE ONLY TIME HE WEARS A MASK IS
AT HIS "EYES WIDE SHUT" PARTIES.
NO, HE REALLY ALWAYS GIVES ME
THE BEST ADVICE.
THIS IS ALL TRUE.
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
I CALLED HIM WHEN I GOT ENGAGED.
I WAS LIKE, "LORNE, I JUST GOT
ENGAGED TO ARIANA GRANDE AFTER
DATING HER FOR TWO WEEKS."
HE GOES, "OH, HOLD ON FOR DEAR
LIFE."
IT'S A TRUE STORY.
AND THEN WHEN I AUDITIONED FOR SNL HE SAID,
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE RIGHT FOR THIS SHOW,
SO
LET'S SCREW THIS UP TOGETHER.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE DID.
AND THAT'S WHY PEOPLE WHO DON'T
THINK I DESERVE THE JOB
SHOULDN'T REALLY HATE ME SINCE
WE HAVE SO MUCH IN COMMON.
LIKE, IF ANYTHING, I SHOULD
INSPIRE HOPE
THAT LITERALLY
ANYONE CAN BE ON "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE."
SERIOUSLY, YOU SEE A GUY BUMMING
CIGARETTES OUTSIDE A 7-ELEVEN AT 2:00 A.M.,
THAT'S NOT SOME METH
HEAD, THAT'S THE NEXT
PETE DAVIDSON.
>> I'M GOING TO MISS YOU, PETE.
>> THANKS, COLIN, EVEN THOUGH I
KNOW IT'S ON YOUR CUE CARD.
YOU HAVE BEEN LIKE A BROTHER TO ME,
IN THAT MY MOM LOVES YOU
MORE.
>> I APPRECIATE "SNL,"
WORK
LORN FOR NEVER GIVING UP ON ME AND
OTHER
BELIEVING IN ME AND ALLOWING ME
TO HAVE A PLACE THAT, LIKE, I
COULD CALL HOME
WITH MEMORIES
THAT WILL LAST A LIFETIME
SO
THANK YOU GUYS.
>> PETE DAVIDSON, EVERYONE.
NOT CLASSIC, "9:15 TO 5:10."
>> BEFORE WE GO IN, JOYCE REED,
WE SHOULD GIVE YOU A WARNING.
>> YEAH, MR. DOOLEY'S A GRADE-A
BIGOT AND MISOGYNIST.
>> BUT IS HE NICE?
>> HE'S THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF
NICE.
SOMEONE OUGHT TO KILL HIM.
>> BUT HE'S OUR BOSS AND IT'S
1981 AND WE'RE THREE WOMEN.
>> AND SOMEONE OUGHT TO KILL
HIM.
COME ON.
>> MR. DOOLEY, ARE YOU DECENT?
>> OH, IN THE SACK?
YEAH, I DO OKAY, BUT JUST GIVE
ME A SECOND TO BUTTON EVERYTHING
BACK UP.
>> OH, MY GOD, DID YOU JUST
SHOOT MR. DOOLEY?
HE BARELY SAID A LINE.
>> WELL, YOU SAID YOU WANTED HIM
DEAD, SO I DID.
>> WHERE DID YOU GET THAT GUN
EVEN?
>> MY HUSBAND GAVE IT TO ME,
IN CASE I SEE A DEER IN THE
STREET.
>> BUT NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
THE SHAREHOLDER MEETING IS IN
TEN MINUTES.
>> ARE WE SURE HE'S DEAD?
I MEAN YOUR PISTOL'S SO TINY.
>> WELL, THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO
FIND OUT.
LET'S TICKLE HIM.
>> WHAT?
TICKLE A DEAD GUY?
>> WE DON'T KNOW HE'S DEAD,
NOT UNTIL WE TICKLE HIM.
>> OKAY.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
>> TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE,
TICKLE!
>> TICKLE, TICKLE!
>> YEAH, WELL, HE DIDN'T EVEN
MOVE.
NOT EVEN A LITTLE, SO I GUESS HE
IS DEAD.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DO?
>> I THINK -- OH, NO, THE
SHAREHOLDERS ARE COMING.
>> WELL, SHOULD WE CUT UP HIS
BODY AND BURN IT?
>> THERE'S NO TIME.
THEY'RE HERE.
FOLLOW MY LEAD.
>> DOOLEY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, OLD
CHEESEBURGER.
I HOPE YOU HAVE SOME GOOD NEWS
FOR US.
>> YEAH, WHAT ARE YOUR NUMBERS
THIS QUARTER?
>> OH, BIG HIGH NUMBERS.
I LIKE TO SEE THAT.
>> I LIKE IT, TOO.
BUT WHY ARE THE WOMEN RAISING
YOUR ARMS?
>> WHO, US?
WE'RE NOT WOMEN.
>> NO, WE ARE WOMEN.
WE'RE JUST NOT HERE.
>> NO, WE'RE HERE.
IT'S JUST THAT BEHIND EVERY
GREAT MAN ARE THREE DUMB WOMEN
MOVING HIS ARMS AROUND, RIGHT?
>> GOOD ONE, DOOLEY.
>> COME ON, DOOLEY, LAUGH WITH
US.
>> OH, WELL, MR. DOOLEY LOVES TO
LAUGH.
>> CLASSIC DOOLEY.
NEEDS THREE WOMEN TO MAKE HIM
LAUGH.
>> WAIT, THAT DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE.
WOMEN AREN'T FUNNY.
HE'S NOT DEAD, IS HE?
>> DEAD?
HARDLY.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THIS DOG.
HIS HANDS ARE ALL OVER OUR
BODIES.
>> OH, MR. DOOLEY!
>> THAT'S GOOD FUN.
HEY, HOW ABOUT A DRINK, DOOLEY?
>> YEAH, IT'S 11:00 A.M.
SOMEWHERE.
>> A DRINK?
MR. DOOLEY MAKES GREAT DRINKS AT
THAT BAR ACROSS THE ROOM.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> OKAY.
>> WHY IS HE STAYING IN THAT
CHAIR?
>> OH, UH, BECAUSE HE JUST GOT A
COLONOSCOPY.
>> YEAH, AND THEY LEFT THE TUBE
IN.
>> OH, THAT'S THE WORST.
>> NOW WE JUST HAVE TO MAKE THE
DRINK.
>> CAN WE OFFER YOU A MAI TAI?
>> BREAKING A LOT OF BOTTLES
THERE, OLD DOOLEY.
>> OH, WAIT UNTIL YOU TASTE IT.
>> OKAY, HERE THEY ARE.
>> PERFECT.
>> MAI THAIS.
>> MR. DOOLEY.
YOU'RE ALL OVER ME.
>> THANK YOU.
WAIT -- WAIT A SECOND.
SOMETHING'S OFF HERE.
LOOK AT DOOLEY.
>> YEAH, HE DOESN'T HAVE A DRINK
IN HIS HAND.
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE HE'S DEAD!
DEAD ON WITH THIS MAI TAI.
GREAT WORK, DOOLEY.
>> BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST IN CASE HE IS DEAD, I'M
GOING TO TICKLE HIM.
>> OH.
TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE!
TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE.
YEP.
DEAD.
THOUGHT SO.
YOU GIRLS ARE GOING TO DO TIME.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE US, WE'RE
GOING TO GO TO THE POLICE.
>> BUT WAIT, THAT'S THE WINDOW,
NOT THE DOOR.
**
* LUCIDITY CAME SLOWLY *
* I AWOKE FROM DREAMS
OF UNTYING A GREAT KNOT *
INTO WHAT SEEMED WERE THOUSANDS
OF SEPARATE STRANDS OF FISHING
LINE *
* ATTACHED TO COARSE BEHAVIOR *
* IT FLOWED A CALM IT URGED
WHAT ELSE IS HERE *
* HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE
AT THE CENTER OF MAGIC
TO LINGER IN TONES AND WORDS *
* I OPENED THE FLOODGATES
AND FOUND NO WATER
NO CURRENT NO RIVER
NO RUSH *
* HOW'S IT FEEL TO STAND
AT THE HEIGHT OF YOUR POWERS
TO CAPTIVATE EVERY HEART *
* PROJECTING YOUR VISIONS
tO STRANGERS WHO FEEL IT *
* WHO LISTEN TO LINGER
ON EVERY WORD *
* OH, IT'S A RUSH *
**
* BUT ALONE IT FEELS LIKE DYING
ALL ALONE I FEEL SO MUCH *
* I WANT MY OFFERING TO WOO,
TO CALM, TO CLEAR, TO SOLVE *
* BUT THE ONLY OFFERING THAT
COMES *
* IT CALLS IT SCREAMS
THERE'S NOTHING HERE *
* HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE
AT THE CENTER OF MAGIC *
* TO LINGER IN TONES AND WORDS *
* I OPENED THE FLOODGATES
AND FOUND NO WATER *
* NO CURRENT NO RIVER NO RUSH *
* HOW'S IT FEEL TO STAND AT THE
HEIGHT  OF YOUR POWERS *
* TO CAPTIVATE EVERY HEART
PROJECTING YOUR VISIONS
TO STRANGERS WHO FEEL IT *
* WHO LISTEN TO LINGER ON EVERY
WORD *
* OH, IT'S A RUSH *
* OH, WHAT A RUSH *
**
>> AND I WANT TO LOOK AS YOUNG
AS I FEEL.
>> BUT ANTI-AGING CREAMS IN HAIR
DYES HAVE HARMFUL CHEMICALS THAT
JUST AREN'T ME.
>> BECAUSE I'M ECO FRIENDLY AND
A LITTLE FUNKY TOO.
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU NEED GRAY
ADULT PIGTAILS.
>> THE NUMBER ONE HAIRSTYLE FOR
WHIMSICAL WOMEN OF A CERTAIN
AGE.
>> WHETHER YOU'RE A PUPPETEER, A
PET PSYCHIC --
>> OR SOMEONE'S AUNT'S
THERAPIST'S WIFE.
>> YOU NEED A HAIR STYLE THAT
SAYS, PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT ME FOR YEARS AFTER
MEETING ME FOR FIVE MINUTES.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE UNIQUE.
>> YOU LOVE ART.
>> AND YOU WANT PEOPLE TO SEE
YOU AND THINK, "GOT IT."
>> so GRAB TWO ELASTICS AND
CHANGE YOUR LIFE WITH GRAY ADULT
PIGTAILS.
>> BECAUSE YOU NEVER STOP
SMOKING POT.
WHY SHOULD YOUR HAIR?
>> PAIR IT WITH --
>> A CRANBERRY'S T-SHIRT.
>> CHILDREN'S TUTU.
>> THIS BAG.
>> BEN IMHAT.
>> RASTA HAT.
>> YOU WISH YOU COULD BE THIS
WHIMSICAL.
I LOOK HOW INCENSE SMELLS.
>> I HAVE A BOYFRIEND WHO COMES
OVER ONCE A WEEK.
HE LIVES IN THE WOODS, KEEPS
BONGOS IN HIS TRUCK, AND IS VERY
MUCH A SCULPTOR.
>> HEY, PUSSYCAT.
>> AH, RICHARD, BABY.
HOW DID YOUR SCULPTING GO TODAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DO THESE SHARP, RUSTY BEAUTIES
ANSWER YOUR QUESTION?
>> OH, RICHARD, BABY.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
I LOVE YOUR MIND EVEN MORE THAN
YOUR BODY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE SHE LOVES?
MY GRAY ADULT PIG TAIL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY'RE NOT JUST FOR LADIES.
THEY'RE FOR RICHARD, TOO.
>> YOU WERE MARRIED TO THAT GOLF
PLAYER FOR WAY TOO LONG.
YOU WANT TO ATTRACT THE RIGHT
KIND OF MAN.
>> wHEN I PUT MY GRAY HAIR WAY
UP HIGH AND IMMEDIATELY GOT A
BOYFRIEND.
>> ME TOO.
SAME ONE.
>> YEAH, WE'RE ALL DATING
RICHARD.
>> HE'S LIKE IF A GUY WAS MAGIC.
>> NINE YEARS AGO WE MET AT A
WHITE BUDDHIST TEMPLE FOR
SWINGERS.
>> HE'S A FREAK FOR THE GRAY
ADULT PIGTAILS.
>> YEAH, WHAT CAN'T I SAY?
CAN'T RIDE A BIKE WITH NO HANDLE
BARS.
>> OH, RICHARD!
>> WITH ARE WE TALKING ABOUT
PIGGY TAILS?
>> LOOK WHAT I MADE.
IT'S A VERY SHARP METAL GUITAR.
>> WE SHOULD BLOW THE ROOF OFF
THIS PLACE.
LET'S HIT IT.
* AND THE SEASONS GO ROUND AND
ROUND *
* AND THE PAINTED MOLDINGS THEY
GO UP AND DOWN *
>> GRAY ADULT PIGTAILS.
BUY THEM AT ANY NATURAL FOOD
HEALTH STORE.
>>> THANK YOU TO JAPANESE
BREAKFAST, FRED ARMISEN, MAYA
RUDOLPH.
HAD THE TIME MY LIFE.
HAVE A GREAT SUMMER.