>> Announcer: AND NOW, A MESSAGE
FROM FORMER PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>>> HELLO.
THANK YOU.
IT'S ME.
HI.
I'M THE PROBLEM.
IT'S ME.
WELL, FOLKS, IT HAPPENED. I GOT INDICTED,
OR AS I SPELL
IT, INDICATED.
AND FRANKLY, IT'S TIME THAT I COME CLEAN,
ADMIT THAT I BROKE
THE LAW, AND GO QUIETLY TO
PRISON.
APRIL FOOLS!
THAT WAS A PRANK.
I WAS DOING A JIM FROM OFFICE.
BUT MAKE NO MISTAKE, WHAT THE
RADICAL LEFT DEMOCRATS ARE DOING TO ME
IS WORSE THAN ANY CRIME
I'VE EVER COMMITTED,
AND I'VE COMMITTED A LOT,
CLOSE TO 34.
SOME ARE SAY I'M GOING TO USE
THIS INDICTMENT TO RILE UP MY BASE
SO THAT THEY GIVE ME MORE
MONEY.
NOT TRUE.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING FROM MY
BASE EXCEPT THEIR LOVE, THEIR VOTES,
PERHAPS THEIR MONEY.
AND I NEED THEIR MONEY MORE THAN
EVER.
NOW YOU MAY HAVE SEEN I'VE BEEN
OPENING MY RALLIES
WITH MY
WONDERFUL SONG, "JUSTICE FOR ALL"
WHICH I PERFORMED WITH THE
J-6 CHOIR.
THAT'S A REAL THING.
VERY DISTURBING.
IT WAS THE NUMBER ONE DOWNLOADED
SONG.
WE BEAT "FLOWERS" BY MILEY,
WHICH AS WE ALL KNOW IS ABOUT
LIAM.
BUT MY SONG RAKED IN SO MUCH
CASH, I THOUGHT WHY STOP THERE.
THAT'S WHY I'M PUTTING OUT MY NEW ALBUM,
"NOW THAT'S WHAT I
CALL MY LEGAL DEFENSE FUND",
AKA, TRUMP BOPZ,
AND I'M BRINGING ALL THE HITS
Boys will come along, a dime by the dozen
♪ THAT AIN'T NOTHING, BUT
DRUGSTORE LOVING ♪
♪ HEY, LITTLE THINGS, LET ME
LIGHT YOUR CANDLE ♪
'Cause mama I'm sure hard to handle, now
WOW, WHAT A DEAL.
JUST 30 CLASSIC OTHERS, ALL
HORRIBLE.
SUNG BY YOUR FAVORITE PRESIDENT
TO DEFEND OUR MOVEMENT,
AND
MOSTLY MYSELF, FROM THE EVIL
MANHATTAN DA.
THAT MEANS DISTRICT ATTORNEY.
BUT I'M A FIGHTER, AND SPEAKING
OF FIGHTING AND TAKING ADVANTAGE OF FIGHTERS,
HERE'S MY FRIEND
DON KING.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
WHAT Y'ALL DOING TO THIS MAN IS
A TRAGEDY.
>> SOMEBODY WITH THE BIG HAIR
MURDERED A GUY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT.
♪ ISLANDS IN THE STREAM,
THAT IS WHAT WE ARE,
NO ONE IN BETWEEN,
HOW CAN WE BE WRONG ♪
WE'RE NOT WRONG.
I'VE NEVER BEEN WRONG.
♪ MAKING LOVE TO EACH OTHER,
DON NG, EVERYBODY.
SPEAKING OF LOVE, ME AND THE
FIRST LADY, MELANIA, ARE IN HIGH
SPIRITS.
SINCE THE NEWS OF MY POSSIBLE
IMPRISONMENT, I'VE NEVER SEEN
MELANIA HAPPIER.
SHE'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN IN THE WORLD,
SECOND ONLY TO
PERHAPS MANY YOUNGER, HOTTER
WOMEN.
BUT WE LIKE HER.
ALSO JUST TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT,
I DIDN'T EVEN SLEEP
WITH STORMY DANIELS,
BUT IN MANY
WAYS, I DID.
ISN'T IT IRONIC THE FIRST TIME I
PAY SOMEONE,
THEY TRY TO SEND ME
TO JAIL.
THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T PAY PEOPLE,
FOLKS.
YOU NEVER PAY PEOPLE.
PRETTY IRONIC.
♪ IT'S LIKE RAIN ON YOUR WEDDING DAY,
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT, IT
FIGURES ♪
AND FOLKS, IF THEY CAN COME FOR
ME, THEY CAN COME FOR YOU TOO.
OR IN THE CASE OF JANUARY 6th,
THEY CAN COME FOR YOU AND NOT
FOR ME.
I LIKE THAT ONE A LITTLE BIT
BETTER.
BECAUSE I REALLY DON'T WANT TO GO TO JAIL,
BUT WHEN I THINK
ABOUT HOW SHREDDED I MIGHT GET,
IT'S AWFULLY TEMPTING.
CAN YOU IMAGINE ME PUMPING IRON
IN THE JAIL YARD WITH THE
HOMIES?
GETTING REAL BIG ON TOP, LITTLE
ON BOTTOM.
TOTALLY PRISON YOLKED, LOOKING
LIKE A CANDY APPLE.
PERHAPS I MIGHT EVEN BECOME RECEPTIVE
TO THE TEACHINGS OF
THE PROFIT MUHAMMAD.
ALTHOUGH WITH, I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANY PICTURES OF HIM.
KIND OF SUS.
UH-OH, WHO'S THIS?
IT'S A MAN WHO, LIKEME, WAS
ILLEGALLY RAIDED,
AND HE'S
TURNING IT INTO BIG BUCKS.
AFRO MAN.
♪ I WAS GOING TO GO TO CLASS,
BUT THEN I GOT HIGH ♪
DRUGS ARE KILLING OUR CHILDREN.
I COULD HAVE CHEATED, BUT I PASSED,
AND THEN I GOT HIGH ♪
REAL SHAME.
KNOW WHY
WHY?
♪ BECAUSE I GOT HIGH, BECAUSE I
GOT HIGH, BECAUSE I GOT HIGH ♪
WE NEED TO BE EXECUTING OUR DRUG
DEALERS.
THANK YOU, AFRO MAN.
FOLKS, FOLKS, YOUR HARD-EARNED
MONEY IS IMPORTANT.
IF I GO TO JAIL, I WILL NEED
MONEY FOR COMMISSARY SNACKS.
I WILL NEED A SUPPLY OF RAMONS
TO SUCCESSF BARTER WITH A
LARGE MAN NAMED LIZARD.
AND NOW MY MOST LOYAL SUPPORTER,
I WISH HE WOULD GO AWAY.
HE'S MY KENDALL ROY.
IT'S DON JR.
>> WOW, DAD, THIS IS REALLY
EMOTIONAL.
IT MIGHT BE THE LAST TIME I SEE
YOU.
>> FROM YOUR MOUTH TO GOD'S
EARS.
♪ THE BOY'S A LIAR, THE BOY'S A LIAR,
HE DOESN'T SEE YA, YOU'RE
NOT LOOKING AT ME, BOY ♪
VERY STRANGE ENERGY, MY SON.
DON'T LIKE IT.
HE'S SAYING THAT I'M GOOD
ENOUGH, GRABBING MY DRRR,
THINK
WE
LOVE ICE SPICE, DON'T WE?
ICE SPICE.
LOOK AT THIS BEAUTIFUL HAIR.
MANHATTAN, I'LL SEE YOU ON
TUESDAY.
WE'LL BE WILD.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, QUINTA
BRUNSON.
>>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
MY NAME IS QUINTA BRUNSON,
AND LET ME JUST FIRST SAY, I AM SO
EXCITED TO BE HERE.
I HAVE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT THIS
SINCE I WAS A KID.
I ACTUALLY -- I WANTED TO BE ON
SNL BACK IN THE DAY.
BUT THE AUDITION PROCESS SEEMED
WELL, LONG.
SO INSTEAD, I JUST CREATED MY OWN TV SHOW,
MADE SURE IT BECAME
REALLY POPULAR, WON A BUNCH OF
EMMYS, AND THEN GOT ASKED TO
HOST.
SO MUCH EASIER.
I HAVE A SHOW CALLED ABBOTT
ELEMENTARY.
AND IT'S KIND OF UNIQUE.
IT'S A STREAMING SHOW --
IT'
NOT A STREAMING SHOW.
IT'S A NETWORK SITCOM,
LIKE
FRIENDS EXCEPT INSTEAD OF BEING
ABOUT A GROUP OF FRIENDS, IT'S
ABOUT A GROUP OF TEACHERS.
AND INSTEAD OF NEW YORK, IT'S IN
PHILADELPHIA,
AND INSTEAD OF NOT
HAVING BLACK PEOPLE, IT DOES.
I GREW UP IN PHILLY, AND MY MOM
WAS A TEACHER THERE,
SO CREATING
A SHOW ABOUT TEACHERS HAS BEEN
REALLY SPECIAL.
NOW, EVERY TIME THERE'S AN ISSUE
WITH THE PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM,
PEOPLE EXPECT ME TO SOLVE IT.
AND THAT'S NOT FAIR.
LAST WEEK WHEN THAT BANK
COLLAPSED,
NO ONE WANTED TO GO
UP TO THE CAST OF SUCCESSION
LIKE HOW DO WE FIX THIS, GREG?
DON'T GET ME WRONG, I LOVE THAT
PEOPLE ARE ENJOYING ABBOTT,
BUT
I WISH THEY DIDN'T EXPECT ME TO
BE LIKE MY CHARACTER ALL THE
TIME.
JANINE TEAGUES IS A CARING
SECOND GRADE TEACHER
WHO IS GOOD
AND WHOLESOME, AND I'M THE
OPPOSITE.
I'M NOT A FILTHY WHORE, BUT I
LIKE TO HAVE FUN.
I NEED TO LIVE MY LIFE WITHOUT
SOMEONE SAYING,
DAMN,
MS. TEAGUES IS OUT HERE GETTING
WASTED AT UNIVERSAL STUDIOS.
PREFER
I JUST WANT PEOPLE TO LOWER
THEIR EXPECTATIONS OF ME.
I'M STILL YOUNG, FIGURING THINGS
OUT.
I'VE HAD TO START LYING TO MY
MOM ABOUT WHO I'M HANGING OUT
WITH.
I'M LIKE, I'M GOING TO CHILL
WITH MY FRIEND IN HER GARDEN,
AND I DON'T TELL HER IT'S
OPRAH'S GARDEN.
OR WHEN I TELL HER I'M GOING OUT
TO DINNER BUT NOT WITH WHO.
BECAUSE
>> I'M HAVING DINNER WITH YOUR
DAUGHTER HERE.
WE'RE SO PROUD OF HER, BUT WE'RE
ALSO PROUD OF YOU
NOT ONLY
BECAUSE YOU'RE A GREAT MOM BUT
BECAUSE YOU ARE A TEACHER.
MOST IMPORTANT JOB THERE IS.
>> AS MY FRIEND BARACK SAID --
I CALL HIM BARACK NOW.
MY MOM REALLY WAS AN AMAZING
TEACHER, AND I'M SO PROUD OF
HER.
BUT I ALSO NO FIRSTHAND THAT
TEACHERS GET TAKEN FOR GRANTED.
LIKE I'VE ALWAYS HAD A
DISHWASHER.
NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT, LOADED
IT UP, KICKED IT SHUT, WENT TO
BED WASTED.
BUT THEN MY HUSBAND AND I MOVED
INTO AN APARTMENT THAT DIDN'T HAVE A DISHWASHER,
AND AFTER ONE
DAY, I WAS LIKE, WE GOT TO GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
THAT'S HOW PARENTS FEEL
WHEN THEY DON'T HAVE A TEACHER DURING
THE PANDEMIC.
SUDDENLY PARENTS ARE LIKE, WE
HAVE TO TEACH THESE DISHES NOW?
FEED THESE DISHES NOW?
WHY DID I HAVE SO MANY DISHES?
THAT LAST DISH WAS A MISTAKE.
SERIOUSLY, TEACHERS ARE PEOPLE,
NOT APPLIANCES.
SO PLEASE, REMEMBER HOW
IMPORTANT TEACHERS ARE.
ACKNOWLEDGE THE WORK THEY DO EVERY DAY,
AND FOR THE LOVE OF
GOD, PAY THEM THE MONEY THEY
DESERVE.
WE GOT A GREATHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
LIL YACHTY
STICK
>>> DUDE, I THOUGHT THIS CLUB
WAS A LITTLE SKETCHY AT FIRST,
BUT THE GIRLS HERE ARE INSANE.
>> I KNOW.
I ALREADY GOT LIKE THREE PHONE
NUMBERS.
>> THE ONLY THING THAT WOULD
MAKE THIS NIGHT MORE PERFECT IS
IF WE COULD SCORE A LITTLE
SOMETHING.
>> YOU MEAN LIKE COKE?
>> YEAH, MAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHY NOT?
WE'RE ON VACATION, RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
AS LONG AS WE CAN FIND SOMETHING
THAT'S PURE.
THERE'S A LOT OF GARBAGE GOING
AROUND RIGHT NOW.
>> HEY.
YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR SOME
COCAINE?
>> WHAT?
>> I SAID, DO YOU WANT TO GET
HIGH?
BECAUSE I CAN MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
>> WAIT, SERIOUSLY?
>> I MEAN, IS IT PURE?
>> IS IT PURE?
DON'T INSULT ME, MAN.
MY PRODUCT IS SO PURE WHITE,
IT'S LIKE A BUNNY RABBIT MAKING
SNOW ANGELS ON A CLOUD.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> HEY.
YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR COCAINE?
>> OH, I THINK WE FOUND SOME
ALREADY.
>> YEAH.
THEY ALREADY FOUND SOME.
GET LOST.
>> WELL, MY STUFF IS SO WHITE,
IT'S LIKE GWENYTH PALTROW SKIING
IN UTAH.
>> OKAY.
>> DAMN.
I'M SOLD.
HOW MUCH FOR THAT?
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
MY COCAINE IS SO PURE WHITE,
IT'S LIKE THE GUY THAT'S SUING
GWENYTH PALTROW BECAUSE HE CAN'T
ENJOY WINE TASTINGS ANYMORE.
>> Y'ALL LOOKING FOR SOME
COCAINE?
>> NO.
>> T ALREADY DECIDED, MAN.
>> WELL, NO, WE HAVEN'T.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO MAKE SURE
IT'S PURE.
>> LET ME TELL YOU THIS, MAN,
THE COKE I GOT IS SO WHITE, ITS
DAD SENDS IT MONEY EVERY MONTH
FOR THE RENT.
>> OKAY.
I THINK I WANT THAT ONE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
THAT IS JUNK.
THIS STUFF RIGHT HERE IS SO
WHITE, IT TAKES ITS SHOES AND
SOCKS OFF ON A PLANE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT, MAN.
THIS COKE RIGHT HERE IS WHITER
THAN SEASON TWO OF "THE WIRE."
>> OH, YEAH?
WELL, MY COKE IS LIKE --
♪ CUT MY LIFE INTO PIECES, THIS
IS MY LAST RESORT ♪
>> MINE IS LIKE --
♪ I CHIMED IN WITH A HAVEN'T YOU
PEOPLE EVER HEARD OF CLOSING THE
GOD DAMN DOOR ♪
>> THAIS WHITE, YEAH.
>> HEY.
YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR SOME
COCAINE?
>> WE GOOD.
>> THEY'RE ALL SET, MAN.
>> WE'RE LOOKING FOR COKE THAT'S
SO PURE WHITE, IT GOT A LITTLE
BOTTLE OPENER ON ITS FLIP FLOPS.
>> MY COKE IS SO PURE, IT WAS
WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY NOAH
BAUMBACH.
>> WHO THE HELL IS NOAH
BAUMBACH?
>> A POET.
>> MAN, THAT'S NOTHING.
THIS COCAINE I GOT SAYS STUFF
LIKE, OOP, LET ME SCOOT RIGHT BY
YOU.
>> NO, NO, NO.
THIS COCAINE IS SO WHITE --
>> OH, SORRY.
HOW WHITE IS IT?
>> THANK YOU.
IT'S SO WHITE, IT STANDS LIKE
THIS ADMIRING ITS LAWN.
>> MY COKE IS SO WHITE --
>> LET ME JUST SCOOT BY YOU
THERE.
OKAY.
TOODLES.
>> IT'S THAT WHITE.
>> I ALREADY SAID THAT ONE.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAN.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HUH, I DON'T KNOW.
I STILL CAN'T DECIDE.
>> HEY.
YOU GUYS LOOKING FOR SOME BLACK
TAR HEROIN?
>> WHAT?
NO.
>> OH, TOO BAD BECAUSE I'VE GOT
SOME BLACK TAR HEROIN THAT'S SO
BLACK, IT'S -- YOU KNOW WHAT,
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T SAY.
>> NO, NO, NO.
WANT TO HEAR IT.
GO AHEAD.
>> PLEASE TELL US.
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY IT'S SO
BLACK THAT IT'S STRONG AND
EQUAL.
AND WE SHOULD ALL REALLY GIVE IT
A CHANCE.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT EVEN HERE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
LIKE I SAID, THIS COKE IS SO
WHITE, IT LIKES TO SAY IT'S FROM
CHICAGO, BUT IT'S FROM A SUBURB
OUTSIDE OF CHICAGO.
>> MY COKE IS 20 PAIRS OF YEEZY
SNEAKERS.
>> THAT DOESN'T SOUND WHITE.
>> THEY'RE ALL DIRTY.
>> THAT'S WHITE.
>> THAT'S ENOUGH.
THOSE ALL SOUND VERY WHITE AND
PURE.
I CAN'T DECIDE.
SO I GUESS WE'LL TAKE ONE FROM
EACH.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AND YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY SURE
THERE IS NO FENTANYL IN THIS,
RIGHT?
>> NOBODY SAID --
>> WELL --
>> AND A NOTE WITH A QUESTION.
>> I JUST GOT THIS FEELING THAT
IT WASN'T THE KIND OF QUESTION
YOU COULD SAY NO TO.
>> WILL YOU --
>> BE MY --
>> BRIDESMAID.
>> FROM THE PEOPLE WHO BROUGHT
YOU KEEP SWEET, WILD WILD
COUNTRY, AND THE DOCUMENTARY
COMES A NEW STORY, I WAS A
BRIDESMAID.
>> EACH YEAR, MORE THAN 6
MILLION WOMEN FALL INTO THIS
TYPE OF CULT.
THEY PREY ON COLLEGE ROOMMATES
AND SISTERS IN LAW.
>> THEY SELL YOU ON A ONE DAY.
THE BUT FOR 18 MONTHS, I WAS
FULLY SUCKED IN.
>> THERE WAS AN EMAIL CHAIN,
GROUP TEXTS, DM, A WHOLE
CONVERSATION AND VENMO.
>> GOT PULLED INTO A 200
QUESTION POLL ABOUT CUSTOMIZED
SHIRTS.
WE ENDED UP GOING WITH BRIDE
TRIBE.
>> THEY ALSO TARGET ANOTHER
VULNERABLE GROUP, OUTGOING GAY
MEN.
>> I HAVE BEEN A BRIDESMAID AT
NINE WEDDINGS THIS YEAR.
WHENEVER A GIRL STARTS CALLING
ME SIS, I KNOW I'M IN TROUBLE.
>> THE BACHELORETTE PARTY IS THE
FIRST MAJOR RITUAL, ALMOST
ALWAYS IN NASHVILLE.
>> I TRY TODAY SAY I COULDN'T GO
BECAUSE OF MY STUDENT LOANS.
THE MAID OF HONOR TEXTED BACK,
NO WORRIES WITH A SPARKLE EMOJI.
I KNEW WHAT THAT MEANT.
>> AT FIRST, I THOUGHT IT WAS
THE BRIDE IN CHARGE, BUT IT WAS
THE WOMAN UNDER HER, MICHELLE.
>> MICHELLE WAS A SOCIOPATH.
>> FIRST, WE'RE GOING TO BE
GETTING UP AT 6:00 A.M. FOR A
POLL DANCE FITNESS CLASS.
WE'RE GOING TO BE RUNNING A NINE
BIKE PERSON, AND DRINKING,
DRINKING, DRINKING.
>> I'M NOT FEELING SO GOOD, SO
I'M GOING TO MEET YOU GUYS
LATER.
>> OH, THAT'S OKAY.
HEY, BRITTANY, CAN WE TALK FOR A
SEC?
>> I DON'T HAVE MANY MEMORIES
FROM THE BACHELORETTE TRIP
BECAUSE I WAS DRUGGED BY MYSELF.
I HAD NO CHOICE.
THESE WOMEN WERE TERRORIZING
EVERY GAY BAR IN TOWN.
>> AS WITH ALL CULTS, THERE IS A
FINANCIAL ELEMENT.
>> I SPENT $300 ON A BRIDESMAID
DRESS.
THE BRIDES I'VE TRIED OTHER
TIMES TO WEAR IT.
WHERE AM I GOING THAT CALLS FOR
A BLUE CHIFFON GOWN?
>> MORE MONEY, MORE GIFTS, THERE
WAS ALL THIS PENIS STUFF,
SASHES, STRAWS, EVERYONE ACTED
LIKE IT WAS HILARIOUS.
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND.
>> THE PENIS STUFF IS VERY
FUNNY.
I WILL SAY THAT.
>> AND FINALLY, IT WAS TIME FOR
THE BIG DAY.
>> I WAS SEPARATED FROM MY
BOYFRIEND AND GIVEN A NEW
PARTNER, THE GROOM'S COUSIN
DONNY, WHO WAS INEXPLICABLY 61.
>> FINAL RITUAL WAS THE MOST
DEMEANING.
WE HAD TO WRITE AND PERFORM
ORIGINAL LYRICS TO FRESH PRINCE
OF BELAIR.
>> AND THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN, IT
WAS OVER.
BUT I JUST GOT ENGAGED.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M GOING TO BE SUCH A CHILL
BRIDE.
>>> IT'S TIME FOR COUPLE GOALS
WITH YOUR HOST, BOB DABILDA.
>> WELCOME TO COUPLE GOALS.
KNOW EACH OTHER
LET'S MEET TODAY'S CONTESTANTS.
THEY RECENTLY CELEBRATED THEIR
TEN-YEAR ANNIVERSARY
IT'S
THOMAS AND MIA ANDERSON.
AND THEY LIVED ACROSS FROM EACH
OTHER DURING THE PANDEMIC,
MARRIED
IT'S
JOHN AND LINDA CRONIN.
LET'S GET STARTED.
AS YOU KNOW, YOUR SPOUSES
ANSWERED A SERIES OF QUESTIONS BEFORE THE SHOW,
AND IT'S UP TO
YOU TO GUESS WHAT THEY SAID.
QUESTION ONE, WHAT WAS YOUR
WIFE'S FAVORITE FOOD?
>> COME ON, BOB, THAT'S EASY.
SHE'S THE QUEEN OF BURGERS.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT MIA SAID.
>> BURGERS.
I'M THE BURGER QUEEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE ANDERSONS ARE ON THE BOARD.
LET'S GO TO THE CRONINS, JOHN.
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH MY GUT
HERE AND SAY CREPES.
>> OH, NO, I SAID FISH STICKS.
WE'LL GET THEM NEXT TIME, BABE.
>> QUESTION TWO.
WHAT IS YOUR HUSBAND'S GREATEST
FEAR?
>> I'VE SEEN THIS MAN IN THE GARAGE,
ANDND TRUST ME, THE ANSR
IS SPIDERS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MIA SAID SPIDERS, AND THOMAS
SAID HIS GREATEST FEAR IS --
THAT YOU'LL FALL DOWN THE STAIRS
AND GET HURT SO BAD
THAT I HAVE
TO GIVE UP MY DREAMS AND SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE CARING FOR
YOU.
WOW.
SO NO POINTS ON THAT ONE.
>> THAT'S YOUR BIGGEST FEAR?
>> SPIDERS, YEAH.
SHOULD HAVE SAID SPIDERS.
>> OKAY.
MOVING ON TO THE CRONINS.
LINDA, WHAT IS YOUR HUSBAND'S
GREATEST FEAR?
>> OH, I GOT THIS.
IT'S AIRPLANES.
>> NO, HONEY.
IT'S SNAKES.
REMEMBER?
>> OH.
SO CLOSE.
>> WAS IT, THOUGH?
WAS IT?
>> OKAY.
NEXT QUESTION.
WHAT'S SOMETHING YOU DO IN BED
THAT YOUR HUSBAND DOES NOT LIKE.
MIA?
>> WELL, THIS IS EMBARRASSING,
BUT KISSING HIM BEFORE I BRUSH
MY TEETH.
>> AND THOMAS SAID,
SLEEP TOO CLOSE TO THE EDGE.
>> THOMAS, YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO FALL OUT OF BED AND BREAK MY
NECK?
>> WHAT'S THE NEXT QUESTION,
MAN?
>> OVER TO LINDA.
WHAT'S ONE THING YOU DO IN BED
THAT YOUR HUSBAND DOES NOT LIKE?
>> I WOULD HAVE TO SAY GET ON
TOP.
>> OKAY.
AND JOHN SAID --
>> HOG THE SHEETS, BABE.
>> ONCE AGAIN, THE CRONINS ARE
NOT REMOTELY ON THE SAME PAGE.
NEXT QUESTION FOR THE ANDERSONS.
WHAT WAS YOUR BIGGEST FIGHT
ABOUT?
>> OH, I KNOW THIS ONE.
THAT WOULD BE THE BASKETBALL
GAME INCIDENT.
>> OKAY.
THOMAS SAYS THE BASKETBALL GAME
INCIDENT, AND MIA SAYS --
THE
TIME I HIT A HALF COURT SHOT AT
A BASKETBALL GAME
AND THEY GAVE
ME FREE ROCK CLIMBING LESSONS FOR LIFE,
AND YOU RAN AND
RIPPED UP THE CERTIFICATE IN
FRONT OF THE WHOLE STADIUM.
FIVE POINTS FOR THE ANDERSONS.
>> WE RUNNINGY IT NOW,
HUH, BABY?
>> THAT SOUND MEANS IT'S TIME
FOR A BONUS QUESTION.
MIA
WHO HAS HAD THE BIGGEST
INFLUENCE ON YOUR HUSBAND'S
LIFE?
>> HIS FATHER.
>> YEP.
MY DAD.
MY PARENTS ARE ACTUALLY HERE
TODAY.
HOW AM I DOING, DAD?
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, SON.
>> BACK TO LINDA.
WHAT IS YOUR HUSBAND'S DREAM
VACATION?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SNEAK WORLD
>> YEAH.RLD?
WORLD.
NO, YOU IDIOT.
I JUST SAID I DON'T LIKE SNAKES.
>> OOH, CALLING YOUR SPOUSE AN
IDIOT AND LOSE A TURN.
ALL RIGHT.
MIA, WHAT'S YOUR HUSBAND'S DREAM
VACATION.
>> AT THIS POINT, WHO KNOWS, BUT
HE ALWAYS SAID ARUBA.
>> YES.
YES, BABY.
>> FINALLY.
THERE'S THE MAN I MARRIED.
>> UH-HUH.
AND WHAT'S THAT LITTLE ASHTRAY?
>> OH, THAT'S JUST THIS.
>> AS LONG AS YOU'RE STILL
HEALTHY.
IF NOT, THEN BIG SUR WITH YOUR
SISTER.
AFTER YEARS OF CARING FOR YOU TOGETHER,
WE WILL HAVE GROWN
CLOSE IN A WAY WE NEVER EXPECTED,
AND WHEN WE FINALLY
CLIMAX TOGETHER UNDER THE REDWOODS,
WE'LL HOLD EACH OTHER AND WEEP,
NOT JUST BECAUSE THE
PLEASURE IS SO INTENSE
BUT
BECAUSE WE FINALLY FEEL RELIEF
FROM OUR TRAGICALLY SHARED
BURDEN.
WELL, YOU BOTH SAID ARUBA, THAT
FIVE POINTS PUTS YOU OVER THE
TOP.
ANDERSONS, YOU HAVE WON OUR
GRAND PRIZE.
>> WAIT, WE DID?
>> WE WON, BABY.
>> AND THAT IS AN ALL EXPENSES PAID TRIP
TO BALI'S TEMPLE OF A
THOUSAND STEPS.
>> NO!
>> OH, MY GOD, DAD, DON'T BE SO
AWKWARD.
>> SHE ALMOST CAUSED AN ACCIDENT
JUST TO SIT THERE IN BUMPER TO
BUMPER TRAFFIC.
HEY!
HELLO?
>> WHAT?
>> YOU CUT ME OFF.
YOU DRIVE CRAZY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
EAT -- EAT ME.
EAT ME.
I HAD MY BLINKER ON.
>> THAT'S A LIE.
YOU LIE.
SHAME ON YOU.
>> OKAY.
EAT -- EAT MY BUTT.
THIS, ALL OF THIS.
>> YOU, YOU ARE A SAD WOMAN.
YOU, SAD WOMAN.
>> OKAY.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU ROLL DOWN
YOUR WINDOW AND SAY THAT TO MY
FACE?
>> WHY DID YOU MIME A CRANK?
NO CARS HAVE THOSE WINDOWS.
POWER WINDOWS NOW.
DO THIS.
BOOM.
THAT'S GOOD.
>> NO.
NO.
THIS IS TOO SMALL.
IT WOULDN'T READ.
>> I GUESS.
I GUESS.
>> YOU -- YOU ARE SCARED BECAUSE
YOU AREN'T A MAN.
YOU'RE NOT A BIG MAN.
>> SHUT UP.
SHUT UP.
I AM A MAN.
I'M A VERY STRONG MAN!
>> NO, NO.
YOU ARE A LITTLE BITCH.
YOU'RE A LITTLE BITCH.
>> IS SHE -- IS SHE USING YOU
FOR THE WORD BITCH?
>> THAT IS SO MESSED UP.
YOU SUCK.
YOU SUCK!
>> HEY, DON'T -- DON'T DO THAT!
FIRST OF ALL, I DON'T LOVE THAT
YOU USED TWO HANDS.
SECOND OF ALL, JUST DON'T DO IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT, BYE.
BYE.
YOU, NOT WORTH MY TIME.
>> BYE.
YOU ARE A GIANT -- THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WHAT WOULD YOUR MOTHER SAY IF
SHE SAW YOU DO THAT?
>> MY MOM TOLD ME TO DO IT.
>> SHAME ON YOU.
THAT WAS RACIST.
>> NO.
DON'T HATE ALL WHITE PEOPLE,
JUST YOU.
>> BRAVO.
BRAVO.
YOU, BAD PERSON.
I FEEL BAD FOR YOUR HUSBAND.
>> NO HUSBAND.
HE WENT BYE BYE.
WE SPLIT UP.
>> OH.
ME TOO.
WIFE LEFT.
BUT IT'S GOOD.
SHE WAS A BITCH.
>> DAD!
>> RESPECT, RESPECT.
HEY, THIS MIGHT BE CRAZY.
BUT ARE YOU HUNGRY?
>> YEAH.
I COULD EAT.
>> DO YOU MAYBE WANT TO EAT THIS
BUTT?
HUH?
EAT THE BUTT.
>> SHAME ON YOU.
SHAME ON YOU.
>> YOU SUCK!
>> STOP DOING THAT!
STOP IT!
♪
♪ SEX SYMBOL
THE BLACK SEMINOLE
A SEX SYMBOL
THE BLACK SEMINOLE ♪
♪ AFRICAN RAMBO
WITH MORE AMMO
CAN'T BE ESCAPED
I'M ON EVERY CHANNEL ♪
♪ WHAT'S WRONG
WHAT'S WRONG
MR. MAN ♪
♪ YOUR EYES ARE LOW
AND YOU'RE WALKING
WITH BOTH HANDS
ON YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ HIS RESPONSE
HE'S ON A CLEAN
CLEAN HIGH♪
♪ BOTH FEET
UP ON THE GROUND
BUT HIS HEAD'S
WAY WAY WAY IN THE SKY ♪
♪
♪ THE BLACK SEMINOLE
A HEAD GENERAL
DISTANT CONNECTIONS
A LARGE INTERVAL ♪
♪ A BLACK MAN WITH
MOUTHS TO FEED
EMBRACING EQUALITY
THROUGHOUT GREED ♪
♪ NO TIME TO JOKE AROUND
THE KID IS NOW A MAN
AND THE SILENCE IS FILLED
WI REMARKABLE SOUNDS ♪
♪ THIS PART
I'VE SEEN IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ LOVE IS NOT A LIE
IT JUST FEELS LIKE
A TARANTINO MOVIE SCENE ♪
♪
♪ EXACTLY ♪
♪ NOW
OH OHH
OHH OHH-OH ♪
♪ OHH OHH OH-OH
OHH OHH-OH OHH-OH OHH-OH
OHH-OHH-OHH OHHH ♪
♪ EE-HEE EE-HEE
OHH-OH ♪
♪ MM-MM MM
MM-HMM MM
MM-HM MM
MM-MM-HM ♪
♪ YEAH-AH
YEAH-AH-AHH
YEAH YEAH-HEE ♪
♪ YEAH-AH
OHH ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
GREAT NEWS
NEW YORK IS FINALLY CRACKING
DOWN ON CRIME.
FORMER PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP
WAS INDICTED IN HIS ROLE
IN
PAYING HUSH MONEY TO STORMY DANIELS,
AND THE TRIAL WILL BE
LIKE A STORMY DANIELS MOVIE,
BECAUSE I'M DEEPLY ASHAMED AT
HOW EXCITED I AM TO WATCH IT.
NEXT WEEK
BUT HIS LAWYER, JOE TACOPINA, WHO HE CALLED
JOE TAPIOCA
SAID HE WILL NOT BE PUT IN HAND CUFFS,
THOUGH HE
WILL WEAR BARACK AWAY HAND CUFF
AND A SUPERMAN T-SHIRT.
POLICE
MUG SHOT
CARES GETTING RIGHT
I'M SURE HE'S HOPING HIS MUG
SHOT WILL LOOK COOL LIKE FRANK
SINATRA'S.
NICK NOLTE
>> TRUMP WILL BE ALSO CHARGED
WITH 34 COUNTS OF BUSINESS FRAUD.
COSTUME
PRESIDENT BIDEN ON FRIDAY TOLD
REPORTERS HE HAD OMME
TRUMP'S INDICTMENT,
ANDHEN HE
DANCED AWAY LILAGS GUY.
>> I THINK IN GENERAL, THE
PEOPLE MIGHT BE OVERREACTING TO
THIS INDICTMENT.
LIKE AN ACTUAL HEADLINE ON CNN
YESTERDAY WAS
NOTHING IN
AMERICAN HISTORY APPROACHES THE TUMULT
CHARGES AND POSSIBLE TRIAL AND
CONVICTION OF A FORMER
PRESIDENT.
A MORE ACCURATE HEADLINE WOULD BE,
MAN WE ALL KNEW WAS CRIMINAL
IS CRIMINAL.
PRO TRUMP
I WENT DOWN TO THE COURTHOUSE
TODAY, AND I WAS THE ONLY
PROTESTOR THERE.
LET GO
STINK
>> I TOLD THEM NOT TO LAUGH AT
YOU.
>> AM I NOT MICCED?
THEN I WAS LIKE, OH, I JUST
SUCK.
>> MOVING RIGHT ALONG --
>> MARJORIE TAYLOR GREEN
>> YOU'RE EVIL.
PLANS
TO COME TO NEW YORK ON TUESDAY
TO PROTEST TRUMP'S INDICTMENT,
BECAUSE APPARENTLY IT TAKES HER
THREE DAYS TO PUT ON HER JOKER
MAKEUP.
THEY'LL PROBABLY LAUGH AT THIS
NEXT ONE.
>> THAT'S THE MEANEST THING
YOU'VE EVER DONE TO ME.
I'M COVERED IN SWEAT.
DON'T EVEN DARE!
DON'T YOU EVEN DARE TRY NOW.
FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON DeSANTIS
WHO THINKS HE'S GASTON,
BUT, GIRL, YOU LeFOU.
RON DE --
I'M SHAKING.
RON DeSANTIS SAID FLORIDA OFFICIALS
WOULD NOT HELP
EXTRADITE TRUMP BACK TO NEW YORK
UNLESS OF COURSE HE AGREES TO
TAKE A BUS LOAD OF MIGRANTS WITH
HIM.
>> IN THE WAKE OF THE NATIONAL
SHOOTING, PRESIDENT BIDEN
ONCE
AGAIN CALLED ON CONGRESS TO PASS
AN ASSAULT WEAPONS BAN,
OR, HEAR
ME OUT, STOP AND FRISK FOR
WHITES.
HOW LONG BEFORE THESE KIDS EARN
A STEREO TYPE?
>> CONGRESSMAN ANDY OGLES WHO
RESPECTS THE DISTRICT WHERE THE
NASHVILLE SHOOTING TOOK PLACE
IS
BEING CRITICIZED FOR A CHRISTMAS
CARD WHERE HE AND HIS FAMILY ARE
HOLDING ASSAULT RIFLES.
SHOOTINGS
WHO ARE YOU PSYCHOS SENDING
THESE CARDS TO?
IF I RECEIVED THAT IN THE MAIL,
I WOULD MOVE.
ALL THIS CARD TELLS YOU IS I AM
ARMED, I HAVE TERRIBLE JUDGMENT,
AND I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE.
>> DEMOCRATIC REPRESENTATIVE
JAMAL BOWMAN AND THOMAS MASSEY
GOT IN A SCREAMING MATCH ON CAPITOL HILL
AFTER BOWMAN CALLED
THEM COWARDS FOR OPPOSING GUN
CONTROL.
IF THERE'S ONE THING REPUBLICANS
HAVE,
IT'S BIG OLD GUTS.
>> TRUMP HAS ALSO BEEN PROMOTING
A SONG CALLED JUSTICE FOR ALL,
WHICH FEATURES HIMSELF AND A
CHOIR OF MEN JAILED FOR THEIR
ROLES IN THE JANUARY 6th ATTACK.
I FEEL BAD FOR THE JANUARY 6th SINGERS
BECAUSE YOU KNOW JAIL GETS MUCH WORSE
WHEN THE OTHER
PRISONERS FIND OUT YOU'RE IN AN
ACAPELLA GROUP.
>> LAST WREAK, A FLORIDA
PRINCIPAL WAS FORCED TO RESIGN
WHEN PARENTS WERE OUTRAGED WHEN
MICHAEL ANGLO'S STATUE WAS
REVEALED.
HERE TO COMMENT, MICHAEL
ANGELO'S DAVID.
>> HEY.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> MICHAEL ANGELO'S DAVID.
I'M SORRY.
I'M OVER HERE.
CAN YOU NOT TURN YOUR HEAD?
>> I'VE ACTUALLY NEVER TRIED.
LET'S FIND OUT.
AHH!
THAT HURT LIKE HELL.
>> SO DAVID, HOW ARE YOU DEALING
WITH THIS FLORIDA CONTROVERSY?
THOSE PARENTS ARE PRETTY UPSET.
>> THOSE PARENTS ARE IGNORANT
PRUDES.
I'M THE WORLD'S GREATEST
SCULPTURE, AND I'M A VERY PRETTY
BOY.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THE PARENTS
DIDN'T WANT THE KIDS TO SEE YOUR
PRIVATES.
>> I'M PROUD OF MY TINY PENIS
AND BIG STONED PRUNED.
I'M BEAUTIFUL, AND I THINK YOUR
AUDIENCE DESERVES TO SEE THAT.
>> NO, YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WHEREAS WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE?
>> WHY?
I WANT TO DO THAT.
>> YOU CAN'T SHOW THAT.
ONE PARENT SAID IT WAS
PORNOGRAPHIC.
>> IT'S ART.
IT'S NOT PORNOGRAPHY.
OKAY, WELL, RIGHT NOW, IT'S
PORNOGRAPHY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN IT'S ART
AGAIN.
>> THAT'S FINE.
IF PEOPLE WANT TO SEE IT, THEY
CAN GO TO A MUSEUM IN ITALY OR
LOOK AT IT ONLINE.
>> OH, YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE GUYS.
I CAN SEE WHATEVER I NEED TO
ONLINE.
THAT'S SAD.
LOOK, I AM FROM THE BIBLE, OKAY?
I KILLED GOLIATH WITH A TINY
ROCK AND MY TINY DONG OUT.
YOU EVER BEEN IN A FIGHT WITH
YOUR DONG OUT?
>> NO.
>> ANSWER ME.
>> I DID ANSWER YOU.
I SAID NO.
>> I'M SERIOUS, CHE.
FIGHT WITH YOUR DONG OUT, YES OR
NO?
>> NO.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
IT REALLY DISTRACTS THE OTHER
GUY.
QUITE A BIT, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
>> NO.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO SHOW IT.
I'LL JUST SHOW IT.
>> PLEASE DON'T, MAN.
>> COME ON!
WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF?
ALL THE BEST ART IS NUDE.
ME, NUDE, VENUS DeMILO, NUDE,
STATUE OF LIBERTY, SHOWS FEET.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> YOU HAVE THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
PIECE OF ART IN THE WORLD NEXT
TO YOU AND YOU DON'T WANT TO
LOOK AT IT.
>> I CAN SEE IT NOW.
>> AND.
>> I'M NO EXPERT, BUT IT'S KIND
OF SMALL.
>> WELL, MOST PEOPLE SEE IT FROM
BELOW.
DO YOU WANT TO COME UNDER AND
SEE IT FROM BELOW?
>> NO, I DO NOT.
>> WELL, WHILE YOU'RE LOOKING AT
IT, DO YOU NOTICE HOW THE HAIR
UP HERE IS THE SAME DOWN HERE?
THAT'S NOT LIKE RIGHT, RIGHT?
IT'S TOO THICK.
IT'S LIKE ROCKS, LOOK.
>> DUDE, NO.
DON'T SHOW THAT, PLEASE.
>> IT'S JUST ROCKS.
GOD, AMERICANS ARE UPTIGHT.
DID YOU KNOW IN THE ITALIAN
VERSION OF SNL YOU CAN SHOW FULL
PENETRATION?
>> WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT, IF YOU WANT TO
SHOW IT SO BAD, JUST SHOW IT.
WE'RE ALL WATCHING.
>> WELL, NOW I'M SHY.
>> MICHAEL ANGELO'S DAVID,
EVERYBODY.
GET OUT OF HERE!
>> APPLE HAS LAUNCHED A NEW
FEATURE CALLED PAY LATER THAT
LETS USERS SPREAD OUT PAYMENTS
FOR APPS OVER THE COURSE OF SIX
WEEKS.
THIS HAS ALSO LAUNCHED MY NEW
FAVORITE INSULT, YO MAMA IS SO
POOR, SHE PUT CANDY CRUSH ON LA
AWAY.
>> AFTER A RECENT CHEMICAL SPILL
IN THE DELAWARE RIVER,
PHILADELPHIA OFFICIALS SAY THE
CITY'S DRINKING WATER IS FINALLY
SAFE, UNLESS IT'S BEING HANDED
TO YOU BY THIS PHILADELPHIAN.
YOU GUYS DON'T LIKE SAFETY
PRECAUTIONS?
CUP NOODLES HAS INTRODUCED A
BREAKFAST VERSION OF THEIR
INSTANT RAMON.
THE FLAVOR WILL BE CALLED, "MOM
LEFT."
I LIKE THIS CROWD A LOT, MAN.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, ME TOO.
AGREED.
AN 89-YEAR-OLD JAPANESE MAN HAS
BEEN RECOGNIZED AS THE OLDEST
MALE SURFER EVER.
HE TRULY EMBODIES THE SURFING
LIFESTYLE BECAUSE EVERY PART OF
HIS BODY HANGS LOOSE.
NEW YORK CITY IS EXPECTED TO END
THE WINTER WITH THE LOWEST
SNOWFALL ON RECORD.
YOU LYING SON OF A BITCH.
>> NEW YORK CITY FIRE DEPARTMENT
RESCUED FIVE CHILDREN WHO GOT
THEMSELVES LOST IN THE STATEN
ISLAND SUER SYSTEM.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE A PLACE
THAT FILTHY AND DISGUSTING HAS A
SUER SYSTEM.
BUILD A BEAR HAS INTRODUCED A
NEW RUE PAUL DOLL.
AND HONESTLY, AFTER A FEW BEERS,
I WOULD.
>> NEW YORK CITY OFFICIALS
ANNOUNCED THEY WILL STOP CALLING
THE CITY'S PARK BATHROOMS
COMFORT STATIONS AND WILL
INSTEAD CALL THEM THE MORE
ACCURATE STANK SHACKS.
SAVED A MAN AFTER HE INSERTED A
WATER GLASS INTO HIS RECTUM FOR
SEXUAL GRATIFICATION, AND IT GOT
STUFF.
I THINK HE FELT POSITIVE ABOUT
THE EXPERIENCE BECAUSE HE SAID
THE GLASS WAS HALF FULL.
>> THE FIRST MARIJUANA
DISPENSARY OWNED BY A WOMAN HAS
OPENED IN QUEENS NEW YORK.
UNFORTUNATELY, THEY HAD TO SHUT
DOWN BECAUSE SHE COULDN'T OPEN
THE WEED JARS ON HER OWN.
>> SIMMER DOWN.
A SPERM DONOR IN THE NETHERLANDS
WHO ALLEGEDLY FATHERED MORE THAN
500 CHILDREN IS BEING SUED FOR
INCREASING THE RISK OF
ACCIDENTAL INCEST AMONG THE
KIDS.
ACCIDENTAL INCEST IS ALSO THE
TITLE OF THE WORST AMERICAN PIE
SEQUEL.
WELL, GUYS, IT'S APRIL, AND THAT
CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING, THE
CELEBRATION OF SHORT MEN THAT
THE INTERNET HAS DUBBED SHORT
KING SPRING.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR VERY OWN
SHORT KING, MARCELLO HERNANDEZ.
>> HEY, COLIN.
IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> HEY, MARCELLO.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
CAN YOU WALK US THROUGH WHAT IT
MEANS TO BE A SHORT KING?
>> COLIN, IT'S BASICALLY
SOMETHING WOMEN SAY AS IF IT'S A
COMPLIMENT.
BUT IT'S KIND OF CONDESCENDING.
>> WELL, IF IT HELPS, I NEVER
THOUGHT OF YOU AS A SHORT MAN,
AND YOU'RE WELCOME FOR THAT.
>> I KNOW I'M SHORT.
WHEN I LIE ABOUT MY HEIGHT, I
SAY I'M 5'9", WHICH MEANS I'M
REALLY 5'7" 1/2, AND I'M LYING
ABOUT THE HALF.
WHAT HEIGHT DO YOU SAY, COLIN?
>> I'M 6 FEET.
>> SO YOU'RE 5'9"?
>> NO, I'M 6 FEET.
>> IF YOU WERE 6 FEET, YOU WOULD
SAY 6'2".
>> I'M EXACTLY 6 FEET.
>> THEN LET'S STAND BACK TO
BACK.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
>> INTERESTING.
COLIN, SHORT INC. CANS LIKE US
SHOULD BE PROUD OF OUR HERITAGE.
WE COME FROM A LONG LINE OF
GREATS, KEVIN HART, BRUNO MARS,
PRINCE, THE MINIONS, AL PACINO,
MARK WAHLBERG, JACK BLACK, YODA,
TOM HOLLAND, LIL WANE, RIGHT
THERE IN THE NAME, MARTIN SHORT,
AGAIN, RIGHT THERE IN THE NAME.
BEETHOVEN, THE COMPOSER, WAS
5'6", AND THE DOG WAS EVEN
SHORTER.
>> GREAT TO KNOW.
I THINK WE GET IT.
>> NOW LET'S THINK OF SOME TALL
GUYS.
OSAMA BIN LADEN IS 6'4", ARMIE
HAMMER, 7'3".
>> ARMIE HAMMER IS NOT 7'3".
>> OKAY.
SORRY, I FORGOT YOU TWO WERE
FRIENDS.
>> WE'RE FRIENDLY.
>> YOU KNOW, THE WORST THING
ABOUT TALL MEN IS WHEN THEY SAY
HELLO TO US PETITE PRINCES.
THEY GO LOW AND USE A BABY
VOICE.
THEY GO, HEY, MAN, EVERYTHING
GOOD DOWN THERE.
AND WHEN THEY' DONE TALKING TO
YOU, IT FEELS LIKE THEY SAY IT,
WHEN THEY'RE DONE TALKING, THEY
GO, ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO BACK
UP.
COLIN, WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
US TINY TITANS, WE GOT TO
STICK --
>> STOP SAYING US.
>> THEN STAND BACK TO BACK WITH
ME.
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
WELL, LOOK, SHORT KINGS, WE WERE
BORN KINGS.
WE'VE BECOME KINGS.
WE'VE DONE THE WORK.
WE LEARNED HOW TO DANCE, NOT
BECAUSE WE WANTED TO BUT BECAUSE
WE HAD TO.
TALL GUYS LIKE MICHAEL CHE DON'T
GOT TO LEARN HOW TO DANCE.
THEY STAND AT THE BACK OF THE
PARTY LIKE -- MEANWHILE, YOU AND
ME ARE ON THE DANCE FLOOR
WORKING, COLIN.
NOT BECAUSE WE WANT TO BUT
BECAUSE WE HAD TO.
>> AGAIN, I'M 6 FEET TALL.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE A TOWER.
ANYWAY.
FOR ALL MY SHORT KINGS WATCHING
AT HOME, STAY STRONG, LIVE
LARGE, AND BE PROUD OF THE TINY
LITTLE PERSON THAT YOU ARE.
SO LET'S SHOW THEM, COLIN.
STAND UP AND GO BACK TO BACK
WITH ME.
>> FOR THE LAST TIME, I CAN'T DO
THAT.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE, MARCELLO, I'M
ALREADY STANDING.
>> I KNEW IT!
I KNEW IT!
>> MARCELLO SHORT KING
HERNANDEZ.
I'M COLIN JOST.
>> I'M
APART.
THIS BABY IS COMING.
>> BUT I'M NOT DUE FOR ANOTHER
TWO WEEKS.
>> I KNOW IT'S SCARY, BUT LISTEN
TO ME AND BREATHE.
>> WHAT ABOUT MY MIDWIFE?
>> HE'S ON HIS WAY.
>> I NEED HIM HERE!
>> CLEAR A PATH, CLEAR A PATH.
I'M THE MIDWIFE.
>> BARRY, THANK GOD.
THIS IS MY MIDWIFE BARRY.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, BARRY.
>> ACTUALLY, WE'VE MET.
>> I'M SORRY.
OF COURSE.
IT IS NICE TO SEE YOU.
SO SHE'S ALREADY DILATED 10
CENTIMETERS, WE'VE GOT TO MOVE
FAST.
>> DO YOU REALLY NOT REMEMBER
ME?
>> SHE'S CROWNING.
>> WE MET AT DANIELLE'S
BARBECUE.
>> CAN YOU ASK HER ABOUT THIS
LATER?
>> FOR SURE.
IT WAS THE BARBECUE BEFORE THE
MACKLEMORE CONCERT?
>> SO WE MET IN 2012 ONE TIME?
I CAN'T DEAL WITH THIS ONE TIME?
>> REALLY?
HOW COME WHILE YOU WERE BEING
DEFENSIVE, I WAS DELIVERING THIS
BABY?
>> PUSH, MRS. SULLIVAN, PUSH.
>> IS MY MIDWIFE HERE YET?
>> CLEAR A PATH.
IT'S BARRY, THE MIDWIFE.
>> THAT'S HIM.
THANK GOD.
>> BARRY, IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN.
>> AGAIN?
OH, HAVE WE MET?
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
NEVER SEEN YOU BEFORE IN MY
LIFE.
>> I PROMISE YOU HAVE.
WE MET AT THIS HOSPITAL IN THIS
EXACT ROOM.
>> WHAT IS THE PURPOSE OF THIS?
TO EMBARRASS ME?
WE'VE NEVER MET.
GIRL, RESPECT YOURSELF.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'LL EXPLAIN.
BARRY IS PRETENDING NOT TO
REMEMBER DR. ROGERS BECAUSE
THREE YEARS AGO SHE DIDN'T
REMEMBER MEETING HIM AT A
BARBECUE.
>> BEFORE A MACKLEMORE CONCERT.
>> MACKLEMORE?
YOU REALLY REMEMBER ME.
I'M CURIOUS AS TO WHY.
ANYWAY, WHILE YOU WERE BEING
DR. GASLIGHT, I WAS DELIVERING
THIS BABY.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING US AT YOUR
BARBECUE, DANIELLE.
>> NO PROBLEM.
I WISH YOU COULD COME TO THE
MACKLEMORE CONCERT LATER.
>> I CAN'T.
I HAVE WORK.
THAT'S WHY I'M DRESSED LIKE
THIS.
>> CLEAR A PATH FOR BARRY THE
HUNGRY MIDWIFE.
>> HI, I'M JILL.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
WOW, YOU LOVE YOUR HAIR.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO  LONG.
>> REALLY?
I DON'T THINK THAT'S A GOOD
IDEA.
I WOULDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU IF I
SAW YOU AGAIN IN THE FUTURE.
>> IS THAT A THREAT?
>> MRS. MURPHY, LONG TIME NO
SEE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS BABY
NUMBER TWO.
>> I KNOW.
LIFE HAPPENS SO FAST.
OH, AND THIS IS MY MIDWIFE.
YOU GUYS REMEMBER EACH OTHER,
RIGHT?
>> ACTUALLY, WE DO.
I'M SO SORRY, DR. ROGERS.
I OWE YOU AN APOLL.
I PRETENDED NOT TO REMEMBER YOU
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T REMEMBER ME,
AND IT MADE ME SO FURIOUS.
>> I'M SORRY, BARRY.
I FELT SO BAD THAT I DIDN'T
REMEMBER YOU, IT MADE ME FEEL
EMBARRASSED.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I WAS BEING AN EMOTIONAL JERK.
>> OH, MY GOD.
DID WE MISS IT?
HONEY, WE GOT HERE AS FAST AS WE
COULD.
>> IT'S OKAY.
THIS IS MY HUSBAND AND MY FIRST
DAUGHTER KAYLA, YOU DELIVERED
HER.
>> HI, KAYLA!
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> ACTUALLY, WE'VE MET.
>> WELL, THEN IT'S NICE TO SEE
YOU, OKAY?
>>> ONCE AGAIN, LIL YACHTY.
♪
♪ IMAGINE LIFE WITHOUT ME
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME
YOU WANT THE KIND OF LOVE
THAT CAN MAKE A CHILD ♪
♪ DON'T WANT JUST ANYBODY
MM YEAH ♪
♪ GOOD LOVE FILLS
MY BODY UP LIKE A GLASS
WHEN YOU POUR IT ALL OUT ♪
♪ IF YOU KNOW ME
YOU KNOW I MIND
SOMEONE LIKE ME
IS HARD TO FIND ♪
♪ NOT MISTAKEN
IF I'M THERE
WELL AWARE
YOU ARE ALWAYS MINE ♪
♪ AND STILL
YOU SEEM SO SURPRISED
WHEN YOU'RE ALWAYS
GON' BE MINE ♪
♪ I WANNA BE WHERE YOU ARE
I JUST CAN'T WALK AWAY
YOU DRIVE ME CRAZY AH
I LOSE IT LOSE IT ♪
♪ AND I WANNA
BE WHERE YOU ARE
I JUST CAN'T WALK AWAY ♪
♪ YOU DRIVE ME CRAZY AH
I LOSE IT LOSE IT ♪
♪ IMAGINE ME
CIRCLIN' THROUGH LIFE
WITHOUT A PIECE OF YOU ♪
♪ SEVEN OUT OF SEVEN DAYS
I'M NEEDIN' YOU
YOU BRIN' LIFE
TO THE PARTY ♪
♪ MM-MM AH AH AH
GOOD LOVE FEELS LIKE
BUTTERFLIES SUFFOCATIN'
YOUR INSIDES ♪
♪ OH IT'S A LATE NIGHT
YOU KNOW I TRY
I CANNOT PICTURE
WHEN YOU RIDE ♪
♪ I'M MISTAKEN
THINKIN' YOU WERE TAKEN
KNOWIN' NOW
YOU WERE ALWAYS MINE ♪
♪ AND STILL
YOU SEEM SO SURPRISE ED
WHEN YOU'RE ALWAYS
GON' BE MINE ♪
♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH
MM HMM
MM HMM-MM ♪
♪
♪ RARELY EVER MISSIN'
TALK IS CHEAP
AND TIME IS TICKIN' ♪
♪ RARELY EVER TRICKIN'
CATCH ME SLIPPIN'
♪ I'M ON MISSION' ♪
PAYIN' MILLIONS
I'M TAKING YOU OUT TO EAT
OKAY OKAY OKAY ♪
♪ OUT LATE NIGHT
I'M SINNIN'
STILL A CHRISTIAN
DON'T TELL MY DEACON ♪
♪ I MEAN PASTOR
OIL HER DOWN
NOT TALKIN' CASTOR ♪
♪ RIDIN' 'ROUND WITH
SIX-SEVEN WITH NO TINT
YOU CAN TELL I'M PIMPIN' ♪
♪ BIG FOUR-FIVE ON MY HIP
LOOK LIKE I'M LIMPIN'
ALWAYS SIMPIN ♪
♪ ONE OF MY COUSINS CRIPPIN'
ALWAYS GRIPPIN'
STUFF GET DANGEROUS ♪
♪ ALWAYS KEEP IT PLAYER
WE CAN SWAP OUT
SWAP OUT SWAP OUT SWAP OUT
♪ OKAY
ONLY LOVE MY MOTHER
MY SISTER MY DAUGHTER ♪
♪ ALL Y'ALL GET SLAUGHTERED,
CAN'T BE MINE
PRAY TO THE FATHER ♪
♪ MM HM
MMM HMM
MM-HM ♪
♪
>>> SO, JANET, HOW'S YOUR FIRST
MONTH HERE BEEN?
>> IT'S BEEN GREAT.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE WORKING HERE.
>> WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
>> I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THIS A
BIG DEAL.
I THINK DANIELS HAS BEEN WEIRD
TO ME.
>> HE'S ALWAYS BEEN COOL TO ME.
>> IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING.
FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
>> HEY, MURPHY, HOW ARE YOU?
HOW ARE THE KIDS?
>> THEY'RE GOOD.
JUST SENT MY OLDEST OFF TO PENN
STATE.
>> GOSH, THAT MUST BE HARD -- ON
THE OLD BANK ACCOUNT.
AND WE HITTING THE LINKS LATER
OR WHAT, BUDDY?
>> 5:00 ON THE DOT, DANIELS.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
AND SIMMONS, BIG BUTT, SETTING
OFF THE PENIS ALARM.
MURPHY, YOU GET THAT REPORT INTO
ME BY MONDAY OR WHAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND BEFORE I FORGET, WE GOT A
COMPANY WIDE ZOOM MEETING AT
6:00 WHERE I'LL BE ZOOMING IN ON
THOSE BOOBIES.
COMPUTER ENHANCE, ENGAGING X-RAY
VISION.
HOUSTON, WE HAVE NIPPLE!
>> MURPHY, LISTEN, THAT TURNER
FILE IS NOT GOING TO FILE
ITSELF, A RIGHT?
>> SO YOU GUYS SAW THAT, RIGHT?
>> SAW WHAT?
>> DANIELS, WHEN HE TALKED TO
ME, HE DID AN IMPRESSION OF A
SEX COMPUTER.
>> I THOUGHT HE WAS BEING GOOFY,
BUT I'M OLD SCHOOL.
>> IF YOU'RE HAVING A PROBLEM
WITH HIM, YOU CAN ALWAYS TALK TO
BENSON.
>> BENSON?
REALLY?
>> TOTALLY.
HE'S BEEN HERE FOREVER.
HE JUST GETS IT.
SPEAKING OF THE DEVIL.
>> LOOKY HERE, ALL OF MY
FAVORITE PEOPLE.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> I WANT TO THANK YOU AGAIN FOR
SHOWING UP TO MY GRANDDAUGHTER'S
FOOD DRIVE.
IT MEANT THE WORLD.
>> ANYTHING FOR YOU, BENSON.
>> WE FED 500 FAMILIES IN NEED
BECAUSE OF YOU GUYS.
I MEAN, SIMMONS, I KNOW IT MEANT
THE WORLD TO MY GRANDDAUGHTER
THAT YOU BROUGHT THOSE.
>> THOSE WHAT?
>> WHY, THOSE BIG BUTTERED YAMS,
OF COURSE.
WHAT I WOULD DO TO JUMP OFF A
DIVING BOARD AND CANNON BALL
INTO THAT CLEAVAGE.
HELP!
I'MDROWNING!
BUT DON'T SAVE  I WANT TO DIE
IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT, TEAM, IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING AT ALL, GIVE ME A CALL.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR YOU
GUYS.
I WOULD EVEN ADOPT THOSE
GORGEOUS TWINS AND RAISE THEM IN
A HOTEL LIKE ZACK AND CODY.
DUTY CALLS, SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> LOVE YOU, MAN.
>> YOU GUYS NOTICED THAT, RIGHT?
>> I WANT TO SAY YES SO YOU
DON'T FEEL CRAZY, BUT NO.
>> HOW?
>> THIS IS INSANE.
>> I'M HEATHER FROM HR, AND IF
ANYONE IS MAKING YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE, WE WILL HANDLE IT
RIGHT NOW IN A COMPANY-WIDE
MEETING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BUT FIRST, WE HAVE A MUSICAL
PERFORMANCE FROM THE PENIS
BROTHERS.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> COME ON, Y'ALL.
THIS ONE GOES OUT TO OUR TWO
FAVORITE LADIES.
SIMMONS LEFT, AND SIMMONS RIGHT,
Y'ALL.
>> OH, MY GOD, THE PENIS
BROTHERS.
>> THE MOMENT YOU'VE ALL BEEN
WAITING FOR, THE BROTHERS BONGO
BOOB EXPERIENCE.
♪
>> HOW I IT MAKING THAT SOUND?
>> MURPHY, YOU GOT THAT FILE FOR
ME OR WHAT?
>> HEY, I DO, DANIELS.
BY THE WAY, I GOT AN EMAIL FROM
CORPORATE, AND YOU'RE BOTH
FIRED.
>>> THIS IS NEW YORK.
THE MELTING POT OF OVER THREE
CULTURES, AND FOOD IS ITS
UNIVERSAL LANGUAGE.
>> MY NAME IS ROCCO.
>> HEAVY CAT.
>> AND MY NAME IS DONALD TRUMP.
WE MOVED HERE FOR COLLEGE, AND
WE'VE BEEN HERE EVER SINCE
EXCEPT FOR COVID.
>> TODAY, WE'RE GOING TO SHOW
YOU OUR NEW YORK, THE REAL NEW
YORK, ONE BITE AT A TIME.
>> THIS IS STREET EATS.
TODAY, WE ARE IN THE MIDDLE OF
JAMAICAN PART OF THE CITY,
JAMAICAN QUEEN, AND WE ARE ON
THE HUNT FOR SOME AUTHENTIC JERK
CHICKEN.
>> AND QUEENS MAKE SOME NOISE!
>> RICE, THE STINKING MAN'S
CHIPS.
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE Y'ALL
DOING?
>> WE'RE JUST HERE TO FIND OUT
WHAT JA-MAKES YOUR FOOD SO
SPECIAL.
>> GOT IT.
SO Y'ALL JUST MOVED HERE FOR
CONNECTICUT, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO STOP YELLING.
>> WELL, I NOTICED YOU WERE
SELLING DELICIOUS JAMAICAN FOOD,
BUT YOU YOURSELF ARE NOT
JAMAICAN.
TELL US ABOUT THAT.
>> NO, I'M JAMAICAN.
>> HOW WOULD THAT BE --
>> SPOTS LIKE THAT ARE EXACTLY
WHAT MAKES NEW YORK SO GREAT.
TACO, OH, SPICY.
>> SO YOU WANT JERK CHICKEN WITH
NO CAYENNE, NO CUMIN, SALT,
PEPPER?
>> NOPE, CAN'T DO IT.
>> SO YOU JUST WANT A BLANK ASS
PIECE OF CHICKEN?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> IN NEW YORK.
>> NEXT, WE DECIDED TO HIT UP A
NEW YORK STAPLE, SO WE HEADED
ALL THE WAY UP AND WE WALKED
HERE BECAUSE WE COULD NOT FIND
THE ONE SAY.
>> KEEP GOING THIS WAY?
>> RULE NUMBER ONE, YOU'VE GOT
TO ORDER LIKE A NEW YORKER.
HEY, YO, BOSS, LET ME GET SOME
MAYO AND BREAD.
>> HEY, THERE'S A LINE.
>> I GOT IT.
HEY, FORGET ABOUT --
>> MY FATHER IS A LAWYER!
>> CAN'T CUT THE LINE, MAN.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING ALL DAY.
>> WELL, I HOPE THE BUILDING
YOU'RE WORKING ON EXPLODES.
THEY HATED US THERE.
BUT AT LEAST WE HAVE FRIENDS IN
THAT FAKE JAMAICAN LADY.
SHE LOVED US.
>> I HATED THEM, BUT I READ THE
COMMENTS ON THEIR VIDEOS, AND NO
ONE SHOULD HAVE TO READ THAT
ABOUT THEMSELVES.
THE NICEST ONE I SAW SAID GAY
FAIL.
I MADE THEM SOME PLAIN ASS
CHICKEN, AND THEY LOVED IT.
>> AUTHENTIC JERK CHICKEN.
>> WHAT A BEAUTIFUL NEW YORK
DAY.
WE HAD SOME CHICKEN.
NO ONE CAN DO IT LIKE US.
>> NEW YORK!
AND THEIR INCREDIBLE BAND.
I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU TO MY
ENTIRE CAST THAT DID A
WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL -- THEY DID
IT -- WHAT DO YOU CALL IT?
PANEL WITHOUT ME TODAY BECAUSE I
WAS HOSTING SNL.
I WANT TO THANK EVERYBODY AT
ABBOTT ELEMENTARY FOR HELPING ME
GET HERE.
THANK YOU TO MY FANS AND FAMILY,
WHO SOME OF THEM ARE HERE
TONIGHT.
I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU TO THIS
INCREDIBLE CREW, THE PEOPLE AT
SNL WORK SO HARD, AND THEY ARE
UNREAL, AND THEY DO IT EVERY
WEEK, AND IT'S NUTS, THE CAST,
THE EW, IT'S I