>>> AND NOW A SPECIAL MOTHER'S
DAY MESSAGE FROM THE CAST OF
SNL.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYBODY.
I AM HERE TONIGHT WITH MY MOMMY,
ANN.
BECAUSE, AS YOU KNOW, IT IS
MOTHER'S DAY IN ABOUT 29
MINUTES.
>> SO STILL PLENTY OF TIME TO
BUY A GIFT.
>> I TOLD YOU, MOM, MY CHILDREN
ARE MY GIFT TO YOU.
>> SO ME BABY SITTING THEM IS MY
GIFT?
HOW GENEROUS.
>> ANYWAY, WITH SO MANY
UPSETTING STORIES IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW,
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD
TAKE A BREAK FROM A REGULAR COLD OPEN
AND HEAR SOME HEART-WARMING
STORIES FROM OUR MOMS INSTEAD.
>> REALLY?
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS EXCITED TO SEE WHO WAS
GOING TO PLAY STORMY DANIELS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
>> MOM, I LOVE YOU, AND I'M SO
GRATEFUL FOR EVERYTHING YOU'VE
DONE FOR ME.
>> WELL, THANKS, ANDREW.
I BROUGHT PHOTOS.
>> YOU WHAT?
>> HERE'S ONE OF ANDREW IN THE
BATHTUB WHEN HE WAS 3.
AND I ALSO BROUGHT ONE OF ANDREW
IN THE BATHTUB WHEN HE WAS 23.
>> ALL RIGHT, MOM.
THANKS FOR COMING.
>> IT'S A TASTEFUL NUDE.
>> MOM, I'M SO EXCITED YOU'RE
HERE TONIGHT.
>> ME TOO, CHLOE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
I'M AT THE ROAST OF TOM BRADY.
>> NO, NO.
MOM, THAT WAS ON SUNDAY.
>> CAN I STILL DO MY JOKE?
>> I GUESS.
>> TOM BRADY'S MARRIAGE FINISHED
SO QUICKLY, I THOUGHT IT WAS
YOUR DAD.
>> MOM!
OH, MY GOD!
>> HEY, GUYS.
THIS IS MY MOM, MARY.
>> HEY, EVERYONE.
>> MY MOM IS MORE THAN JUST A
MOM.
SHE'S LIKE A SUPERMOM.
>> AND YOU'RE LIKE A SUPER
DAUGHTER.
BECAUSE YOU'RE SWEET, YOU'RE FUNNY,
AND YOU'RE STRONGER THAN
ANY MAN I'VE EVER MET.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, HONEY.
>> AW, THANKS, MOM.
IS THERE ANYTHING SPECIAL YOU
WANT FOR MOTHER'S DAY?
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'VE ALREADY
GIVEN ME THE GREATEST GIFT OF ALL,
THAT BEAVIS AND BUTT-HEAD SKETCH,
EVERYONE KNOWS ME AS
BUTT-HEAD'S MOM.
>> BUTT-HEAD'S MOM, YEAH, NICE.
>> I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE HERE,
MOM.
>> AW, I LOVE WATCHING YOU ON
THE SHOW, HONEY.
IT'S THE BEST PART OF MY SUNDAY.
>> WAIT.
YOU WATCH THE SHOW ON SUNDAY?
>> DOESN'T EVERYBODY WATCH IT ON
SUNDAY?
I MEAN, SATURDAYS I'M IN THE
CLUB.
>> WELL, MOM, YOU ALWAYS ASKED
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO WEAR A BALD
CAP ON THE SHOW.
>> NOW I KNOW.
IT'S HOT, IT'S ITCHY,
AND IT'S
GOING TO MAKE THIS OUR DUMBEST
CHRISTMAS CARD PHOTO EVER.
>> THIS IS MY MOM.
EVERYTHING I DO, ALL MY WORK
HERE, I DO IT FOR HER.
>> EXCEPT THE STUFF THAT BOMBS.
>> RIGHT.
EXCEPT THE STUFF THAT BOMBS.
THOSE ONES I DO FOR MY DAD.
>> I MEAN, CAN YOU BELIEVE WE'RE
ON SNL TOGETHER, MOM?
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD BE GREAT ON THE SHOW
FROM ALL THE FUNNY HOME
VIDEOS YOU USED TO MAKE.
LOOK.
>> I LOVE CORN.
MM, CORN.
>> MOM, THAT WASN'T ME.
>> I KNOW.
BUT IT'S FUNNY.
>> HEY, MOM.
ARE YOU EXCITED TO BE HERE?
>> OF COURSE I AM.
AND I LOVE ALL THE INCREDIBLE
IMPRESSIONS YOU DO.
>> OH, THANKS, MOM.
>> WANT TO SEE ME DO AN
IMPRESSION?
>> SURE.
>> IN THIRD GRADE YOU LOST YOUR
GAME BOY, AND THIS IS WHAT YOU
DID.
COME
>> MOM, I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE
HERE, MAMA.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, MARCELLO.
YOU GREW UP SO FAST,
BUT NOT SO
HIGH.
>> THANKS.
>> AND CAN I JUST SAY SOMETHING?
>> SURE, YEAH.
>> ALL THE MALE CAST MEMBERS
HAVE BEEN SO NICE TO ME.
>> OH, WOW.
>> MICHAEL CHE EVEN GAVE ME
FLOWERS.
>> WOW.
>> BUT THE NOTE WAS JUST A PHONE
NUMBER.
>> OKAY.
MY MOM, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU.
>> AND ARE YOU EXCITED TO BE
HERE TOO, MOM?
>> OH, SO EXCITED.
I NEED TO FIND LORNE MICHALES AND SAY
THANK YOU.
WITHOUT HIM, WHERE WOULD YOU BE?
A DOCTOR AT A HOSPITAL?
THANKS A LOT, LORNE.
>> MOM, CAN YOU BELIEVE I'M ON
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE?
>> HONESTLY, NO.
I ALWAYS HOPED YOU WOULD BE ON
JACK ASS.
BUT THIS IS YOUR WEEK TO SHINE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> RFK JR. SAID THEY FOUND A
WORM IN HIS BRAIN.
YOU COULD BE THE WORM.
>> OH, THANKS, MOM.
>> AND WE'RE ONLY SORT OF IN THE CAST,
SO THEY WOULD ONLY LET US
INVITE OUR DADS.
>> DAD, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
SMOKE IN HERE.
>> WILL YOU JUST RELAX?
IT'S JUST CRACK.
>> WELL, MOM, WE'RE LAST.
BECAUSE WE RAN OUT OF TIME
AND WE HAD TO CUT COLIN AND HIS MOM
AND MATCHING HAIR CUTS.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
IF I DON'T HAVE A LINE, I DON'T
GET PAID.
>> WELL, HOW DO YOU THINK I
FEEL?
I MEAN, I SPENT DAYS GROWING
THIS OUT.
>> WELL, MOM, DO YOU HAVE AN
UPLIFTING MESSAGE FROM THE MOMS
TO LEAVE ON?
>> I DO.
WE ARE FROM ALL OVER THE COUNTRY,
POLIITICAL SPECTRUM
BUT WE HAVE ONE THING
IN COMMON.
WE LOVE OUR CHILDREN WITH ALL
OUR HEART.
>> OH, WOW, THAT'S REALLY SWEET,
MOM.
>> I HAVE A TOM BRADY JOKE TOO.
TOM BRADY IS SO HANDSOME, HE
SHOULD GIVE ME A CALL.
>> MOM, YOU'RE MARRIED TO DAD!
>> IT'S A MOTHER'S DAY HALL
PASS.
>> OKAY.
EVERYBODY GETS ONE.
EVERYBODY GET BACK ON STAGE.
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY FROM EVERYONE
AT SNL.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MAYA
RUDOLPH!
THANK
OH, IT'S SO GOOD TO BE BACK!
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY
HEART.
IT IS SO GOOD TO BE BACK.
AND FOR THE MOTHER'S DAY
EPISODE.
AND FOR ME, IT'S EXTRA SPECIAL
BECAUSE I AM A FOUR-TIME MOM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAVE FOUR BEAUTIFUL KIDS --
THAT I KNOW OF.
>> HEY, MAYA.
>> BOWEN, SARAH, HEY GUYS.
>> WE WANTED TO SAY HAPPY
MOTHER'S DAY.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE NOT JUST A MOM.
YOU'RE MOTHER.
>> YOU'RE A 30 ROCK LEGEND.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR FOOT ON OUR
NECKS SINCE Y2K.
>> REALLY?
>> OF COURSE,
YOU WERE THE FIRST
TO SLAY DOWN THE HOUSE, BOOTS
QUEEN.
>> YOU HAVE ACHIEVED EXTRA
TERRESTRIAL MOTHER STATUS.
>> ME?
MOTHER?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MY NAME
IS MR. INFINITY DECOR.
WE DID NOT COME TO PLAY WITH YOU
HOES.
WE CAME TO SLAY, BITCH.
AND ALSO DO SOME COMEDY BITS.
OH, YES.
THIS IS MAYA'S HOUSE NOW.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, GAZE AND THEYS,
I GIVE TO YOU MOTHER OF
THE HOUSE OF ROCKEFELLER.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I'M YOUR -- OOPS I MADE YOU
DANCE.
REMEMBER IN THAT MOVIE WHEN I
POOPED MY PANTS?
WHEN YOU WERE A BABY YOU POOPED
YOUR PANTS,
AND I CHANGED YOUR
DIAPER 'CUZ I'M YOUR MOTHER.
WHO COINED SWEATER WEATHER AND
GET YOU A CAR MADE OF LEATHER, I
DID.
I ALSO SAID CLEAN YOUR ROOM, I'M
YOUR MOTHER.
IT'S MOTHER'S DAY, Y'ALL!
TODAY WE CELEBRATE ALL KINDS OF
MOTHERS.
STEP MOTHERS, GODMOTHERS,
MOTHERS FROM ANOTHER BROTHER,
DANCE MOMS, OCTOMOMS.
>> WHAT ABOUT DOG MOMS?
>> WHAT ABOUT THEM?
AND HONEY, THAT'S NOT A DOG.
THAT'S A BITCH.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I'M YOUR -- BOW DOWN 'CUZ I'M
YOUR MAMA.
IT'S GIVING QUEEN, IT'S GIVING
DRAMA.
THIS PLACE GAVE YOU CONEHEADS,
IT'S 11:30 GO TO BED.
WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE FUNTY?
IT'S ME, KAMALA HUNTY!
I WILL ALSO TURN THIS CAR AROUND
IF YOU DON'T STOP HITTING YOUR
SISTER.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
>> MAYA!
MAYA!
>> NOT NOW, CHILD.
MOTHER IS MOTHERING.
>> I KNOW BUT I HAVE A MESSAGE
FROM THE GUYS.
THE MONOLOGUE, IT'S GIVING
BODY-ODY-ODY.
>> BODY-ODY-ODY?
>> YES, MOTHER.
THE RESULTS ARE IN!
>> TEN.
>> I'M GAGGED.
>> GAGGED?
SAY LESS.
LISA LOOPNER, DEBBIE D.,
BABA WAWA, AND DOONISE.
MARTHA STEWART GAVE GOOD HURR,
MARY CATHERINE GALLAGHER,
SWEENEY SISTERS, DONATELLA, LISA
FROM TEMECULA.
GIVING GORGEOUS, SERVING PRETTY,
THEY DID IT LIVE FROM NEW YORK
CITY.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I'M YOUR -- MOTHER.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
VAMPIRE WEEKEND IS
SEAN EVANS, AND THIS IS HOT
ONES.
THE SHOW WITH HOTTER QUESTIONS
AND EVEN HOTTER WINGS.
ARTIST, ICON, AND QUEEN, BEYONCE
KNOWLES CARTER.
>> HOWDY, SEAN EVANS.
IT'S A PLEASURE FOR YOU TO HAVE
ME.
>> ABSOLUTELY, DEFINITELY.
SO YOU APPEARED ON THE SHOW ONCE
BEFORE, AND YOU STRUGGLED A BIT
WITH THE SAUCES.
SO WE'RE THRILLED YOU'VE
RETURNED FOR A SECOND TRY.
>> WELL, THIS WAS THE ONLY THING
I HAVE ATTEMPTED THAT I DID NOT
SLAY.
AND THAT BOTHERED BOTH ME AND MY
HUSBAND.
MY HUSBAND IS JAY-Z.
>> OH, YEAH.
I KNOW.
>> OH, OKAY.
I ASSUMED YOU DIDN'T BECAUSE
YOU'RE THE WHITEST MAN I HAVE
EVER SEEN.
BOTH YOUR SKIN AND THE WAY YOU
CARRY YOURSELF.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
I WOULDN'T DISAGREE WITH THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, SHALL WE GET STARTED?
>> GIDDY UP, LET'S GO.
>> OUR FIRST SAUCE IS SATAN'S
TAINT CHARRED CHILI SAUCE, WHICH
HAS A SCOVILLE RATING OF 65,000.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS ONE'S GOOD.
YOU ALLUDED TO THE ICY RECEPTION
YOU RECEIVED AT THE 2016 CMAs AS
THE INSPIRATION FOR YOUR LATEST
ALBUM, COWBOY CARTER.
CAN YOU TALK MORE ABOUT THAT?
>> WELL, I JUST THOUGHT WHO GETS
TO DEFINE COUNTRY MUSIC?
WHY NOT ME.
THAT'S A TASTY WING.
NOT THAT SPICY.
I'M FROM TEXAS, BABY, YOUR GIRL
LIKES IT CALIENTE.
LET'S DO THE NEXT ONE.
>> OUR NEXT SAUCE THE SERGEANT
SPHINCTER'S VOLCANO SAUCE WITH A
SCOVILLE RATING OF 530,000.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS ONE LOOK GOOD.
HMM.
>> YEAH.
THIS ONE'S ONE OF MY FAVES.
SO I WANTED TO TALK A LITTLE
ABOUT THE SONG YA YA.
BEYONCE?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> DEFINITELY, BOO.
>> OKAY.
GREAT.
SO, YEAH, THERE'S A LYRIC IN YA
YA, WHOLE LOT OF RED IN THAT
WHITE AND BLUE.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN TO YOU?
>> UM, I FORGET.
THIS WING IS STOMPING MY ASS.
DAMN, MY BONES ARE HOT.
THAT WING WAS A REAL ONE.
OOH, YOU'RE ABOUT TO MAKE ME
SING.
♪ THIS AIN'T TEXAS ♪
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S YA YA ABOUT TO YOU?
>> WILL YOU EXCUSE ME?
I'M ABOUT TO START SPEAKING IN
TONGUES.
I AM ZULE.
I'M SO SORRY.
I BONES ARE STILL ON FIRE.
WHERE IS MY ASSISTANT DERAFAEL?
COME HERE?
>> I'M HERE FOR YOU, B.
>> I NEED YOU TO GO ON GOOGLE
AND SEARCH, IS IT POSSIBLE TO
TAKE SOMEONE'S BONES OUT THEY
BODY, REPLACE THEM WITH BONES
THAT AREN'T ON FIRE.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
>> I'LL LOOK INTO IT, B.
>> OKAY.T SAUCE DOESN'T HAVE A
NAME.
IT'S JUST A PICTURE OF A TOILET
ON FIRE.
AND IT HAS A SCOVILLE RATING OF
1.5 MILLION.
>> MM, SOUNDS YUMMY.
DELICIOUS.
>> YEAH.
THIS ONE'S PRETTY GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
SO COWBOY CARTER IS PART OF A
THREE-ALBUM TRILOGY.
>> YOU NEED TO SHUT YOUR CHARLIE
BROWN LOOKING ASS FOR A MINUTE,
AND YOU NEED TO LISTEN TO ME.
BEYONCE ABOUT TO DO SOMETHING
VERY HUMAN, SO I NEED YOU TO
BLUR MY FACE IN THREE, TWO,
ONE -- OH, THEY TRYING TO MAKE A
BITCH CACA HERSELF.
OKAY.
I'M GOOD.
>> OKAY.
SO WHAT CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT
PART THREE?
>> I'M NOT GOOD.
OOH.
CAN I HAVE YOUR MILK?
>> YEAH.
OF COURSE.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU NEED TO KILL YOURSELF,
GOLLUM.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR GIVING
THE WORLD'S BADDEST BITCH SWAMP
ASS ON YOUTUBE.
DERAFAEL?
WHAT'S THE STATUS ON TAKING MY
BONES OUT?
>> WE CAN'T DO IT, B.
>> PLAN B.
TAKE MY COCO BUTTER, ALAE LOTION
OUT OF MY BAG AND GET AS MUCH AS
YOU CAN INTO MY MOUTH.
>> BUT, B, YOU CAN'T EAT LOTION,
ESPECIALLY NOT ON CAMERA.
>> GET MY $6,000 COCO LOTION OUT
MY BAG AND INTO MY MOUTH.
OR I WILL BREAK YOU IN HALF.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M DOING
THIS.
OKAY.
OPEN WIDE, QUEEN.
>> MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE.
OH!
SEAN EVANS, IT'S NOT WORKING.
WHY CAN'T I SLAY THIS?
WHY IS THIS JANKY HOT WINGS SHOW
THE ONE THING BEYONCE CANNOT DO?
>> ALL RIGHT.
JUST HANG IN THERE, QUEEN.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I WANT TO TALK ABOUT YOUR
ACTING RIGHT NOW.
HOW DO YOU CHOOSE LIKE WHICH
ROLES ARE WORTH TAKING A BREAK
FROM AND -- DERAFAEL?
>> LOOK INTO THE LIGHT, PLEASE.
BEYONCE WAS NEVER HERE AND NOT
IN THE SHOW.
>> FOR HOT ONES, I'M SEAN EVANS.
>>> SO NEXT WEEKEND, WE'RE
ACTUALLY GOING TO SIOUX FALLS.
>> OH, THAT'LL BE GREAT.
WHY SIOUX FALLS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST KIND OF ALWAYS WANTED TO
GO.
>> THAT'S SO FUN.
BY THE WAY, CHELSEA, I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO SAY I LOVE YOUR
SHIRT.
WHERE'S IT FROM?
>> AN INSTAGRAM AD.
IT TOTALLY POPPED UP IN MY FEED.
>> THE IT KNOWS WHAT YOU WANT TO
SEE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
SHOW OUR EXPLORE PAGES.
>> I'LL GO FIRST.
THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
IT'S ALL COOKIE RECIPES.
>> SHARE THOSE WITH ME.
>> AND MINE IS LITERALLY JUST
PUFFIES.
NOT ONE.
>> OKAY.
YOUR TURN, BOYS.
WHO'S NEXT?
>> NO.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M NOT PLAYING YOUR LITTLE
GAME.
>> GUYS, COME ON.
IT'LL BE FUN.
>> IT WILL RUIN THE NIGHT.
>> WHAT?
MARK SHOW US YOUR PHONE.
>> I THINK I LEFT IT IN THE CAR.
>> WHAT IS WITH YOU GUYS?
IF IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF HOT
GIRLS IN BIKINIS, WE CAN HANDLE
THAT.
>> LET'S JUST DROP IT.
>> UH-OH, IS IT A BUNCH OF
BUTTS?
>> YEAH.
>> NO.
IT'S JUST LIKE THIS ONE WOMAN.
>> HEY THERE MR. LITTLE MAN.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> I'M UNEESA CONFIDENCE, AN
ONLINE GIRLFRIEND FOR MEN WITH
SELF ESTEEM ISSUES.
>> SO IT'S A SELF-CONFIDENCE
THING?
I MEAN, JOHN, WHY WOULD YOU.
>> IT'S ALL THAT LADY?
>> I'VE NEVER EVEN SEEN THESE
VIDEOS BEFORE.
>> SPECIAL THANK YOU TO MARTIN
FOR HIS $2,000 DONATION.
>> YOU GAVE THIS BITCH $3,000?
>> IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
>> LOOK OUT FOR YOUR VICTORY
GIFT, MARTIN.
HERE'S A HINT.
>> SO IT IS A SEXUAL THING.
>> YEAH, A SEXUAL THING, YEAH.
YES, IT IS.
>> GIVE ME YOUR --
>> WHAT'S UP, BABY?
>> DID YOU EAT YOUR PHONE?
>> DID I EAT MY CELL PHONE?
BABE, WILL YOU HELP ME CALL 911?
>> SURE.
>> HELLO.
>> DON'T FORGET TO JOIN ME AT
OUR SECOND ANNUAL CONFIDENCE CON
IN SIOUX FALLS.
>> THAT'S WHY WE'RE GOING TO
SIOUX FALLS?
>> HEY, GUYS, LISTEN, I'M SORRY
FOR LISTENING, BUT I KNOW THOSE
VIDEOS SEEM WEIRD, BUT RIGHT
NOW, THERE IS AN EPIDEMIC OF MEN
LONELINESS IN THIS COUNTRY.
LOOK AROUND YOU.
MAYBE SOME CONFIDENCE IS EXACTLY
WHAT THEY NEED RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE WE ALL NEED SELF
CONFIDENCE, BECAUSE THE WORLD
RIGHT NOW IS A REALLY WEIRD
PLACE.
ALSO, YOUR FRIEND THAT SWALLOWED
HIS iPHONE DIED A WHILE AGO.
>> NO!
>> LOOK AT MY BEAUTIFUL BREASTS.
>> HEY, KIDS.
>> WOW, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WE'VE ALMOST MADE IT TO THE END
OF THE SCHOOL YEAR.
>> I'VE LEARNED SO MUCH FROM MY
STUDENTS.
>> BUT SOMETIMES THE CLASS ROOM
CAN FEEL LIKE A BATTLEFIELD AND
A WAR BETWEEN TEACHERS AND KIDS.
>> NOW, AS WE REFLECT ON THE
2023 TO '24 SCHOOL YEAR, WE JUST
WANTED TO COME TOGETHER WITH A
MESSAGE FOR OUR SPECIAL
STUDENTS.
Y'ALL WON.
>> Y'ALL WON.
>> ABSOLUTELY, Y'ALL WON.
>> Y'ALL RUDE AND Y'ALL NASTY.
NOT ONLY CAN YOU NOT READ, BUT
YOU ARE ON DRUGS AND SPECTRUM
THAT DID NOT EVEN EXIST IN 2006.
ON TOP OF THAT, YOU SPEAK IN
RIDDLES.
RIZZLER, GYAT, CHEEK, FANUM TAX.
LOOK, COVID BROKE SOMETHING WE
CAN'T FIX.
BUT AS FOR ME MYSELF PERSONALLY,
I HAVE OFFICIALLY ENDURED BY
LAST SKIBIDI TOILET.
I AM RETIRING.
COME HERE, DAMIEN.
THIS IS DAMIEN.
TELL THEM, YOUNG MAN, WHEN I
GAVE YOU A D ON YOUR MATH QUIZ,
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
OH, REALLY?
BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
PRETTY FUNNY IN NOVEMBER.
WHAT DID YOU SAY, DAMIEN?
>> I SAID YOU HAD A FUNKY NECK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SAID I HAD A FUNKY NECK.
HELL NO.
Y'ALL WON.
>> THIS IS JAY.
THIS IS KENDALL.
THESE TWO GOT IN A FIGHT IN ANY
CLASS ROOM, AND WHEN I TRIED TO
BREAK IT UP, THEY TURNED ON ME.
I GOT PIECED UP BY TWO
12-YEAR-OLD NONBINARY ASEXUALS.
Y'ALL WON.
I'M OUT.
>> SOMETIMES I LIKE A LITTLE
PACKET OF CRYSTAL LIGHT IN MY
WATER, AND THE KIDS COULDN'T LET
IT SLIDE.
TELL THEM WHAT YOU SAID.
>> I SAID IT WAS BECAUSE YOU
COULDN'T AFFORD LEMONADE.
>> THEN I FOUND OUT THEY STARTED
A GO FUND ME TO HELP ME BUY
LEMONADE.
IT RAISED $10,000.
YEAH, Y'ALL WON.
>> THIS YEAR, I LIVED BY ONE
WORD, T-S-I-D-D-A-H-N.
THAT SPELLS -- SIT DOWN!
I SAY THIS WORD ABOUT 628 TIMES
A DAY.
FOR EXAMPLE, IF Y'ALL DON'T
TSIDDAHN!
OR PERHAPS, KIARA, I THOUGHT I
TOLD YOU TO -- TSIDDAHN!
OR SOMETIMES, I'M NOT GONNA TELL
YOU AGAIN, JENNIFER, TSIDDAHN!
ANYWAY, KIDS, I GIVE UP, AND
THERE IS LIQUOR IN THIS THERMOS.
>> AND I TRIED TO PLAY CAHOOT
WITH MY KIDS AS AN ICE BREAKER,
BUT WE HAD TO STOP BECAUSE THEY
MADE USER NAMES LIKE POOP FEAST
420, OLIVER DE NIPPLE, AND MY
PERSONAL FAVORITE, ZDICK IN
BALLS TWO.
NEEDLESS TO SAW, Y'ALL WON.
>> I WORE A YELLOW RAINCOAT ON A
RAINY DAY, AND IS SIXTH GRADERS
CALLED ME CORALINE.
THAT WAS MY NAME IN THE
YEARBOOK.
I DON'T SEE IT, BRO.
>> I DO.
MY BAD.
THIS YEAR, WE HAD TO CONFISCATE
SOME OF THE STRANGEST ITEMS I'VE
EVER SEEN.
>> I WENT IN THAT BATHROOM AND
HAD TO CONFISCATE A WHOLE
ROTISSERIE CHICKEN.
THEY WERE COOKING IT OVER THE
URINAL.
I GIVE UP.
Y'ALL WON.
>> WHAT A SCHOOL YEAR.
WE'VE GOT THIS ONE MONTH LEFT,
AND FROM US TEACHERS TO YOU
KIDS, Y'ALL PUT UP A GOOD FIGHT,
AND Y'ALL WON.
>> Y'ALL WON.
FROM EVERY TEACHER TO THOSE
RUDE, STICKY, ILLITERATE
CHILDREN, WE GIVE UP.
>> MS. WILLIAMS, CAN WE JUMP OFF
THE TOP OF THE SWING SET?
>> NO!
TSIDDAHN!
>> BECAUSE Y'ALL WON.
FUR, BIG RED ASSES.
>>> 40,000 YEARS AGO, CAVEMEN
ROAMED THE EARTH, THE WHOLE
EARTH, INCLUDING THE PARTS YOU
DON'T NORMALLY THINK ABOUT.
THIS IS BRITISH CAVEMEN.
>> 40,000 B.C., THE AREA THAT
WILL ONE DAY BECOME MODERN
LONDON.
USING FOSSIL RECORDS, MODERN
COMPUTER MODELS ARE NOW ABLE TO
RECONSTRUCT THESE PRIMITIVE MEN,
HOW THEY LOOKED, MOVED, AND
SOUNDED.
OBSERVE AS TWO BRITISH CAVEMEN
DISCOVER THE BONES OF AN
UNFAMILIAR BEAST.
>> WHA?
OOGA BOOGA?
UNGAH BUNGA?
>> THEIR WORLD WAS GOVERNED BY A
STRICT SOCIAL HIERARCHY WITH
EACH KNOWING THEIR PLACE.
SEE THEM NOW, THE WARRIORS.
>> HNH, HNH.
>> THE UPPER CLASS.
>> OH.
>> THE WORKING CLASS.
EVEN LITTLE CAVE CHILDREN.
>> OY, OY, FILLA.
>> THE POOR CHILD IS DISTRESSED
BECAUSE SHE CAN'T FIND HER
FATHER.
BUT IT'S 3:00 P.M., SO HE'S AT
THE LOCAL WATER HOLE DRINKING
DISTILLS GRAIN.
HERE WE SEE HIM MAKING
OUTLANDISH CLAIMS TO A FEMALE
MEMBER OF THE TRIBE.
>> OOGA BOOGA.
>> OH.
>> THE WATERING HOLE IS ALSO A
PLACE FOR STORY TELLING.
HERE WE SEE AN EARLY FORM OF
GOSSIP.
>> DIN GAH DA BOOGA.
>> WHA?
>> THEY CAN DO THIS FOR HOURS,
AND NO ONE EVER GETS ANNOYED.
HERE, AN ATTRACTIVE FEMALE
PERUSES THE LOCAL ART.
SHE'S INTERRUPTED, THOUGH, BY A
PEACOCKING YOUNG MALE FROM THE
GENUS AMICUS McJAGGEROUS.
SHE LIKES IT, AND IN RESPONSE,
SHE GIVES A BEAUTIFUL SMILE.
AND NOW, SOMETHING AMAZING
HAPPENS.
THE TOUGHEST MEMBER OF THE TRIBE
HAS JUST CREATED FIRE.
SHORTLY AFTER, HE'S ALSO THE
FIRST TO DISCOVER THAT FIRE IS
HOT.
REFUSING TO SHOW PAIN, HE KEEPS
A STIFF UPPER LIP.
THE PAIN INTENSIFIES.
HE LETS OUT A SMALL WHIMPER.
AT LAST, THE AGONY IS SO GREAT,
IT INSPIRES HIM TO UTTER THE
FIRST MODERN PHRASE.
>> BLOODY HOT, ISN'T IT?
>> WHA?
>> REMARKABLE.
TRULY, THESE WERE BRITISH
CAVEMEN.
WHEN WE RETURN, A STRANGER
ARRIVES FROM A DISTANT SHORE,
THE FRENCH CAVEMAN.
>> HNH, HNH, HNH.
>> YEAH.
BUT, CAN YOU COME GET ME?
>> IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I JUST WANT TO COME HOME.
CAN YOU COME PICK ME UP?
>> OKAY.
SURE, HONEY.
WHEN THEY ASK WHY, WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
>> CAN YOU JUST MAKE SOMETHING
UP?
AND, PLEASE, DON'T EMBARRASS ME.
>> OH, HEY, SHARON.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
KAYLIE NEEDS TO COME HOME.
>> HOW COME?
>> HER GRANDMA'S HAVING A
FUNERAL.
>> AT 2:00 A.M.?
>> HER WISH WAS FOR A NIGHT
FUNERAL.
SHE LOVED THE NIGHT.
COME ON, KAYLIE.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> KAYLIE, WHAT IS IT?
>> CAN YOU COME AND GET ME?
>> AGAIN?
IT'S HER FATHER.
HE HAS BECOME GAY.
>> RIGHT.
>> WE HAVE ANOTHER MEMORIAL FOR
JFK.
ROWLING.
THAT'S REALLY SAD.
I NEED HER TO TEACH ME ENGLISH.
SHE HAS TO FLY LIKE PAPER, GET
HIGH LIKE PLANES.
>> LIKE THE M.I.A. SONG?
>> YEAH.
SO IF YOU CATCH HER AT THE
BOARDER, SHE GOT VISAS IN HER
NAME.
LET'S GO.
>> I'M SORRY, MOM.
>> FINE, BUT YOUR DAD'S COMING
THIS TIME.
>> NO!
>> SHE WANTS TO LEAVE BECAUSE
YOUR DAUGHTER'S MEAN AND YOUR
HOUSE SMELLS WEIRD.
>> DAD, STOP.
>> GET UP.
>> SHE GOT HER PERIOD, AND SHE
DON'T WANNA SAY, AND EVEN WHEN
SHE WEARS PADS, IT GOES INTO
HER -- INTO THE UNDERWEAR
SOMETIMES.
>> DAD, DAD.
>> LET'S GO.
BY THE WAY, I'M NOT GAY.
HELLO, WE ARE POLICE.
>> WE'RE HERE TO ARREST THE
GIRL.
>> AND TAKE HER TO GIRL JAIL.
>> CICADAS.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> KAYLIE, TIME TO GO.
>> MOM, YOU ALWAYS DO THIS.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME IN FRONT
TO MY FRIENDS.
>> I DON'T CARE.
YOU'RE COMING HOME, YOUNG LADY.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE, I'M YOUR MOTHER, AND
I'M A BITCH.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
THANKS, MOM.
>> YEP.
>> HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY FROM SNL.
THANKS FOR PICKING US UP.
♪♪
AND SHARPEN THE AXE
FOREVER CURSED
TO LIVE UNRELAXED ♪
♪ WE MAKE NO BONES
A HOUSE IS NOT A HOME
AND A HOME
IS NOWHERE WE CAN STAY ♪
♪ DODGED THE DRAFT
BUT CAN'T DODGE THE WAR
FOREVER CURSED
TO LIVE INSECURE ♪
♪ THE CURTAIN DROPS
A GANG OF GEN X COPS
ASSEMBLES ♪
♪ TREMBLING BEFORE
OUR HUMAN NATURE
IT WASN'T BUILT FOR ME
IT'S YOUR ACADEMY ♪
♪ BUT IN THAT TIME
YOU TAUGHT ME HOW TO SEE
EACH GENERATION
MAKES ITS OWN APOLOGY ♪
♪♪
♪ WELCOME BACK
MY OLDEST FRIEND
ARE YOU CURSED TO DEPART
AGAIN ♪
♪ YOUR WAYS AND MEANS
ETERNALLY OBSCENE
AND ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR OBSCENITY AND HATRED ♪
♪ IT WASN'T BUILT FOR ME
IT'S YOUR ACADEMY
BUT IN MY TIME
YOU TAUGHT ME HOW TO SEE ♪
♪ EACH GENERATION
MAKES ITS OWN APOLOGY ♪
♪♪
♪ IT WASN'T BUILT FOR ME
IT'S YOUR ACADEMY
BUT IN MY TIME
YOU TAUGHT ME HOW TO SEE ♪
♪ EACH GENERATION
MAKES ITS OWN APOLOGY
IT'S BY DESIGN
AND CONSEQUENTIALLY ♪
♪ EACH GENERATION
MAKES ITS OWN APOLOGY ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THIS WEEK IN COURT, STORMY
DANIELS GAVE A DETAILED
DESCRIPTION OF SEX WITH DONALD
TRUMP, WHICH WAS SO DISGUSTING,
EVEN THE SKY TURNED GREEN.
STORMY DANIELS, SEEN HERE AS
DRAWN BY THE CREATOR OF KATHY,
WAS ACCUSED BY TRUMP'S LAWYERS
OF LYING ABOUT THEIR AFFAIR FOR
PROFIT, WHICH WOULD MAKE HER THE
ONLY PERSON TO DO BUSINESS WITH
TRUMP AND MAKE MONEY.
IT'S ALSO BEEN IMPLIED THAT
STORMY DANIELS GOT INTO BED WITH
TRUMP AND LET HIM DO WHATEVER HE
WANTED JUST TO ADVANCE HER
CAREER.
YOU KNOW, LIKE EVERY REPUBLICAN.
>> STORMY DANIELS TESTIFIED THAT
DONALD TRUMP DID NOT WEAR A
CONDOM.
HE TRIED TO PUT ONE ON, BUT HE
WAS BLOCKED BY HIS TIE.
STORMY DANIELS TESTIFIED IN
DONALD TRUMP'S HUSH MONEY TRIAL
AND WAS ASKED TO LIST SOME OF
THE MOVIES THAT SHE'S WORKED ON.
AFTER SHE FINISHED, THE JUDGE
BANGED THE GAVEL AND OPENED ORAL
ARGUMENTS -- WERE THE NAMES OF
THE MOVIES.
OH, MAN.
THAT WAS A GOOD JOKE.
BREAKS MY HEART, COLIN.
>> BEFORE HER TESTIMONY, STORMY
DANIELS AGREED NOT TO DESCRIBE
DUMP'S GENITALIA IN COURT, AFTER
SHE WAS OFFERED HUSH MONEY BY
THE JURY.
BUT THEN, FLORIDA SENATOR RICK
SCOTT APPEARED IN COURT TO
SUPPORT TRUMP, SO IN A WAY, WE
DID GET TO SEE WHAT TRUMP'S
PENIS WOULD LOOK LIKE.
>> ISRAELI OFFICIALS ARE
REPORTEDLY FURIOUS AFTER THE
U.S. WITHHELD A SHIPMENT OF
WEAPONS.
YES, SOMETIMES PEOPLE GET ANGRY
AT THEIR INTERVENTION.
ALL RIGHT.
PRESIDENT BIDEN ON TUESDAY
ISSUED A CALL TO FIGHT HATE
AGAINST ANTI-SEMITISM SAYING,
THERE IS NO PLACE FOR IT IN
AMERICA.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, COLIN'S
COUNTRY CLUB.
>> IT'S A NICE PLACE.
AT A WHITE HOUSE CEREMONY
HONORING THE WNBA CHAMPION LAS
VEGAS ACES, PRESIDENT BIDEN
MISTAKINGLY CALLED CANDICE
PARKER ONE OF THE GREATEST
ALL-TIME COACHES.
WORSE, HE THOUGHT THIS WOMAN WAS
THEIR POINT GUARD.
>> DURING A CEREMONY IN RUSSIA,
VLADIMIR PUTIN WAS SWORN IN FOR
HIS FIFTH TURN AND SWORN IN BY
THE RUSSIAN CONSTITUTION, WHICH
IS JUST A LABELED BOTTLE OF
VODKA.
ROBERT F. KENNEDY JR. REVEALED
HE HAD A BRAIN WORM.
I OFFERED TO EAT FIVE MORE BRAIN
WORMS AND STILL BEAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND PRESIDENT BIDEN IN A
DEBATE, HE SAID, WHICH IS SUCH
AN INSANE THING TO PROBABLY BE
RIGHT ABOUT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
ROBERT F. KENNEDY JR. ADMITTED
TO HAVING A WORM THAT ATE PART
OF HIS BRAIN.
HERE TO COMMENT IS RFK JR.'S
BRAIN WORM.
>> WHAT'S UP?
AREN'T YOU SO GLAD I'M HERE?
>> NO.
YOU ARE HORRIBLE TO LOOK AT.
>> OH, COME ON, COLIN.
GIVE ME A KISS.
>> I'M NOT GONNA KISS YOU, BRAIN
WORM.
OKAY.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE NOW A HUGE
FAN OF RFK JR.?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, COME O LOOK AT THIS
GUY.
HE LOOKS LIKE A PACK OF CHICKEN
THIGHS LEFT OUT IN THE SUN.
CHECK OUT HIS FACE, HE LOOKS
LIKE SOMEONE LEFT BRUCE
SPRINGSTEEN IN THE MICROWAVE TOO
LONG.
HIS FACE IS SO RED, HE LOOKS
LIKE YOU WHEN YOU'RE SCREAMING
AT THOSE COLLEGE PROTESTORS,
COLIN.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HOW DID YOU GET INTO HIS BRAIN
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
>> SAME WAY YOU GET TO CARNEGIE
HALL.
>> PRACTICE, PRACTICE, PRACTICE?
>> NO.
THROUGH THE ANUS.
BUT LOOK, RFK'S BODY WAS A
WORM'S PARADISE.
NOT A SINGLE DROP OF VACCINE IN
SIGHT.
MY WHOLE PARASITE POSSE HUNG OUT
IN THERE.
SHOUT OUT TO HOOK WORM, BOT FLY,
THAT FISH THAT SWIMS UP YOUR PEE
STREAM.
AND MY MAN, PAUL SANDOVAL.
BUT TONIGHT, I WANT TO BE THE
FIRST TO OFFICIALLY ENDORSE RFK
FOR PRESIDENT.
>> YOU'RE ACTUALLY NOT THE
FIRST.
A FEW DAYS AGO, HE WAS ENDORSED
BY KEVIN SPACEY.
>> OH, YOUR OLD PAL.
I WAS IN THAT GUY'S BRAIN TOO.
I ATE THE PART THAT UNDERSTOOD
THE WORD NO.
WHAT?
COME ON!
I'M A WORM.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS EXPECT?
I LOVE CRAZY WHITE BOY BRAIN.
SPEAKING OF THAT, LET ME GET A
BITE OF THAT BRAIN, COLIN.
COME ON.
I'M STARVING.
STAY STILL.
LET ME TAKE A SIP OF YOUR
MEMORIES.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
HEY, STOP.
I NEED MY MEMORIES.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A FEW MEMORIES
I COULD GET RID OF FOR YOU.
OH!
LIKE THAT ONE TIME YOU RAN OVER
A CYCLIST WITH YOUR PORSHE.
>> HE CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
>> HE WAS ON A PELOTON, COLIN,
IN HIS LIVING ROOM!
>> ALL RIGHT, WORM, YOU GOT TO
GO.
>> BEFORE I DO, I WANT TO SAY
SOMETHING TO RFK.
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS RIGHT
NOW, I WANT TO SAY SOMETHING TO
YOU.
HEY, RFK.
I MISS YOU.
I MISS YOUR BODY.
I MISS THAT BEEF JERKY FACE.
I WANT YOU BACK.
AND IF YOU WANT ME BACK, HEY,
MEET ME AT THE TOP OF THE EMPIRE
STATE BUILDING TONIGHT.
I'LL BE THERE WEARING MY MARILYN
MONROE DRESS SINGING --
♪ HAPPY WORM BRAIN, MR. FUTURE
PRESIDENT ♪
>> RFK JR.'S BRAIN WORM,
EVERYONE.
>> A NEW PLANT HAS OPENED IN
ICELAND, WHICH IS DESIGNED TO
REMOVE CLIMATE POLLUTION FROM
THE ATMOSPHERE USING THE WORLD'S
LARGEST VACUUM.
OH, A NEW VACUUM JUST IN TIME
FOR MOTHER'S DAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THOUGHT YOU
WOULD LIKE THAT.
>> IT WAS ANNOUNCED THAT ACTOR
ANDY CIRCUS WILL STAR IN AND
DIRECT A NEW LORD OF THE RINGS
MOVIE FOCUSSING ON GOLLUM.
UNFORTUNATELY, HIS CHANNELER
STYLE RELATIONSHIP WITH FRODO
AND SAM.
THIS YEAR'S MOST POPULAR BABY
NAMES FOR BOYS WERE LIAM AND
NOAH.
GREAT, ANOTHER GENERATION OF
PUSSIES.
>> A GROWING NUMBER OF WOMEN WHO
USED WEIGHT LOSS DRUGS ARE
REPORTING SURPRISE PREGNANCIES,
WHICH ARE BEING CALLED OZEMPIC
BABIES.
I BELIEVE THAT WAS ALSO THE
THEME OF THE MET GALA.
ONLINE CRITICS SAID THE DRESS
KIM KARDASHIAN WORE TO THE MET
GALA HAD SUCH A TIGHT WAIST THAT
IT SEEMED LIKE IT WAS CRUSHED
HER ORGANS.
BUT I ALREADY WATCHED HER ORGANS
GET CRUSHED BY RAY JAY.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE THE SHOW.
>> I THINK IT DID.
I THINK SOMEONE SCREAMED.
A DOG WAS RESCUED
NEXT TIME, SAID KRISTI NOEM.
>> A WORKER ON A CRUISE SHIP
HEADING TO ALASKA WAS ARRESTED
FOR ATTACKING THREE PASSENGERS
WITH SCISSORS.
HE WAS EVENTUALLY SUBDUED BY A
PASSENGER WITH ROCK.
>> SO DUMB.
THIS YEAR MARKS THE FIRST TIME
SINCE 2009 THAT A MARVEL MOVIE
HAS NOT KICKED OFF THE SUMMER
MOVIE SEASON, WHICH BETTER BE A
ONE-TIME THING BECAUSE A LOT OF
PEOPLE RELY ON MARVEL MOVIES TO
PAY FOR THE FERRIES THEY BOUGHT.
>> THE WNBA WILL SOON ALLOW
TEAMS TRAVELING FOR AWAY GAMES
TO FLY ON PRIVATE CHARTER
PLANES, WHICH PREVIOUSLY ONLY
HAPPENED AFTER THEY WERE
RELEASED FROM RUSSIAN PRISON.
THIS MIGHT BE MY FAVORITE SHOW.
THIS IS MY EMMY SHOW.
ON WEDNESDAY, THE REIGNING MISS
TEEN USA ANNOUNCED SHE WAS
GIVING UP HER TITLE.
MAN THIS WEEK KEEPS GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE FOR DRAKE.
>> WELL, TOMORROW IS MOTHER'S
DAY.
HERE WITH SOME GIFT IDEAS TO
SURPRISE HER MOM IS A MOM WHO
SAYS SHE'S NOT MAD.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
COLIN.
I GUESS I'M HERE TO TALK ABOUT
MAMA'S DAY.
YEA!
>> IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> YEP.
I SAID I'M GOOD, SO I'M GOOD.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
SO YOU'RE HERE TO TALK ABOUT
MOTHER'S DAY GIFTS.
>> IF YOU'LL LET ME, YEAH.
AND THE NUMBER ONE THING TO GET
YOUR MAMA ON MOTHER'S DAY IS --
>> SUNGLASSES?
>> JESUS CHRIST, COLIN, NO.
BRUNCH.
THE SUNGLASSES WERE JUST TO BE
FUNNY.
I WAS GOING TO PUT THEM ON, PULL
THEM DOWN AND SAY, TABLE FOR
TWO.
IT'S A PROP.
BUT SURE, BRUNCH.
TAKE YOUR MOM TO BRUNCH.
>> I'M SORRY.
ALSO, IT'S PROBABLY A LITTLE
LATE TO GET A RESERVATION FOR
BRUNCH NOW.
>> YEAH, IT PROBABLY IS.
HOW ABOUT YOU JUST LET ME KNOW
WHEN I'M NEEDED?
>> TEN SIGNS YOUR MAN IS
GASLIGHTING YOU.
>> OKAY.
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY MAD.
>> NO.
I'M NOT.
ARE YOU INSANE RIGHT NOW?
IF ANYTHING, YOU'RE MAD.
>> OKAY.
WELL THEN IF YOU CAN'T GET A
BRUNCH RESERVATION, MAYBE YOU
COULD MAKE YOUR MOM BREAKFAST IN
BED.
>> LOST MY SHIRT.
GREAT IDEA.
>> YOU'RE FOLDING LAUNDRY NOW?
>> YEAH.
WHAT?
I'M GOOD.
>> YOU DON'T SEEM GOOD.
>> OKAY.
WELL THEN WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TELL ME HOW TO BE?
BY THE WAY, I WORE THE NICEST
THING I OWN.
THIS WAS MY PROM DRESS.
FOR WHAT?
ALSO, HI, CHE.
I'VE BEEN SITTING OUT HERE FOR
FIVE MINUTES.
YOU HAVEN'T SAID A WORD TO ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW YOU.
>> OKAY.
I'M GONNA GO.
>> NO.
DON'T GO.
PLEASE STAY.
WE WOULD ALL -- WE WOULD LOVE TO
HEAR YOUR MOTHER'S DAY GIFT
IDEAS.
PLEASE.
PLEASE STAY.
TELL US YOUR IDEAS.
>> OKAY.
I'LL STAY.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE I WANT TO.
>> GREAT.
>> OKAY.
SO, THE BEST MOTHER'S DAY GIFT
OF ALL, I BELIEVE, IS HONESTY.
DON'T LIE TO A WOMAN AND TELL
HER SHE'S HOSTING SNL AND THEN
JUST HAVE HER ON THE WORST PART
OF THE SHOW, "WEEKEND UPDATE."
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE MAD?
YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE HOSTING?
>> BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT SHE TOLD
ME.
I EMAILED AND SAID, IN TOWN, CAN
I HOST.
AND I IMMEDIATELY GOT A
CONFIRMATION EMAIL FROM YOUR
ASSISTANT.
>> MY ASSISTANT?
>> YES.
MAILER DAMON.
>> OH, MY GOD.
A WOMAN WHO SAYS SHE'S NOT MAD.
>> I'M NOT
SET.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE WE GOT
THREE-TIME OSCAR WINNING DAWN
FARRAWAY FOR THIS COMMERCIAL.
ARE YOU IN NERVOUS?
I'VE HEARD SHE MAKES DIRECTORS
CRY.
>> I'VE HEARD THAT AS WELL.
LET ME START BY SAYING, I LOVE
THIS COFFEE SO MUCH.
AND THE SCRIPT, IT'S PERFECTION.
IT'S A LOVE LETTER TO DECAF
COFFEE, KUDOS.
>> MS. FARRAWAY, I'M GORGE, THE
DIRECTOR.
>> TANYA GRIGGS FROM TIPTOP
COFFEE.
HUGE PLEASURE.
>> I LOVE YOUR PRODUCT.
I LOVE THIS COFFEE.
>> SHOULD WE READ IT ONCE BEFORE
WE SHOOT?
>> FIRST, ANOTHER COFFEE.
AND THEN WE CAN PUT IT ON THE
GRILL, AS THEY SAY.
HELLO.
NOW LET'S SEE HERE.
I LIKE COMING OUT WITH A RICH
CUP OF COFFEE.
I COULD DRINK IT DAY OR NIGHT.
AND THE FLAVOR, MM, IT'S AS GOOD
AS COFFEE GETS.
>> MS. FARRAWAY, THAT WAS
AMAZING.
>> LET'S DO IT.
RIGHT AFTER I GET A TOP OFF OF
THIS DELICIOUS COFFEE.
I CAN'T STOP DRINKING IT.
>> ARE YOU A COFFEE CONNOISSEUR?
>> I'VE NEVER HAD IT BEFORE.
MY DOCTOR SAID DO NOT.
>> YOU SAID SHE WAS DIFFICULT,
BUT SHE'S BEING A TOTAL PRO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TIPTOP COFFEE COMMERCIAL TAKE
ONE.
>> AND ACTION.
>> I LOVE CURLING UP WITH A RICH
CUP OF COFFEE.
I COULD DRINK IT DAY OR NIGHT.
WHY?
BECAUSE TIPTOP COFFEE -- CAN YOU
PLEASE LEAVE?
>> WHO ME?
I'M THE CAMERA MAN.
>> WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT IN MY EYE
LINE, AND I DON'T LIKE THAT.
NOW, GIVE ME ANOTHER CUP OF THIS
G.D. DELICIOUS COFFEE AND LET'S
GO AGAIN RIGHT AWAY.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LET'S TRY ONE MORE TIME.
>> TIPTOP COMMERCIAL, TAKE TWO.
>> AND ACTION.
>> I LOVE CURLING UP WITH A RICH
CUP OF COFFEE.
I COULD DRINK IT DAY OR -- LINE?
>> DAY OR NIGHT.
>> WHO IS THIS?
CAN SHE LEAVE?
>> MS. FARRAWAY, IS THERE AN
ISSUE?
>> YES, I DON'T LIKE HER, AND I
WOULD LIKE HER TO LEAVE.
>> MS. FARRAWAY?
>> YES?
>> DID YOU JUST?
>> NOPE.
LET'S GO AGAIN.
WHERE'S THE COFFEE BOY?
JUST GIVE ME THE ENTIRE SAMOVAR.
>> MAYBE YOU SHOULD SLOW DOWN ON
THE COFFEE.
I DON'T THINK IT'S SITTING WELL.
>> THE COFFEE IS THE ONLY REASON
I'M STILL HERE.
IF IT WASN'T SO DAMN GOOD, I
WOULD BE HALFWAY DOWN THE
BOULEVARD
I DON'T KNOW WHO LET FROGS IN
HERE, BUT THEY'RE VERY LOUD, AND
THEY'RE RUINING MY TAKE.
SOMEONE POWDER ME AGAIN.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
NOT HER, I DON'T LIKE HER.
>> I DON'T LIKE YOU EITHER.
>> OH, I LIKE HER.
>> MRS. FARRAWAY, DO YOU NEED A
MOMENT?
>> WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
TANDALAYA?
>> TANYA.
>> WHAT I NEED, TANDALAYA IS TO
GET THIS DAMN SPOT IN THE CAN.
NOW LET'S SHOOT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
MS. FARRAWAY.
>> COFFEE COMMERCIAL, TAKE
THREE.
>> AND ACTION.
>> I -- LINE.
>> LOVE.
>> LINE.
>> CURLING.
>> UP WITH.
>> LINE.
>> A RICH CUP.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> OF COFFEE.
BECAUSE TIPTOP COFFEE IS DECAF
NATED.
>> IT IS?
WHY DIDN'T ANYBODY TELL ME?
CAN YOU PLEASE LEAVE?
>> I'M THE DIRECTOR.
>> THEN YOUR WIFE NEEDS TO
LEAVE.
>> I'M THE CLIENT.
>> NO ONE IS LEAVING.
ONE MORE TIME.
ALL THE LINES IN A ROW.
WE'RE PAYING YOU $8 MILLION.
>> WOW.
KITTY HAS CLAWS.
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE A REPUTATION FOR BEING
DIFFICULT.
BUT WHEN IT'S TIME TO DO IT,
IT'S TIME TO DO IT.
>> I THINK WE GOT IT THIS TIME.
LET'S RESET.
AND ACTION.
>> I LOVE CURLING UP WITH A RICH
CUP OF COFFEE.
I COULD DRINK IT DAY OR NIGHT.
WHY?
BECAUSE TIPTOP COFFEE IS DE
CAFFEINATED, AND THE FAVOR IS AS
COFFEE AS IT GETS
AND CUT.
WELL, YOU ALL LIKED IT THAT
MUCH?
>> NO.
WE'RE TRYING TO CREATE A WIND
AWAY FROM US?
>> TANDALAYA, PLEASE LEAVE.
PLEASE.
♪ CAN'T REACH THE MOON NOW
CAN'T TURN THE TIDE
THE WORLD LOOKED DIFFERENT
WHEN GOD WAS ON YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ WHO BUILDS THE FUTURE
DO THEY CARE WHY
I KNOW
YOU'RE TIRED OF TRYIN' ♪
♪ LISTEN CLEARLY
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TRY
CAPRICORN ♪
♪ THE YEAR THAT
YOU WERE BORN
FINISHED FAST ♪
♪ AND THE NEXT ONE
WASN'T YOURS
TOO OLD FOR DYIN' YOUNG
TOO YOUNG TO LIVE ALONE ♪
♪ SIFTING THROUGH CENTURIES
FOR MOMENTS OF YOUR OWN ♪
♪♪
♪ ALONE AND WOUNDED
BUT IN MY PRIME
I CALLED THE HOSPITAL
THEY DIDN'T HAVE THE TIME ♪
♪ I'D SEEN IT COMIN'
IT'S NO SURPRISE
I KNOW
YOU'RE TIRED OF TRYIN' ♪
♪ LISTEN CLEARLY
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TRY
CAPRICORN ♪
♪ THE YEAR THAT
YOU WERE BORN
FINISHED FAST ♪
♪ AND THE NEXT ONE
WASN'T YOURS
TOO OLD FOR DYIN' YOUNG
TOO YOUNG TO LIVE ALONE ♪
♪ SIFTING THROUGH CENTURIES
FOR MOMENTS OF YOUR OWN ♪
♪♪
♪ A HUNDRED DOLLARS
ON SOMEONE'S DIME
I LOOKED FOR ANSWERS THERE
THEY WEREN'T MINE TO FIND ♪
♪ GOOD DAYS ARE COMIN'
NOT JUST TO DIE
I KNOW
YOU'RE TIRED OF TRYIN' ♪
♪ LISTEN BABY
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TRY
CAPRICORN ♪
♪ THE YEAR THAT
YOU WERE BORN
FINISHED FAST ♪
♪ AND THE NEXT ONE
WASN'T YOURS
TOO OLD FOR DYIN' YOUNG
TOO YOUNG TO LIVE ALONE ♪
♪ SIFTING THROUGH CENTURIES
FOR MOMENTS OF YOUR OWN
CAPRICORN ♪
♪ THE YEAR THAT
YOU WERE BORN
FINISHED FAST ♪
♪ AND THE NEXT ONE
WASN'T YOURS
TOO OLD FOR DYIN' YOUNG
TOO YOUNG TO LIVE ALONE ♪
♪ SIFTING THROUGH CENTURIES
FOR MOMENTS OF YOUR OWN ♪
>>> IT'S NATIONAL NURSE'S WEEK.
A TIME TO HONOR THE HARD-WORKING
WOMEN AND MEN, I GUESS, WHO CARE
FOR US AND KEEP US HEALTHY.
>> TO ME, BEING A NURSE MEANS
STANDING BY YOUR SIDE DURING
LIFE'S MOST IMPORTANT MOMENTS.
>> TO ME, BEING A NURSE MEANS
DOING WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
THERE'S NO TASK TOO BIG OR TOO
SMALL.
>> 90% OF MY JOB IS CLEANING UP
A GROAN MAN'S DOOKIE.
THE OTHER 10% IS SPONGE BATHS,
WHICH IS SOMEHOW WORSE.
BY THE WAY, WHERE'S YOUR ACCENT
FROM?
>> THE JAMAICAN PART OF IRELAND.
>> I WORK IN A MATERNITY WARD,
SO I GET TO WITNESS MIRACLES
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> I SPECIALIZE IN ONCOLOGY, AND
THERE'S NO BETTER FEELING THAN
GETTING TO TELL SOMEONE THEY'RE
CANCER-FREE.
>> EVERY TIME WE TRY TO TAKE
CURTIS' TEMPERATURE, HE SAY,
WRONG HOLE.
>> AND HE'S KIND OF RACIST.
HE KEEPS CALLING ME VENUS.
>> AND ME SERENA.
>> BUT IN HIS DEFENSE, HE'S GOT
DEMENTIA.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> I'M GOING TO NEED YOU TO HAVE
DEMENTIA, CURTIS.
>> I LOVE GETTING TO MAKE AN
IMPACT ON PATIENTS' LIVES.
BEING A NURSE ISN'T EASY, BUT I
WOULDN'T TRADE IT FOR THE WORLD.
>> WE'RE IN CHARGE OF ORGANIZING
THIS MAN'S PILLS, AND HIS PILL
BOX BE LOOKING LIKE AN ADVENT
CALENDAR.
>> ALSO, HE KEEPS DUMPING OUT
HIS PILLS AND REFILLING THE
WHOLE THING WITH VIAGRA.
>> IT'S ALL I NEED.
>> YOU DON'T NEED VIAGRA.
YOU NEED TO MEET JESUS.
CURTIS, IF YOU SEE THE LIGHT, GO
FOR IT.
>> LAST WEEK, HE GAVE HIS REAL
PILLS TO THE EMOTIONAL SUPPORT
DOG FRANKIE.
FRANKIE ALWAYS LIT AS HELL.
>> THERE'S NOTHING LIKE WATCHING
A PATIENT WHO WAS SICK BEAT THE
ODDS AND LEAVE THE HOSPITAL
HAPPY AND HEALTHY.
>> I HAD TO PUT A TUBE IN
CURTIS' PENIS.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
DESCRIBE IT EXCEPT LIKE HAVE YOU
EVER TRIED PUTTING A STRAW
INSIDE ANOTHER STRAW?
>> WEEKS LATER, WE FOUND OUT
CURTIS DIDN'T EVEN NEED A
CATHETER.
HE JUST MADE IT UP BECAUSE HE
WANTED TO SEE HOW IT FEEL.
>> IT FELT BAD.
>> NURSES, THEY'RE THE REAL
HEROES.
MAKE SURE TO SAY THANK YOU.
>> YOU USED TO BANG POTS AND
PANS FOR US, AND THAT WAS REALLY
ANNOYING, BUT YOU ALSO STOPPED
REALLY QUICKLY, WHICH SOMEHOW
FELT WORSE.
>> WE DON'T DO IT FOR THE
RECOGNITION, BUT WE DO
APPRECIATE YOUR GRATITUDE.
>> LISTEN, IF YOU CAN DO ANY
OTHER JOB, DO IT.
>> CLEANING GRAVE WARDS, COAL
MINING, ANY OTHER JOB.
>> UH-OH, LADIES.
MY ICE CREAM FELL.
CLEAN UP ON AISLE ME.
">>> SPRING IS SPRUNG, AND YOU
KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS."
IT'S TIME TO GET YOUR YARD READY
FOR SUMMER.
>> WE'RE STEVE AND SANDY
LANZETTI OF LANZETTI'S LAWN
CARE.
>> MOWING, MULCHING, WEEDING, WE
DO IT ALL, AND NOBODY BEATS OUR
PRICES.
WE GUARANTEE OUR LANDSCAPERS
WILL NOT GET WITH YOUR WIFE.
>> TASTE TALE AS OLD AS TIME.
YOUR WIFE IS BORED, SEES A
HANDSOME YOUNG MAN MOWING THE
LAWN, AND BAM, YOU'RE THE JOKE
OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
WELL, THAT WON'T HAPPEN WITH US.
WHY?
>> BECAUSE WE ONLY HIRE HOPELESS
WILL BE SEXLESS, SOCIALLY
AWKWARD ZEROS.
>> HEY.
>> THEY'RE BUSTED, CORNY, AND
THEY WOULDN'T DREAM OF TAKING
THEIR SHIRT OFF IN FRONT OF A
WOMAN.
>> I WOULD, BUT MY DERM WAS
LIKE, SHIRT STAYS ON.
>> TRUST ME, YOUR WIFE WILL WANT
NOTHING TO DO WITH THESE BOTTOM
FEEDERS.
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT JUST
UNATTRACTIVE, THEY'RE ALSO
SOCIALLY REPELLANT, LIKE GABE
WHO SPEAKS IN EVERY VOICE BUT
HIS OWN.
>> WOW.
THE LAWN LOOKS AMAZING.
>> WHY, THANK YOU.
DOUBLE CUT IT, I DID.
AND WEED WHACKED IT, DUDE.
>> NOBODY'S RUINING THEIR
MARRIAGE FOR THAT.
>> AND THEY DEFINITELY WON'T
RUIN IT FOR DERRICK, WHO PANICS
AROUND WOMEN AND COMES OFF REAL
RUDE.
>> COULD YOU MULCH THE GARDEN
BEFORE --
>> OKAY!
>> OR MAYBE WE'LL SEND CHRIS WHO
LIKES TO DO CRINGY WHAT-IFS.
>> DO YOU THINK THIS AREA IS TOO
SHADY FOR TULIPS?
>> SHADY, SLIM SHADY LIKE WHAT
IF EMINEM IS DOING YOUR
LANDSCAPING AND HE'S ALL TIRED,
ARM SPAGHETTI, MOWING YOUR LAWN
ALREADY.
>> COULD I GROW TULIPS HERE?
>> WHAT IF I SAID NO BUT YOU
ACTUALLY COULD?
>> DUDE!
>> NO MATTER WHO WE SEND, YOUR
WIFE WILL WALK AWAY FROM IT
COMPLETELY SEXUALLY DEAD.
>> IN CASE YOU'RE WONDERING,
THEY'RE NOT MUCH BETTER WITH
GUYS EITHER.
>> DID YOU PUT THE GRASS SEED
DOWN BY THE PATIO?
>> HELL YEAH, DUDE!
>> WE STARTED THIS COMPANY TEN
YEARS AGO AFTER I MADE AN ERROR
IN JUDGMENT.
>> YEP, A 23-YEAR-OLD ERROR
NAMED JASON.
>> IT WAS ONE TIME.
>> YEP, ONE TIME, BT IT HAPPENED
THREE TIMES DURING THAT ONE
TIME.
>> AND I NEVER REPEATED THAT
ERROR AGAIN.
>> NOT WITH JASON, BUT YOU
REPEATED IT WITH DIEGO.
>> AND IT MEANT NOTHING.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU PLANNED TO
KILL ME?
YOU WERE SERIOUS ENOUGH TO BUY A
BARREL THAT YOU DISSOLVE BODIES
IN.
>> I HAD POSTPARTUM DEPRESSION.
>> OUR DAUGHTER WAS IN COLLEGE,
SANDY!
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER BECAUSE I
WON'T MAKE THAT MISTAKE AGAIN,
AND IF YOU GO WITH LANZETTI'S
LAWN CARE THIS SEASON, NEITHER
WILL YOUR WIFE.
LANZETTI'S LAWN CARE WHERE THE
ONLY TEMPTATION --
>> IS OUR LOW PRICES.
>> WHAT
ALL THE MOMS.
THIS BEAUTIFUL BUILDING, LORNE,
AND MY ENTIRE FAMILY HERE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS WAS A FANTASTIC MOTHER'S
DAY PRESENT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
I LOVE YOU!