WEEK
ACCESS
LEAVING
BRIEFING
WITH CREATORS
INSIDE
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH FOR COMING
AND ANSWERING YOUR NATION'S CALL
IN A TIME OF NEED.
>> OH, YEAH, SURE.
>> NO PROB.
TW
>> OUR SCHEDULES ARE ACTUALLY
SUPER FLEXIBLE.
>> AND WE LOVE WHITE HOUSE.
* JASON DERULO *
>> ALSO, I WANT TO THANK MY
PRESS SECRETARY JEN PSAKI FOR
HAVING THE VISION TO SET THIS
UP.
>> I SUGGESTED IT AS A JOKE, AND
THEN IT ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
FIRST
THIS IS TOUGH ON ME BECAUSE
I'M THE LANDLINE OF PRESIDENTS.
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU.
I UNDERSTAND PUTIN.
I UNDERSTAND WAR.
BUT THERE'S ONE THING I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S COMPUTER.
>> HE MEANS TECHNOLOGY BUT HE
SAYS COMPUTER.
>> COMPUTERS ARE ALWAYS VERY
MEAN TO ME.
UPDATE
TURN ON
TYPING
COMPUTER SAY, DID YOU MEAN
MAGENTA?"
>> THE POINT IS WE NEED FRESH
IDEAS FROM YOU GUYS ABOUT HOW WE
CAN WIN THE INFORMATION WAR ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
YES, YOU.
>> HEY, GUYS.
I'M AN ACTRESS FROM THE CW.
>> GREAT, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> ACTRESS FROM THE CW.
AND WHILE PUTIN MAY HAVE TANKS AND BOMBS,
THERE'S SOMETHING
EVEN MORE POWERFUL WE CAN ATTACK
HIM WITH.
POEMS.
>> OH, NO, IT'S THAT GIRL.
>> DEAR VLADAMIR PUTIN,
IF I WAS YOUR MOTHER,
I WOULD LOVE YOU
MORE.
IF I WAS YOUR WIFE,
I WOULD HAVE
BEEN SO, SO, SO MAD AT YOU.
BABY BROTHER
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
DO YOU HAVE ANY ACTUAL USEFUL
SUGGESTIONS?
>> OH, SURE.
HERE ARE FIVE WAYS TO STOP THE
WAR IN UKRAINE.
>> WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
YOU SEE ANYTHING?
>> I THINK SHE'S EXPECTING TECH
TO SHOW UP.
>> OKAY.
HEY, YOU.
WHAT'S YOUR THING?
>> OH, ME?
LET'S JUST SAY I DO RAPS AND
PRANKS.
MAYBE YOU'VE HEARD OF MY SQUAD,
THE BOO-BOO BOYS?
>> I THINK YOU KNOW THE
PRESIDENT HAS NEVER HEARD OF THE
BOO-BOO BOYS.
>> WAIT A SECOND.
THE BOO-BOO BOYS?
DON'T YOU LIVE IN THE YEESH
HOUSE WITH ONE NET KEVIN AND
DUMBASS LARRY?
>> OH-OH, WE GOT A BOO-BOO HEAD!
>> Y'ALL, ONE TIME THEY PRANKED
A WOMAN DOWN FIVE FLIGHTS OF
STAIRS, IT WAS HILARIOUS.
>> WELL, THAT SOUNDS LIKE AN
AMAZING HOBBY.
>> WE MADE $13 MILLION LAST
YEAR.
>> GOD, I HATE THIS WORLD.
AND DID YOU HAVE A PLAN FOR HOW
TO DEFEAT PUTIN?
>> OH, YEAH, I'M COOKING
SOMETHING UP.
>> IS IT PUSHING HIM DOWN A
FLIGHT OF STAIRS?
>> IT IS.
>> GREAT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
* JASON DERULO *
>> YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW THAT'S
YOUR NAME, BUT WHAT DO YOU DO?
* JASON DERULO *
>> I'M SKIPPING YOU, YOU'RE
SKIPPED.
* JASON DER RULE LA *
>> HOW ABOUT YOU, LITTLE GIRL?
GOD, LOOK, YOU'RE INCREDIBLY
CUTE.
>> THANKS.
I DO SILLY ANIMAL MAKEUP FOR
KIDS.
>> WELL, THAT'S ADORABLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK WE CAN DO TO
WIN THIS WAR?
>> OH, YOU MEAN THE ONE STARTED
BY YOUR SON, HUNTER BIDEN.
WHEN HE AND HIS PALS AT BURISMA --
WHERE'S THE LAPTOP,
IS IT IN THIS ROOM?
>> OKAY, THANK YOU, SWEETHEART.
ANIMAL
WHAT ABOUT THIS RANDOM
MIDDLE-AGED GUY?
>> HELLO.
MY NAME IS CHARLES F. D'AMELIO.
I'M A ROOFER FROM PITTSBURGH.
>> OKAY.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I SUSPECT MAYBE THAT YOU HAVE
CONFUSED ME FOR CHARLI D'AMELIO,
THE 17-YEAR-OLD GIRL WITH
130 MILLION FOLLOWERS ON TIKTOK.
>> SOUNDS RIGHT, YEAH.
>> SO I TELL YOU WHAT, I'M JUST
GOING TO HEAD OUT.
BUT FIRST,
DO Y'ALL HAPPEN TO HAVE ONE OF THOSE COVID STIMMY
CHECKS AROUND, BY ANY CHANCE?
>> AFRAID NOT.
>> WE DON'T, I'M SO SORRY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GOOD LUCK WITH THE
WORLD WAR.
NOT WHAT YOU CARE WHAT A ROOFER
THINKS ABOUT PUTIN, BUT
MAYBE
YOU SHOULD PUT SOMEONE UP ON A
ROOF AND --
BAM BAM BAM.
Y'ALL HAVE A GOOD ONE.
THANK
>> GREAT.
IT'S DOWN TO YOU.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WHO, ME?
OH, I JUST GO UP BEHIND PEOPLE ON THE STREET
WITH THIS WEIRD
PIPE AND I GO -- OONGYANGYO!
>> WHAT WOULD YOU DO ABOUT
UKRAINE?
>> I WOULD GO UP BEHIND THE
RUSSIAN TANKS AND GO OONGYANGYO.
>> AND HOW DID YOU GET HERE
TODAY?
>> YOU FLEW ME FIRST CLASS FROM
CALIFORNIA,
AND ON THE PLANE,I
WENT UP THERE TO THE PILOT
AND I
SAID, "OONGYANGYO."
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY BEST PLAN
I'VE HEARD SO FAR.
HEARD
HEY, HEY, SORRY I'M LATE, GUYS.
SECURITY WAS GIVING ME A HARD
TIME.
>> OKAY, THIS IS AWESOME.
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
>> I DO A PUNCH OF INSANE TRICKS
USING A TOILET PLUNGER STUCK TO
MY NIPPLES.
I'M ONE OF THE FAMOUS PEOPLE ON TIKTOK,
IT'S LIKE ME AND
REESE WITHERSPOON.
>> OKAY, WELL WE'RE ACTUALLY
ABOUT TO WRAP THIS MEETING UP
BECAUSE IT WAS CLEARLY A BAD
IDEA.
>> HEY, DON'T DO THAT.
DON'T JUST TEAR THE PLUNGER OFF
THE NIPPLE LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, THE IDEA OF ASKING
TIKTOK STARS HOW TO FIGHT RUSSIA
MIGHT SOUND LIKE A JOKE,
BUT
REMEMBER, THEY SAID THE SAME
THING ABOUT THE RADIO IN WORLD
WAR II.
NEVER UNDERESTIMATE THE
IMPORTANCE OF NEW TECHNOLOGY
AND
YOUNG PEOPLE.
NEVER UNDERSTAND
GIMMICKS
MAY HAVE MORE POWER AND
INFLUENCE THAN THE "NIGHTLY
NEWS."
THAT WAS TRULY INSPIRING, YOUNG
MAN.
>> OH, I'M 55.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I'M
GOING TO GO MOVE THIS PLUNGER TO MY CROTCH,
ATTACH A KNIFE TO THE
END, AND TRY TO SLICE AN APPLE
IN HALF.
GOD BLESS AMERICA!
>> AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL GUEST, ROSALIA
AND YOUR HOST, ZOE KRAVITZ!
LADIES
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT IS SO FANTASTIC TO BE HERE.
I'M YOUR HOST, ZOE KRAVITZ.
I CURRENTLY HAVE A NEW MOVIE OUT
CALLED "THE BATMAN."
CAT
THE CATWOMAN
TO PREPARE FOR THE ROLE, I
WATCHED THE MOVIE MUSICAL "CATS"
EVERY DAY FOR A YEAR.
WHICH IS ACTUALLY HOW I HEARD
JOAQUIN PHOENIX PREPARED TO PLAY
THE JOKER.
>> SOMEONE HERE TALKING ABOUT
CATS?
>> I WAS, YEAH.
I WAS JUST DOING THE MONOLOGUE.
YOU'RE ALSO CATWOMAN?
>> YES.
I'M CATWOMAN FROM THE '90S.
THE ONE WITH THE WHIP.
YOU KNOW.
LIKE CATS HAVE.
SO YOU'RE PART OF A PROUD
LINEAGE OF CATWOMEN,
EACH WITH
OUR OWN ORIGIN STORIES.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW MINE?
>> YEAH, SURE, WHAT'S YOURS?
>> I FELL OUT OF A WINDOW INTO A
PILE OF CATS.
THEY LICKED ME BACK TO LIFE,
AND
NOW IT'S JUST LIKE SANDY FROM A
PORNO VERSION OF "GREASE."
IT'S STILL CALLED "GREASE."
>> COOL.
WELL -- THANK YOU, IT'S REALLY
GREAT TO HAVE A FELLOW CATWOMAN
SUPPORT.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GET BACK TO --
>> HANG ON, WE MUST FIRE UP THE
CAT SIGNAL.
>> I'M SORRY, CAT SIGNAL?
>> YEAH, FOR ANY TIME YOU NEED A
CATWOMAN.
BEHOLD.
I LOVE THAT.
IT'S A NOBLE CAT READY TO POUNCE
OFF THE LEDGE.
>> OR MAYBE IT'S JUST DOING ITS
BIZ IN THE LITTER BOX.
>> I SAW THE SIGNAL, IS SOMEONE
IN DANGER?
TOO
>> INDUBITABLY.
I WAS THE FIRST BLACK CATWOMAN.
>> RIGHT, YES, OF COURSE,
EARTHA KITT FROM THE 1960S TV
VERSION.
>> YEAH, PEOPLE CALLED IT CAMPY,
TURNS OUT IT WAS SUPER GAY.
BE GRATEFUL YOUR OUTFIT ISN'T LATEX
BECAUSE THIS IS HOW I
SNEAK UP ON BAD GUYS.
NICE HAVING ALL THIS CATWOMAN ENERGY UP HERE,
BUT I REALLY
SHOULD GET BACK TO THE
MONOLOGUE.
SO CAN WE TURN OFF THE CAT
SIGNAL BEFORE WE --
>> BEFORE ME?
>> ANOTHER CATWOMAN?
>> YEAH.
YEAH, I'M MORE OF A CAT LADY, I
GUESS.
THIS IS MY HUSBAND.
SORRY CAT,
AND WE'RE HERE TO
MEET ROSALIA.
DO YOU TAKE ME TO HER OR HOW
DOES THAT WORK?
>> I DON'T THINK I CAN DO THAT
RIGHT NOW, I KIND OF HAVE TO
HOST THE SHOW, SO --
>> OH, YEAH.
I GET IT.
YOU KNOW, I HOSTED THE SHOW
DOZENS OF TIMES.
IN MY MIND.
WHERE IT'S CALLED "SATURDAY
NIGHT CATS."
>> NOT "CATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"?
>> DANG IT.
MEET SO MANY CAT -- PEOPLE.
AND NOT THAT I'M NOT LOVING IT,
BUT MAYBE THAT'S ENOUGH, SO
LET'S JUST --
>> EVEN IF THE NEXT ONE WAS DOJA
CAT?
>> OH, MY GOD, IS SHE HERE?
>> NO, BUT THEY WERE ABLE TO GET
ME.
IT IS I, KAT WILLIAMS!
>> COME ON.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN A WOMAN.
>> I AM A LOVER OF WOMEN, MEOW!
AND IF I WANTED TO MEET ROSALIA,
HOW WOULD I DO THAT?
>> SERIOUSLY, IS THERE AN OFF
BUTTON SOMEWHERE?
>> THE CAT SIGNAL BROUGHT US ALL
TOGETHER.
WORLD NEEDS
CAN GET.
NOW LET'S GO FIGHT SOME CRIME,
YES!
>> OKAY.
BEEN TRYING TO SAY.
WHICH IS, WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT.
ROSALIA IS HERE.
STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
>>> I ALWAYS GOT THE SENSE THAT
MATT LOOKED DOWN ON ME, BUT
THAT'S ONLY 'CAUSE HE'S TWO
INCHES TALLER.
NO, BUT I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU,
BUDDY, I LOVE YOU, BRO.
TO MATT AND TANYA, CHEERS!
>> OKAY.
YES, HOW ABOUT A HAND FOR MATT'S
BEST MAN, NATE!
ALL RIGHT!
YAY.
I'M SO SORRY I'M CHEWING, THAT
WAS JUST AN INCREDIBLY SHORT
SPEECH.
IT OPENED WITH THAT "LOOKED DOWN
ON ME" JOKE, AND, IT JUST KIND
OF ENDED A FEW SENTENCES LATER.
SO I WAS SURE IT WOULD BE
LONGER, WHICH IS WHY I TOOK A
BITE OF FOOD, BUT I WAS WRONG.
BUT STILL, A VERY NICE SPEECH
FROM NATE.
OKAY.
NOW LET'S HEAR FROM THE MAID OF
HONOR.
IT'S TANYA'S BEST FRIEND, SARAH,
COME ON UP, SARAH!
>> YEAH!
>> HI, EVERYONE.
I'M SARAH.
UM, MATT, LET ME JUST TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
YOU'RE A REALLY LUCKY GUY.
BECAUSE TANYA IS THE BEST GIRL
IN THE WORLD.
>> AW.
>> I MEAN, THIS GIRL IS LIKE --
>> YES, SHE IS.
>> SHE'S LIKE A SISTER TO ME.
AND NOT JUST BECAUSE WE'VE BOTH
SEEN MY DAD NAKED.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE'S ALWAYS HAD MY BACK.
EVEN WHEN NOBODY ELSE AGREED
WITH ME, SHE ALWAYS SAID,
"SARAH, IF YOU SAY YOU'RE SOBER
ENOUGH TO DRIVE THEN I BELIEVE
YOU."
AND THAT MEANT THE WORLD TO ME,
GIRLIE.
AND WHEN I STUMBLE, WHEN I MAKE
A MISTAKE, SHE'D NEVER MAKE ME
FEEL BAD.
SHE'D SAY, "GIRLIE, DON'T BEAT
YOURSELF UP, NOBODY KNEW THAT
THING WAS LOADED."
>> DID SHE SHOOT SOMEONE?
>> BABE, I'M TRYING TO LISTEN.
>> AND WHEN SHE'S GOING THROUGH
A TOUGH TIME HERSELF, SHE
DOESN'T COMPLAIN, SHE DANCES.
PROFESSIONALLY.
>> WHAT KIND OF DANCING?
>> BABE?
>> LIKE, SHE'S NOT PERFECT.
>> NO WAY.
>> WHAT KIND OF DANCING?
>> SHE HAS BEEN A BIT OF A
BRIDEZILLA, AND NOT JUST BECAUSE
SHE ATTACKED A LOT OF JAPANESE
PEOPLE.
I AM IN AWE OF HER.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL OF YOU,
BUT IF MY LAST 15 BOYFRIENDS
KILLED THEMSELVES, I'D GIVE UP
ON ROMANCE.
BUT NOT TANYA.
>> SHE'S -- SHE'S JOKING, RIGHT?
>> 'CAUSE SHE BELIEVES IN LOVE.
WHEN I STARTED DATING MY
NOW-HUSBAND, SHE WAS SO HAPPY
FOR ME.
EVERYONE ELSE SAID, "YOU'RE A
MONSTER."
BUT WHAT DID YOU SAY, GIRLIE?
>> "YOU'RE NOT A MONSTER, YOU'RE
JUST HIS MATH TEACHER."
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
LOVE IS LOVE, RIGHT, BABY?
>> NO DOUBT.
>> BUT MOST OF ALL, TANYA IS
BRAVE.
GIRLIE, I KNOW YOU REMEMBER
THIS.
WE WERE AT A PROTEST FIGHTING
FOR JUSTICE.
AND YOU GOT RIGHT IN THAT COP'S
FACE.
NO FEAR AT ALL.
AND DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT YOU
SAID?
>> "I'M STORMING THE CAPITOL AND
I'M GOING TO KILL MIKE PENCE."
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND MATT, YOU MAKE HER SO HAPPY.
I DON'T WANT TO EMBARRASS YOU,
BUT WHEN YOU GUYS FIRST GOT
TOGETHER, ME AND TONIA ARE
HAVING SOME GIRL TALK AND I
SAID, YOU KNOW, "HOW'S THE
CHEMISTRY IN THE BEDROOM?"
>> HA, NO, HERE WE GO.
>> AND SHE SAID, "HE'S TRYING
HIS BEST."
AND THAT'S WHAT MAKES MATT
DIFFERENT FROM THE HUNDREDS AND
HUNDREDS OF OTHER GUYS THAT
SHE'S DRAGGED HOME OVER THE
YEARS.
>> HUNDREDS?
>> BABY.
>> AND SURE, MAYBE HE'S NOT
FAMOUS LIKE STEVE-O FROM
JACKASS, OR "WEE MAN" FROM
JACKASS.
MAYBE HE'S NOT MYSTERIOUS, LIKE
BAM MARGERA FROM "JACKASS."
BUT HE PUT IN THE WORK.
LIKE JOHNNY KNOXVILLE, FROM
JACKASS.
>> SO YOU JUST GOT WITH THE
WHOLE "JACKASS" GANG, THEN?
>> HEY HONEY.
I LISTENED TO YOUR FRIEND'S
SPEECH, OKAY?
COME ON.
>> SHE LOVED YOU RIGHT AWAY,
MATT.
AFTER YOUR FIRST DATE SHE SAID,
I MET MY PERSON, AND SHE
DELETED ALL THE DATING APPS.
MATCH, TINDER, CHOKE PONY, TOR
DARK WEB BROWSER, ALL OF THEM.
AT LEAST, I THINK SHE DID.
>> YES, I DID, YOU CAN CHECK MY
PHONE.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE THREE PHONES?
>> SO YEAH, SHE LOVES YOU, MATT.
AND I KNOW WHEN SHE'S FINALLY
ABLE TO GET HER KIDS BACK, THEY
WILL LOVE YOU TOO.
>> WHAT -- WHAT KIDS?
>> AND ALL THOSE KIDS' DADS ARE
GONNA RESPECT YOU.
>> WHAT KIDS AND WHAT DADS?
>> BECAUSE IT'S NOT EVERY MAN
WHO HAS THE COURAGE TO MARRY
SUGE KNIGHT'S EX.
BUT YOU DO, MATT.
YOU DO.
SO CONGRATS, BOTH OF YOU!
CHEERS!
>> CHEERS!
>> LOVE YOU, GIRLIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'M GONNA DIE.
SINCE
NEW WAY TO SHOP
WHERE YOU CAN JUST GRAB AND GO.
IT'S AMAZON GO.
>> GRAB WHAT I WANT AND LEAVE?
>> YEP.
>> WOW.
THAT'S SO EASY.
>> USE THE AMAZON GO APP TO
ENTER, THEN START SHOPPING.
>> THAT'S IT?
>> THAT'S IT.
NO LINES, NO CHECKOUT, NO
PROBLEM.
AT AN AMAZON GO STORE, YOU CAN
WALK IN, GRAB  WHAT YOU WANT,
PUT IT
IN YOUR BAG, AND JUST GO.
>> OH, YOU WANT ME TO JUST TAKE
SOMETHING AND WALK OUT?
NAH, SON.
>> BUT -- IT'S SO CONVENIENT.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NICE TRY.
>> WE KNOW SOME PEOPLE ARE
SKEPTICAL.
>> SOME PEOPLE?
>> WELL, HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
WE USE COMPUTER VISION.
>> UH-HUH?
>> DEEP LEARNING ALGORITHMS.
AND SENSOR FUSION.
>> OH, OKAY.
SO IT'S A TRAP.
SO WHERE DO YOU PAY?
>> THERE'S NO REGISTER.
IT ALL HAPPENS WITH OUR OF GRAB
AND GO TECHNOLOGY.
>> BUT WHERE DO YOU PAY?
>> YOU DON'T.
>> NO, I DO.
I ALWAYS PAY, OKAY?
WHO DO YOU THINK I AM?
>> IT'S SIMPLE.
TAKE WHAT YOU WANT.
PUT IT IN YOUR OWN BAG.
AND WALK OUT.
AND WE HAVE EVERYTHING YOU LOVE.
>> OH, HEY, THEY HAVE MY
FAVORITE BRAND OF KOMBUCHA.
>> OH, IT'S GREAT, YOU SHOULD
GRAB IT.
>> SURE.
CAN YOU GRAB IT?
>> ME?
NO, JUST GRAB IT.
>> YOU SHOULD PICK IT UP.
>> BABE, IT'S FINE.
>> PICK IT UP.
>> I'M LEARNING.
>> IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND, JUST
PUT IT BACK.
OUR TECHNOLOGY WILL UPDATE YOUR
VIRTUAL CART INSTANTLY.
>> OKAY, I AM -- PUTTING THE
SANDWICH BACK, YOU ALL!
I HAVE DECIDED TO GET A
DIFFERENT SANDWICH TODAY!
I GOT NO MORE SANDWICHES NOW!
>> SO GET YOUR PURCHASE AND GO.
>> GO AHEAD, LEAVE.
JUST WALK OUT.
>> HERE I GO.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT,
YOU'VE ALREADY PAID.
>> WELL, THEN -- IT'S A TIP.
IT'S A TIP!
>> THEY'RE TRYING TO TRICK ME
HERE WE GO, I TOLD YOU.
>> IT'S JUST NOTIFYING YOU OF
YOUR RECEIPTS.
>> IT WAS HIM!
ALEXA. SEARCH
AMAZON GO BLACK MAN TRAP
AMAZON GO.
NO LINE, NO CHECKOUT.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
>> IT'S A DAMN TRAP.
>>> THANKS AGAIN FOR BRINGING
OVER MY CALCULATOR.
SORRY, I FORGOT IT IN STUDY
HALL.
>> OH, IT'S MY PLEASURE.
WELL, MY MOTHER'S RUNNING LATE
SO I'LL JUST STAND BY THE
MAILBOX AND WAIT TO BE
RETRIEVED.
>> NO, JOSH -- YOU CAN WAIT
HERE.
COME SIT.
>> OVER HERE?
OKAY.
WOW.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY IT'S BEEN
REALLY GREAT BEING IN MATH CLASS
WITH YOU.
>> CASSIE, I WOULD HAVE TO
RETURN THE SENTIMENT.
>> I LOVE HOW YOU DO IMPRESSIONS
FROM THE CHARACTERS FROM
FRASIER.
>> OH.
THE NILES CAME QUICK.
I'M STILL WORKING AT MY RAW.
>> TOTALLY.
ANYWAY, I JUST WANTED TO SAY,
I'M GLAD YOUR MOM IS LATE.
>> GLAD, YOU SAY?
WOW.
>> YEAH.
REALLY GLAD.
>> TOOT, TOOT.
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME FOR A
MOMENT?
BECAUSE I'M GETTING MY -- A CALL
FROM MY SCHWAB AGENT HERE.
JUST ONE SECOND.
HI.
IS MY B-F-F, JASON, THERE?
YES, I'LL HOLD.
>> HELLO, YOU HAVE JASON.
>> HI, JASON?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE WHAT
I'M ABOUT TO TELL YOU.
I AM SITTING EXCEEDINGLY CLOSE
TO THE HILLARY DUFF OF OUR
ALGEBRA CLASS.
>> I AM SITTING ON NEXT TO HER
ON THE EDGE.
>> AND WHAT IS SHE DOING?
>> SHE'S LOOKING AT ME.
>> MY FRIEND, WE FIND OURSELVES
IN CHOPPY WATERS.
WE NEED TAKE HER BREATH AWAY.
SO PERHAPS WHISPER A SECRET IN
HER EAR, AND DO IT SENSUALLY.
>> YES.
PLEASE HOLD.
TROMBONE.
>> WOW, THANKS FOR TELLING ME
THAT.
I FEEL LIKE I KNOW YOU BETTER.
>> OKAY, THAT WENT SHOCKINGLY
WELL.
>> GOOD NEWS, OLD CHAP.
NOW TIME TO IMPRESS HER.
TELL HER A RECENT
ACCOMPLISHMENT.
>> RIGHTO.
CASSIE, YOU KNOW, MY -- MY
PARENTS SAID I WAS VERY
EMOTIONALLY MATURE WHEN WE PUT
DOWN MY TURTLE.
>> OH, WELL, AT LEAST HE DIDN'T
SUFFER.
>> WELL, HE ACTUALLY DID, THE
DOCTOR DIDN'T HIT HIM IN THE
RIGHT SPOT.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE REALLY
STRONG.
>> JASON, AGAINST ALL ODDS, I AM
CONTINUING TO CRUSH.
>> WITH MY ADVICE, I CAN'T FEIGN
SURPRISE.
BUT YOU NEED TO FIND OUT IF SHE
IS AVAILABLE.
>> YES, YES.
PLEASE HOLD.
CASSIE, ARE YOU CURRENTLY DATING
ANYONE?
>> NO, I'M DONE WITH JOCKS.
I LIKE QUIET GUYS.
OR, ACTUALLY, GIRLS TOO.
>> UNLESS MY BRAIN SHORT
CIRCUITED, WE HAVE A MODERN
WOMAN ON OUR HANDS.
>> GOOD.
THEN LET'S UP THE ROMANCE.
ACT LIKE YOU'RE IN A MOVIE AND
WIPE AN EYELASH FROM HER FACE.
>> OKAY, BRILLIANT.
STAND BY, PLEASE.
OKAY, I DID IT.
>> WELL, HOW DID IT GO?
>> I DIDN'T TELL HER THAT'S WHAT
I WAS DOING, SO I'M NOT SURE.
>> DANG, I KNEW THE EYELASH WAS
A TYPO.
>> CAN I PUT MY HEAD ON YOUR
SHOULDER?
>> SHOULDER.
>> CALL ATTENTION TO YOUR KNEE
SO SHE KNOW IT'S THERE.
NOW, IF SHE LIKED, SHE MAY TOUCH
IT WITH HER OWN.
>> OKAY, WE HAVE CONTACT.
THE KNEE.
WE ARE AFFIRMATIVE.
PATELAU ON PATELAU AND I CAN
FEEL MY PEN IN MY HEAD.
>> THIS IS OFFICIALLY ABOVE MY
PAY GRADE.
>> YOU HAVE TO STAY WITH ME.
THE STAKES ARE LIFE AND DEATH.
>> WELL, CHECK FOR SHOULDER
DEMEANOR.
STIFF OR LOOSE?
>> I'M CHECKING, REMAIN ON THE
LINE, PLEASE.
OH, DEAR GOD, SHE'S MET MY GAZE.
WE'RE LOOKING AT EACH OTHER,
WE'RE SHARING BREATH, WE'RE
BECOMING SOULMATES.
AND YET, I FEEL AFRAID.
NOT OF LOVE BUT OF LOSING YOU,
>> NAY, SAVOR THIS, MY GOOD MAN.
'TIS THE SPICE OF LIFE.
>> HEY, CAN -- CAN WE KISS NOW?
>> YOU HEARD THE WOMAN.
I'LL SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE.
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING DISNEY MINUS,
THE MOVIES DISNEY DOESN'T
PROMOTE AS MUCH.
FROG
* TALE AS OLD AS '09
TAKES PLACE IN A BAR *
* PRINCESS FINALLY BLACK
WHY THE PLOT SO WHACK
PRINCESS AND THE FROG *
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS, BUT I THINK I'VE FALLEN IN
LOVE.
WITH A FROG.
>> I KNOW, IT'S CRAZY, RIGHT?
I'M LIKE THIS FROG, YOU'RE LIKE
THIS PRINCESS.
BUT I GUESS IT'S TRUE WHAT THEY
SAY.
LOVE IS LOVE IS LOVE.
I HOPE I'M NOT BEING TOO
FORWARD, TIANA, BUT WILL YOU
KISS ME?
>> OF COURSE I WILL.
BECAUSE LOVE CONQUERS ALL.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU LOVE ME FOR ME.
YOU DON'T CARE THAT I'M A FROG
AND FROGS DON'T HAVE PENISES.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> IT'S JUST A SCIENTIFIC FACT.
FROGS DON'T HAVE PENS.
AND THAT'S WHY I LOVE YOU.
>> AND THAT'S JUST SOMETHING
EVERYBODY KNOWS?
IT'S ONE OF THE FIRST THINGS
THAT COMES UP WHEN YOU GOOGLE
FROG PENIS.
YOU KNOW WHAT LET'S JUST KISS
AND GET MARRIED AND WE'LL TACKLE
THE WHOLE NO PENIS THING LATER.
>> SORRY.
JUST -- SO IF YOU DON'T HAVE A
PENIS, WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
>> OH, IT'S EVERY WOMAN'S DREAM.
I GOT BALLS THAT JUST SHOOT
STUFF DIRECTLY ON YOU.
NO PESKY PENIS GETTING IN THE
WAY.
>> OH, WOW.
>> IT'S LIKE THEY ALWAYS SAY.
WHO NEEDS A STRAW WHEN I CAN
JUST THROW THE MILKSHAKE IN YOUR
FACE?
HOW ABOUT THAT KISS?
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW -- I MIGHT
HAVE TO RETHINK THIS A BIT.
>> OH, COME ON.
SIZE DOESN'T MATTER.
>> I THINK IT DOES WHEN IT'S
ZERO.
HOW DO YOU EVEN HAVE SEX?
>> OH, I'LL EXPLAIN IN GREAT
DETAIL.
YOU SEE, I CLIMB ON YOUR BACK
AND I WRAP MY FORELIMBS AROUND
YOUR BODY, THEN I STAY THERE
ABOUT TWO DAYS AND CROAK LOUDLY
IN YOUR EAR UNTIL YOU LAY YOUR
EGGS.
HOW MANY EGGS DO YOU TYPICALLY
LAY?
>> I DON'T LAY EGGS.
>> OH, THAT COULD BE A DEAL
BREAKER.
>> YOU KNOW THIS NEVER CAME UP
WHEN WE DISSECTED FROGS IN HIGH
SCHOOL.
>> WHAT?
>> DR. FACILIER, THE VOODOO
WITCH DOCTOR FROM THIS MOVIE.
>> SO, IF I KISS THIS FROG,
HE'LL TRANSFORM INTO A PRINCE?
>> ONLY IF IT'S TRUE LOVE.
>> UH-HUH?
UH-HUH?
AND WHAT WOULD HAPPEN WITH
HIS -- PENIS?
>> HIS PENIS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, APPARENTLY FROGS DON'T
HAVE THEM.
>> THE HELL?
WELL, THEN, HOW DO THEY --
>> IT JUST SHOOTS UP THE NUTS.
>> ON THE PLUS SIDE, I CAN DO
ORAL FROM LIKE FIVE FEET AWAY.
>> WELL.
I GUESS IF HE CHANGED BACK TO
BEING A HUMAN, HE WOULD GET HIS
PENIS BACK.
>> THEN LET'S DO IT!
LET'S KISS AND JOIN OUR SOULS
FOREVER!
>> AND WHAT IF I DIDN'T HAVE A
PENIS BEFORE?
>> WHAT?
>> I MEAN, AS A HUMAN, BEFORE
THE CURSE.
WHAT IF I, HYPOTHETICALLY, GOT
RIPPED CLEAN OFF AT A BOWLING
ALLEY?
IF SHE KISSED, WOULD IT GROW
BACK?
>> A BOWLING ALLEY?
>> I TRIED TO HUMP THE BALL
RETURN MACHINE, AS A JOKE.
CLEAN OFF.
>> STOP SAYING CLEAN OFF.
>> IF YOU SAW IT, YOU'D AGREE.
>> YOU ARE A WEIRD FROG, DUDE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON WITH YOU.
BUT AT LEAST YOU'RE A PRINCE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE PRINCE OF NEWARK,
NEW JERSEY.
>> OKAY.
I'M -- I'M OUT.
>> YEAH, EVEN FOR VOODOO, THIS
IS MESSED UP.
* IT'S NOT EASY BEING GREEN
IT'S ABOUT TIME I INTRODUCED
MYSELF.
MY NAME RAYMOND.
BUT EVERYBODY CALLS ME RAY.
I'M THE CAJUN FIREFLY IN THE
MOVIE.
WHICH THAT'S WRONG.
AND CRITICALLY, I MIGHT BE JUST
ABOUT THE WORST DISNEY CHARACTER
EVER CREATED.
DISNEY ASKED KIDS LEAVING THE
MOVIE, "WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
OLD RAY?"
EVERY KID SAY, "KILL HIM.
WE DON'T WANT TO SEE RAY NO
PLACE, NO WHERE, NEVER AGAIN."
ON TIME, THEY INVITE OLD RAY TO
ONE OF THEY CHARACTER BREAKFASTS
OVER AT THE DISNEY WORLD.
THEY GIVE KIDS METAL BATS, SAY
"GO GET HIM.
GO KILL OLD RAY TILL HE'S DEAD!"
BUT DON'T WORRY, AT THE END OF
THE DAY, OLD RAY GOING TO BE
JUST FINE.
AAYOUR HONOR!
>> THE END.
>>> OH!
>> LOOK HOW CUTE SHE IS.
>> THIS IS SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
GETTING CATWOMAN A CAT?
>> YEAH, THAT'S A PERFECT GIFT.
>> PLUS, IT'S LIKE --
>> TRULY CLASSIC, YEAH.
>> OH, CUTE CAT.
ZOE'S HERE TO SEE YOU.
>> OH, YEAH, SEND HER ON IN.
>> HEY, ZOE, THEY'RE READY FOR
YOU.
>> OKAY, GREAT, THANKS.
HEY, GUYS.
>> WE LOST THE CAT!
>> WHAT?
>> SHUT THE DOOR, ZOE!
SHUT THE DOOR!
>> SHUT IT, SHUT IT!
CLOSE IT!
>> WAIT, WHAT?
>> IS THAT ALL YOU CAN SAY?
HELP US FIND YOUR GIFT.
>> WHY DID YOU BUY ME A CAT?
>> WE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE FUNNY
TO GET CATWOMAN A WARMING CAT.
>> IT'S CLASSIC.
>> IT'S ENTERTAINING, OKAY?
WE GOT ANT-MAN A MAN ANT.
>> COME ON.
>> WAIT, STOP, NO.
STOP.
THIS IS INSANE.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE CAT'S NAME IS SNUGGLEBUCKET
AND IT LOOKS LIKE THIS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
LET'S FIND THE [ BLEEP ] CAT.
>> NOT UNDER THERE.
>> I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM!
>> OH, NO, THAT'S BAND.
>> IT'S OKAY, JUST KEEP LOOKING.
>> GOD, WHY DID WE ASK FOR THE
SMALLEST INFECTED CAT THEY HAD?
>> MAN, IS IT IN YOUR DESK?
>> NO, IT'S JUST A STUPID DOG.
>> OH!
>> GOD, CHECK THE SHELF!
>> CHECKING THE SHELF!
NOT ON THE SHELF.
>> YAY!
>> OH, MY GOD, I FOUND HER.
>> THANK GOD.
>> OH, SWEETIE.
YOU LOOK SCARED.
>> BUT THE GOOD THING IS, WE
FOUND HER.
>> WAIT, WHERE DID THE CAT GO?
>> NO!
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> ANYTHING UNDER THE COUCHMART?
>> JUST SOME CRUMBS, A COIN, AND
A MAN.
>> WHAT?
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> PAUL DANO?!
>> LAME.
>> PAUL, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> GOSH.
I'M SORRY, I'VE BEEN LIVING DOWN
THERE, RESEARCHING A NEW MOVIE
ABOUT THREE GUYS WHO SUCK.
COME ON, MAN.
IT'S LIKE YOU GUYS.
I PLAY BEN.
>> IT'S JUST SO CRAZY, MAN.
LIKE, EVERYTHING --
>> THE CAT!
>> IT'S GONE!
>> WAS I PETTING IT?
>> I'M CHECKING OUR STATS.
THEY DON'T SEE IT.
>> DAMN.
>> SEAN, FIND HIM!
>> HEY, GUYS, I FOUND THE CAT.
>> BUY, GUYS.
WHAT A CRAZY ADVENTURE WE HAD.
>> I'M GOING TO MISS THAT CRAZY
CAT.
>> I'LL MISS YOU, DUDE.
>> NO!!!!!
>>> ALL RIGHT.
I PUT ALL THE FOOD AWAY, AND NOW
MY KITCHEN IS CLEAN.
PLEASE NOBODY GO IN THERE AND
MESS IT UP.
>> YES, MOM.
>> NOW, WHAT ARE YOU ALL
WATCHING?
>> SOME OLD HOME MOVIES?
>> WAIT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HEY, KIDS, IT'S ME, DADDY.
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS, THAT
MEANS I'M ALREADY DEAD.
>> WHAT?
WHERE'S DAD?
>> HE'S UPSTAIRS ON THE TOILET.
>> WHERE DID YOU FIND THIS TAPE?
>> NOW I HID THIS TAPE IN A BOX
LABELED "FOOTBALL HIGHLIGHTS" SO
YOUR MAMA WOULDN'T WATCH IT.
THERE'S SO MUCH THAT I WANT TO
TELL YOU KIDS.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TURN THIS OFF.
>> SHH, I WANT TO HEAR THIS.
>> OKAY, SO BY NOW THE LAWYERS
HAVE PROBABLY INFORMED YOU THAT
I AM FLAT BROKE.
>> BROKE?
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED TO OUR
SAVINGS?
>> I WAS TOO EMBARRASSED TO SAY
ANYTHING.
NO MAN WANTS TO HAVE TO TELL HIS
FAMILY, "I BLEW MY WHOLE
RETIREMENT ON JB SMOOVE'S NEW
SPORT BETTING APP."
>> ALREADY?
I JUST DOWNLOADED THAT FROM HIM
LAST WEEK.
>> WALTER, GET IN HERE!
>> NO, MOM, WE CAN'T LET DADDY
KNOW WE SAW THIS.
IT WILL EMBARRASS HIM.
>> AYE, NOW, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
MY FUNERAL.
>> ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS PAY FOR
IT.
>> NO IDEA WHAT TOOK ME OUT.
COULD HAVE BEEN THE RONA,
MAYBE BECAUSE I HAVEN'T HAD A
GLASS OF WATER SINCE 2003.
COULD HAVE BEEN JB SMOOVE COMING
TO COLLECT.
>> IS THAT A TOILET?
>> TURN THIS OFF.
DAD MUST BE COMING DOWN.
>> THAT WAS -- THAT WAS ONLY HIS
FIRST FLUSH, WE GOT ABOUT
20 MINUTES.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT ELSE, WHAT
ELSE?
OH, I ALSO HAVE A SECRET
DAUGHTER.
SHE PROBABLY BE AT MY FUNERAL
>> NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT HOW YOU THINK.
I WOULD NEVER CHEAT ON YOUR
MOTHER RAW.
>> EWW.
>> TRUTH IS, I WAS A SPERM DONOR
BACK IN THE DAY.
YEAH, BUT I NEVER WOULD HAVE
DONE THAT HAD I KNOWN THAT THEY
WAS GOING TO USE IT TO MAKE
BABIES.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK THEY WERE
GOING TO USE IT FOR?
>> AND TO MY ONLY SON,
WALTER JR.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE FOR PASSING
DOWN THE ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION.
>> EWW!
>> WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE THAT.
>> YOU MAY NOT HAVE IT RIGHT
NOW.
BUT YOU DEFINITELY WILL.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE MY SON,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
SO I'M LEAVING YOU THIS HERE
SPECIAL PUMP.
I PUT THE GOOGLY EYES SO IT SO
THE GIRLS WON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
NOW -- IT MAY NOT GET YOU ALL
THE WAY THERE.
BUT CERTAINLY, IT WILL GET YOU
CLOSE ENOUGH.
>> CAN YOU FAST FORWARD PAST
THIS PART?
>> LOOK.
MAYBE I WASN'T THE BEST DAD.
OR THE BEST HUSBAND.
BUT I WANT YOU KIDS TO KNOW I
TRIED MY VERY BEST.
TO WRITE THE GREATEST CRIME
DRAMA HOLLYWOOD HAS EVER SEEN.
>> CRIME DRAMA?
>> DAD WROTE A MOVIE?
>> IT'S CALLED "DALLAS CITY
BOUNCERS."
>> WHAT THE HELL IS "DALLAS CITY
BOUNCERS"?
>> OH GOD, NOT THIS STUPID
MOVIE.
>> OPEN ON WINDY DALLAS NIGHT.
LONE SAXOPHONE CRIES OUT IN THE
DISTANCE.
CAMERA REVEALS DETECTIVE
RICO TREMAINE, PLAYED BY THE
BROTHER FROM "DJANGO UNCHAINED,"
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
>> JAMIE FOXX.
>> YOU KNOW, THE MAIN BROTHER,
THE ONE THAT PLAYED RAY.
>> JAMIE FOXX.
>> HE WAS ON "THE JAMIE FOXX
SHOW."
YOU KNOW, I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
MAIN GUY.
>> JAMIE FOXX!
>> YOU KNOW, I CAN'T WITH THIS
MAN.
JUST FAST FORWARD PAST THIS
MOVIE IDEA, PLEASE.
>> YOU KNOW, WITH THE MONEY FROM
THE DVD SALES, YOU SHOULD BE
ABLE TO PAY BACK JB SMOOVE ONCE
AND FOR ALL.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE SHOWER.
>> I THINK WE HAVE MORE TIME.
PRESS PLAY.
>>, WANT YOU KIDS TO
GIVE THIS IMPORTANT MESSAGE TO
YOUR MOTHER FOR ME.
>> NO, WHAT, HOLD ON NOW, I WANT
TO HEAR THIS.
>> BABY, WHEN I MET YOU, YOU
WERE THE SMARTEST, MOST
BEAUTIFUL GIRL AT THE DISCO.
AND I WAS JUST SOME LONELY
BACKUP SINGER FOR THE
COMMODORES.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU, I WAS
NEVER A BACKUP SINGER FOR THE
COMMODORES.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOUR FATHER
LIED TO ME.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE GAVE ME
EREC TILE DYSFUNCTION.
>> I HAVE SOMETHING VALUABLE IN
A TOP SECRET LOCATION.
BUT BEFORE THAT, LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT "DALLAS CITY DANCERS 2,
RICO'S REVENGE"
>> JUST FAST FORWARD.
>> WHAT'S HIS NAME?
HE SINGZ R&B TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
*
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
ROSALIA.
**
>> ROSALIA!
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> COLIN JOST.
>> THIS WEEK MARKS TWO YEARS
SINCE THE BEGINNING OF THE FIRST
COVID LOCKDOWN AND LET'S JUST
SAY SOME PEOPLE HAVE HANDLED THE
STRESS BETTER THAN OTHERS.
RUSSIA HAS PASSED A FAKE NEWS
LAW THAT MAKES IT ILLEGEL FOR
ANY ORGANIZATION TO REPORT
INFORMATION THAT CONTRADICTS
WHAT THE GOVERNMENT SAYS.
WHICH EXPLAINS THE RECENT
HEADLINE, "BELOVED 6'5" PUTIN
HAS NOT GONE INSANE."
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN DOWN PLAYED
THE POSSIBILITY OF MILITARY
INTERVENTION, SAYING WE WILL NOT
FIGHT THE THIRD WORLD WAR.
WHICH I GET ON A POLITICAL
TO WATCH PUTIN BOMBING THINGS
LIKE SCHOOLS, A MATERNITY AWARD,
I'M JUST GOING TO ASSUME, PUPPY
DAYCARE CENTERS, AND NOT FEEL
ANYTHING.
THIS SITUATION HAS GOTTEN SO
UPSETTING I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT
MARCHING DOWN TO THE NEAREST
ARMY ENLISTMENT OFFICE AND
SIGNING CHE UP.
>> AFTER THE U.S. BAN ON RUSSIAN
OIL, GAS PRICES HIT A RECORD
HIGH OF $4.30.
WHICH IS SO EXPENSIVE, THAT WE
MIGHT HAVE TO MOVE BACK IN WITH
OUR EX.
COME ON, IRAQ.
YOU KNOW WE NEVER STOPPED LOVING
YOU, BABY.
RESPONDING TO SANCTIONS BY
BANNING THE EXPORT OF
RUSSIAN-MADE CARS.
BUT A RUSSIAN-MADE CAR IS JUST A
DRUNK BEAR ON ROLLER SKATES.
>> STARBUCKS HAS RESPONDED BY
SHUTTING DOWN LOCATIONS IN
RUSSIA, IN HOPES OF SENDING A
MESSAGE TO PRESIDENT VANDER PUMP
RENKEN?
>> AFTER McDONALD'S ANNOUNCED IT
WOULD STOP DOING BUSINESS IN THE
COUNTRY, RUSSIANS HAVE BEGUN
HOARDING THEIR SANDWICHES,
INCLUDING SOME HONORARY
RUSSIANS.
>>> CONGRESS PASSED A BILL THAT
MAKES LYNCHING A A FEDERAL HATE
CRIME PUNISHABLE BY UP TO 30
YEARS IN PRISON.
AND THEY'RE NOT MESSING AROUND.
YOU CAN GET 150 DAYS FOR JUST
MAKING ONE UP.
>>> DISNEY EMPLOYEES WERE UPSET
THAT THE COMPANY TOOK SO LONG TO
CONDEMN FLORIDA'S PROPOSED
DON'T SAY GAY BILL.
ALTHOUGH AT DISNEY, THEY
ACTUALLY DON'T SAY GAY, THEY SAY
TIMON M'PUMBAA.
>> FLORIDA GOVERNOR RON DESANTIS
SEEN HERE WAVING COVID INTO THE
CLUB ATTACKED DISNEY FOR
OPPOSING THE STATE'S DON'T SAY
GAY BILL, CALLING THE COMPANY A
WOKE CORPORATION.
DISNEY DENIED THE CLAIMS OF
WOKENESS WITH ROUGHLY 90 YEARS
OF CARTOONS.
HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST NIGHT IS
FILM CRITIC HARRY PINK.
>>.
>> MR. JOST, IT'S A PRIVILEGE TO
BE BACK, MY SIR.
>> I UNDERSTAND YOU'VE SEEN
EVERY FILM UP FOR AN OSCAR THIS
YEAR.
AM I RIGHT?
>> BINGO.
AND EVERY FILM NOT NOMINATED
TOO.
IT'S BEEN ONE HECK OF A 48
HOURS.
>> YOU WATCHED EVERY SINGLE
MOVIE FROM THIS YEAR IN THE LAST
TWO DAYS?
>> YEAH?
>> AND HOW IS THAT EVEN
POSSIBLE?
>> THERE THANKS TO A LITTLE
MULTIVITAMIN I TAKE CALLED LSD.
LSD HELPS ME LSD ALL THESE
TERRIFIC.
FIRST UP, MY PICK FOR BEST FLICK
IS "POWER OF THE DOG."
WHO LET THE DOG OUT OF THE
CLOSET?
THAT'S THE QUESTION POSED BY
DIRECTOR JANE CAMPION IN THIS
HYSTERICAL GAY WESTERN.
BENEDICT CUMBERBATCH RIDES HIGH
AS THE TITULAR DOG THE BOUNTY
HUNTER, THAT IS, UNTIL BIZARRELY
STEPPING THROUGH THE SCREEN TO
MAKE FUN OF MY UNDIES IN THE
VOICE OF MY MIDDLE SCHOOL
BULLIES.
ASIDE FROM THAT, IT'S THE BEST
MOVIE I'VE EVER SEEN.
COLIN?
>> "POWER OF THE DOG" ISN'T
ABOUT DOG THE BOUNTY HUNTER.
AND YOU REALIZE LSD ISN'T A
VITAMIN, IT'S A HALLUCINOGEN.
>> YOU SAY TUMOTTO, I SAY --
ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP, ANIMATION.
RHYTHMIC FUN FOR THE WHOLE
FAMILIA, "ENCANTO" FEELS WORSE
THAN BEING ON FIRE.
HAND-DRAWN BY LEGENDARY AUTEUR
THE ZODIAC KILLER, THIS ALL GRAY
THROBBING STRESS DREAM DOES DRAG
IN SPOTS.
BUT LOCAL GANGSTER RAPPER
LIN-MANUEL SAMANTHA SAVES THE
DAY ONCE AGAIN WITH HIS CATCHY
HIT "12 HOURS OF SCREAMING."
CATCHY TUNE.
THIS FILM WARMED MY HEART, BROKE
MY BRAIN, DILATED MY PUPILS TO
THE SIZE OF PIE PLATES, THEN
STOLE MY KIDNEY AND SOLD IT FOR
DOGECOIN.
I GIVE "ENCANTO" 10 TINY
TERRIFIED TERRYS.
MR. PRESIDENT?
>> OH, MAN.
I'M REALLY STARTING TO WORRY
ABOUT YOU, TERRY.
>> AND I'M STARTING TO WORRY
THERE IS NO TERRY.
>> OKAY.
>>> NEXT UP, MY PICK FOR BEST
ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY, KENNETH
BRANAGH'S
BELFAST.
JOHNNY KNOXVILLE AND HIS MERRY
BAND OF IDIOTS FLOP AROUND TOWN
AND TORTURE EACH OTHER'S BALLS
IN THIS TROUBLED-ERA TEAR
JERKER.
BUT IT'S DAME JUDI DENCH WHO
LITERALLY SOARS AS WEE-MAN SHOT
OUT OF A CANNON INTO MY OPEN
MOUTH, YUMMERS!
I COULDN'T START LAUGHING OR
CRYING OR DOING THE NAY-NAY
UNTIL I WAS FORCIBLY REMOVED BY
REGAL CINEMA'S STRONGEST TEAM.
I GIVE "JACKASS BELFAST" 40
TWERKING TICKLISH TERRYS.
TERRY?
>> YOU ARE TERRY.
>> AND YOU'RE A WONDERFUL
FRIEND.
>> TERRY FINK, EVERYONE.
>> I'M GOING TO DO IT, YEAH.
SOME DAY.
HIGHLIGHTING WEALTHY BLACK
FAMILIES THAT LIVED IN NEW YORK
IN THE LATE 1800S, UNTIL THEY
WERE DRIVEN OUT BY WEALTHY
INDUSTRIALIST COLIN JOST THE
FIRST.
>> NOT TRUE.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT QUEEN
ELIZABETH II HAD MOVED OUT OF
BUCKINGHAM PALACE AND, THIS IS
WEIRD, IN WITH JOHN MAYOR.
INCLUDE JOHN TRAVOLTA AND AS
TRAVOLTA CALLED HER, THE
WICKEDLY TALENTED LUCRICIA.
METH USERS MET ONLINE TO USE THE
DRUG TOGETHER ON A METH USER ACT
CALLED TOOTH GRINDER.
GET IT.
>> THEY WOULD NAME RIVERS AND
LANDMARKS THAT USE A RACIAL SLUR
FORINATE AIVE AMERICAN WOMEN.
WOW.
SO WE CHANGE THOSE NAMES BUT
THEY CAN STILL JUST CALL A
RESTAURANT CRACKER BARREL?
>> TUESDAY WAS INTERNATIONAL
WOMEN'S DAY.
SO, HOPEFULLY YOU REMEMBERED TO
SMILE.
>> SCIENTISTS ARE SAYING THAT BY
USING NEW GENE-EDITING
TECHNOLOGY, THEY COULD BRING
BACK THE EXTINCT CHRISTMAS
ISLAND RAT.
OR NOT.
THE OTHER OPTION IS NOT.
>> A VIDEO HAS GONE VIRAL OF A
MAN URINATING ON A NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY WHILE OTHER PASA CHGERS
APPEAR NOT TO CARE.
THEY WERE PROBABLY TOO NERVES TO
SAY SOMETHING BECAUSE I'M ON TV.
>> AND AN ASSISTANT PRINCIPAL IN
MISSISSIPPI WAS FIRED AFTER HE
READ THE CLASS A CHILDREN'S
BOOK, "I NEED A NEW BUT."
IT'S ABOUT A LOVABLE RABBIT WHO
JUST ATE AT CHIPOTLE.
UNHAPPY AND INSECURE ABOUT THEIR
LIVES.
HERE TO TALK IS LIFESTYLE
INFLUENCER.
>> SO, DAN, YOU'RE SUPER RICH
AND SHOW OFF YOUR CRAZY LIFE ON
INSTAGRAM, RIGHT?
>> SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
IT'S ON BASICALLY LIFE, STRAIGHT
UP.
LIFE.
PARTY'S ON.
BABES EVERYWHERE, SNOWBOARDING
WITH, LIKE, A BEZOOKAU.
MY LIFE IS INSANE.
>> YEAH, THAT'S COOL, MAP.
>> ASK ME HOW MANY GIRLS I'M
DATING RIGHT NOW.
>> HOW MANY GIRLS ARE YOU?
>> 940.
>> OKAY, COOL, MAN.
>> IT IS COOL, I AGREE.
OVER 900 GIRLS, I GOT THE NEW
BOOK.
WHY IS WRITING SO EASY?
YOU JUST HAVE TO PASS IT OUT.
>> YOU'RE WRITING A BOOK?
>> YEAH, MAN.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE HEMMINGWAY BUT
FOR GUYS.
>> WRITING ABOUT MY STRUGGLES
WITH SHIRTS.
>> BLOWING CROWDS AND CHANGING
THE WORLD THROUGH POSITIVITY.
IT'S CALLED AS BOOK.
>> THAT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
HOW DO YOU STAY SO DOWN TO
EARTH?
>> LET ME PUT IT THIS WAY.
YOU KNOW THE ANCIENT STORY A OF
THE FARMER AND THE CROW?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK I DO.
>> FARMER HAS THREE DOGS.
FARMER SAYS NO.
SECOND FARMER GOES YES, I SAW A
CROW.
DADDY SAYS NAAA.
THEN TO AN OLD MADE AND THE
FIRST GIRL -- UM.
I'M TRYING TO REMEMBER.
>> HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT, MAN?
>> YEAH, THE POINT OF THE STORY
IS, LIKE, EVERYTHING IS JUST
INSANE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S IT?
>> I THINK SO.
>> NO.
>> MY LIFE'S CRAZY.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
GOODNIGHT.
REMEMBER HOW RICHARD DAWSON
WOULD KISS ENTIRE FAMILIES?
WELL, YOU DO NOW.
BUT FIRST, IT'S "WORD CRUNCH."
>> WELCOME BACK TO "WORD
CRUNCH."
I'M YOUR HOST, GENE BABY.
SAY HELLO TO OUR CONTESTANTS,
CARA, SHEILA, AND DAVE.
>> HI, THERE.
>> HAPPY TO BE HERE.
>> WHOO!
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE GAME IS SIMPLE.
WE'LL SHOW YOU A BUNCH OF
LETTERS, AND THOSE LETTERS, SOME
MAKE WORDS.
FIND THOSE WORDS, YOU GET
POINTS.
AND THOSE POINTS IS MONEY, WOW.
SORRY, FOLKS.
THERE'S A WRITER'S STRIKE SO OUR
SOUND ENGINEER WROTE ALL THIS
HERSELF.
THANKS, CHRIS.
>> YOU GOT IT, BABY, LOVE YA!
>> ALL RIGHT.
CONTESTANTS, LET'S PULL UP OUR
FIRST WORD CRUNCH.
IF YOU SEE A WORD, JUST SHOUT IT
OUT.
AND YOUR TIME STARTS NOW.
>> OH, I SEE "HAPPY."
>> YOU GOT IT.
5 POINTS.
>> I SEE "CAT."
>> GREAT, THAT'S 3 POINTS.
>> I SEE "MOM HOLE."
>> NO, SORRY ABOUT THAT, CARA,
NO POINTS.
BUT THERE'S STILL TIME, KEEP
GUESSING.
>> "DOG."
>> NICE, 3 POINTS FOR DAVE.
>> OH, I'VE GOT ONE, "MOM HOLE."
>> YEAH, AGAIN, CARA, MAYBE STOP
GUESSING "MOM HOLE."
WE CANNOT ACCEPT "MOM HOLE."
>> WHY NOT?
>> WELL, IT'S A FEW REASONS.
FOR ONE, IT'S TWO WORDS.
YOU COULD DO "MOM," AND THEN
AFTER THAT, YOU COULD SAY
HOLE.
>> BUT I WANT TO CONNECT THEM.
>> WELL, YOU CAN'T.
PLEASE GUESS SOMETHING ELSE.
>> FINE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, "MOM HOLE."
>> YES, OH, I TOLD YOU NOT TO
SAY THAT.
>> NO, NO, THE OTHER ONE.
>> WHY ARE THERE TWO?
>> I DON'T KNOW, GENE, THIS
ISN'T MY GAME.
>> OH, OH, I'VE GOT ONE.
I SEE "APPLE."
>> GREAT, 5 POINTS.
>> SO WAIT, LET ME GET THIS
STRAIGHT.
SHE SAYS "APPLE," WHICH IS
5 POINTS, AND YOU THINK THAT'S
COOL.
BUT THEN WHEN I SAY "MOM HOLE,"
WHICH IS 7, I GET NOTHING?
THAT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
>> WELL, APPLE IS A REAL THING,
SO --
>> SO IS MOM HOLE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO THINK ABOUT
IT, BUT THEY'VE GOT THEM.
>> OH, I'VE GOT ANOTHER ONE.
POTHOLE.
>> OH, GREAT, 7 POINTS.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> CARA, CARA, RELAX.
>> OKAY, SO IF I HAD SAID
POTHOLE THAT WOULD HAVE
COUNTED?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
SO "MOM HOLE."
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST GET A NEW PUZZLE UP
HERE.
>> AM I ALLOWED TO GUESS?
>> YES, AS LONG AS IT'S NOT "MOM
HOLE."
>> NO PROBLEM.
HIM HOLE.
>> NO.
>> "GAY HOLE."
>> WOW, THERE'S A FOUR ON THE
BOARD.
>> "JACKSON HOLE."
>> WHAT?
>> "HOLE FOODS."
MY HOLE.
>> OKAY.
>> "CORN HOLE."
>> COME ON!
>> AND "MMM HOLE."
>> OKAY, THAT IS NOT "MMM HOLE,"
THAT'S JUST THREE MS AND THEN
HOLE.
WHAT IS "MMM HOLE"?
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE "MMM, YUMMY,
LIKE I'M EXCITED FOR THAT HOLE."
>> OH, MY GOD.
CHRIS, WHAT IS WITH THESE WORD
SEARCHES?
>> JUST TRYING TO PUT MY SPIN ON
IT, LOVE YA, BABY, MWAH!
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT, GUYS,
NEW RULE OF THIS SHOW.
IF YOU SEE "HOLE" ON THE BOARD,
DON'T SAY "HOLE."
WE NO LONGER ACCEPT ANY "HOLE"
>>
>> WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM WITH
MOMS?
>> LET'S GET A NEW PUZZLE AND NO
MORE HOLE STUFF.
I DON'T WANT TO GET IN TROUBLE
BUT I SEE PORN.
>> MOM PORN.
>> WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM WITH
MOMS?
>> DO YOU SEE ANYTHING ELSE?
>> FRIEND.
>> BEACH.
>> SCISSORING.
>> CLOUD.
>> "WATER."
>> "BALLS."
LIPS.
BUTT.
"SLIT.
BLOW."""
GAG.
JUICE.
TITTY.
HORNY.
AND "TIME."
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
I DON'T EVEN CARE.
FINE.
LET'S DO THE LAST PUZZLE.
OH, NO.
>> I DO, I SEE ONE.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, I'M SURE YOU DO.
>> WELL, IS IT OKAY IF I SAY IT?
>> YEAH, JUST DO IT, WHATEVER.
>> "BEE."
>> THAT IS -- THAT'S -- I'M
SORRY, THAT'S DUMB.
>> PLEASE DON'T PICK IT UP FOR
ANOTHER SEASON.
GOODNIGHT.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, ROSALIA.
**
FOUND THE KILLER.
WE CAN GO.
>> UNRELATED HAS ANYONE HEARD
THE NEW BILL CATCH ON?
>> HE'S SUCH A FORWARD THINKING
ARTIST.
>> FACETIME.
>> SPEAKING OF STRAIGHT FIRE,
KNOW WHAT I'VE BEEN INTO LATELY?
THE MAEFRP AING BAND VERSION OF
DON'T STOP BELIEVING.
>> WHAT?
>> I'VE BEEN MAINLINING THE
TRACK.
I HAVE IT CUED UP.
YOU WANT TO HEAR IT?
>> NO, THAT'S OKAY.
>> LET ME BREAK YOU OFF A PIECE.
>> DON'T EVER CALL PLAYING MUSIC
THAT.
>> CORTANA PLAY DON'T STOP 11 BY
OHIO STATE MARCHING BAND.
>> THERE'S A TYPO IN SPOTIFY.
SHUT UP.
>> YOU GUYS HEAR IT?
>> HEAR WHAT?
>> IT'S TUBAS PLAYING --
>> WHO THINKS OF THAT?
>> MARCHING BANDS.
>> WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
>> STEAM RISING AFTER
PERCOLATING UP AND UPWARD,
FASTER, WALKING DOWN THE STREET.
FEELING INVINCIBLE, LIKE YOUR
WHOLE LIFE IS AHEAD OF YOU,
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY TO THE HIGH
SCHOOL GRADUATION AND YOU
BUILDING UNTIL SUDDENLY --
>> IS IT OVER?
>> IT'S JUST BEGINNING.
>> HEY -- *
>> LIKE ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE ALL
AT ONCE AGAIN.
>> WAIT.
THE INSTRUMENTS ARE DOING THE
THING THAT STEPHEN TYLER IS
SINGING.
>> STEPHEN TYLER WASN'T IN
JOURNEY.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER, OKAY.
THE MUSIC IS -- AM I IN HEAVEN
OR ON RAINBOW ROAD IN MARIO KART
8?
>> IT'S THE SONG.
>> AND NOW THERE GOES.
THE TRUMPETS.
>> I DID NOT KNOW THEY COULD DO
GUITAR.
>> THEY CAN.
* LIVING DOWN IN SAN FRAN SIS
>> THOSE ARE NOT THE WORDS.
>> AND NO ONE HAS EVER CALLED IT
SAN FUR SIS.
>> NO ONE IS GETTING MY MONEY
EXCEPT CLARA.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
MEETING YOU EXCEPT FOR YOUR
SOCIAL MEDIA POST.
>> THEY'RE LIKE THE BIGGEST BAND
IN THE WORLD AND VIOLINS.
MY GOD.
IT'S THE SAME THING.
YES.
* OH *
>> SERIOUSLY, IMAGINE PLAYING
MARIO KART 8 AND HEARING THIS?
>> THAT INSPIRED ME TO DO SO
MUCH BETTER AT MARIO KURKS ART.
AND WHILE I'M CRUISING DOWN
RAINBOW ROAD.
>> MARCHING BAND VERSION OF
DON'T STOP BELIEVING TAKES PLACE
ON RAINBOW ROAD?
>> IT DOES.
IF YOU DON'T STOP 11.
AND THEY'RE TAKING IT HOME.
>> THAT WAS AMAZING.
I'D NEVER HEARD A SONG WITHOUT
WORDS BEFORE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S OVER.
>> IT'S JUST BEGINNING.
LIFE THAT IS.
>> ARE YOU GUYS ABOUT TO HOOK
UP?
>> IT MAKES SENSE.
>> YOU'RE BOTH GAY.
>> NOT ANYMORE.
>> I STILL AM.
>> KNEE.
ME TOO.
>> OH.
*
GOODNIGHT EVERYONE!
GOODNIGHT!
**