>>> YOU'RE WATCHING NBC
FROM THE
ADRIENNE ARSHT CENTER FOR THE
PERFORMING ARTS IN FLORIDA,
IT'S THE THIRD REPUBLICAN DEBATE.
>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M LESTER HOLT
AND WELCOME TO
THE REPUBLICAN KIDS TABLE
DEBATE.
LET'S MEET THE CANDIDATES.
FORMER NEW JERSEY GOVERNOR CHRIS
CHRISTIE.
>> MY WIFE SAID I COULD TRY THIS
ONE MORE TIME.
>> FORMER U.N. AMBASSADOR, NIKKI
HALEY.
>> EXCITED TO LOOK GOOD IN
COMPARISON.
>> FLORIDA GOVERNOR AND OWNER OF
THE WORLD'S MOST UPSETTING SMILE,
RON DeSANTIS.
ENTREPRENEUR, VEVIK RAMASWAMY.
TONIGHT
AND SENATOR TIM SCOTT.
>> IS THAT ME?
>> IT IS.
LET'S GET TO THE QUESTIONS.
MR. RAMASWAMY, IF ELECTED, WHAT
WOULD YOU DO ON YOUR FIRST DAY
IN OFFICE?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO BEGIN BY NOT
ANSWERING YOUR QUESTION,
AND
INSTEAD USE THIS PLATFORM TO SAY
HER DAUGHTER IS ON TIKTOK.
>> KEEP MY DAUGHTER'S NAME OUT
OF YOUR VOICE.
>> ALMOST SAID THAT RIGHT.
MR. SCOTT, ANYTHING YOU WOULD
LIKE TO ADD?
>> I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
>> OKAY.
>> LISTEN.
ABOUT HER, SHE'S REAL,
AND I
KNOW HER, AND SHE IS MY GIRLFRIEND,
AND WE MET THROUGH DATING,
AND FOR HER, I FEEL A
REAL SENSE OF HUMAN LOVE.
>> GOT IT.
NOW, FORMER PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
LEADING IN THE POLLS WITH 56%.
AMBASSADOR HAILEY, WHY SHOULD
VOTERS CONSIDER YOU INSTEAD?
>> LOOK, HE WAS THE RIGHT CHOICE
IN 2016, BUT WE NEED TO MOVE ON.
I PROMISE YOU ONE OF US ON THIS
STAGE TONIGHT
WILL BE THE
REPUBLICAN NOMINEE FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> HOW ADORABLE.
THEY ACTUALLY THINK THEY'VE GOT
A CHANCE.
SAD IN SOME WAYS, BUT IN OTHER
WAYS, FUNNY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT, FOLKS?
91 INDICTMENTS, FOUR TRIALS,
AND
I'M STILL THE BEST CHOICE.
NOW THEY'RE ALL STUCK BEHIND ME,
AND THERE'S NOTHING THEY CAN DO
ABOUT IT, JUST LIKE IN REAL
LIFE.
3%, 8%, 14%, 5%.
AND HOW ABOUT POOR TIM SCOTT,
HUH?
1%.
VERY LOW.
LOWER THAN FRANKLY MILK.
APPARENTLY THERE'S A MILK LOWER
THAN 1%.
PEOPLE ARE CALLING IT SKIM.
WE'VE NEVER HAD IT.
WE DON'T DRINK IT.
BUT WE LIKE SKIM SCOTT.
WE LOVE HIM.
AND HIS GIRLFRIEND.
NOT A LOT OF CHEMISTRY BETWEEN
THOSE TWO, RIGHT?
THEY MAKE ME AND MELANIA LOOK
LIKE TAYLOR AND TRAVIS.
AND HOW ABOUT VIVEK RAMASWAMY?
WE LIKE TO SAY RAMASWAMY,
BUT DO WE LIKE HIM?
HE MAKES IT HARD, DOESN'T HE?
HE CHECKS A LOT OF BOXES.
HE'S RICH, RUDE, HE'S GOT WEIRD
HAIR.
HE'S A LOT LIKE ME EXCEPT FOR ONE THING
THAT MATTERS A LOT TO
MY HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE BASE,
WHITE.
SAD HE'S GOING NOWHERE.
LOOK WHO SNL HAS PLAYING HIM.
POOR EGO.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT, SHE DOESN'T
LIKE IT.
SHE USED TO BE LISA FROM
TEMECULA.
NOW SHE'S VIVEK FROM RAMASWAMY.
AND LOOK WHO THEY GOT PLAYING
MEATBALL RON.
ONE OF THE DESTROY BOYS.
RON'S WATCHING AT HOME LIKE, WHO
THE HELL IS THAT.
POOR RON DeSANTIS.
EVEN SNL DOESN'T THINK HE HAS A
CHANCE.
IF THEY DID, IT WOULD BE LIKE
PAUL RUDD OR SOMETHING IN THERE,
RIGHT?
HOW ABOUT NIKKI HALEY, RIGHT?
I CALL HER BIRD BRAIN, BUT ONLY
IN PUBLIC.
SHE MADE SOME TERRIBLE POINTS IN
THAT DEBATE.
I THINK.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I HAVE TROUBLE HEARING WOMEN
OVER 25.
BUT LET'S BE HONEST.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE A
PRESIDENT WHOSE NAME IS NIKKI.
PRESIDENT NIKKI.
JUST DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT.
PROBABLY BECAUSE IT'S A WOMAN'S
NAME.
AND HOW CAN WE FORGET CHRIS
CHRISTIE?
IT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY EASY.
YOU JUST WALK AWAY.
ISN'T IT SAD, FOLKS, NONE OF
THEM CAN BEAT JOE BIDEN,
THE
WORST PRESIDENT SINCE, FRANKLY,
ME.
JOE BIDEN, HE'S SO OLD.
THE MENTALS ARE CLEARLY IN
DECLINE.
AND I AM LOSING IT ALSO.
YOU'RE SEEING IT ALL THE TIME.
WE'RE SEEING IT A LOT.
I SAY THINGS LIKE I'M BEATING
OBAMA.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
BUT I SAY IT.
IT'S FUN.
AND THEY SAY, WHY AREN'T YOU AT
THE DEBATE, MR. TRUMP.
WHERE'S TRUMP?
BUT I COULDN'T BE AT THE DEBATE
BECAUSE I'M VERY, VERY BUSY.
I'M GOING FROM TRIAL TO TRIAL.
I'M BASICALLY DOING HOUSE
HUNTERS BUT WITH COURTROOMS.
BUT HOW HORRIBLE ARE THESE
TRIALS, MAKING ALL MY CHILDREN
TESTIFY AGAINST ME.
MY SWEET LITTLE MIDDLE-AGED
CRIMINAL CHILDREN.
SO AWFUL TO BRING IN THE FAMILY.
IT'LL BE VERY SAD WHEN I PIN IT
ALL ON ONE OF THEM,
PROBABLY
ERIC.
WOW, LOOK AT THEM BACK THERE
STILL FROZEN,
TRYING NOT TO
BLINK, TRYING NOT TO MOVE.
STUCK ON STAGE WHILE I COOK.
BUT THEY'RE AFTER ME, FOLKS.
THEY'RE COMING AFTER ME.
THEY'RE SAYING I COMMITTED
FRAUD.
NOT TRUE.
I'VE COMMITTED A LOT OF THINGS,
ADULTERY, TREASON,
A LOT OF FRAUD PERHAPS,
BUT I'VE BEEN ON
MY BEST BEHAVIOR IN COURT.
THE JUDGE ASKS, DID YOU APPROVE
THESE FINANCIAL REPORTS,
AND I
VERY RESPECTFULLY SAY YOU'RE A
DUMB ASS, THIS IS A SHAM.
WHEN I'M PRESIDENT AGAIN, I'LL
HAVE YOU EXECUTED.
THEY'RE NOT BIG FANS, ESPECIALLY
TISH JAMES,
ATTORNEY GENERAL WHO
IS VERY RACIST.
THE WORST KIND OF RACISM, RACISM
AGAINST WHITES.
AFTER EVERYTHING WE'VE DONE FOR THE WORLD
IN TERMS OF AIRPLANE
AND WITH REGARD TO BEACH BOYS.
SO THAT CONCLUDES THE DEBATE,
AND THAT'S PROBABLY A WRAP ON
SOME OF THESE IMPRESSIONS AS
WELL.
LOOK AT EGO, SO RELIEVED.
ANYWAY, I'LL PICK ONE OF THESE
LUCKY FIVE TO BE MY VP,
OR IN
MANY WAYS, I WILL NOT AT ALL.
MAYBE IN MY THIRD TERM.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, TIMOTHEE
CHALAMET!
>>> OH, MAN.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT IS GREAT TO BE HERE.
IT'S MY SECOND TIME HOSTING
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
BUT IN A LOT OF WAYS, IT FEELS
LIKE MY FIRST TIME
BECAUSE THE
LAST TIME WAS DURING COVID,
AND
THAT WAS JUST WEIRD.
I WAS WEARING A MASK THE WHOLE
WEEK.
I DON'T THINK LAUREN MICHAELS
KNEW WHO I WAS.
KEPT CALLING ME WYNONA.
AFTER STRIKE
I'VE BEEN TOLD TWO DAYS AGO, AND
I KNOW THIS IS WHAT WE WERE ALL THINKING ABOUT,
ACTORS COULDN'T
TALK ABOUT THEIR MOVIES.
ONLY THING I WAS ALLOWED TO TALK
ABOUT WAS THE PERFUME I HAVE
COMING OUT.
IT'S AN ADD FOR A PERFUME
DIRECTED BY MARTIN SCORSESE.
CALL
WANTS TO DIRECT YOU
AND THE FIRST THING YOU THINK
IS, MAN, I REALLY HOPE IT'S A
PERFUME COMMERCIAL.
NOW THE STRIKE IS OVER,
AND IT'S LIKE WE'RE ALL RETURNING TO THIS
MAGICAL WORLD.
WHERE ACTORS CAN ONCE AGAIN TALK
ABOUT THEIR PROJECTS.
♪ COME WITH ME, AND YOU'LL BE
IN A WORLD OF SHAMELESS
SELF-PROMOTION ♪
♪ IT'S OKAY, I CAN SAY --
>> THAT MY NEW FILM WONKA IS OUT
IN THEATERS DECEMBER 15th.
FANGO KEY WORD HUGH GRANT.
FANDANGO.COM.
KEY WORD, DAMN HUGH GRANT
GOT
THAT OOMPAH LOOMPAH DUMP TRUCK.
♪ IF YOU WANT TO VIEW A THREE
AND A HALF HOUR FILM,
GO SEE
KILLERS OF THE FLOWER MOON ♪
♪ OR JUST WAIT FOR PART TWO OF DUNE
JUST MAKE SURE BEFORE TO
USE THE BATHROOM ♪
YOU KNOW, AFTER SPENDING 118
DAYS THINKING ABOUT AI,
IT IS SO
REFRESHING TO BE HERE AMONGST
REAL HUMAN BEINGS.
OH, YOU SMELL GREAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU SEEM LIKE YOU HAVE
SECRETS.
BUT THANKS TO THE NEW S.A.G.
DEAL, TV SHOWS CAN'T JUST USE AI
TO MAKE THE CROWD LOOK BIGGER
THAN IT ACTUALLY IS.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT PEOPLE IN THE
BLEACHERS?
LOOK, THE REALLY IMPORTANT THING
IS THE RETURN OF AMERICA'S
FAVORITE INDUSTRY, HOLLYWOOD.
♪ IT'S ALL DONE, AND WE WON,
NO MORE NEWS --
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> HEY, MARCELLO, WHAT'S UP?
>> THAT OLD-TIMEY STUFF IS CUTE
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT I WAS JUST
THINKING, AND YOU AND I ACTUALLY
HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
>> DO WE?
>> YEAH.
YOU'RE A BIG HUGE MOVIE STAR,
AND I'M ON MY SECOND SEASON OF
SNL.
>> OH, YEAH.
OKAY.
>> BUT THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE
THAT WE HAVE IN COMMON.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE BOTH HAVE A BABY FACE.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
>> LET'S TALK TO THEM, RIGHT?
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> OKAY.
THIS SONG IS DEDICATED TO ALL
THE BABY FACE DUDES OUT THERE.
>> SHOUTOUT JUSTIN BIEBER AND
BRUNO MARS.
CHECK
LISTEN
♪ I GOT A BABY FACE.
SAY MY HIPS DON'T LIE,
SAY I'M A BAD KID, I'M A BAD
GUY ♪
♪ I GOT A BABY FACE, BUT I'M
HUNG LIKE MY DAD,
TRUST ME,
BABY, I'M THE BEST YOU EVER
HAD ♪
♪ I GOT A FACE LIKE A YOUNG ONE
BUT THE BODY LIKE A DUDE ♪
To hide your wife, hide your Grandma too
Child like demeanor but I'm full grown
I GOT TRAPPED
IN THE BOOBIES, CALL MY ASS HOME
ALONE ♪
I got a baby face and I walk right away
♪ I TOOK HER OUT TO DENNYS AND
MY ASS ATE FOR FREE
ME AND YOUR GIRL HAVE FUNSY,
AND YOU WANT TO
SEE ME IN A ONESY ♪
♪ I GOT A BABY FACE.
yeah I look real shy
SAY I'M A BAD KID, I'M A BAD
GUY ♪
I got a baby face, and yo girl at my crib
Trust me baby, I eat the booty with a bib
♪ I SMOKE, I GO TO COURT,
I GAMBLE, I GOT DIVORCED ♪
- FACE
- HORSE
♪ I DO MY TAXES ON MY OWN,
NOBODY DO IT FOR ME,
BUT BEFORE
WE GO TO SLEEP, WE NEED A
BEDTIME STORY ♪
♪ WAKE UP IN THE MORNING LITTLE
MAN UP IN MY SHEETS,
I THOUGHT
HE WAS A KID, I HAD TO CHECK HIS
ID.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT GUY IS 33.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
AT THE BAR HE WAS CUTE, HE WAS
SHY, HE WAS NICE,
BITCH, FOUND
OUT MY MAN WENT TO JAIL TWICE.
I'M IN LOVE BECAUSE I KNOW HE A BOSS,
AND I DO WHAT HE SAY, AND
I DO WHAT HE WANT.
>> WHOA, Y'ALL REALLY GOING TO
DO A BABY FACE SONG WITHOUT YOUR
BOY.
MY BAD KENAN.
WHY DON'T YOU SPIT SOMETHING?
>> OH, YOU MEAN LIKE THIS.
YO, YO, I'VE HAD THIS FACE SINCE
KENAN AND KEL.
I AGE LIKE A VAMPIRE, I AGE LIKE
FAR RELIGIOUS.
ALL MY LIFE, I'VE BEEN A CUTIE
ON TV.
THEY THINK I'M 19, BUT I'M
REALLY 63.
♪ I GOT A BABY FACE.
SAY MY HIPS DON'T LIE,
SAY I'M A BAD KID, I'M A BAD
GUY ♪
♪ I GOT A BABY FACE, BUT I'M
HUNG LIKE MY DAD,
TRUST ME,
BABY, I'M THE BEST YOU EVER
HAD ♪
GREAT
STICK
FIRST EVER MUSEUM OF HIP HOP
HERE IN THE BOOGIE DOWN BRONX.
I'M NUNYA BUSINESS FROM DOUBLE
XL.
AND IT'S MY HONOR TO WELCOME OUR
ESTEEMED PANEL TODAY TO
CELEBRATE 50 YEARS OF THE
CULTURE WE KNOW AND LOVE.
FIRST UP, THE QUEEN OF HIP HOP
AND SOUL, MARY J. BLIGE.
>> YES, INDEED.
>> SUPER PRODUCER, AUTHOR, AND
THE COFOUNDER OF DEAF JAM
RECORDS, RICK RUBIN.
INTELLECTUAL CIVIL RIGHTS ICON
AND POLITICAL ACTIVISTS, THE
HONORABLE DR. CORNEL WEST.
>> YES.
AND BLESSINGS OF PROSPERITY UNTO
YOU, SISTER NUNYA.
>> AND FINALLY, HIS GROUP BROKE
THE RECORDS FOR MOST STREAMS
MAKING HIM TECHNICALLY THE MOST
SUCCESSFUL HIP HOP ARTIST OF ALL
TIME, IT'S
SMOKECHEDDADAASSGETTA.
>> YES, SIR.
BACK IN THIS BITCH, MAN.
YES, SIR.
>> THANK YOU, ALL.
WELL, AFTER 50 YEARS, A LOT HAS
CHANGED, BUT HIP HOP IS STILL
HERE.
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
>> WELL, BECAUSE HIP HOP IS MORE
THAN MUSIC.
WE SPIN OUR PAIN INTO POETRY.
>> AND THAT ENERGY RESONATES
WITH PEOPLE ALL OVER THE WORLD.
>> YES.
AND MOREOVER, IT'S PRECIOUS
HISTORY EMPOWERS THE PEOPLE TO
EXPRESS, INVEST, AND PROGRESS TO
A BETTER TOMORROW.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN, I GUESS I'M
JUST LIKE CHILLING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> OKAY.
FIRST OF ALL, I'M GOING TO NEED
TO SEE YOUR FACE, YOUNG MAN.
YOU'RE IN A MUSEUM.
>> OH, YEAH.
MY BAD, MISS.
SO WHEN THEY DISCOVER HIP HOP?
LIKE 2014?
>> NO.
50 YEARS AGO.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE ALL HERE.
>> TO ME, IF IT SLAP, YEAH, THE
ONES GON' SLIDE, BUT THE ENDS BE
POPPING REGARDLESS, YOU FEEL ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT ANY OF THAT
MEANS.
>> YES.
EXPOUND ON THAT, PLEASE, BROTHER
SMOKECHEDDA.
>> SO PEEP, I DO MUCK BANGS,
RIGHT?
I EAT NOODLES ON STREAM.
AND MY DMs BE ALL CHEATS, I'M
TALKING BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I'M LIKE SHEESH!
>> OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT HAD TO DO
WITH IN IG.
>> I THINK MY FRIEND IS SPEAKING
TO THE FLEXIBILITY OF THE
GENERA.
RAP IS NOT A MONOLITH.
>> EXACTLY.
ANYONE CAN TAP INTO THAT JOY OR
THAT TRAUMA.
>> I FEEL THAT.
MY DAD MADE ME GET BRACES.
I WANTED INVISALIGN.
LIFE CRAZY.
>> ARE YOU SAYING THAT WAS
TRAUMATIC FOR YOU?
>> HELL YEAH.
PLUS MY BOY GUAP -- MY BOY GUAP,
MAN, I MISS HIM SO MUCH, MAN.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS GRACIOUS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO BROTHER GUAP
LORD?
>> HE WAS FUND RAISING FOR THE
HOMEY MAYOR ERIC ADAMS.
HE GOT TO LAY LOW IN TURKEY FOR
A MINUTE.
>> OKAY.
WELL, IT WOULDN'T BE A HIP HOP
DISCUSSION WITHOUT GOAT TALK.
RICK, YOU'VE WORKED WITH
EVERYBODY.
WHO DO YOU THINK IS THE GREATEST
RAPPER OF ALL TIME?
>> WOW.
SO MANY OPTIONS.
L.L., JAY-Z, ANDRE 3,000.
>> TUPAC, KIM.
>> I'LL SAY ME, JASON DERULO, I
LIKE DIXIE D'AMELIO.
AND WHAT SHE CALLED?
I LIKE THAT INSURANCE GIRL.
>> INSURANCE GIRL?
BROTHER SMOKECHEDDA, TO WHOM ARE
YOU REFERRING?
>> YOU KNOW, NATIONWIDE IS ON
YOUR SIDE.
THAT'S SLAP, BRO.
I BE RAPPING THAT ALL DAY.
♪ NATIONWIDE IS ON YOUR SIDE ♪
THAT'S FIRE, MAN.
>> SO FOR YOU IT'S THE
NATIONWIDE JINGLE.
PERSONALLY, I LOVE BIGGIE.
WE CAN ALL AGREE HE'S THE MAN,
RIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO THAT IS.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW BIGGIE SMALLS?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO NONE OF
Y'ALL IS.
EXCEPT HIM.
>> ME?
>> YEAH.
YOU WAS IN THE MATRIX
REVOLUTIONS.
THAT'S THE G.O.A.T. RIGHT THERE.
>> NO DISRESPECT TO DR. WEST,
BUT BIGGIE SOLD 20 MILLION
RECORDS.
>> SO HE A FLOP.
>> FLOP?
>> WATCH YOURSELF, BROTHER.
>> MY NEW SOLO HAD A TRILLION
STREAMS IN TWO DAYS ON SOUND
CLOUDS.
>> TRILLION?
>> YEAH.
IT'S A SMART ONE TOO.
IT'S ACTUALLY A CRITIQUE OF
CAPALISM.
>> I THINK YOU MEAN CAPITALISM.
>> YEAH.
EVERYBODY CAPPING ALL THE TIME,
RIGHT.
I LIKE IT.
IT'S MY NEW JOINT.
IT'S CALLED CLING, CLING, CLING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
BUS IT.
♪ CLING, CLING, CLING, YOU
CAPPING, DRIP, SLASH, WATER,
DRIP SPLASH, DRIP, WATER ♪
>> NO!
NO, NO, NO!
YOU DO NOT DO THAT, YOUNG MAN.
NOW SIT DOWN.
>> YOU SEE?
SPANK YOUR KIDS, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU, HIP HOP FOR 50 YEARS.
HERE'S TO 50 MORE.
>> HEY, MOM.
CAN YOU CALL AN UBER?
I DON'T LIKE THE BRONX AT ALL.
>>> I'M BEYOND TOUCHED THAT MY
BOOK, THE WOMAN IN ME, HIT
NUMBER ONE ON THE NEW YORK TIMES
BEST SELLER LIST.
TO SAY THE LEAST, MY AUDIO BOOK
IS READ BY THE AMAZING MICHELLE
WILLIAMS.
BUT SHE WASN'T THE ONLY ONE WHO
WANTED TO READ IT.
HERE'S A PEEK AT SOME OF THE
OTHER ACTORS WHO AUDITIONS TO
READ THE WOMAN IN ME.
>> OKAY.
ALLISON JANNEY, CHAPTER 25.
>> SHAVING MY HEAD WAS A WAY TO
SAY TO THE WORLD FU.
WHO WROTE THIS?
>> TIMOTHEE CHALAMET.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> AND ANY TIME YOU'RE READY TO
START.
MARTIN SCORSESE.
>> WHO'S SAYING ACTION?
I'M SAYING ACTION?
YOU SAYING ACTION?
>> STEVE-O FROM JACK AS.
>> HOW COULD I EXPLAIN I JUST
WANTED TO BE HELD BY KEVEN
FEDERLINE IN A SWIMMING POOL.
SWEET, A STAPLER.
STAPLE MY NUTS TO MY THIGH.
>> JOHN MULANEY.
>> WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL, ALL
I WANTED FOR CHRISTMAS WAS A
HORSE.
A HORSE, YOU KNOW, LIKE A TALL
DOG.
I WAS ADDICTED TO DRUGS.
>> KEVIN JAMES.
YOU GOING TO READ FROM THE
SCRIPT?
OKAY.
NEXT.
NATASHA LEON.
>> SO AT THIS POINT, I'M NOT A
GIRL BUT NOT YET A WOMAN.
I'M [ BLEEP ] IN BETWEEN.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> FRED SNIDER FROM THE B 52s.
>> MY LITTLE SISTER WAS A TOTAL
BITCH.
>> JULIA FOX.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
I'M READY, PUT IT IN, I SAID.
AND HE REPLIED, IT'S IN.
MY WHOLE WORLD COLLAPSED.
>> JADA PINKETT SMITH, THE
CHAPTER ON KEVEN FEDERLINE.
>> THAT NIGHT WAS CHAOTIC.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE THAT WILL, MY
HUSBAND, SLAPPED CHRIS ROCK.
>> I BELIEVE YOU'RE READING FROM
THE WRONG BOOK.
>> AM I?
TUPAC HAS ALOPECIA.
>> HE SAID FOR SHIZ, FOR SHIZ,
GENUINE, WHAT'S UP HOMEY, FOR
SHIZ.
>> THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> IS BRITNEY GOING TO BE HERE?
>> NO.
>> CAN WE CALL HER?
>> CAN I CALL HER?
>> NSYNC WAS WHAT PEOPLE CALLED
BACK THEN SO PITCH.
THEY WERE WHITE BOYS, BUT THEY
LOVED HIP HOP.
I'M ENTRANCED BY THIS FLORIDIAN
VERNACULAR.
>> ICE SPICE.
>> EVERYONE LIKE THOUGHT I HAD
IMPLANTS, AND LIKE, THAT'S
CRAZY.
DA, DA, DA.
>> MAGGIE SMITH.
>> WHEN I WAS PREGNANT, I WANTED
EVERYONE TO STAY AWAY.
I THINK BRITNEY WOULD HAVE
BEEN --
>> BILL HADER.
>> WHEN I WAS LITTLE, I WANTED
TO BE A STAR LIKE MADONNA.
>> NEXT.
TIMOTHEE CHALAMET, TAKE 27.
>> NAH, NAH.
FOR SURE, FOR SURE.
>> JUST READ THE LINES PLEASE.
>> ACTUALLY, I CAN'T READ.
♪ HIT ME BABY ONE MORE TIME ♪
I'M TAKING A BATTLE ROPES CLASS
AT THIS HIGH INTENSITY TRAINING
GYM, AND THIS MORNING'S CLASS
WAS SO BRUTAL.
WAIT.
OH, I LEFT MY BAG AT THE GYM.
I'LL CALL YOU RIGHT BACK.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
IS THIS SHRED ZONE GYM?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, OKAY.
SORRY.
I WAS CONFUSED BECAUSE
BUSINESSES DON'T USUALLY ANSWER
THE PHONE WITH JUST HELLO.
WHO AM I SPEAKING WITH?
>> OH, ME.
>> RIGHT.
I MEANT WHAT'S YOUR NAME.
>> I'M BRETT.
DO YOU WANT TO SIGN UP FOR
CLASSES?
>> NO.
>> OH, COOL.
BYE.
>> OH.
NO, WAIT.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
I JUST CALLED.
I THINK I LEFT MY BAG THERE THIS
MORNING.
HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN IT?
IT'S A CROSS BODY.
>> WE'RE A FULL-BODY GYM.
>> NO.
THE STYLE IS CROSS-BODY.
IT'S A LULULEMON BAG.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN A BAG OF
LEMONS TODAY.
I'M SORRY LULU.
>> MY NAME'S NOT LULU.
IT'S TRACEY.
LULULEMON IS THE BRAND OF THE
BAG I LEFT AT THE GYM.
>> HELLO?
>> IS THERE SOMEONE ELSE I CAN
SPEAK TO MAYBE?
>> YEAH.
I'LL TRANSFER YOU TO KEITH.
PLEASE HOLD, LULU.
♪
>> JESUS.
>> HELLO?
>> HI, KEITH?
>> HEY.
MY NAME'S KEITH TOO.
>> SORRY.
MY NAME'S TRACEY.
I WAS HOPING YOU CAN HELP ME.
>> NO DOUBT, KEITH.
ARE YOU TRYING TO CUT OR BULK?
>> NEITHER.
I LEFT A LULULEMON BAG THERE.
IT'S SALMON.
>> SALMON IS A FISH, THOUGH.
>> IT'S ALSO A COLOR.
COLOR IS SALMON.
>> NO.
A DOG ISN'T THE COLOR DOG.
>> RIGHT.
BECAUSE DOGS ARE DIFFERENT
COLORS, BUT SALMON AREN'T.
>> HELLO?
>> YEAH.
I'M STILL HERE.
I'M SORRY.
CAN SOMEONE CHECK IF MY BAG'S
THERE?
IT WAS SUPER EXPENSIVE, AND I
DON'T WANT SOMEONE TO TAKE IT.
>> YOU WOULDN'T SAY APPLE IS THE
COLOR OF APPLE OR LIKE ORANGE IS
THE COLOR -- OH, WAIT.
HOLD ON.
>> OKAY.
YOUR BRAIN BROKE.
CAN YOU TRANSFER ME BACK TO
BRETT?
>> NO DOUBT, KEITH.
♪ I LIKE TO MOVE IT, MOVE IT ♪
>> THAT IS TOO LOUD.
>> HELLO?
>> KEITH, YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
TRANSFER ME TO BRETT.
>> OH, FOR SURE.
ONE SEC.
>> HELLO?
>> WHO'S THIS?
>> KEITH.
WHO'S THIS?
>> IT'S BRETT.
WHAT UP, KEITH?
>> WHAT UP, BRETT?
SICK.
WAIT.
WHERE'S THE GIRL?
>> GUYS?
>> HELLO?
>> HELLO.
IS THIS KEITH?
>> YEAH.
HOW YOU DOING?
>> GUYS?
HELLO?
I'M NOT LULU.
>> IS THIS KEITH?
>> THIS IS TRACEY.
>> WHAT'S UP, BRETT?
>> HELLO?
>> HI?
HELLO?
>> HELLO?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IS THERE A WOMAN THERE I CAN
TALK TO?
>> OH, YEAH.
NO DOUBT.
HEY, MISS, WOULD YOU MIND
TALKING TO THIS LADY?
>> HELLO?
>> NEVER MIND.
I'LL JUST BUY A NEW BAG.
BYE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BYE, KEITH.
>> OH, WAIT.
WHO'S LIGHT PINK BAG IS THIS?
YOU GOT TO PUT IT IN A CUBBY.
JUNIPER BASE 2057
HOURS
>> WHAT'S TAKING THEM SO LONG?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THEY WERE EVERYWHERE.
IT'S LIKE THEY KNEW WE WERE
COMING.
>> WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
>> THEY'RE GONE, OKAY?
THEY'RE ALL GONE!
SOCKET, WHAT ARE THE ODDS OF US
SURVIVING THE NEXT ASSAULT?
>> WITH SOME LUCK, THERE'S A 0.2
CHANCE OF SURVIVAL.
>> GREAT.
SO WE'RE ALL GOING TO DIE.
>> THERE IS ONE HOPE.
I CAN MEET WITH THE DESTROYER.
>> NO.
IT'S SUICIDE.
>> HE'S CLOSE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
HE'LL LISTEN TO ME.
HE KNOWS ME.
♪ IT'S EXTRA BAD IN THE FUTURE TONIGHT,
AND I'M FEELING REALLY
SCARED ♪
♪ 'CUZ TODAY I'M GONNA SEE MY
OLD FRIEND,
BUT TODAY HE LOOKS A
LITTLE DIFFERENT ♪
♪ THERE HE IS, MY GIANT HORSE,
HE'S IN A BATTLE IN SPACE,
YEAH, HE WANTS TO CRUSH THE HUMAN
RACE ♪
♪ HE'S EVIL, YEAH,
THERE HE IS, MY GIANT HORSE,
HE'S EXTRA GIANT TODAY,
YEAH, HE WANTS TO TAKE MY
LIFE AWAY FROM ME,
GIANT
HORSE ♪
>> WHY HAVE YOU COME HERE, BOY?
HE'S BIG NOW.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
>> GIANT HORSE, WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
BALANCE
THIS ISN'T YOU, BOY.
YOU'RE TINIER THAN THIS.
>> ENOUGH.
GIANT HORSE, CRUSH HIM.
>> NO.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, BOY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
DESTROY HIM.
>> NO.
BOY, THINK OF THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
WE WERE POOR, BUT WE WERE HAPPY.
JUST PROMISE ME ONE THING.
DO GREAT THINGS.
>> FINE.
IF YOU WON'T DO IT, I WILL!
>> HELP ME, GIANT HORSE.
I NEED YOU.
YOUNG
YOU DIE!
NO!
THE PROPHESY WAS TRUE!
♪ THERE HE IS, MY TINY HORSE,
HE'S BACK TO TINY TODAY,
I ALWAYS KNEW HE'D SAVE THE DAY
FOR ME, YEAH ♪
♪ THERE HE IS, MY TINY HORSE,
HE'S EXTRA TINY TODAY, YEAH,
NO ONE IS TAKING HIM AWAY FROM ME,
YEAH, TINY HORSE ♪
♪ BLACK HOLE OPENED IN THE
KITCHEN EVERY CLOCK'S A
DIFFERENT TIME ♪
♪ IT WOULD ONLY TAKE THE
ENERGY TO FIX IT
I DON'T KNOW WHY I AM ♪
♪ THE WAY I AM NOT STRONG
ENOUGH TO BE YOUR MAN I TRY
I CAN'T STOP STARING AT THE
CEILING FAN AND ♪
♪ SPINNING OUT ABOUT THINGS
THAT HAVEN'T HAPPENED
BREATHING IN AND OUT ♪
♪ DRAG RACING THROUGH THE
CANYON SINGING
BOYS DON'T CRY ♪
♪ DO YOU SEE US GETTING
SCRAPED UP OFF THE PAVEMENT
I DON'T KNOW WHY I AM ♪
♪ THE WAY I AM NOT STRONG
ENOUGH TO BE YOUR MAN I LIE
I AM JUST LOWERING
YOUR EXPECTATIONS ♪
♪ HALF A MIND THAT KEEPS THE
OTHER SECOND GUESSING
CLOSE MY EYES AND COUNT ♪
♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD
ALWAYS AN ANGEL
NEVER A GOD ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHY I AM THE
WAY I AM THERE'S SOMETHING
IN THE STATIC I THINK I'VE
BEEN HAVING REVELATIONS ♪
♪ COMIN' TO IN THE FRONT
SEAT NEARLY EMPTY SKIP THE
EXIT TO OUR OLD STREET
AND GO HOME ♪
♪ GO HOME ALONE ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THE THIRD REPUBLICAN DEBATE WAS HELD THIS WEEK,
AND VIVEK RAMASWAMY STARTED BY SAYING
THE
GOP HAD BECOME A PARTY OF
LOSERS.
WEIRDLY, A PARTY OF LOSERS WAS
ALSO HOW NBC ADVERTISED THE
DEBATE.
HE THEN CRITICIZED NIKKI HALEY'S
DAUGHTER FOR HAVING A TIKTOK
ACCOUNT.
HE ALSO STRESSED IT'S NOT
IMPORTANT HOW HE KNOWS THAT.
THEN NIKKI HALEY RESPONDED TO
THE ATTACK BY SAYING
LEAVE MY
DAUGHTER OUT OF YOUR VOICE,
WHICH WAS PULLED DIRECTLY FROM
THE JAPANESE SUBTITLES
OF THE
WILL SMITH SLAP.
>> RON DeSANTIS' PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN GOT A MAJOR BOOST
AFTER
IOWA GOVERNOR ENDORSED HIM.
ALSO GIVING DeSANTIS A LIFT, HIS
HOOKER BOOTS.
THE FBI LAUNCHED A CORRUPTION
INVESTIGATION INTO MAYOR ERIC
ADAMS.
TWO CELL PHONES,
ONE INDICATED
SHORTIES AND SHADY STUFF.
>> AFTER NEW POLLS SHOW DONALD
TRUMP LEADING JOE BIDEN,
DEMOCRATIC STRATEGISTS ARE
CALLING BIDEN'S RE-ELECTION
CAMPAIGN A FIVE-ALARM FIRE,
WHICH IS SCARY FOR BIDEN BECAUSE IN A FIRE,
YOU HAVE TO USE THE
STAIRS.
A NEW CENSUS REPORT SHOWS BY THE
END OF THE YEAR 2060,
ONE OUT OF
EVERY FOUR AMERICANS WILL BE
LATINO.
THAT'S HOW GOOD BAD BUNNY'S
MUSIC IS.
>> ON MONDAY, DONALD TRUMP
TESTIFIED UNDER OATH IN HIS
CIVIL FRAUD TRIAL.
HE WAS TECHNICALLY NEVER SWORN
IN BECAUSE THE BIBLES KEPT GOING
UP IN FLAMES.
>> FTX FOUNDER HAS BEEN FOUND OF
SECURITY FRAUD, WIRE FRAUD,
AND MAKING A WEAVE OUT OF A --
FORMER
IN PRISON
IRONICALLY HE
WILL BE USED AS AN ALTERNATIVE
CURRENCY.
>> COLIN.
A NEW SURVEY SHOWS THAT 92% OF ADULTS
PREFER TO DATE SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN TO THERAPY
WHILE 8%
PREFER GOOD SEX.
>> IN A NEW INTERVIEW, BARBARA
STREISAND SAID SHE DIDN'T LIKE
THE WAY SIRI PRONOUNCED HER NAME
CALLED CEO
AND ASKED TO CHANGE IT.
MORE
ANECDOTES
>> A NEW APP HAS BEEN INTRODUCED CALLED RAP
THAT CLAIM IT CAN
SHOW INSTAGRAM USERS WHO IS
LOOKING AT THEIR PICTURES.
UH-OH, SAID A BUNCH OF HIGH
SCHOOL TEACHERS.
>> A NEW STUDY IS BEING
CONDUCTED TO EXPLAIN
WHY
REDHEADS SEEM TO EXPERIENCE PAIN
DIFFERENTLY.
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL WITCHES.
SCIENTISTS HAVE DETERMINED THE
CAUSE OF THE MYSTERIOUS DEATHS
OF DOZENS OF AFRICAN ELEPHANTS
WAS A BACTERIAL INFECTION,
AND
NOT MARGARET, THE ONE ELEPHANT
WHO STOOD TO INHERIT EVERYTHING.
>> IN INDIANA WOMAN WAS ARRESTED
AFTER SHE DROVE HER CAR INTO A BUILDING
BECAUSE SHE THOUGHT IT
WAS A, QUOTE, ISRAEL SCHOOL.
WELL, THAT'S WHY THEY DON'T LET
WOMEN DRIVE IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
YOU DON'T LIKE IT OR --
A FIRST CLASS DINING MENU FROM THE TITANIC
IS BEING AUCTIONED OFF
FOR OVER $80,000.
THE MENU INCLUDES DUCK IN A PORK
WINE SAUCE, SPRING LAMB,
AND
BOTTOMLESS WATER.
>> TITANIC.
>> BECAUSE OF TITANIC, RIGHT.
>> IT SUNK.
>> DOMINOS HAS LAUNCHED A NEW
PROGRAM CALLED EMERGENCY PIZZA,
WHICH OFFERS CUSTOMERS A FREE
PIZZA WHENEVER THEY NEED IT
MOST.
WHICH IS STRANGE BECAUSE ALL OF
MY EMERGENCIES
COME RIGHT AFTER
EATING A DOMINOS PIZZA.
ACTOR JARED LETO CLIMBED TO THE
TOP OF THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING
TO PROMOTE HIS BAND 30 SECONDS
TO MARS.
THE WAY THE PROMOTION WORKS IS
IF WE BUY ENOUGH ALBUMS, HE'LL
JUMP.
SCIENTISTS
IN NEW GIINEA HAVE REDISCOVERED
A LONG LOST MAMMAL
WHICH HAS THE
QUILLS OF A HEDGE HOG, THE SNOUT
OF AN ANT EATER,
THE FEET OF A
MOLL, AND THE ASS OF AN ANGEL.
I'M JUST READING IT, MAN.
>> ACCORDING TO THE BUREAU OF
LABOR STATISTICS, THE FIVE-DAY
WORK WEEK IS OVER AS EMPLOYEES
ARE NOW ACCUSTOMED TO A FLEXIBLE
HYBRID SCHEDULE.
HERE TO COMMENT IS YOUR COWORKER
WHO'S EXTREMELY BUSY DOING
SEEMINGLY NOTHING.
>> HI.
OH, MY GOD, COLIN, I KNOW WE
BOOKED OUT AN HOUR FOR THIS
PRESENTATION, BUT I GOT TO GET
BACK.
>> YEAH.
WE DIDN'T BOOK AN HOUR FOR IT.
HIGH, CRYSTAL.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> ICE BREAKER, HOW'S THE
WEATHER?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M ALWAYS UNDERWATER.
>> SO CRYSTAL, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT FLEXIBLE WORK SCHEDULES?
>> I GUESS I AM PRETTY FLEXIBLE
SINCE I'M BENDING OVER BACKWARDS
DOING EVERYBODY ELSE'S JOB.
>> WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU DO FOR
WORK?
>> LET ME BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU.
I DO THIS.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS AIN'T RIGHT.
I'M IN HELL.
>> YOU'RE IN HELL?
THIS IS A FLYER SIGNUP SHEET FOR
THANKSGIVING POT LUCK.
>> YEAH.
AND GUESS WHAT I'LL BE BRINGING.
WON'T BE A MAN, TELL YOU THAT.
GOOD THING THIS VIBRATES SO
MUCH.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> I DO, AND I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> I DO.
AND SASHA JUST CALLED IN SICK.
I'M SCREWED.
>> CRYSTAL, CAN YOU JUST TELL ME
ONE THING YOU'RE WORKING ON?
>> YEAH.
ONE THING, COLIN?
TRY 900 EMAILS -- TODAY.
>> I'M LOOKING AT YOUR EMAILS.
THEY'RE ALL FROM HOROSCOPE.COM.
>> WELL, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
SERIOUSLY, WHAT DO YOU DO?
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR WORK?
>> BUST MY BALLS.
>> I MEAN LIKE WHERE DO YOU
WORK?
>> IN HELL.
AND MY BOSS JUST TEXT -- AND I'M
WORKING ON TURKEY DAY.
I'M SCREWED.
>> STOP THROWING PHONES.
LOOK, CLEARLY YOU'RE OBSESSED
WITH WORK.
I NEED YOU TO TAKE BETTER CARE
OF YOURSELF.
>> GUESS WHAT I HAD FOR DINNER
LAST NIGHT?
A COOKIE AND A CIGARETTE.
MIGHT SURPRISE YOU WHICH ONE I
ATE.
>> JESUS.
>> JUST NEED A ONE-SECOND POWER
NAP.
WHERE AM I?
>> CRYSTAL, THAT'S REALLY SCARY.
DID YOU EVEN EAT TODAY?
>> GOOD REMINDER.
FIRST MEAL OF THE YEAR.
COLD CHIPOTLE, MY FAVORITE.
MM.
KIND OF NICE EATING AT A DESK
AND NOT UNDER IT.
>> YOU EAT UNDER YOUR DESK?
>> AND THERE GOES MY BURRITO
PHONE.
>> YOUR BURRITO PHONE?
WHAT DOES IT -- WHAT DOES IT
SAY?
>> HELLO?
YEP.
JUST AS I SUSPECTED, I'M
SCREWED.
>> CRYSTAL, WHAT IS YOUR JOB
TITLE?
>> BOSS ASS BITCH.
>> I'M LOOKING AT YOUR KEYBOARD
RIGHT NOW, AND NONE OF THE KEYS
ARE IN THE RIGHT ORDER.
AND ALSO THE SPACE BAR IS
MISSING.
>> IF I DON'T GET BREAKS,
NEITHER DO MY WORDS.
>> I'M SORRY TO SAY THIS, BUT
YOU'RE MAKING ME THINK YOU DON'T
ACTUALLY DO ANYTHING FOR WORK.
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY CRAZY BECAUSE
I ACTUALLY HAVE A REALLY
IMPORTANT JOB.
>> YOU DO?
WHAT'S YOUR JOB.
>> I'M THE INSTAGRAM
CHOREOGRAPHER FOR BRITNEY
SPEARS.
>> OH, WOW.
YOUR EXTREMELY BUSY COWORKER
EVERYONE.
>> I'M
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> GREAT.
NOW TELL ME WHY YOU CAN'T SLEEP
AT NIGHT.
>> WELL, EVERY NIGHT WHEN I GO
TO SLEEP, IT FEELS LIKE THERE'S
SOME SORT OF FIGURE WITH ME IN
THE ROOM.
>> WELL, THAT'S VERY COMMON WITH
SLEEP PARALYSIS.
>> OH, IT IS?
THANK GOODNESS.
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE.
>> WE CAN GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
THIS USING THIS COMPUTER, I CAN
INDUCE YOUR HALLUCINATION WHILE
YOU'RE AWAKE SO YOU CAN DESCRIBE
TO ME EXACTLY WHAT YOU'RE SEEING
AS YOU'RE SEEING IT.
CAN YOU DO THAT FOR ME?
>> ALL RIGHT, DR. YI, I'LL DO MY
BEST.
WHOA, OKAY.
THIS FEELS WEIRD.
BUT -- OH, I SEE HIM.
HE'S RIGHT HERE NEXT TO ME.
>> GREAT.
GREAT.
WHAT DOES HE LOOK LIKE?
>> IT'S JUST A GUY, BUT LIKE, A
GAY GUY?
>> NOT JUST ANY GAY GUY, HOMEY.
IT'S ME, TROYE SIVAN.
LET'S GO.
♪
>> HE'S MOVING!
HE'S DANCING?
>> OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, KAYLA.
TRY ASKING HIM WHAT HE IS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU?
ARE YOU A DEMON?
>> NO.
NOT QUITE, GIRLY.
I'M AN AUSTRALIAN YOUTUBER
TURNED INDY POP STAR, AND MODEL
TURNED ACTOR TROYE SIVAN PLAYED
BY AN ACTOR WHO CAN'T DO AN
AUSTRALIAN ACCENT.
BYE, DIVA.
>> WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
>> HE SAID HIS NAME WAS TROYE
SIVAN.
>> OH, NO.
I WAS AFRAID OF THIS.
SHIRT AS SMALL AS CAN BE, PANTS
AS BIG AS THEY COME?
WE'RE SEEING THIS MORE AND MORE
NOW THAT THIS BOY IS SNEAKING
HIS WAY INTO THE MAIN STREAM.
YOU'RE THE FOURTH WOMAN I'VE
SEEN THIS WEEK SUFFERING FROM
THIS.
>> WHY IS TROYE SIVAN DANCING AT
ME?
>> THAT'S HARD TO SAY.
THERE'S A LOT WE DON'T KNOW
ABOUT SLEEP SCIENCE AND TROYE
SIVAN.
>> ISN'T HE KIND OF FAMOUS?
>> HE'S GAY FAMOUS.
IT'S DIFFERENT!
>> SO HE'S LIKE NATHAN LANE?
>> NOT AT ALL.
I'M GOING TO INDUCE YOU AGAIN.
THIS TIME IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
YOU TELL ME EXACTLY WHAT THE
DANCE LOOKS LIKE, OKAY?
>> HEY, HOMEY.
WATCH ME DO CHOREO.
LET'S GO.
>> HE'S BACK, AND HE'S STILL
DANCING.
>> BREATHE, KAYLA.
CAN YOU DESCRIBE THE DANCE?
>> WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S
TRYING OUT A NEW PAIR OF LEGS.
>> WHAT ELSE?
WHAT ELSE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S SHOWING ME -- HE'S SHOWING
ME HIS TINY LITTLE RED UNDIES.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
I'M GOING TO WIN THE AWARD FOR
BEST GAY DOCTCTOR.
>> DR. YI, AM I GOING TO BE
OKAY?
>> MAYBE.
DOES THE DANCE LOOK LIKE THIS?
LET'S GO.
♪
WELL?
WAS IT LIKE THAT?
>> YES.
YES, EXACTLY.
BUT MEDICALLY SPEAKING, DOCTOR,
WHY DOES HE HAVE MY PSYCHE IN A
CHOKE HOLD?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I LOOK LIKE A MOISTURIZED
MACHINE GUN KELLY, AND I'M THE
MOST ICONIC BLOUSE EVER, BYE,
DIVA.
>> WHY DID HE CALL HIMSELF A
BLOUSE?
>> BREATHE, KAYLA, A BLOUSE IS A
FEM TOP!
>> BUT WHY IS THIS HAPPENING TO
ME?
>> ARE YOU A STRAIGHT WOMAN
WHO'S TRIED POPPERS ONCE?
>> YES.
DOCTOR, PLEASE, IS THERE
ANYTHING WE CAN DO TO GET RID OF
HIM?
>> I CAN PRESCRIBE YOU SOMETHING
SO STRAIGHT IT PUSHES HIM OUT OF
YOU.
>> DOCTOR, I CHANGED MY MIND.
I CAN'T GET RID OF HIM.
AT FIRST HE SCARED ME, BUT NOW I
THINK HE'S THE ONLY THING THAT
TURNS ME ON.
>> OH, NO.
I REALLY WISH YOU DIDN'T SAY
THAT, KAYLA.
IF YOU INVITE HIM IN, HE STARTS
TO MULTIPLY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MORE GAY GUYS?
HUBBA, HUBBA.
>> COME ON, TROYS, GET YOUR TINY
T-SHIRTS AND BIG PANTS, AND
LET'S GET INTO THIS WOMAN'S
SUBCONSCIOUS.
>> HEY, HOMEY.
THANKS FOR INVITING US.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S GIVE THIS STRAIGHT WOMAN
WHAT SHE WANTS.
>> OUR TINY LITTLE RED UNDIES.
>> HOW MANY TROYS ARE THERE NOW,
AND DOES THEIR DANCE LOOK LIKE
THIS?
LET'S GO.
DUDE
>> ESPECIALLY ON WRITING NIT
NIGHTS.
OH, MY GOD!
DUDE, LOOK!
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
>> DUDE, DUDE!
>> SIR, SIR?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING WORTH LIVE
FOR.
>> COME ON, MAN.
THERE MUST BE SOMEONE OR
SOMETHING YOU CARE ABOUT.
>> I GUESS.
IT'S MY MUSIC.
>> YOUR MUSIC?
>> YEAH.
I MAKE MUSIC.
I'M TOO MUCH OF A COWARD TO EVER
SHOW ANYONE.
GOD, YOU'RE SO PATHETIC, FRANK.
>> NO, MAN, SHOW US YOUR MUSIC.
>> WE WOULD BE LUCKY TO HEAR IT.
>> REALLY?
>> YES!
>> YES, FRANK, PLEASE, PLAY US
SOME OF YOUR MUSIC!
>> THANK YOU!
SO WHAT DID YOU GUYS THINK?
>> GOOD.
>> REALLY?
>> SOUNDS LIKE IT WAS MADE BY
LIKE A COOL FROG.
>> AND JUST CONSTRUCTIVE
CRITICISM-WISE,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SAY THANK YOU AT THE END OF
YOUR SONG.
>> I GOT LIKE OTHER SONGS.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
>> THANKS IN
>> SHOULD WE JUST LEAVE?
NOBODY SAW US.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS SAYING DOWN
THERE?
>> NOTHING, MAN, THE SONG IS
AWESOME.
SUPER GURGLY.
ARE YOU FEELING BETTER?
YOU WANT TO MAYBE HEAD INSIDE?
>> WOULD YOU SHARE IT ON
INSTAGRAM?
>> IF IT MEANS YOU WON'T KILL
YOURSELF, YEAH.
>> WHAT'S YOUR BAND'S NAME?
>> IT'S H-A-M-A-S.
>> HAMAS?
I'M NOT SHARING A SONG BY HAMAS
ON INS GLAM.
GOD
>> MY LIFE SUCKS!
MY BAND'S NAMED HAMAS.
MY GIRLFRIEND BROKE UP WITH ME.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT'S COMPLICATED.
BUT I WROTE A SONG ABOUT IT.
I CHEATED!
>> THAT'S NOT COMPLICATED, MAN.
>> THERE'S A COP.
HEY, SIR.
>> THIS ONE'S MY FAVE.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> COME BACK, MAN!
>> THIS ONE'S ABOUT MY MOM
PASSING.
>> THEN WHY DOES IT SOUND LIKE
THAT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
A RECORD COMPANY WANTS TO HEAR
MY MUSIC.
>> THERE YOU GO!
NO, NO!
ALL MY SONGS WERE ON THERE.
QUICK, PUT IT IN RICE!
PUT IT IN RICE, QUICK!
>> THAT'S NOT GOING TO HELP,
BUDDY.
>> IT'S SHATTERED.
>> THAT'S IT.
IT'S OVER.
I'M DONE.
>> NO, NO.
>> COME ON.
DUDE, WE CAN HELP YOU.
WE WORK FOR SNL.
MAYBE WE COULD USE ONE OF YOUR
SONGS IN A VIDEO.
>> WAIT.
YOU'RE THOSE GUYS.
>> YEAH, MAN.
WE'RE PLEASE DON'T DESTROY.
AND WE ARE --
>> NAH.
I'M GOOD.
>> OUR VIDEOS CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
>> HE WAS DEPRESSED.
HE WAS A DEPRESSED PERSON.
>> SHOULD WE GET BACK TO WORK?
>>> ONCE AGAIN, BOYGENIUS!
♪ WILL YOU BE A SATANIST
WITH ME MORTGAGE OFF YOUR
SOUL TO BUY YOUR DREAM
VACATION HOME IN FLORIDA ♪
♪ THE COLLATERAL THE DEVIL'S
REPOSSESSIN' FROM ME
TRYIN' TO SCORE SOME
OFF-BRAND ECSTASY ♪
♪ WILL YOU BE AN ANARCHIST
WITH ME SLEEP IN CARS AND
KILL THE BOURGEOISIE ♪
♪ AT LEAST UNTIL YOU FIND
OUT WHAT A FAKE I AM SPRAY
PAINT MY INITIALS
ON AN ATM ♪
♪ I BURN MY CASH AND SMASH
MY OLD TV ♪
♪
♪ WILL YOU BE A NIHILIST
WITH ME IF NOTHIN' MATTERS
MAN THAT'S A RELIEF ♪
♪ SOLOMON HAD A POINT WHEN
HE WROTE ECCLESIASTES IF
NOTHING CAN BE KNOWN
THEN STUPIDITY IS HOLY ♪
♪ IF THE VOID BECOMES A BORE
WE'LL TREAT OURSELVES TO SOME
SELF-BELIEF ♪
♪
SLOW PULL A SEISMIC DRIFT ♪
♪ LEANIN' OVER THE EDGE
OF THE CONTINENT ♪
♪ IT'S SO HARD TO COME BACK
YOU HANG ON UNTIL IT DRAGS
YOU UNDER YOU UNDER
YOU UNDER YOU UNDER ♪
>>> OF COURSE. I CERTAINLY WILL,
MRS. MEDDLESON.
UH-HUH.
BYE BYE, NOW.
WELL, MRS. PIPPENSTUFF, WHAT DID
SHE SAY?
>> THAT SHE AND MR. MEDDLESON
THINK YOU'RE A LOVELY GIRL,
BUT --
>> THEY DON'T WANT TO ADOPT ME,
DO THEY?
>> NO, SWEETHEART.
I'M AFRAID NOT.
OFF TO BED, GIRLS.
IT'S LATE.
>> CASSIDY, IF I WAS A GROWNUP,
I WOULD ADOPT YOU.
>> THANKS, AMEILA.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
OH, MR. MOON, WHAT'S WRONG WITH
ME?
>> WHATEVER DO YOU MEAN,
CASSIDY?
>> I MEAN, SOMETIMES IT FEELS
LIKE NOBODY WANTS ME.
♪ WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME THAT THEY
DON'T UNDERSTAND, WHAT IS IT
ABOUT ME THAT THEY DON'T GET ♪
♪ OH, WHAT IS IT THAT MAKES ME
NEVER GET ADOPTED, OH, WHAT IS
IT ABOUT ME ♪
>> CHIN UP, CASSIDY.
I THINK YOU'RE PERFECT.
♪ IS IT 'CUZ OF MY HAIR ♪
>> IT'S PRETTY.
♪ IS IT 'CUZ OF MY LAUGH ♪
>> THAT'S CUTE!
♪ IS IT 'CUZ I LOVE JUST TOO
MUCH ♪
>> NOT A CHANCE!
♪ IS IT 'CUZ OF MY CLOTHES ♪
>> YOU HAVE STYLE.
♪ IS IT 'CUZ I'M 26 YEARS OLD.
>> WAIT, WHAT?
♪ NO, THAT CAN'T BE IT ♪
>> THAT MIGHT BE IT.
YOU SAID YOU'RE 26 YEARS OLD?
>> WELL, 26 AND 18 MONTHS.
>> SO 27.
YOU'RE 27 YEARS OLD.
>> AND STILL AN ORPHAN.
♪ WHY DON'T I FEEL LIKE THE
OTHER GIRLS ♪
>> 'CUZ YOU'RE OLD!
♪ IS THERE A FAMILY FOR ME ON
THIS EARTH ♪
>> HONESTLY, YOU'RE OLD ENOUGH
TO START YOUR OWN FAMILY.
♪ WILL I FIND PARENTS ON THIS
WHOLE FLAT EARTH ♪
>> OH, NO.
OH, NO
♪ ARE THEY SOMEWHERE ON THIS
EARTH THAT IS DEFINITELY FLAT ♪
>> YOU'RE DUMB TOO?
♪ SO WHAT, I BIT A GIRL LAST
WEEK STRAIGHT DOWN TO THE BONE ♪
>> THE BONE?
♪ AND YEAH, I HAVE $600,000 IN
STUDENT LOANS ♪
>> YOU WENT TO COLLEGE?
>> YES.
♪ BUT I WAS THE ONE WHO ATE THE
BAT IN WUHAN, CHINA ♪
>> YOU STARTED COVID?
♪ AND YEAH, I WRITE SHORT
STORIES WHERE I HAVE SEX WITH
MONSTERS IN A DUNGEON ♪
>> PLEASE STOP.
♪ JUST CHILLING HAVING SEX WITH
GAY GARGOYLES LIKE IT'S MY JOB ♪
>> STOP.
♪ OH, WHAT IT IS ABOUT ME THAT'S
SO HARD TO LOVE ♪
>> I THINK WE'RE RUNNING INTO A
FEW POSSIBLE ISSUES HERE.
>> YO, CASSIDY, BABY, YOU GET
ADOPTED YET?
>> NOT YET, PUTTY.
>> DAMN.
>> I'M SORRY.
WHO'S THAT?
>> IS THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND OR
SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, MAN.
I'M PUTTY, MAN.
I'M 49 AND 30 MONTHS.
>> SO YOU'RE 51.
>> NO DOUBT.
BUT CASS, BABY, YOU GOT TO GET
ADOPTED, GIRL.
REMEMBER THE PLAN.
>> HOLD UP.
THE PLAN?
THAT SOUNDS SO SHADY.
WHAT PLAN?
>> I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT,
SILLY MOON.
♪ STEP ONE, WHILE MY NEW DAD IS
SLEEPING, I MAKE A MOLD OF HIS
TEETH, YEAH ♪
♪ STEP TWO, I GIVE THE TEETH TO
PUTTY --
>> STOP SINGING!
STOP IT.
DON'T CALL ME SILLY MOON, OKAY?
MY CONCERNS ARE VERY VALID.
YOU HAVE SOME SHADY PLAN WITH
YOUR 51-YEAR-OLD BOYFRIEND NAMES
PUTTY?
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
FACTS.
>> I KNOW I'M YOUR IMAGINARY
FRIEND, BUT I CAN'T HANG WITH
YOU ANYMORE.
SORRY.
>> OH, MR. MOON, MR. MOON!
OH, WELL, AT LEAST I HAVE MY
REAL FRIENDS.
>> GET OUT!
♪ OH, WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME ♪
>> YOU'RE A BAD PERSON.
EVERYONE HERE AT THE CALM APP IS
THE BIGGEST FAN.
>> OH, MAN, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LISTEN TO YOUR MEDITATIONS ALL
THE TIME ON SET.
THIS IS HUGE FOR ME.
>> AWW.
SO YOU KNOW THE DRILL THEN.
JEANETTE WHO WROTE THE SLEEP
STORY WILL BE LISTENING IN AS
WELL.
>> HI.
THANK YOU.
>> LET US KNOW IF YOU HAVE ANY
QUESTIONS.
SHALL WE GET CALM?
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
>> HI.
I'M TIMOTHEE CHALAMET.
AND TONIGHT I'M GOING TO READ
YOU A SLEEP STORY.
SO TURN DOWN THE LIGHTS, AND LET
EVERYTHING FADE AWAY.
THIS IS THE SPLENDOR OF NATURE.
AS THE SUN SET AND THE CITY FELT
QUIET, THE SOFT WINDS WHOOSHED
OVER THE BUILDINGS AND INTO THE
GARDEN WHERE DAPHNE WAS PLANTING
SUNFLOWERS.
THAT WAS HER PLACE OF PEACE.
THEN SHE STEPPED ON A MOON PIE.
OH, HELL KNOW.
WHAT THE HELL.
SURE ENOUGH, A DOG HAD DOODIED
IN THE AZALEAS.
BIG DUMP.
IS THE SLEEP STORY ABOUT A DOG
POOPING IN THE GARDEN?
>> IS THAT AN ISSUE?
>> NO.
JUST MAKING SURE.
>> AND MAYBE A LITTLE LESS
CHATTER IN BETWEEN TAKES.
COOL?
>> SURE.
MY BAD.
ALL RIGHT.
THE GARDEN WAS FULL OF
POTENTIAL.
THERE WERE PLANTS TO POT,
FLOWERS TO BLOOM.
I SWEAR TO GOD IF HIS BLIND ASS
BRINGS THAT DUMB DOG ROUND HERE
AGAIN, I'M GOING TO BE SERIOUSLY
PISSED OFF.
HELL, I MIGHT EVEN SWING ON HIM.
I'M SORRY, AREN'T PEOPLE
SUPPOSED TO BE FALLING ASLEEP TO
THIS?
>> YOU ARE GOING TO DRIVE ME
CRAZY, BABY BOY.
YOU HAVE TO GAB, DON'T YOU?
>> I MEAN NO DISRESPECT.
IT'S A GREAT STORY.
>> THEN READ THE WORDS, CHATTY
LITTLE BITCH.
>> OKAY.
AND YOU WANT IT LOUDER?
YOU'RE SURE?
DAPHNE WAS SO PISSED SHE PICKED
UP A ROCK, AND SHE THREW IT.
DAMN IT!
NOW I GOT DOO DOO ON MY HANDS!
I CAN'T GO TO THE BALL LIKE
THIS.
I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET THE
PRESIDENT TONIGHT.
THIS SUCKS!
>> BETTER.
NOT GOOD, BUT BETTER.
>> OKAY.
AND YOU WANT ME TO SCREAM AT
THIS PART?
>> YEAH, MAN.
>> AHH!
>> NOT LIKE THAT.
DO IT QUIET.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING -- YOU
JUST SAID DO IT LOUD.
>> NOT THE SCREAM.
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO SLEEP TO
THIS.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST GONE
WITH SPONGEBOB AI, MAN.
>> WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, TIMMY,
YOU ARE A NIGHTMARE TO WORK
WITH.
>> WHAT?
YOU OKAY, MAN?
MAYBE YOU NEED TO RELAX.
>> I JUST DON'T FEEL NORMAL NO
MORE.
EVERYTHING'S CHANGING SO FAST.
MY MOM TOLD ME TO LOSE WEIGHT.
MY BUMBLE PROFILE SUCKS.
>> LET IT OUT, BABY.
>> I HAVE A MILLION DOLLARS, AND
I LOOK EXACTLY LIKE BRAD PITT.
WHY DON'T WOMEN LIKE ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I THINK YOU HAVE SOME STUFF YOU
NEED TO WORK THROUGH.
>> NAH.
THAT'S NOT IT.
TELL YOU WHAT, WOULD YOU DO
SOMETHING FOR ME, TIMMY?
>> WHAT?
>> WOULD YOU KICK ROCKS, BUDDY?
GET OUT OF HERE.
>> WHATEVER, MAN.
>> WHO'S UP NEXT?
BETTER BE SOMEONE GOOD.
>> YEAH.
WE GOT ALEC BALDWIN.
>> OKAY.
TESTING ONE, TWO, THREE.
OKAY, EVERYBODY.
LET'S GET CALM!
>> YEAH!    We are Grocery
>>> THANK YOU TO BOYGENIUS!
ALEC BALDWIN.
BIG THANKS TO EVERYONE.
BIG THANK YOU TO LAUREN
MICHAELS.
S.A.G. STRIKE IS OVER.
YEA.
AND STAGE MANAGER, YOU GUYS SAW
DONNA RUNNING AROUND.
SHE'S A LEGEND HERE.
CREWS HERE AT SNL ARE L LEGENDS.
EVERYBODY GETS TO GO BACK TO
WORK.
IT'S A GREAT THING.
STAY POSITIVE.
STAY NICE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,