>>> WE NOW GO LIVE TO PRESIDENT
JOE BIDEN'S PRESS CONFERENCE
AFTER HIS LONG-AWAITED MEETING
WITH CHINESE PRESIDENT XI
JINPING.
>> HEY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
IT'S ME, OUR OLD BOY JOE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
TO KEEP THINGS ON THE RAILS, I'M
GOING TO READ FROM THE
TELEPROMPTER.
OUR GREAT MEETING WITH PRESIDENT
ROMAN NUMERAL 11 --
EXCUSE ME.
PRESIDENT XI.
THIS MEETING WAS A TOTAL WIN.
SURE, WE MADE AGREEMENTS ABOUT
COMMUNICATIONS, FENTANYL, CLIMATE CHANGE,
BUT MOST
IMPORTANTLY, WE GOT THE THING
AMERICA REALLY NEEDS RIGHT NOW,
MORE PANDAS.
ALL RIGHT.
I LIKE TO OPEN UP TO QUESTIONS.
FIRST UP, WALL STREET JOURNAL.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
CHINA RELATIONS BROKE OFF THIS PAST YEAR,
PARTLY BECAUSE YOU
CALLED PRESIDENT XI A DICTATOR.
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BUT YOUR SUMMIT LAST WEEK SAW
REMARKABLE STRIDES IN MENDING
THAT RELATIONSHIP.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COMPLETELY
UNDO YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENT BY
CALLING HIM A DICTATOR AGAIN?
>> I WOULD.
NEXT QUESTION, LA TIMES.
>> THANK YOU MR. PRESIDENT
AND CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR HISTORIC
AND PRODUCTIVE SUMMIT.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
YOU'RE OLD.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M NOT SURE HOW THAT'S A
QUESTION.
I MEAN, MAN, WHY CAN'T WE TALK
ABOUT THINGS THAT ARE GOING WELL
LIKE THE ECONOMY?
WE OUTPACED CHINA FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN 40 YEARS.
OR HOW I CREATED THE MOST JOBS
SINCE FDR.
GO AHEAD.
WASHINGTON POST, ASK AWAY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, I WOULD LIKE
TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE HANDLING OF
THE BORDER CRISIS.
>> OH, GOOD, YEA.
ALL RIGHT.
THE BORDER.
I GOT TO GET SOMETHING.
LET ME TAKE THE ELEVATOR REAL
QUICK.
JUST ONE SECOND.
SORRY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, DON'T DO A
FAKE ELEVATOR TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET ME JUST TAKE IT BACK UP.
LITTLE BOUNCE.
ALL RIGHT.
MOVE AWAY FROM THAT TOPIC BY
WELCOMING A VERY IMPORTANT
CHINESE DIGNITARY
TO HELP SHED
LIGHT ON WHAT HAPPENED THIS
WEEK.
PLEASE WELCOME TIN TIN.
>> HELLO.
IT'S ME, TIN TIN.
>> HI, TIN TIN.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WE'RE ALL EXCITED TO HEAR FROM A
GIANT PANDA.
>> OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
THANK YOU.
BUT NO NEED TO SAY GIANT.
I THINK I'M REALLY MORE
SLIM-THICK.
>> OKAY.
>> TRULY, I'M HONORED TO BE
HERE.
AM I THE ONLY ONE THAT WAS
SURPRISED THAT THE PRESIDENTS OF
THE TWO BIGGEST ECONOMIES IN THE WORLD MET,
AND EVERYONE'S JUST
LIKE, WHAT'S UP WITH THE PANDAS?
I MEAN, I'M HOT, I'M SMART, I'M
ALLURINGLY ASEXUAL,
BUT THERE
HAS TO BE BIGGER ISSUES, RIGHT?
>> NOT TONIGHT.
NEXT QUESTION.
HOW ABOUT AXIOS?
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN, TRUMP'S TEAM
HAS ANNOUNCED
THEY WILL REPLACE
ALL FEDERAL WORKERS WERE TRUMP
LOYALISTS.
MY QUESTION IS -- PANDA, DID YOU
LIKE AMERICA?
>> HONESTLY, I LOVED IT.
THERE'S SO MUCH I'M GOING TO
MISS.
LEGAL WEED --
ANYWAY, GOING BACK
TO CHINA, IT'S GOING TO BE A BIG
CHANGE.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW ANYONE IN
CHINA.
I HAVEN'T BEEN BACK SINCE I WAS A BABY,
AND NOW I HAVE TO MAKE
FRIENDS AS AN ADULT?
YUCK.
HOW DO I PANDA EXPRESS THIS?
I JUST WANT TO EAT BAMBOO,
SNEEZE IN A CUTE WAY,
AND NOT
HAVE SEX.
OKAY?
>> EXCUSE ME, PANDA, THAT'S
RIGHT, YOU REFUSE TO MATE IN THE
ZOO.
WHY DON'T YOU LIKE SEX?
>> HAVE YOU HAD IT?
IT'S CRAZY.
NEXT QUESTION.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND THEY ALL DON'T HAVE TO BE
FOR THE PANDA.
LET'S GET ONE FOR ME.
>> SURE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOUR MIDDLE
EAST POLICY.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK PEOPLE ARE
LIKING THE PANDA, RIGHT?
NEXT QUESTION.
>> XI DESCRIBED YOU PANDAS AS
ENVOYS OF FRIENDSHIP.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> SORRY.
BEAR WITH ME.
BEING CUTE.
BUT AS THE RARE PERSON WHO
IDENTIFIES AS BLACK, WHITE, AND CHINESE,
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN THE
UNIQUE POSITION TO UNITE MANY
PEOPLES OF THE WORLD.
I'M JUST LIKE ANOTHER HOT
BLASIAN ICON, TIGER WOODS,
EXCEPT FOR, AGAIN, I HATE SEX.
YES, YOU, SIR?
>> HEY, I THOUGHT I PICKED THE
REPORTERS.
>> YEAH, BUT THE PANDA ALREADY
CHOSE ME.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT RETURNING
TO CHINA?
>> HONESTLY, I THINK THE TIMING
IS RIGHT.
I HAVE TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY NOW,
YOU KNOW.
IF TRUMP GETS ELECTED IN 2024,
THAT WOULD BE A DISASTER.
HE SAID HE'LL ROUND UP
IMMIGRANTS AND PUT THEM IN
CAMPS.
DEMOCRACY MIGHT END.
THERE MIGHT BE A CIVIL WAR.
>> SO YOU WILL VOTE FOR BIDEN?
>> MM, MAYBE.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
HEY, MAN.
>> I'M KIDDING.
I'M A BEAR.
I CAN'T VOTE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, I'M GLAD WE DID THIS,
PANDA.
NOW, YOU AND I REALLY AREN'T SO
DIFFERENT.
WE'RE DADS, WE'RE CUTE,
PEOPLE LOVE SHARING VIDEOS OF US
FALLING DOWN.
ANYTHING ELSE YOU WANT TO SAY
BEFORE YOUR 19-HOUR COACH FLIGHT
BACK TO CHINA?
>> YEAH.
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, JASON
MOMOA!
>>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT IS GREAT TO BE BACK AT SNL.
IT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME.
MY MOM IS HERE.
IF YOU SEE HER, BE CAREFUL,
SHE'S STILL RECOVERING FROM
GIVING BIRTH TO ME.
BUT I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
I LOVE THIS PLACE.
I LOVE LIFE!
I LOVE --
I LOVE WAKING UP WASHING MY
LUXURIOUS HAIR
WITH A FULL BODY OF SHAMPOO,
AND I LOVE PLAYING
AQUA MAN.
BECAUSE I LOVE THE OCEAN.
IT'S TRUE.
GROWING UP, ALL I WANTED TO BE
WAS A MARINE BIOLOGIST,
WHICH
MAKES SENSE BECAUSE I'M BUILT
LIKE A SCIENTIST.
THE PROBLEM WAS THAT EVEN THOUGH
I WAS BORN IN HAWAII, I GREW UP IN IOWA,
AND NOT REALLY KNOWN
FOR THEIR OCEANS.
THEN ONE DAY, I WAS SITTING AT
HOME
WATCHING A MOVIE CALLED "IN GOD'S HANDS",
WHICH WAS SHOT IN HAWAII,
AND I SAW MY COUSIN
BRIAN IN THESE 50 FOOT WAVES,
IOWA
SO
I WENT BACK TO HAWAII TO SURF
WITH MY FAMILY,
AND I ENDED UP
GETTING ON A TV SHOW CALLED
BAYWATCH.
I CALL IT THE B WORD.
BUT I FELL IN LOVE WITH ACTING,
AND I ONLY STAYED FOR A FEW SEASONS
BECAUSE YOU REALLY DON'T
WANT TO GET STUCK IN THE B HOLE.
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE MY LIFE HAS
COME FULL CIRCLE.
I DO A LOT OF WORK PROTECTING
OUR OCEANS AND SMALL ISLAND
NATIONS.
I EVEN STARTED MY OWN WATER
COMPANY TO ELIMINATE SINGLE USE
PLASTIC WATER BOTTLES.
THANK YOU.
IT'S CALLED -- WHICH IN HAWAIIAN
STANDS FOR SUCK IT DASANI.
THIS WORK REALLY MEANS A LOT TO
ME.
I'M SERIOUS.
WE'RE GOING TO SAVE THE WHALES,
THE CORAL REEF, THE SPONGEBOBS
BECAUSE JASON MOMOA LOVES LIFE.
THERE IS A SAYING --
TAKE CARE OF THE EARTH, TAKE
CARE OF EACH OTHER.
I AM JASON MOMOA.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.♪
Tate McRae
STICK
PBS
MASTERS OF THE PEN
>> I'M EILEEN TIBBS, AND WELCOME
TO MASTERS OF THE PEN
IN WHICH
WE EXPLORE THE AUTHORS BEHIND
ICONIC BOOKS.
TODAY WE WILL LOOK AT WIZARD OF
OZ AUTHOR, L. FRANK BAUM.
GUEST PROFESSOR
AN EXPERT IN BAUM'S LIFE AND
CAREER.
>> HELLO, EILEEN, AND YOU'RE
WELCOME FOR BEING HERE.
>> OH, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
SORRY.
>> NO WORRIES.
I'M JUST BEING FUN.
>> I UNDERSTAND YOU'VE COME
ACROSS SOME ASTOUNDING FOUND
FOOTAGE.
>> INDEED. IT'S FROM THE EARLY 1900s,
AN
AMATEUR FILM MAKER SHOT NEW YORK CITY,
AND WE SPOTTED L. FRANK
BAUM IN THE BACKGROUND.
>> DID YOU BRING THE FOOTAGE?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, NO.
>> BOO.
>> I'M KIDDING, OF COURSE I
BROUGHT IT.
SIDEWALK
THIS IS FOOTAGE SHOT OUTSIDE A
STORE IN NEW YORK.
THE DATE'S UNKNOWN, BUT IT'S THE
EARLY 1900s.
THAT MAN ON THE BENCH THERE IS
L. FRANK BAUM.
>> OH, WOW.
SOMEONE JUST ZOOMED BY.
THAT MAN WAS FAST.
>> BACK THEN, FILM WAS SHOT AT A
LOWER FRAME RATE, SO EVERYTHING
LOOKED SPED UP.
>> LOOKS LIKE MR. BAUM IS
WRITING SOMETHING.
COULD HE BE WRITING THE WIZARD
OF OZ HERE?
>> THERE ARE SOME CLUES THAT
MAKE US BELIEVE HE IS.
IT'S HARD TO SEE BECAUSE THIS
BUSINESSMAN
HAS NOTED THE
CAMERA.
>> YEAH, HE SEEMS VERY EXCITED.
>> WELL, A FILM CAMERA WAS A
RARE SIGHT BACK THEN,
SO IT'S A
BIG DEAL FOR THIS MAN.
ANYWAY, SO LOOK AT BAUM RIGHT
THERE.
HIS EYES SEEM TO WANDER IN THOUGHT,
THEN HIS GAZE SETTLES
ON SOME SHOES IN THE STORE
WINDOW.
>> ARE THOSE SLIPPERS?
IS THIS THE EXACT MOMENT HE GOT
THE IDEA FOR DOROTHY'S RUBY
SLIPPER --
>> WE'LL NEVER KNOW.
THE BUSINESS GENTLEMAN HAS
BROUGHT HIS LARGE FRIEND TO SEE
THE CAMERA.
>> THE LARGE FRIEND SEEMS VERY
HAPPY TO SEE THE CAMERA.
>> YES.
HE'S CLEARLY VERY PUMPED.
ALL RIGHT.
MR. BAUM SEEMS TO BE TALKING TO
HIMSELF.
ANY IDEA WHAT HE'S SAYING?
>> WELL, THERE IS AI SOFTWARE TO
DECIPHER WHAT HE'S SAYING,
BUT
WE WEREN'T ABLE TO USE IT
BECAUSE THE BUSINESS GENTLEMAN
AND HIS FRIEND
GOT AHOLD OF A
WOMAN'S HAT AND BLOCKED THE
BACKGROUND.
>> THEY THINK THIS IS VERY
HILARIOUS.
>> YEAH.
YES, THEY DO.
KEEP IN MIND, THIS IS THE EARLY 1900s,
SO THIS MIGHT BE THE MOST
FUN THESE PEOPLE HAVE IN THEIR
ENTIRE LIVES.
>> WELL, I LOVE SEEING L. FRANK
BAUM.
>> SO DO I.
AND --
>> THIS WOMAN'S HERE NOW.
UNFORTUNATELY, SHE SEES THE
CAMERA TOO.
>> WOW, SHE IS BLINKING FAST.
HOW DOES SHE DO THAT?
>> I JUST TOLD YOU THE FILM IS
SPED UP.
OKAY.
THERE SHE GOES.
>> OH.
NOW WHAT IS MR. BAUM LOOKING AT?
HE SEEMS INTRIGUED WHATEVER IT
IS.
>> YES.
IT'S HARD TO TELL
BECAUSE AN OLD
LADY WALKS BY, WHO'S --
SURPRISE, THE LARGE FRIEND.
>> YEAH.
>> HE THINKS IT'S THE GREATEST
THING IN THE WORLD.
>> UH-HUH.
SO HERE WE HAVE AN INCREDIBLE
MOMENT WITH MR. BAUM.
HE NOTICES THE CAMERA AND
APPROACHES WITH HIS NOTEBOOK.
>> OH, MY GOD.
DOES HE SHOW HIS NOTEBOOK TO THE
CAMERA?
MAYBE A DRAWING OF A SCARE CROW?
>> WE'LL NEVER KNOW BECAUSE THIS
RANDOM MAN WANTED TO SHOW HIS
HOT DOG.
>> OH, NO, WHY?
>> REMEMBER, THIS WAS THE EARLY 1900s,
PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
WAS GOOD OR INTERESTING.
>> NOW L. FRANK BAUM IS GONE.
>> I WISH WE HAD MORE TO SHOW
YOUR VIEWERS.
THERE IS A LOT MORE OF THE
BUSINESS MAN AND HIS FRIEND IF
YOU WANT TO SHOW THAT.
>> WHY NOT. THIS IS PBS
SO ONLY ABOUT TEN
PEOPLE ARE WATCHING.
LET'S DO IT.
>> YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
♪ LATELY, IT SEEMS
LIKE THE
MAGIC IS GONE ♪
♪ HE'S THE LOVE OF MY LIFE,
BUT SOMETHING IS WRONG ♪
♪ HE'S STARING OUT THE WINDOW,
WHAT DOES HE SEE ♪
♪ IS HE DREAMING OF ANOTHER WOMAN
HE WANTS MORE THAN ME ♪
♪ HE'S GOT ME FEELING SO ALONE
LIKE OUR HOUSE IS NOT A HOME ♪
♪ WOULD HE BE HAPPIER ON HIS
OWN ♪
>> WHAT YOU THINKING ABOUT,
BABY?
>> ME?
I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT --
♪ THE ROMAN EMPIRE ANCIENT ROME,
FIVE TIMES A DAY IT POPS INTO MY DOME,
WHICH REMINDS ME, IT'S THE DOME,
IT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
THAT I THINK ABOUT ROME ♪
♪ SEE CZAR, DIDN'T GIVE A [ BLEEP ],
DRANK ICE COLD WATER
FROM AN AQUA DUMP ♪
♪ BUT IT'S THE ETERNAL CITY,
IT'S HIM AND HIS TWIN SUCKING ON
A WOLF'S TITTY ♪
BORN
>> HE'S A SPECIAL LITTLE GUY.
I HAND HIM TO HIS DADDY.
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S GONNA CRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW HIS HEART IS FILLED WITH --
ROME, ROME,
EYE
IN THE YEAR DOUBLE M, DOUBLE X TRIPLE I.
DID YOU KNOW THAT THEIR STATUES
WEREN'T WHITE ♪
WHAT
♪ THEY PAINTED THEM IN COLORS
BOLD AND BRIGHT ♪
DAMN
♪ HE ILL KILLED HIS OWN MOTHER,
WHEN THEY KILLED HIS [ BLEEP ]
THEY SAT NEXT TO EACH OTHER ♪
♪ BILLS PILING UP ♪
BANK
♪ GLADIATORS,
IT'S NOT LIKE THE
MOVIE, THEY MOSTLY STAY ALIVE,
GOOD
THEY FEELING USED TODAY,
AND
EMPEROR ADRIENNE, OPENLY GAY ♪
♪ IT'S ROME, ROME, ANCIENT ROME,
THEY HAVE CENTRAL AIR AND HEAT
IN THE HOME ♪
NO. YOU'RE DONE.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I SAID YOU'REE THE
BUSY GODS RIGHT NOW.
>> STOP TALKING ABOUT ROME ALL
THE TIME.
YOU GOT OUR SON DOING IT TOO.
>> ROME?
NO.
I'M THINKING ABOUT
DINOSAURS,
Big Diplodocus to Tyrannosaurus
THEY RULED THE WORLD,
BUT NOW THEY NOT AROUND,
ONLY
TRACES NOW BURIED IN THE
GROUND ♪
♪ KIND OF LIKE ROME, ROME,
ANCIENT ROME ♪
Founded London and Paris, Zurich and Cologne
And in terms of religion
>> HEY, NO!
YOU NEED TO BE THINKING ABOUT
THINGS THAT MATTER TODAY.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE --
♪ ASTROLOGY, astrology, reading the stars
AND HOW THEY
DETERMINE WHO WE ARE,
He's a Scorpio, I know he's gonna cheat all day
♪ AND IF YOU A TRIPLE GEMINI
STAY THE [ BLEEP ] AWAY ♪
ASTROLOGY
>> THE ROMANS ARE ACTUALLY INTO
ASTROLOGY TOO.
>> I SAID YOU'RE DONE!
♪ IN ROME ♪
>>> COME ON IN, COME ON IN.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON IN.
WOW.
MAN, I LOVE WORKING AT THE CLUB,
MAN.
>> EVERYBODY, THEY LOVE US.
WE GOT THE POWER.
>> BUT REMEMBER, RUI, WHEN YOU
GOT THE POWER, YOU GOT THE
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> LIKE SPIDERMAN.
>> YEAH, RUI, THAT'S RIGHT.
LIKE A SPIDERMAN.
BUT, REMEMBER, WHEN YOU SAY NO
TO THE PEOPLE, YOU GOT TO BE
NICE.
YOU GOT TO LET THEM DOWN EASY.
>> SO THEY LEAVE, BUT THEY NO
CRY.
>> YES, RUI.
THAT'S RIGHT, RUI.
YOU SO SMART.
WHO'S NEXT?
COME ON, MOMMYS.
COME IN.
>> HI.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU LOOK AMAZING, MOMMY.
YOU LOOK LIKE CAMERON DIAZ.
>> AWW, GRACIAS MI AMIGO.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
JUST SAY THANK YOU NEXT TIME.
OKAY?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
>> WHAT?
YOU LET MY FRIEND IN.
NOW I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO, RUI.
BE NICE.
>> SO YOU KNOW WHEN ONE BIRD IS
BEAUTIFUL, LIKE A BLUE BIRD OR A
FLAMINGO?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ARE AN UGLY PERSON.
>> RUI!
NO, RUI!
RUI!
YOU SAY THAT TO HER, NOW SHE'S
GOING TO BE SAD, RUI.
OH, MY GOD, MOMMY.
YOU GO IN, AND YOU GET A BOTTLE
ON ME.
>> OH, WOW, THANK YOU.
>> YES.
A BOTTLE OF BUD LIGHT.
ENJOY.
>> I WAS TRYING TO TELL HER
SOMETHING.
>> I KNOW, RUI.
I KNOW.
IT'S NOT EASY TO BE SPIDERMAN.
OKAY.
NEXT, PLEASE.
>> HEY.
MY GIRLFRIEND'S ALREADY IN
THERE.
>> WHOA.
>> HEY, NOW, RUI, WATCH THIS.
LISTEN HOW NICE I'M GOING TO BE.
MY FRIEND, IMAGINE THAT YOU'RE
GETTING MARRIED, RIGHT?
>> OH, WOW, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> IT'S NOT REAL, RUI.
OKAY.
IMAGINE ME AND RUI, WE SHOW UP
TO YOUR WEDDING, RIGHT, AND
WE'RE WEARING SHORTS, FLIP
FLOPS, AND NO SHIRT.
>> OH.
I DIDN'T REALIZE MY CLOTHES WERE
SO BAD.
>> NO, NO, NO.
LISTEN, LISTEN, I'M TRYING TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
>> YOU KNOW WHEN THERE'S A
GARAGE FULL OF CARS, AND LIKE A
LAMBORGHINI, A FERRARI?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ARE LIKE AN UGLY PERSON.
>> RUI!
RUI!
COME ON, MAN!
>> CAN YOU JUST LIKE ASK THE
MANAGER OR SOMETHING?
MY GIRLFRIEND IS LITERALLY IN
THERE.
>> YES.
I'M GOING TO ASK HIM.
ONE SECOND.
>> HEY, MAN, I SORRY I CALLED
YOU AN UGLY PERSON.
>> IT'S FINE.
>> I JUST SAID THAT BECAUSE I'M
LIKE SPIDERMAN.
>> OH, COOL.
SO CAN I GO IN?
>> NO.
YOU'RE TOO UGLY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FINE.
>> HEY, CONGRATULATIONS ON THE
WEDDING.
>> WHERE DID HE GO?
RUI!
WHAT HAPPENED, MAN?
YOU MAKE HIM LEAVE, MAN?
NOW THAT GUY, THE WHITE GUY, HE
GONNA LEAVE A BAD REVIEW ON
YELP, AND HUMAN RELATIONS,
PUBLIC RESOURCES, RUI.
>> RUI, TONY, LOOK AT THIS LINE,
MAN.
YOU TALKING TO EVERYBODY FOR TOO
LONG.
>> ARE YOU MAD AT US?
>> NO, NO, NO.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU HIRE TWO GUYS
TO LET PEOPLE INTO THE CLUB, BUT
THEY KEEP TALKING IN METAPHORS
AND THEY DON'T LET ANYBODY INTO
THE CLUB?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY,
BOSS?
>> ARE WE FIRED?
>> NO, NO, NO, LISTEN.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
YES, YOU FIRED.
>> NO!
>> RUI!
THANKSGIVING WEEK AIRPORT
PARADE.
♪ IT'S CHAOS, IT'S MAYHEM, AND
EVERYONE'S AFRAID, IT'S
THANKSGIVING WEEK AIRPORT
PARADE ♪
>> GOOD MORNING FROM NEWARK
AIRPORT, EVERYONE'S THIRD
CHOICE.
UMBERTO, IS THAT SPANISH?
>> NO.
IT'S FILIPINO.
YOUR BOY'S PINOI.
>> WELL, IT'S THE BIGGEST
TRAVELING WEEK OF THE YEAR, AND
THE PARADE WILL DRAW THOUSANDS
OF TRAVELERS.
WHO CAN WE EXPECT TO SEE THIS
YEAR?
>> SOME NEW APPEARANCES AS WELL
AS SOME TIMELESS CLASSICS.
>> UP FIRST, IT'S A COUPLE ON
THEIR LAST THANKSGIVING TRIP
TOGETHER.
>> CAN YOU JUST NOT BE VEGAN FOR
ONE DAY.
>> DON'T.
>> TURKEY IS BARELY A MEAT, AND
YOU DON'T GET ENOUGH PROTEIN.
>> I SAID DON'T.
>> SOUNDS LIKE HE BETTER DON'T.
>> NEXT, AN AIRPORT STAPLE.
IT'S A WOMAN WITH A SERVICE
ANIMAL SHE CLEARLY DOESN'T NEED.
>> WOW, MA'AM, YOU ARE REALLY
GOING FOR IT THIS YEAR, THREE
DOG?
>> THIS ONE'S FOR MY ROSACEA.
THIS ONE'S FOR ME ECZEMA, AND
THIS ONE'S FOR MY ANXIETY.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE ANXIETY?
>> I'M TRAVELING WITH THREE
DOGS!
>> OF COURSE.
LET'S THROW IT OVER TO THE
PARADE STAMGING AREA, AKA, THE
BAR WITH CAPTAIN GARY ROGERS.
GARY.
>> THANKS UMBERTO.
OH, CHAR, YOU LOOKING GOOD.
YOU LIKE MY STRIPES?
>> I SURE DO.
ME AND CAPTAIN GARY GOT A LITTLE
FLIRTATION GOING ON.
I'M TRYING TO BE TAPPING THE
CAPTAIN.
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, I GIVE
EVERY WOMAN I SLEEP WITH ONE OF
THESE NICE LITTLE WING PINS.
>> YUCK.
THOSE ARE SUPPOSED TO BE FOR
KIDS.
ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP NOW IS A TSA AGENT
SHOUTING THE SAME THING 12
DIFFERENT WAYS.
>> LAPTOP OUT THE BAG.
LAPTOP OUT THE BAG.
IF YOU GOT A LAPTOP IN THE
BAGGING WITH GO ON AND TAKE IT
OUT.
>> IT'S LIKE HE'S STUCK ON LOOP.
>> SIR, ARE YOU ENJOYING THE
PARADE?
>> LAPTOP OUT THE BAG.
>> WONDERFUL.
NEXT UP, YOU MAY THINK THIS IS A
SLOW BASED ON HOW SLOWLY SHE'S
MOVING, BUT IT'S ACTUALLY A
WOMAN WHO TOOK HER AMBIEN A
LITTLE TOO EARLY.
>> DO NOT LET ME ORDER A WINE.
>> LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GETTING AN
AUDIENCE QUESTION FOR CAPTAIN
GARY.
GARY, WHAT ARE YOUR THANKSGIVING
PLAN?
>> SPENDING IT AT HOME IN MY
APARTMENT WITH 14 OTHER PILOTS.
>> A MAN WITH ROOMMATES.
THAT'S MY TYPE.
>> WE'RE NOW ENTERING THE FAMILY
PORTION OF THE PARADE.
>> YES.
IT'S A GENTLE PARENTING FATHER
AND HIS OUT OF CONTROL EVIL
CHILD.
>> HANNAH, SWEETIE, YOUR
FEELINGS ARE VALID, BUT DADDY
WONDERS IF THERE'S A MORE
PRODUCTIVE WAY TO EXPRESS
YOURSELF BECAUSE WE WANT TO HAVE
A GOOD THANKSGIVING, RIGHT?
>> SCREW YOU, BITCH.
>> SEE, SOMETIMES YOU JUST GOT
TO WHOOP THEM.
WHOOP 'EM.
>> CAPTAIN GARY, WHAT YOU GOT
COOKING?
>> I'M HERE WITH A GUY WHO WANTS
A PATDOWN FOR ALL THE WRONG
REASONS.
>> YOU CAN USE THE FRONT OF YOUR
HAND IF YOU WANT.
>> WHY WOULD I WANT THAT?
>> BROTHER, I LIKE YOUR STYLE.
>> OOH, YIKES.
I HOPE CAPTAIN ROGERS ISN'T
ABOUT TO FLY, BUT IF HE IS, I
PRAY MY EX-BOYFRIEND IS ON THE
FLIGHT.
I WON'T SAY HIS NAME BECAUSE I'M
CLASSY, SO I'LL JUST FLASH HIS
NAME ON THE SCREEN.
>> AND WOW, LOOK, IT'S AN
AIRPORT PARADE MAIN STAY, WOMAN
WHO REFUSES TO CHECK A BAG.
>> 75 DAMN DOLLARS TO CHECK A
BAG.
THAT TICKET TO BOSTON WAS ONLY
40 DAMN DOLLARS.
MAKE THAT MAKE DAMN SENSE.
>> WELL, DAMN.
>> IT'S TIME FOR OUR GRAND
FINALE.
THE IT'S THE BIGGEST STAR OF THE
PARADE, WOMAN WHO'S ABOUT TO GO
VIRAL.
>> I AM TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW,
THAT IS NOT REAL.
>> YO, THIS VIDEO GON' GO VIRAL
ON BLACK TWITTER AND WHITE
TWITTER.
>> NOW WE HAVE ONE LAST SURPRISE
PERFORMANCE BY THE ONLY PEOPLE
HAPPY TO BE WORKING THIS WEEK.
IT'S THE GAY FLIGHT ATTENDANTS
WHO ARE ESTRANGED FROM THEIR
FAMILIES.
>> MY CHOSEN FAMILY IS MY
COWORKERS.
>> WELL, WE'VE HAD A LOVELY
THANKSGIVING WEEK AIRPORT
PARADE.
HAVEN'T WE, CHARTRAUSE?
WHERE DID SHE GO?
>> SHE WAS GETTING HER WINGS.
>> OH, DAMN IT.
>> PEOPLE USE THAT ROOM FOR
BREAST FEEDING.
>> SO DID HE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT TO SING OURSELVES OUT.
LET'S GO
♪ BE SURE TO REMEMBER, WE'RE
BACK IN DECEMBER FOR THE
CHRISTMAS WEEK AIRPORT PARADE ♪
>>> I AM HUNGRY AS A HORSE.
>> I'M STARVING.
>> SHOULD WE DO RAMON FEVER?
IT'S SO GOOD.
HAVE YOU HAD IT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT THAT
PLACE.
>> DUDE, I'LL GET THE ORDER.
>> RAMON TIME.
>> RAMON FEVER, BOYS.
>> RAMON FEVER!
RAMON FEVER!
>> HEY, BABY.
SO FEE I CAN'T.
>> I GOT A PRESCRIPTION, AND THE
ONLY RAMON IS MORE FEVER.
>> YOU ALMOST HAD IT.
>> SOPHIA JUST BROKE UP WITH ME.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO MOVE IN
TOGETHER.
GOD
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M FREAKING OUT.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> MY WHOLE PAST TWO YEARS HAS
BEEN ENTIRELY ABOUT HER.
RAMEN FEVER
>> ME AND MARTIN ARE GOING TO BE
HERE FOR YOU 100%.
>> I FEEL LIKE MAYBE SHE'S JUST
LIKE UPSET, AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I DID.
FOOD
YUP
BELIEVE
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT'S HER DEAL?
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING SPEND
THE REST OF OUR LIFE TOGETHER.
NOW SHE'S LIKE, WHAT, LEAVING ME
ALL ALONE.
>> HEY, DUDE,
WHAT DO I DO, MAN?
>> YOU'RE ASKING ME?
>> WAS SHE EMBARRASSED OF ME?
ADD A PORK BUN
LIKE,
SHE NEVER INTRODUCED ME TO
HER FRIENDS,
AND IT'S LIKE, AM I
A LOSER?
>> YES.
>> DUDE, COME ON, MAN.
>> NO.
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND SOMEONE
NEW.
SOMEONE WHO DESERVES YOU.
>> YEAH, JOHN.
MAYBE EVEN SOMEONE WHO'S SPICY.
>> SPICY?
>> MAYBE MEDIUM SPICY.
>> WITH BUNS, WITH EXTRA BUNS.
>> LIKE A PLAIN LOOKING GIRL
WITH A BIG ASS?
GUESS
>> MAYBE SHE'LL EVEN HAVE BABY
BACH CHOI.
TALKING
FEEL BETTER
I DON'T THINK SOFIA IS GOING
TO LAND ANYONE AS GOOD AS YOU.
>> THANKS, MAN.
VERGARA
SORRY
I FEEL SO DEFEATED.
PAY
YESTERDAY
>> HEY, JOHN.
>> YEAH.
>> GIVE ME A HUG, BUD.
>> SOMETIMES YOU JUST NEED A HUG
FROM SOMEONE YOU TRUST.
>> OF COURSE, MAN.
I LOVE YOU.
>> THIS IS THE HARDEST DAY OF MY
ENTIRE LIFE, AND I --
>> TEXT FROM MARTIN.
I'M TOO HUNGRY TO LISTEN TO THIS
BITCH COMPLAIN.
>> IS THAT ABOUT ME?
ORDER
♪
♪ HE SAID, ARE YOU SERIOUS
I'VE TRIED, BUT I CAN'T ♪
♪ FIGURE OUT
I'VE BEEN NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ ALL NIGHT AND STILL DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE ABOUT ♪
♪ YOU KEEP TA-TA-TA-TALKIN'
BUT NOT MUCH COMIN' ♪
♪ OUT YOUR MOUTH
CAN'T YOU TELL ♪
♪ THAT I WANT YOU
I SAY, YEAH ♪
♪ I WOULD WANT MYSELF
BABY, PLEASE BELIEVE ME ♪
♪ I'LL PUT YOU THROUGH HELL
JUST TO KNOW ME ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH
SO SURE OF YOURSELF ♪
♪ BABY, DON'T GET GREEDY
THAT JUST WON'T END WELL
END WELL ♪
♪ UH-UH, UH-UH-UH
UH-UH, WOO ♪
♪ I SEE YOU EYEIN' ME DOWN
BUT YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ MUCH PAST MY NAME
OR HOW I'M RUNNIN' THIS ♪
♪ ROOM AROUND AND THAT I'M
STILL HALF YOUR AGE ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU'RE
LOO-LOO-LOO-LOOKIN' AT ME
LIKE I'M SOME SWEET ESCAPE ♪
♪ OBVIOUS THAT YOU WANT ME
BUT I SAID ♪
♪ I WOULD WANT MYSELF
BABY, PLEASE BELIEVE ME ♪
♪ I'LL PUT YOU THROUGH HELL
JUST TO KNOW ME ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH
SO SURE OF YOURSELF ♪
♪ BABY, DON'T GET GREEDY
THAT JUST WON'T END WELL
END WELL ♪
♪ HE SAID, I'M JUST CURIOUS
IS THIS FOR REAL ♪
♪ OR JUST AN ACT
CAN'T TELL IF YOU ♪
♪ LOVE OR HATE ME
NEVER MET SOMEONE ♪
♪ LIKE THAT
DRIVE ME SO SO SO CRAZY ♪
♪ DID YOU KNOW YOU
GOT THAT EFFECT
I SAID, LEMME CHECK ♪
♪ I WOULD WANT MYSELF
BABY, PLEASE BELIEVE ME ♪
♪ I'LL PUT YOU THROUGH HELL
JUST TO KNOW ME ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH
SO SURE OF YOURSELF ♪
♪ BABY, DON'T GET GREEDY
THAT JUST WON'T END WELL
END WELL ♪
♪
♪ I WOULD WANT MYSELF ♪
♪ UH-UH, UH-UH-UH, UH ♪
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>> AFTER PRESIDENT BIDEN
SUCCESSFUL MEETING WITH CHINA'S
PRESIDENT XI JINPING,
REPORTERS
ASKED BIDEN IF HE STILL BELIEVED
XI WAS A DICTATOR,
AND I DON'T
KNOW IF BIDEN WAS SUPPOSED TO SAY YES
BECAUSE LOOK AT THIS
REACTION FROM SECRETARY OF STATE
ANTHONY BLINKEN.
REFER
DICTATOR
TERM EARLIER
>> LOOK, HE IS.
>> OH, MAN.
THAT'S THE SAME FACE I MAKE WHEN
MY UNCLE STARTS A STORY
BY
MENTIONING THE RACE OF THE
WAITRESS.
THAT'S ACTUALLY THE SAME FACE I
MADE WHEN I HEARD BIDEN SAY THIS
ABOUT LL COOL J.
>> LLJ COOL J.
BY THE WAY, THAT MAN'S GOT
BICEPS BIGGER THAN MY THIGH.
>> LLJ COOL J?
I THINK THE SECOND J STANDS FOR
JESUS.
>> INSIDERS ARE CONCERNED THAT
PRESIDENT BIDEN'S CHANCES FOR RE-ELECTION
COULD BE DAMAGED BY
HIS UNWAVERING SUPPORT FOR ISRAEL,
BUT I THINK THE BIGGER
PROBLEM IS HE IS SIX YEARS OLDER
THAN ISRAEL.
THE HOUSE ETHICS COMMITTEE
RELEASED ITS REPORT ON GEORGE SANTOS
SEEN HERE ASKING YOUR
GRANDMA FOR HER SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER
AND CONCLUDED THAT THERE
IS SUBSTANTIAL EVIDENCE
HE USED
CAMPAIGN FUNDS FOR SHOPPING AND
COSMETIC PROCEDURES.
SANTOS WOULD HAVE DENIED THE
ALLEGATIONS, BUT HE HAD TO REST
HIS NEW LIPS.
>> SEVERAL MAJOR MEDIA COMPANY,
INCLUDING NBC UNIVERSAL
HAVE
PULLED THEIR ADVERTISING FROM ELON MUSK'S X
OVER CONCERNS ADS
OF THEIR SHOWS COULD BE NEXT TO
PRO-NAZI PROPAGANDA.
RELIEF
WORRIED
END UP
THIS WEEK, DONALD TRUMP JR.
TESTIFIED IN HIS FATHER'S CIVIL FRAUD TRIAL,
AND BASED ON THIS
COURTROOM SKETCH, I FEEL LIKE IT
DIDN'T GO GREAT.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE TALKING
ABOUT REAL ESTATE,
BUT HE LOOKS
LIKE HE'S ON LAW AND ORDER
SAYING THAT GIRL CAME ON TO ME.
UNLIKE THE OTHER PACKED
COURTROOM DAYS, ONLY FOUR PEOPLE SHOWED UP
AND DONALD TRUMP SR.
YUZ NOT PRESENT,
WHICH IS JUST
LIKE ALL DON JR.'S CHILDHOOD
BIRTHDAY PARTIES.
>> THE SUPREME COURT
RECENT
IS ADOPTING
A NEW CODE OF CONDUCT REPLACING
THEIR OLD CODE OF CONDUCT,
MONEY
UP FRONT, NO KISSING ON THE
MOUTH.
SENATOR TIM SCOTT ANNOUNCED HE
IS DROPPING OUT OF THE 2024
PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
WITH SCOTT GONE, THE MOST
PROMINENT BLACK REPUBLICAN
IS
ONCE AGAIN THE BLACKS FOR TRUMP
GUY.
ALL RIGHT.
WHATEVER.
>> A FIST FIGHT ALMOST BROKE OUT
AT A CONGRESSIONAL HEARING
AFTER
MARK WAYNE MULLEN CHALLENGED THE
PRESIDENT OF THE TEAMSTERS TO A
FIST FIGHT.
CHALLENGED TO FIGHT?
DOES HE HAVE A DEATH WISH?
THE TWO THINGS I LEARNED GROWING
UP IN NEW YORK WERE NEVER MESS
WITH THE TEAMSTERS,
AND DON'T
DRINK THAT SNAPPLE YOU FOUND ON
THE SUBWAY.
>> THE MAN WHO ATTACKED NANCY
PELOSI'S HUSBAND WITH A HAMMER
HAS BEEN FOUND GUILTY
AND IS
EXPECTED TO BE IMPRISONED UNTIL
TRUMP'S FIRST DAY BACK AT
PRESIDENT.
HE GON' WIN.
>> NEW YORK MAYOR ERIC ADAMS
RESPONDED TO ALLEGATIONS
HE
ACCEPTED ILLEGAL DONATIONS FROM TURKEY SAYING
I HAVE
NOT BEEN ACCUSED OF WRONG DOING,
AND I WILL CONTINUE TO
COOPERATE.
THEN HE PUT ON HIS FEZ AND SPED
AWAY ON A FLYING CARPET.
NASA RECENTLY DISCOVERED A TINY MOON
ORR BYING THE ASTEROID
300 MILLIION MILES
HERE TO COMMENT IS THE SCIENTIST
WHO MADE THE DISCOVERY.
OH, NO.
IT'S GEORGE SANTOS.
>> HI, GEORGE.
YEAH.
THIS HAS NOT BEEN A GOOD WEEK
FOR YOU.
THE HOUSE ETHICS COMMITTEE
RELEASED A SCATHING REPORT ABOUT
YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> IT SAID YOU SPENT CAMPAIGN
FUNDS ON ONLYFANS.
>> YOU DID.
>> AND PLAYING ROULETTE.
>> YOU LET.
>> SHOPPING AT IRMEZ.
>> YOU'RE THE MEZ.
>> GEORGE, THIS IS SERIOUS.
THEY'RE CALLING FOR YOUR
EXPULSION.
>> WELL, THEN, GIRL, EXPUL ME.
>> THAT IS NOT A WORD.
>> GIRL IS A WORD.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
LOOK, YOU'RE IN CONGRESS, BUT
YOU'RE WATCHING ONLYFANS
INSTEAD.
>> OH, PLEASE.
ISN'T CONGRESS LIKE ONLYFANS
ANYWAY?
PEOPLE PAYING YOU TO DO NASTY
THINGS ON A BAD LIVE STREAM?
>> GEORGE, YOU NEED TO EXPLAIN
YOURSELF.
THE REPORT SAID YOU SPEND
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS ON CLOTHES
AT STORES LIKE FERAGAMO.
WHAT DID YOU BUY?
>> THIS SWEATER.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU PICK SND.
>> OKAY.
YOU'RE A BITCH.
>> YOU ARE.
>> THAT WAS PRETTY CATTY OF ME.
I'M SORRY.
IT ALSO SAID YOU SPENT $3,000 ON
BOTOX.
>> I DIDN'T GET BOTOX.
I GOT BOTOX,
WHICH IS SHORT FOR
BIG OLD THING OF BOTOX.
>> THAT'S JUST THE SAME THING.
>> HOLD ON.
I'M GETTING A CONFERENCE CALL ON
MY PHONE.
HELLO?
PINK, X TINA, MAYA, LIL KIM?
SURE, I'LL BE IN LADY MARMALADE
TWO.
NEXT WEEK?
SEE YOU ON SET.
GEORGE, EVERYTHING OUT OF YOUR MOUTH
IS A LIE.
YOU'RE LYING ABOUT BEING JEWISH.
ARE YOU EVEN GAY?
>> OF COURSE I'M GAY.
I INVENTED BEING GAY.
I WAS THE ONE AT STONE WALL WHO SAID,
HERE'S AN IDEA, YOU GUYS
SHOULD KISS.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT HAPPENED.
JUST STOP LYING.
>> OH, COME ON.
EVERYONE LIES.
LOOK AT YOU WEARING THESE
STRUCTURED SUITS.
ISN'T THAT A LIE LETTING
EVERYONE THINK YOU HAVE A
PERFECT BODY?
>> BUT, GEORGE, I DO HAVE A
PERFECT BODY.
>> HOLD ON.
I HAVE TO TAKE THIS.
HELLO?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> EXCUSE ME.
I'M ON THE PHONE.
IT'S MARTHA STEWART.
HI, MARTHA.
DARK MEAT, PLEASE.
OKAY.
YEAH.
SEE YOU AT FRIENDSGIVING.
OKAY, BYE
>> THAT WAS NOT MARTHA STEWART,
AND THAT IS NOT A PHONE.
>> YES, IT IS.
IT'S THE NEW iPHONE BABY.
>> WELL, GEORGE, YOU HAD QUITE A
RUN.
YOU CAME IN HOT, AND NOW YOU'RE
GOING OUT CHAOTIC.
>> OH, COLIN, EVERYONE JOKES
ABOUT ME, BUT YOU ALL KNOW THE
TRUTH.
YOU'RE GONNA MISS ME WHEN I'M
GONE.
♪ YOU'RE GONNA MISS ME BY MY
SASS, YOU'RE GONNA MISS ME BY MY
ASS ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA MISS ME WHEN I'M
GONE ♪
I INVENTED THIS CUP THING.
>> GEORGE SANTOS, EVERYONE.
>> YOU LOVE ME.
>> THE DATING APP BUMBLE SAYS
THAT NEXT YEAR THEY EXPECT TO
SEE A SURGE IN RELATIONSHIPS
WHERE ONE PERSON DATES SOMEONE
CONSIDERABLY OLDER
THE THOSE
STUDENT LOANS AREN'T GOING TO
PAY FOR THEMSELVES.
>> RUPERT MURDOCH HAS STEPPED
ASIDE AS THE CEO OF FOX NEWS,
PASSING IT ON TO HIS ELDEST SON,
DARTH MURDOCH.
THIS WEEK WAS INTERNATIONAL
FRAUD AWARENESS WEEK,
BUT I'M
AWARE OF A FRAUD EVERY DAY WHEN
I LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT THE
GENDER DEATH GAP IS RISING
WITH
MEN DYING AN AVERAGE OF SIX
YEARS BEFORE WOMEN,
WHICH IS --
YEAH.
IT'S ACTUALLY SCIENTIFIC PROOF
THAT MEN ARE DYING A LITTLE
EVERY TIME WE HAVE TO LISTEN TO
YOUR BORING ASS STORIES.
>> MICHAEL.
A BRITISH WOMAN WHO WAS ARRESTED
FOR KEYING SEVERAL PARKED CARS
BLAMED HER ACTIONS ON, QUOTE,
FEELING MENOPAUSAL.
INCIDENTALLY, FEELING MENOPAUSAL
WAS ALSO THE WORKING TITLE OF
AND JUST LIKE THAT.
>> THIS WEEK, THE NBA SUSPENDED
GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS DRAYMOND GREEN FIVE GAMES
FOR PUTTING
ANOTHER PLAYER IN A CHOKE HOLD.
HERE TO COMMENT IS DRAYMOND
GREEN.
>> THANKS, CHE.
I APPRECIATE Y'ALL GIVING ME
THIS PLATFORM TO PUBLICLY
APOLOGIZE.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU ARE SORRY?
>> HELL NO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO DO IT AGAIN.
>> SO WHY ARE YOU SO ANGRY?
YOU CHOKED RUDY GOBERT FOR NO
REASON.
>> I HAD A REASON.
HE'S A TALL FRENCHMAN WHO'S BEEN
PISSING ME OFF FOR YEARS.
IMAGINE IF YOU HAD A 7-FOOT
BAGETT IN YOUR FACE,
YOU WOULD
WANT TO DO SOMETHING TOO.
>> YOU GOT TO UNDERSTAND WHY THE
LEAGUE IS MAD, RIGHT?
>> NOT REALLY.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CHOKED LeBRON OR
KEVIN DURANT.
WE TALKING ABOUT RUDY GOBERT,
THE FOURTH BEST PLAYER IN
MINNESOTA.
YEARS
SOUNDS LIKE YOU REALLY HOLD A
GRUDGE.
>> I WOULDN'T SAY THAT, BUT WHEN
SOMEONE CROSSES ME, I NEVER
FORGET IT.
I FEEL LIKE THE WHOLE SITUATION
IS BEING BLOWN OUT OF
PROPORTION.
>> YOU CHOKED A MAN DURING A
GAME.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
BUT I WAS TRYING TO KILL HIM.
SO IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT, I
SHOWED RESTRAINT.
>> YOU DON'T FEEL BAD EVEN A
LITTLE BIT?
>> I ALWAYS FEEL MAD.
>> NO.
I SAID BAD.
EVEN YOUR OWN COACH CALLED YOUR
ACTIONS INEXCUSABLE
AND SAID
YOUR FIVE
GAME SUSPENSION WAS DESERVED.
>> HE REALLY SAID THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> HMM, INTERESTING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU WRITING, MAN?
>> JUST A LITTLE LIST.
STUFF I GOT TO DO LATER.
>> DRAYMOND, THIS ISN'T EVEN
YOUR FIRST SUSPENSION.
YOU ONCE STEPPED ON A GUY'S
CHEST.
YOU KICKED ANOTHER PLAYER IN THE
GROWN.
>> I HAD TO KICK HIM IN THE
GROIN.
THAT'S WHERE HIS NUTS AT.
>> WHAT IS ALL THIS REALLY
ABOUT?
>> IT'S SIMPLE.
THE LEAGUE IS TOO SOFT THESE
DAYS.
AIN'T NOTHING BUT A BUNCH OF
LIGHT SKIN DUDES.
SEE ME, I PLAYED DARK SKIN
BASKETBALL.
I AIN'T DRIBBLING ALL FANCY AND
SHOOTING FROM HALF COURT.
I'M PUTTING BIG MEN IN HEAD
LOCKS.
>> BUT WHY?
>> I'M AN ENFORCER.
THAT'S MY JOB.
I SEE MY TEAMMATES IN TROUBLE,
AND I STRANGLE THAT TROUBLE.
ALL I CARE ABOUT IS THE SAFETY
OF MY TEAMMATES.
>> WHAT ABOUT WHEN YOU PUNCHED
YOUR OWN TEAMMATE IN THE FACE?
>> YOU TRYING TO GET ON THE
LIST?
>> NO!
I'M TRYING THE UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE A VERY VIOLENT
REPUTATION.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THAT WASN'T A COMPLIMENT,
MAN.
>> HOW COME NOBODY TALKS ABOUT
THE GOOD STUFF I DO OFF THE
COURT?
EVERY THANKSGIVING,
I GO TO MY
OLD NEIGHBORHOOD AND WHIP
TURKEYS AT PEOPLE.
IT'S FUN.
>> WHAT KIND OF MESSAGE DO YOU
THINK THAT SENDS TO THE KIDS
WATCHING?
>> TO ALL YOU LITTLE HOOPERS OUT
THERE, I HOPE Y'ALL LEARN THIS,
PLAY WITH PASSION, TAKE BOXING LESSONS,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
BE DARK SKINNED.
>> DRAYMOND GREEN, EVERYBODY.
>> SIX FLAGS HAS UNVEILED A PLAN
FOR A NEW ROLLER COASTER, WHICH
WILL BE THE WORLD'S TALLEST AND
FASTEST WITH A 600-FOOT DROP
THAT REACHES SPEEDS OF 150 MILES
AN HOUR.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS IF YOU HIT A
BUG, YOU DIE.
>> A WOMAN REVEALED SHE
ACCIDENTALLY ORDERED A COCKTAIL
THAT COST $2,000.
INGREDIENTS INCLUDES, BEGIN AND
A MAC BOOK PRO.
>> DISNEYLAND HAS ANNOUNCE IT'S
PERMANANTLY CLOSING ITS
ATTRACTION BEASTS LIBRARY AND
REPLACING IT WITH -- THIS IS
WEIRD -- GASTON GAY GYM.
>> A DOCTOR FROM SINGAPORE HAS
GONE VIRAL WITH A VIDEO TELLING
PEOPLE THEY CAN GET RELIEF FROM
CONSTIPATION BY SITTING ON A
TOILET CROSS LEG.
SO THAT'S WHAT THEY MEAN WHEN
THEY SAY CRISSCROSS APPLE SAUCE.
I GET IT NOW.
>> OH, NO, NO.
EVERY WEEK AT SNL, AS YOU KNOW,
WE HAVE A MUSICAL GUEST.
WHAT MANY PEOPLE DON'T KNOW IS
HE ALWAYS BOOK A BACKUP MUSICAL
GUEST JUST IN CASE.
PLEASE WELCOME TONIGHT'S BACKUP
MUSICAL GUEST, REMEMBER LIZARDS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> STOKED TO BE HERE, COLIN.
>> STOKED TO HAVE YOU.
REMEMBER LIZARDS.
THAT NAME SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
I THINK I'VE HEARD OF YOU GUYS.
>> PROBABLY NOT.
YOU'RE PROBABLY THINKING OF
IMAGINE DRAGONS, WHICH IS A
COMMON MISTAKE BECAUSE WE ARE OF
A SIMILAR GENERA.
UPLIFTING KID FRIENDLY HIP HOP
SLASH ARENA ROCK WITH A PUMP UP
EDGE.
>> WHAT DOES THAT SOUND LIKE?
>> IT'S LIKE IMAGINE DRAGONS.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH.
HERE'S AN EXAMPLE.
WE'LL SHOW YOU.
♪
♪ I'M WALKING THROUGH THE WOOD
AND YOU FLIP A SWITCH, AND I
FEEL ELECTRIC, MONKEYS RUNNING
THROUGH MY VEINS, AND THEN YOU
TURN TO ME AND SAY ♪
♪ YEAH, I'M RANDOM, I'M YEAH ♪
>> WOW.
WOW.
NO OFFENSE, BUT THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A REALLY BLATANT RIPOFF OF
IMAGINE DRAGONS.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
>> LOOK, I JUST HONESTLY DIDN'T
REMEMBER WHAT IMAGINE DRAGONS
SOUNDED LIKE, AND THEN I HEARD
YOU GUYS DO A WORSE VERSION OF
IT, AND I REMEMBERED.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> YOU'RE NOT --
>> COLIN, YOU GOT TO COME SEE US
NEXT WEEKEND IN VEGAS.
>> OH, YEAH, MAN, HAVE YOU EVER
HEARD OF THE SPHERE, COLIN.
>> YOU GUYS ARE PLAYING THE
SPHERE?
>> NO, WE'RE PLAYING THE
CYLINDER.
>> IT'S AN ABANDONED GRAIN FARM
IN VEGAS, SOUTH DAKOTA.
>> WE'RE LEAVING RIGHT AFTER
THIS.
WE GOT TO GET THERE A WEEK IN
ADVANCE TO CLEAR OUT THE CROWS.
ANYWAY, CHECK OUT OUR NEW TRACK,
CHEMICAL PARENTHESES POISON.
♪ I TOOK THE POISON FROM THE
CHALLENGE I BE HOLDING, IT'S A
POISON THAT'S FLOWING DOWN MY
THROAT INTO MY SOUL AND THEN I ♪
♪ CHEMICAL, CHEMICAL, YOU GOT ME
WITH THE CHEMICAL, THE CHEMICAL,
CHEMICAL, YOU GOT THE POISON
RUNNING THROUGH MY CHEMICALS
YEAH ♪
>> YOU FEEL THAT, COLIN?
>> YOU GET THAT, CHEMICALS?
>> YEAH, I DEFINITELY HEARD THE
WORD CHEMICAL.
SEEMS LIKE YOU GUYS ARE DOING
LIKE BAD IMAGINE DRAGONS.
>> NO.
WE'RE SIMILAR BUT VERY DISTINCT.
THEIR THING THE POSITIVE ARENA
ROCK THAT IS CHRISTIAN CURIOUS.
>> AND WE DO UPLIFTING ARENA
ROCK THAT IS DECIDEDLY
CHRISTIAN.
>> THAT SOUNDS VERY SIMILAR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> NOT A COMPLIMENT.
>> THINK YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO
LIKE THIS NEXT SONG.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
♪ I GOT THE FIRE BURNING DEEP
INSIDE MY SOUL AND THEN I --
FIRE, MAG MA, LAVA, WE LOVE
LAVA ♪
>> REMEMBER LIZARDS, EVERYONE.
>> IMAGINE DRAGONS ARE REALLY
NICE GUYS.
>> FOR
OVER FOR DINNER.
IT'S KIND OF SUS.
>> I THOUGHT LAIRD WAS DEAD
BECAUSE HIS PLANE EXPLODED OVER
THE OCEAN, AND THEN TWO DAYS
AGO, A CRUISE SHIP FOUND HIM
FLOATING ON A PIECE OF A PORTA
POTTY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
THAT'S HIM.
TRY AND BE NICE, OKAY?
HE WAS STRANDED ON THAT ISLAND
FOR FIVE YEARS.
HE'S PROBABLY ALL MESSED UP AND
FRAIL.
LAIRD.
>> ELAINE.
>> YOU LOOK -- DIFFERENT.
>> THE ISLAND, IT CHANGED ME.
>> I CAN SEE THAT.
>> DIDN'T CHANGE EVERYTHING.
>> I CAN FEEL THAT.
>> UH, I'M DENNIS, BY THE WAY.
I'M ELAINE'S HUSBAND NOW.
SORRY IF THAT'S WEIRD OR
ANNOYING FOR YOU.
>> NOT AT ALL.
I'M GLAD ELAINE FOUND SOMEONE IN
MY ABSENCE.
SHE DESERVES TO BE HAPPY.
>> TOTALLY.
I'M ALWAYS SAYING STUFF LIKE
THAT.
SHE DESERVES TO BE HAPPY.
>> DON'T JUST STAND IN THE
DOORWAY, LAIRD.
COME, SIT DOWN.
>> WELL, I MUST SAY, YOU HAVE A
VERY LOVELY HOUSE, ELAINE.
>> AND DENNIS.
IT'S BOTH OF OURS.
WE LIVE HERE TOGETHER AND MAKE
LOVE OFTEN AND IN ALL THE
POSITIONS.
>> DENNIS, YOU'RE BEING SO
WEIRD, AND THAT'S NOT EVEN TRUE.
WE MAKE LOVE IN ONE POSITION.
>> SIDE TO SIDE, BOTH LAYING
DOWN.
THAT WAY EVERYONE CAN RELAX.
>> GOD, WE'RE BEING SO RUDE.
LAIRD, PLEASE, HAVE SOME WINE.
TONIGHT IS A CELEBRATION.
>> IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE
I'VE HAD WINE.
TO OLD REKINDLING FLAMES.
>> TO OLD REKINDLING FLAMES.
>> BUT AND TO LOYALTY.
>> OH, I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT HOW TO DRINK OUT OF A
CUP.
I MUST TAKE MY SHIRT OFF.
>> NO.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE A SHIRTS ON IN
THE HOUSE RULE.
>> NO, NO, WE DON'T.
>> OKAY.
COOL.
WELL, THEN I'LL TAKE OFF MINE
ALSO.
>> EWW.
>> DON'T SAY EWW.
>> LAIRD, LET ME TAKE YOUR
SHIRT.
I'LL THROW IT IN THE WASH.
>> SO HOW DID YOU PASS THE TIME
ON THAT ISLAND?
PROBABLY YANKED IT A LOT.
>> NOT ONCE.
>> YOU BOYS GETTING ALONG?
>> YEAH.
LAIRD ACTUALLY JUST TOLD ME HE
NEEDS TO LEAVE.
>> WHAT?
BUT HE JUST GOT HERE.
>> IT'S OKAY, ELAINE.
SOMETIMES I LOSE TRACK OF TIME.
I SUPPOSE IT'S IRONIC THAT MY
WHOLE LIFE HAS BEEN DICTATED BY
THE CLOCK.
ON THAT ISLAND, THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERED WAS SURVIVAL.
>> OH.
>> THE SIZE OF THE FIRE I COULD
BUILD WITH MY OWN HANDS.
>> OOH.
>> THE PRIMITIVE SKILLS I COULD
SUMMON TO HUNT.
>> I KNOW YOU WERE ON AN ISLAND,
LAIRD, BUT I WAS ON AN ISLAND
TOO.
>> IN WHAT WAY?
>> YOU'RE NOT ALONE ANYMORE.
>> OKAY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GET OUT OF
HERE BEFORE I KICK YOUR ASS.
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
LAIRD IS OUR GUEST.
>> FINE!
THEN A PUSHUP CONTEST.
>> WHAT?
>> WINNER GETS ELAINE.
>> DENNIS, THAT'S INSANE.
WINNER SHOULD GET ME AND THE
HOUSE.
>> I ACCEPT THOSE TERMS.
>> THEN GENTLEMEN, GET IN THE
POSITION.
ON MY MARK, GO!
>> GUESS I LOST, HUH?
KIND OF FUNNY.
NOW THAT I'VE BEEN BEATEN AND
HUMILIATED, I FEEL TOTALLY ALONE
AND ISOLATED.
GUESS IN A WAY, I ALSO KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE ON AN ISLAND,
HUH, ELAINE?
>> OKAY.
THAT'S PRETTY SUS.
♪
♪ ONE CHANCE, TWO CHANCES
THREE THINK I GOT, GOT ♪
♪ TOO MUCH SYMPATHY, YEAH
I HOLD MY GRUDGES ♪
♪ LIKE I HELD YOU
HOW DOES ME TRYING TO ♪
♪ FIX IT TURN INTO
I'LL JUST FORGIVE IT ♪
♪ ONE CHANCE, TWO CHANCES
WERE LOST ON YOU ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY DIG
THE GRAVE SO DEEP ♪
♪ BEFORE YOU START TO
TAKE ME DOWN WITH YOU ♪
♪ WITH YOU, WITH YOU
I COULD NEVER MAKE YOU ♪
♪ WANT ME LIKE I WANTED
TO BE WANTED ♪
♪ I COULD NEVER REALLY
CHANGE YOU LIKE I THOUGHT ♪
♪ THAT I COULD
I WAS TRYING TO MAKE ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUTTA NOTHING
WE WERE NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY DIG
THE GRAVE SO DEEP ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY TRY TO
SAVE SOMETHING
THAT'S NOT ALREADY GONE ♪
♪ SO YOU'VE BEEN GOING OUT
WITH ALL YOUR BOYS ♪
♪ I'M CRAZY IF I
CALLED YOU, RIGHT ♪
♪ TABLES TURNED
NOW I'M OUT AND ♪
♪ YOU JUST CALLED
LIKE 30 TIMES ♪
♪ ALWAYS A FUNNY THING
WATCHING THE TOUGH ♪
♪ GUY PLEAD OH BABY
YOU CAN ONLY DIG ♪
♪ THE GRAVE SO DEEP
BEFORE YOU START TO ♪
♪ TAKE ME DOWN WITH YOU
WITH YOU, WITH YOU ♪
♪ I COULD NEVER MAKE YOU
WANT ME LIKE I WANTED ♪
♪ TO BE WANTED
I COULD NEVER REALLY ♪
♪ CHANGE YOU
LIKE I THOUGHT ♪
♪ THAT I COULD
I WAS TRYNA MAKE US ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUTTA NOTHING
WE WERE NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY DIG
THE GRAVE SO DEEP ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY TRY TO
SAVE SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT'S NOT ALREADY GONE
THAT'S NOT ALREADY GONE ♪
OOOOH ♪
♪ YOU HAD ME
YOU HAD ME FOR A MINUTE ♪
♪ THE SAD THING IS
YOU NEVER WOULD ADMIT ♪
♪ THAT YOU HAD ME
YOU HAD ME FOR ♪
♪ A MINUTE THERE
OOOOH ♪
♪ YOU HAD ME FOR
A MINUTE THERE ♪
♪ BUT I COULD NEVER MAKE YOU
WANT ME LIKE I WANTED ♪
♪ TO BE WANTED
I COULD NEVER ♪
♪ REALLY CHANGE YOU
LIKE I THOUGHT ♪
♪ THAT I COULD
I WAS TRYNA MAKE US ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUTTA NOTHING
WE WERE NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY DIG
THE GRAVE SO DEEP ♪
♪ YOU CAN ONLY TRY TO
SAVE SOMETHING
THAT'S NOT ALREADY GONE ♪
UNTOLD
>>> IT'S BEEN 50 YEARS SINCE
BILLY JEAN KING
DEFEATED BOBBY
RIGS IN THE BATTLE OF THE SEXES.
SHE SHOCKED THE WORLD AND STOOD
UP TO MISOGYNY IN THE TENNIS
COMMUNITY.
BUT WHAT IF I TOLD YOU SHE
WASN'T THE FIRST?
>> ANOTHER VICTORY FOR CHARNA
LEE DIAMOND.
>> THERE WOULD BE NO BILLY
WITHOUT CHARNA.
THERE WOULDN'T BE.
>> SHE TAUGHT GIRLS YOU DIDN'T
NEED TO PLAY IT SAFE.
>> THIS IS FOR WOMEN!
>> SHE WAS A BRASH FEMINIST ICON,
BUT THE WORLD WASN'T READY
FOR THAT.
>> MS. DIAMOND,
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THE MEN TELLING YOU THERE'S
NO PLACE FOR GIRLS IN THIS
SPORT?
>> IF ANY MAN OUT THERE THINKS
THEY HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO BEAT ME,
LET'S PLAY.
NO MORE QUESTIONS.
>> AFTER THAT, PROMOTERS WERE
CHOMPING AT THE BIT TO SET UP A MATCH,
AND EVENT WILL I, CHARNA
FOUND AN OPPONENT, THE BIGGEST
STAR IN MEN'S TENNIS,
RONNIE DUNSTER.
EMPHASIS ON BIG.
ODD CHOICE
BECAUSE AT THE TIME, I WAS THE
LARGEST MAN TO EVER PLAY TENNIS.
>> ALL EYES ARE ON THE HOUSTON
DOME TONIGHT
TO WITNESS THIS
HISTORIC MATCH.
AND HERE COMES THE FIRST SERVE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT
COMING.
HE WAS 300 POUNDS OF PURE MUSCLE,
AND SHE WAS ONE OF THE
LOWEST RANKED FEMALE PLAYERS AT
THE TIME.
>> DID I RUIN IT?
DID I RUIN IT FOR WOMEN?
>> HEY, CHARNA, YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> THERE'S A HOLE IN HER
STOMACH, MAN.
>> IT WAS SHOCKING TO SEE HOW
HARD RONNIE HIT THAT BALL.
BUT WHAT WAS EVEN MORE SHOCKING
WAS CHARNA NOT GIVING UP.
>> AND BY SOME MIRACLE, CHARNA
REFUSES TO STOP PLAYING.
>> SERVE.
AGAIN.
SERVE.
>> WHAT?
NO.
>> THIS IS BIGGER THAN YOU,
RONNIE.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> NOW, YOU GIANT MORON!
NOW!
NO
BELIEVE REASON
A WOMAN PRESIDENT.
>> IT SEEMS THE ADRENALINE IS
KEEPING HER ALIVE.
I HIGHLY SUSPECT SHE WILL DIE
MOMENTARILY.
>> I CAN'T PLAY ANYMORE, RIGHT?
THAT WOULDN'T BE COOL.
IT WAS DEFINITELY THE [ BLEEP ]
WEIRDEST GAME OF TENNIS I'VE
EVER PLAY.
>> EVEN THOUGH SHE'S NOT AS WELL
KNOWN AT BILLY JEAN KING,
CHARNA
LEE DIAMOND'S LEGACY LIVES ON IN
THE TENNIS HALL OF FAME.
MEMORIAM
>>> HEY, THANKS FOR THE LIFT,
MAN.
THE CAB LINE AT THE AIRPORT WAS
INSANE.
>> YEAH, WELL, THANKSGIVING --
THAT'S THANKSGIVING FOR YOU,
PAL.
IT'S PRETTY NUTS THIS TIME OF
YEAR.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO D.C.
BEFORE?
>> WAIT.
AREN'T WE IN ALBANY?
>> WE ARE.
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF YOU'VE
EVER BEEN TO D.C.
SEEMS LIKE A PRETTY WHACKY
PLACE.
>> GOT IT.
I'M GOING TO SIT BACK HERE AND
DRINK MY COFFEE IF THAT'S OKAY.
>> NO WORRIES.
I'M GETTING A CALL.
MIND IF I TAKE THIS?
>> NO, PLEASE.
>> THIS IS DR. CASSIDY'S OFFICE,
AND SHE'S GOT YOUR TEST RESULTS.
IS NOW A GOOD TIME?
SOME OF THE RESULTS AREN'T
GREAT.
>> YES, PLEASE.
>> MAYBE YOU WAN TO TAKE THAT
OFF SPEAKER?
>> I DON'T MIND.
PROBABLY JUST ROUTINE.
>> JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
ABOUT A FEW THINGS HERE.
>> SURE.
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW IF I
SHOULD BE HEARING THIS.
>> AS FAR AS THE NEGATIVES GO,
YOUR CHOLESTEROL IS QUITE HIGH.
>> WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
I'M EATING A BUNCH OF SHRIMP AND
HAM RIGHT NOW.
>> ON THE POSITIVE SIDE, YOU'RE
POSITIVE FOR HERPES.
>> EVERYBODY'S GOT THAT.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT, PAL.
>> I AM BEGGING YOU TO TAKE IT
OFF SPEAKER.
>> LASTLY, YOU HAVE SOMETHING
WE'RE CALLING HEPATITIS GOLD.
>> I LIKE THE SOUND OF THAT.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T.
>> WHAT IF WE JUST LET ME OUT ON
THIS HIGHWAY.
>> JUST TALKING TO MY DOCTOR.
ANYTHING ELSE?
>> YOU ALSO ASKED ME ABOUT THE
E.D.
>> EMPTY DIAPERS?
>> I WAS TALKING ABOUT ERECTILE
DYSFUNCTION, BUT WE CAN SKIP
AHEAD.
SHORT ANSWERS ARE THE DIAPERS
ARE EMPTY BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
PUTTING THEM ON.
THAT'S WHY EVERYTHING IS
SHOOTING STRAIGHT INTO THE PAN.
>> DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE WRITING
THIS DOWN.
>> NO.
SERIOUSLY, THIS IS NOT OKAY.
>> YOU HAVE LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
>> WELL, THAT'S A RELIEF.
>> WHAT IS?
>> WELL, I THOUGHT I HAD LOW
BLOOD.
I HEARD IT FROM A SOUTHERN SASSY
LADY WHO SAID, YOU GOOD LOW
BLOOD, SUGAR.
AND GOING BACK TO THE WEINER
STUFF?
>> SO WE RAN SOME TESTS ON YOUR
PENIS, AND IT'S NEGATIVE, LIKE
NEGATIVE IN LENGTH.
>> THAT EXPLAINS A LOT, OR I
GUESS I SHOULD SAY A LITTLE.
>> DO NOT HIGH FIVE ME.
>> ARE YOU SEXUALLY ACTIVE?
>> ACTIVE?
NO.
I JUST KIND OF LIE THERE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M JUST GOING
TO PUT ON A PODCAST.
>> PAIRING WITH CAB DRIVER'S
PHONE.
>> HOW?
>> JUST A FEW MORE QUESTIONS.
>> AH!
>> I'M NOTICING YOU HAVE SOME
MISSING INFORMATION ON YOUR
CHART.
CAN I ASK YOU ABOUT YOUR FAMILY
HISTORY?
>> MOM AND DAD DID IT, AND I
CAME OUT FIVE MONTHS LATER.
>> FIVE MONTHS?
>> THAT'S WHY THEY CALL ME LIL
SQUIRT.
HIGH FIVE.
>> I SAID NO.
>> HOW MANY DRINKS DO YOU HAVE
PER NIGHT?
>> WHAT'S THAT, A HOLIDAY FOR
CATS?
>> NOT PURR LIKE A CAT.
SHE'S ASKING YOU HOW MANY DRINKS
YOU HAVE IN A WEEK.
>> OH, ZERO.
UNLESS YOU'RE COUNTING RUM.
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> THEN A THOUSAND.
>> PULL OVER.
>> ALSO, YOUR VISION TEST CAME
BACK, AND I'M AFRAID TO SAY
YOU'RE LEGALLY BLIND.
>> LIKE REESE WITHERSPOON?
>> THAT IS LEGALLY BLOND, YOU
DUMMY.
DOCTOR, HOW HARD IS IT TO JUMP
FROM A MOVING CAB AND LIVE?
>> THAT'S NOT MY AREA, BUT HOW
FAST ARE YOU GOING?
>> OH, MY GOD.
TEN MILES AN HOUR.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THAT'S IT.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
I WILL WALK TO THE RADDISON.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO LAUREN
MICHAELS!
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME, LAUREN.
ALL MY LOVE TO MY MOTHER WHO
INTRODUCED ME TO SNL.
THANK YOU TO MY MOTHER.
AND EVERYONE BACK IN IOWA WHO
WATCHED THIS WITH ME, YOU RAISED
ME ON THIS.
I'M RAISED IN THE MIDWEST.
I LOVE THIS SHOW.
I'M COMING BACK, BABY.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.