>>> WOW, WHAT A DAY!
YOU KNOW, YOUR SPEECH WAS
TERRIFIC, KETANJI.
I'M SORRY, I MEAN, SUPREME COURT
JUSTICE KETANJI BROWN JACKSON.
>> BET YOU CAN'T SAY THAT THREE
TIMES FAST.
>> I WAS SHOCKED I'M ABLE TO SAY
IT ONE TIME SLOW.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
I'M SO GRATEFUL YOU PUT YOUR
TRUST IN ME.
>> I MADE A CAMPAIGN PROMISE TO
PUT A BLACK WOMAN ON THE COURT
AND I DID.
ONE CAMPAIGN PROMISE DOWN, ONLY
74 MORE TO GO.
>> I WAS HAPPY TO DO MY PART.
WORK TWICE AS HARD AS A WHITE
MAN MY ENTIRE LIFE,
THEN SPEND A
WEEK LISTENING TO TED CRUZ CALL
ME A PEDOPHILE.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, THE RECEPTION
STARTS IN FIVE MINUTES.
>> THANKS.
I SHOULD GO GET READY.
KETANJI, IT'S A BIG BAM DEAL,
RIGHT?
YOU'RE THE FIRST BLACK FEMALE
JUSTICE BUT YOU WON'T BE THE
LAST.
IT'S JUST A NORMAL THING NOW,
LIKE WEARING CROCS IN PUBLIC
>> THANK YOU?
>> TAKE A MOMENT IN THIS ROOM.
SOMETIMES I LIKE TO IMAGINE ALL
THE GREAT AMERICANS WHO CAME
HERE BEFORE ME.
YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY?
>> THAT YOU MISS OBAMA?
>> EVERY DAY LIKE CRAZY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, WE REALLY HAVE
TO GO.
>> OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU IN A
MINUTE.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> WOW.
THERE IS A LOT OF HISTORY IN
THIS ROOM.
WHO WOULD I WANT TO TALK TO?
OH, I KNOW.
GREET
RUTH BADER GINSBURG, HOW IS THIS
POSSIBLE?
IMAG
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
>> I WOULD LOVE SOME ADD VIEGS.
>> OKAY.
HERE'S MY ADVICE.
ALWAYS LABEL YOUR LUNCHES.
FINGERS
SECOND, IF YOU ARE ANYTHING LIKE ME,
WHITE LADIES WILL START WEAR
YOUR FACE WITH AN I VOTED
STICKER.
FREAKY
WELL
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I KNOW YOU WILL DO A GREAT JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
THAT MEANS A LOT.
>> LOOK, I KNOW YOUR
CONFIRMATION PROCESS PUT YOU
THROUGH THE RINGER,
BUT IT IS
END PEOPLE DID THE RIGHT THING.
I WAS CONFIRMED
>> WHAT WAS YOUR VOTE?
>> 53-47.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
A LOT WALKED OUT.
ONE GUY KEPT ASKING ME IF BABIES
ARE RACIST.
>> TEXAS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN THAT
MAN, HE ACTUALLY SAT THERE ON TV
AND READ A CHILDREN'S BOOK AT
ME, HA.
>> WELL, IT WAS TED CRUZ, SO I
BET THE BOOK WAS CALLED "GOOD
NIGHT CANCUN."
THAT'S THE GINSBURG.
>> DID I MISS IT?
OH, DAMN.
>> OH MY GOD, JUSTICE THURGOOD
MARSHALL!
>> YES, THAT'S EXACTLY WHO
YOU'RE IMAGINING.
WHAT AN EXCITING DAY.
WE'VE COME A LONG WAY.
>> WELL, THANKS TO YOU.
YOU WERE ON THE FRONT LINES OF
THE CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT.
>> YEP, I WAS THERE WHEN PEOPLE
OF COLOR IN THIS COUNTRY CAME
TOGETHER WITH ONE VOICE
AND
SAID, ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
AND THEN WHITE FOLKS SAID, WE'LL
THINK ABOUT IT.
BUT THAT WAS A DIFFERENT TIME.
>> SOME THINGS ARE STILL
SIMILAR?
>> OH, YEAH.
THREAT OF NUCLEAR WAR WITH
RUSSIA?
>> YES.
>> INFLATION STILL POPPING UP?
>> FOR SURE.
>> JOE BIDEN STILL A POLITICIAN?
>> VERY MUCH SO?
>> SO WHAT ADVISE TO YOU HAVE
FOR ME.
>> WELL, NEVER GIVE UP.
SLOW AND MESSY.
IT STUMBLES, BUT OVER TIME IT
MOVES FORWARD.
I WAS THE FIRST BLACK SUPREME COURT JUSTICE,
SO YOU MUST BE
WHAT, THE 10th, THE 20th?
>> NOPE, JUST THE THIRD.
>> NO FURTHER QUESTIONS, YOUR
HONOR.
>> YEAH.
I HAVE SOME QUESTIONS.
>> HARRIET TUBMAN?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND CONDUCTOR OF THE UNDERGROUND
RAILROAD.
>> MY QUESTION IS.
WHAT ARE WE DOING IN THE WHITE
HOUSE?
DID WE GET IN TROUBLE?
>> NOT AT ALL. BECAUSE OF WOMEN LIKE YOU
A LOT OF DOORS OPENED UP TO A LOT
OF PEOPLE.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> I HAVE A SEAT AT THE TABLE.
>> AND I'M GOING TO HAVE THIS
JOB FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
>> DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> TRAP
OKAY.
BUT IF IT IS, LIGHT TWO CANDLES
AND MEET ME IN THE FARMHOUSE AT
MIDNIGHT.
>> NO, I'M GOOD.
EXCITED
I WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO ONE MORE
PERSON WHO BROKE DOWN A BARRIER.
>> THAT'S MY, JACKIE ROBINSON.
FIRST
LET ME TELL YOU, BEING THE FIRST
IS KIND OF FUN.
YEAH.
IT'S FUN.
HERE'S MY ADVICE.
WATCH OUT FOR BATTERS.
YOU WILL GET SO MANY BATTERIES
THROWN AT YOU.
>> I THINK THE SUPREME COURT IS
TOO CIVILIZED FOR THAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID ABOUT
BASEBALL.
BUT THEY STILL THREW THOSE
BATTERIES, THOUGH.
DAMN, WISH WE HAD HELMETS BACK
THEN, HA HA!
THE GOOD NEWS IS, YOU'RE
PROBABLY MAKING A LOT MORE MONEY
THAN A BASEBALL PLAYER.
>> I WISH.
BASEBALL PLAYERS TODAY AVERAGE
ABOUT $4 MILLION A YEAR.
>> OH, EXCUSE ME FOR A SECOND.
THANK YOU.
I'VE BEEN HOLDING THAT IN SINCE
1947.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR ADVICE.
I WILL DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO
HONOR YOUR LEGACY.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
EVEN THE BAD PLAYERS GET $4
MILLION A YEAR?
>> YEP.
>> AIN'T THAT SOMETHING.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
JAKE GYLLENHAAL!
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK
YOU.
THANK YOU.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE BACK AT
SNL.
THE LAST TIME I HOSTED WAS THE
YEAR 2007.
YOU KNOW HOW LONG AGO THAT WAS?
THAT WAS LIKE 400 MARVEL MOVIES
AGO.
TO GIVE YOU AN IDEA OF WHAT IT
WAS LIKE IN 2007,
IN THE SHOW I
HOSTED --
THERE WAS A GEORGE W. BUSH
SKETCH.
THERE WERE JOKES ABOUT THE FIRST
iPHONE.
AND THIS IS A PHOTO OF ME FROM
MY MONOLOGUE.
YEAH.
THERE I AM IN FULL DRAG SINGING
A SONG FROM "DREAM GLS GIRLS"
TO
PROMOTE A MOVIE WHERE I PLAYED A
GAY COWBOY.
AND THAT WAS ACTUALLY THE LEAST
PROBLEMATIC THING IN THAT
EPISODE.
LOOKING BACK, I FEEL LIKE I WAS
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S FUNNY.
I GOT THIS REPUTATION FOR BEING
THIS SERIOUS, INTENSE METHOD
ACTOR.
BUT HONESTLY, I WASN'T EVEN THAT
GOOD AT METHOD ACTING.
I REMEMBER FOR THIS MOVIE
NIGHTCRAWLER, I WENT TO THE DIRECTOR
AND I WAS LIKE, GET
READY FOR ME TO LOSE 48 POUNDS
AND WIN THE OSCAR.
AND THEN A WEEK LATER I WAS
LIKE, HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE
AN ACTOR LOSE 36 POUNDS
AND WIN
THE GOLDEN GLOBE?
AND THEN I SHOWED UP ON SET AND
I WAS LIKE, YOU'RE LOOKING AT A
GUY WHO GAINED 10 POUNDS
AND
DOESN'T CARE ABOUT AWARDS.
THE TRUTH IS, I WAS ONLY DOING
THAT METHOD STUFF
BECAUSE I
THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT YOU HAD TO
DO TO BE A SERIOUS ACTOR,
AND I
KIND OF FORGOT HOW TO HAVE FUN.
THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED SOMETHING
I SHOULD HAVE REALIZED A LONG
TIME AGO.
ACTING IS A REALLY STUPID JOB.
IT'S PRETEND.
AND IT'S FUN AND IT SHOULD BE
FILLED WITH JOY.
WELL, I'M FINALLY EMBRACING THAT
JOY AGAIN,
AND THAT'S WHY I'M
BACK STANDING ON THIS STAGE.
>> I MEAN, I NEVER THOUGHT "SNL"
WOULD COME CALLING AGAIN.
I MEAN, IT'S BEEN 15 YEARS.
I WASN'T SURE I'D REMEMBER HOW
TO HOST.
BUT BEING HERE TONIGHT, IT FEELS
LIKE EVERYTHING IS SUDDENLY
COMING BACK.
* THERE WERE NIGHTS WHEN THE
WIND WAS SO COLD
THAT MY BODY
FROZE IN BED *
* IF I JUST LISTENED TO IT RIGHT
OUTSIDE THE WINDOW
* WHEN I SEE YOU LIKE THIS
AND I
HOST YOU LIKE THAT *
* I JUST HAVE TO ADMIT
THAT IT'S ALL COMING BACK TO ME *
* IT'S ALL COMING BACK IT'S ALL
COMING BACK TO ME NOW *
* MOMENTS OF GOLD AND THERE WERE
FLASHES OF LIGHT *
* THERE WERE SKETCHES I'D NEVER
DO AGAIN BUT THEN THEY ALWAYS
SEEMED RIGHT *
** THERE WERE NIGHTS OF ENDLESS
PLEASURE.
** IT WAS MORE THAN ANY SHOWS
ALLOWED.
BABY BABY *
* IF YOU WANT ME LIKE THIS
IF YOU NEED ME LIKE THAT *
* IT WAS ALL FOR THE GOOD
BUT IT'S ALL COMING BACK TO ME *
* I CAN BARELY RECALL
BUT IT'S ALL COMING BACK TO ME NOW *
>> WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
CAMILA CABELLO IS HERE
SO STICK
AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
LOVE
WHY'D YOU LIKE
IT" WITH YOUR HOST
DENNY DONIGAN.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME TO "WHY'D YOU LIKE IT?"
THE GAME SHOW WHERE WE ASK
CONTESTANTS, "WHY'D YOU LIKE
IT?"
I'M YOUR HOST DENNY DONEGAN,
AND TONIGHT'S CONTESTANTS ARE
BETH --
>> HI, CAN'T WAIT TO PLAY.
>> KENNY --
>> SUP, Y'ALL, LET'S DO THIS.
>> AND BRAD.
>> EXCITED TO BE HERE, DENNY.
I'M STILL NOT TOTALLY SURE WHAT
THIS SHOW IS, BUT LOOKING
FORWARD TO FINDING OUT.
>> WELL, THE GAME IS EASY.
WE SHOW YOU A PICTURE THAT YOU
LIKED ON INSTAGRAM,
AND ASK YOU
THE SIMPLE QUESTION, "WHY'D YOU
LIKE IT?"
SO BRAD, LET'S START WITH YOU.
>> UH, OKAY.
>> ON MARCH 19th, YOU LIKED THIS
PHOTO.
SO THE QUESTION IS, "WHY'D YOU
LIKE IT?"
>> UH -- SHE'S MY FRIEND.
I LIKE HER DOG?
I THOUGHT SHE WAS ATTRACTIVE.
>> STILL DOESN'T EXPLAIN WHY YOU
LIKED IT.
I MEAN, YOU COULD HAVE JUST
LOOKED AT IT, BUT YOU DID THE
DOUBLE TAP.
SO THE QUESTION REMAINS, WHY?
>> I GUESS SOME PART OF ME
THOUGHT THAT IF I LIKED IT,
SHE
WOULD SEE THAT I LIKE IT,
AND THEN SHE WOULD FOLLOW ME BACK,
THEN WE'D DM,
AND THEN MAYBE AT
SOME POINT, I DON'T KNOW, SHE'D
WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH ME.
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
THANK
AND JUST TO BE CLEAR, YOUR
GIRLFRIEND IS HERE TONIGHT?
>> SHE -- SHE IS, YEAH.
>> YOU ARE A STUPID MAN.
>> I REALLY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE PREMISE OF THE SHOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP WE GOT
KENNY.
>> PASS.
>> NOPE.
YOU CAN'T PASS.
ALL RIGHT.
TWO WEEKS AGO, YOU LIKED THIS
PHOTO.
>> OKAY, THAT'S ART.
THAT'S NOT EVEN BAD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THEN THIS QUESTION SHOULD BE
EASY.
WHY'D YOU LIKE IT?
>> I'M CULTURED.
>> I'D LIKE TO POINT OUT THIS
ART PHOTO WAS POSTED BY
MEGANTHESTALLION.
WHO HAS 28 MILLION FOLLOWERS,
AND AVERAGES 2 MILLION LIKES PER
POST.
SO AGAIN, WHY'D YOU LIKE IT?
>> I'M A FAN OF HER MUSIC.
I'M A FAN OF HER ART.
I'M A FAN OF INSTAGRAM IN
GENERAL.
OKAY, I GUESS I -- I SAW THAT
THIS POST WAS GETTING LESS LIKES
THAN THE ONES WITH MEGAN'S FACE
AND BOOTY.
SO I THOUGHT IF I LIKED THIS
ONE, IT'S MORE LIKELY THAT SHE'D SEE IT,
AND SHE'D KNOW THAT I
LIKE HER FOR MORE THAN HER BODY,
BUT LIKE, ALSO HER MIND.
AND THEN IT'D BE LIKE A
NOTTING HILL TYPE OF
SITUATION,
SHE'D DM ME, ONE THING LEADS TO
ANOTHER, AND PRETTY SOON WE'RE
HAVING SEX.
>> WOW.
THAT'S PATHETIC.
>> DO NOT SPEAK.
>> CAN I LEAVE?
>> NOPE.
ALL RIGHT, BETH, YOU'RE UP.
>> OKAY, WELL, THIS SHOULD BE
EASY FOR ME, BECAUSE I DON'T GO
AROUND LIKING THIRST TRAPS ON
INSTAGRAM.
>> HA HA, LOVE THE CONFIDENCE.
BECAUSE YESTERDAY YOU LIKED THIS
PHOTO FROM 2017.
>> SEEMS FINE.
>> IT IS A PICTURE OF YOUR
EX-BOYFRIEND'S SISTER.
SO, WHY'D YOU LIKE IT?
>> WE STILL KEEP IN TOUCH.
I LIKE HER DOG.
WATERFALL.
>> YOU SCROLLED BACK FIVE YEARS
TO LIKE IT.
>> OKAY.
I THOUGHT THAT IF I LIKED THE PHOTO,
SHE'D SEE MY NAME POP UP
ON HER FEED AND REMEMBER THAT I
WAS NICE.
AND THEN MAYBE AT THE NEXT
FAMILY DINNER, SHE'D TURN TO MY EX
AND BE LIKE, "YOU KNOW WHO I
MISS?
BETH!"
AND THEN MY EX WOULD DM ME AND
MAYBE SAY,
LET'S GRAB A COFFEE SOMETIME.
CUT TO TWO HOURS LATER AND WE'RE
RAW-DOGGING IN A STARBUCKS
BATHROOM.
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU
PEOPLE?
>> WHY DID YOU BRING US HERE?
>> UH-OH, YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
SOUND MEANS.
>> YOU KNOW THAT WE DON'T.
>> WELL, IT'S TIME FOR ROUND
TWO.
WHY DO YOU FOLLOW 'EM?
SHOW
TELL ME,
>> PASS.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THAT PROFILE UP.
YOU ALL FOLLOW JOE BIDEN.
WHY?
>> HE'S THE PRESIDENT.
>> HE KNOWS OBAMA.
>> DURING THE ELECTION, I FELT
LIKE I WASN'T DOING ENOUGH POLITICALLY,
SO I THOUGHT
FOLLOWING JOE BIDEN WAS
LITERALLY THE LEAST I COULD DO.
>> SO CLOSE.
>> AND I THOUGHT MAYBE IF
SOMEONE POLITICAL SAW I WAS
FOLLOWING HIM, THEY'D WANT
TO HAVE SEX WITH ME.
>> I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
>> I -- I WASN'T GONNA DO
ANYTHING --
UNLESS ONE OF THEM DMED ME AND
COMMENTED ON
ONE OF MY PHOTOS.
ALL -- ALL RIGHT, LOOK, MAYBE --
MAYBE IN THE PAST I'VE BEEN
PRETTY SHALLOW WHEN IT COMES TO
SOCIAL MEDIA.
BUT THANKS TO THIS GAME SHOW, I
NOW REALIZE SOCIAL MEDIA IS NOT MY FRIEND
AND MAYBE IT'S TIME TO
GET OFF THIS THING FOR GOOD.
>> OKAY, WELL IN THE TIME IT
TOOK FOR THE CAMERA TO CUT TO ME JUST NOW,
YOU LIKED, UN-LIKED,
AND LIKED AGAIN THIS PHOTO.
>> I'M SORRY, I CANNOT CHANGE.
>> UNDERSTOOD.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THE
BREAK WITH ROUND THREE,
"WHY
STICK AROUND!
>> WE'RE THE "DREAM HOME
COUSINS."
>> MY COUSIN GAGE AND I HAVE
BEEN HARD AT WORK DESIGNING A
DREAM HOME FOR LILIAN AND HER
QUIET, MILQUETOAST HUSBAND PAT.
WHO IS DEEPLY UNCOMFORTABLE ON
CAMERA.
AND NOW, WE'RE READY TO SHOW
THEM THE PLANS WE DREW UP.
>> FOR THE RECORD, I DID MOST OF
THE DRAWING.
>> OH, BROTHER.
>> DON'T YOU MEAN, "OH, COUSIN"?
>> LILIAN, PAT?
YOU GUYS READY TO SEE OUR FINAL
DESIGN?
>> YES, I'M SO EXCITED.
>> PAT?
>> NOW, WE ALL AGREED ON A
DESIGN.
BUT YOU GUYS THREW US A BIT OF A
CURVEBALL WHEN PAT INFORMED US
THAT HIS MOTHER, BEA, AND HER
27-YEAR-OLD CAT, CHARLES-DAVID,
WOULD ALSO BE MOVING INTO YOUR
HOUSE.
WHICH REQUIRED US TO CHANGE A
FEW THINGS.
>> BUT IT'S STILL GOING TO BE MY
DREAM HOUSE, RIGHT?
WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT?
>> YOU BET, JUST SLIGHTLY
MODIFIED.
LET'S START WITH THE LIVING
ROOM.
>> LILIAN, YOU WANTED THIS SPACE
TO BE, QUOTE, "AN OASIS OF
RELAXATION."
>> OH, I LOVE THAT.
>> BUT BEA WANTED THIS SPACE TO
BE, QUOTE, "WHERE WE PUT MY
CAT'S MEDICAL EQUIPMENT."
>> AND UNFORTUNATELY, THE AMOUNT
OF MACHINERY IT TAKES TO KEEP A
27-YEAR-OLD CAT WITH NO KIDNEYS
ALIVE REALLY CLUTTERED UP THE
SPACE.
>> GOD -- THIS CAT.
>> NOW FOR THE KITCHEN.
WE THOUGHT THIS CAPTURED
LILIAN'S VISION OF AN OPEN
CONCEPT DESIGN.
>> OH, WOW.
>> AND WE WOULD HAVE LOVED TO
BUILD THAT, BUT SINCE BEA'S
GOING TO BE DOING MOST OF THE
COOKING --
>> ALL THE COOKING.
SKINNY MINI CAN'T COOK.
>> WE WENT WITH A MORE CLOSED
CONCEPT FEEL.
>> AND SINCE BEA IS AFRAID OF
GAS, WE SWAPPED THE SIX-BURNER
VIKING RANGE FOR AN OLIVE GREEN
ELECTRIC STOVE AND OSTER TOASTER
OVEN, BOTH FROM BEA'S CURRENT
HOME, AND BOTH MANUFACTURED
IN 1978.
>> BACK WHEN AMERICA STILL BUILT
THINGS.
>> ARE YOU GONNA PICK ANYTHING I
WANT?
>> NOW LILIAN, I SENSE THAT
YOU'RE PROBABLY FEELING THAT
YOUR VISION HAS BEEN COMPROMISED
DOWNSTAIRS.
>> YES.
>> BUT UPSTAIRS?
>> HAS ALSO BEEN COMPROMISED.
WE HAD TO PARTITION THE GRAND
STAIRCASE TO ACCOMMODATE
CHARLES-DAVID'S MOTORIZED
STAIR-CHAIR.
>> BUT GOOD NEWS, LILIAN, WE
WERE ABLE TO PRESERVE YOUR YOGA
STUDIO FROM OUR ORIGINAL DESIGN.
>> YAY, IT'S PERFECT.
>> BUT IT WILL HAVE TO DOUBLE AS
THE DISPLAY ROOM FOR BEA'S
COLLECTION OF WISE QUACKERS.
LARGE, CERAMIC STATUE'S OF DUCKS
IN 1930s GANGSTER OUTFITS.
AND WITH 90 WISE QUACKERS TO
DISPLAY, THE YOGA STUDIO WILL BE
A LITTLE CRAMPED.
SO, WHAT DO WE THINK SO FAR?
>> I THINK THAT SKINNY MINI
OPENED HER LEGS AND STOLE MY
SON.
I KNOW SHE TOOK YOUR SWEETNESS
BEFORE YOUR WEDDING NIGHT.
>> WHAT, YOU TOLD HER?
>> I GAVE MY SWEETNESS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OKAY, LET'S SHOW YOU WHAT WE
CAME UP WITH FOR THE PRIMARY
BEDROOM.
>> OH, THAT'S GORGEOUS.
>> HERE'S WHERE WE LANDED AFTER
TALKING TO BEA.
SINCE THIS WILL BE HER BEDROOM
AS WELL, WE'LL SWAP THE KING BED
FOR THREE SINGLES.
>> AND SINCE BEA HATES LARGE
OPEN SPACES --
>> THE DEVIL'S IN THE RAFTERS.
>> THE 15 FOOT CATHEDRAL
CEILINGS WILL COME DOWN TO ABOUT
6 FEET.
>> YOU'RE 6'1."
>> I'LL CROUCH.
>> BUT DON'T WORRY, BEA, WE MADE
SURE THERE WAS ENOUGH WALL SPACE
FOR ALL THE OLD BLACK AND WHITE
PHOTOGRAPHS OF YOUR
STERN-LOOKING ANCESTORS.
>> THAT WAS WHEN MEN WERE MEN.
>> AND NOW, DRUMROLL PLEASE.
FOR THE PRIMARY BATHROOM,
LILLIAN WANTED WINDOWS TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF YOUR BEAUTIFUL
VIEW.
BUT BEA WAS VERY CONCERNED WITH
PEEPERS INVADING HER PRIVACY,
WHICH TOOK THE BATHROOM WINDOW
COUNT, DOWN FROM SIX TO NO
WINDOWS.
>> YOU KNOW THEM PERVERTS AND
TUGGERS WANT TO SEE MY MAKE MY
DIRT.
>> NO ONE WANTS TO SEE YOU "MAKE
YOUR DIRT."
>> HIT HER.
>> MAMA, NO.
>> ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT IT?
>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
UPSTAIRS DEMO BEGINS.
>> TWO, ONE --
>> OW.
YOU'RE ENJOYING THE MUSIC AND
DINNER.
IF ANYONE DROVE HERE IN A BLUE
TOYOTA COROLLA, I JUST WANT TO
SAY, I HAVE THE SAME CAR.
SO LET'S TALK.
AND NOW, WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
OUR BIGGEST ACT OF THE NIGHT,
THE SINGERS FOUR.
TONIGHT IS A SPECIAL REUNION.
THEY HAVEN'T PERFORMED TOGETHER
IN 5 YEARS, BUT WE ARE SO LUCKY
THAT THEY ARE ALL BACK IN TOWN
TONIGHT.
PLEASE WELCOME THE SINGERS FOUR!
**
>> HELLO, EVERYBODY.
I SEE SOME BEAUTIFUL WATERS AND
BREADS IN THE CROWD.
>> WE ARE THE SINGERS FOUR.
WE'RE SO GLAD TO BE WITH YOU
TONIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, SO MANY SONGS ARE
DEDICATED TO GREATNESS.
BUT WE HAVE LIVED LONG ENOUGH TO
KNOW THAT NOT EVERYONE CAN BE
GREAT.
SOME OF US ARE JUST WALKING
AROUND.
>> THIS SONG GOES OUT TO THE
FOLKS IN THE MIDDLE, CELEBRATING
THE LITTLE THINGS.
>> BECAUSE IT'S WHAT WE'VE GOT.
IT'S ALL WE WANT.
AND IT'S ACTUALLY A LOT.
** I DON'T HAVE TASTE
** I DON'T HAVE PLANS.
I'VE BEEN PASSED OVER
I'VE BEEN PICKED LAST *
* I'M NOT WINNING ANY MEDALS
NOT NUMBER ONE
TWO OR THREE *
>> WHO THE HELL'S COUNTING?
* BUT I'VE MADE MY BED
EVERY DAY THIS MONTH
I CAN PARALLEL PARK
UNDER ANY CONDITION *
* WHEN I PUMP INSIDE OF
A LADY STUFF COMES OUT *
* AND THAT'S MY DAY FOR ME *
>> LOOK, NO ONE CAN CLIMB
EVEREST.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST DID?
>> WELL, TELL US, JOHNNY.
>> I FINISHED AN ENTIRE
CHAPSTICK WITHOUT LOSING IT.
>> I'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
>> I KNOW.
AND I THINK THAT MEANS I'M A
GOOD DAD.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THAT
MEANS.
* I'M NOT A QUEEN
I'M NOT THE BEST
MIGHT NOT BE SPECIAL
MIGHT NOT BE BLESSED *
* IF IT'S GRADED ON A CURVE
I'M THE ONE GETTING Bs
THAT'S ALMOST AN A *
** BUT THIS MORNING I WOKE UP
TWO MINUTES BEFORE MY AWILL
REMEMBER.
* I USED TO SMOKE
BUT THEN I STOPPED
MY EMAIL INBOX
HAS ZERO EMAILS *
** AND THAT'S MY THING FOR ME
>> TELL ME WHAT ARE YOU HANGING
OUR HATS ON THESE DAYS?
>> I'LL NEVER WIN THE NOBEL
PRIZE, BUT I CAN SAY THAT I MET
ERIC MEESE.
>> WOW!
AND WHO IS THAT?
>> HE WAS IN THE ORIGINAL CAST
OF "THE REAL WORLD."
>> WELL, THAT'S TERRIFIC!
>> YOU KNOW, ONE THING THAT I
LIKE TO
TELL PEOPLE ABOUT ME IS THAT I'M
NOT THE BEST AT SEX.
>> OKAY.
TELL ME MORE.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
ANYTHING NEW, BUT I GUARANTEE
ONE THING.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO FEEL SCARED
OR UPSET.
>> OH, YOU GO, GIRL!
>> MY GRANDMOTHER SAYS I'M
CLASSICALLY HANDSOME.
>> I GREW OUT OF A PEANUT
ALLERGY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY BUT I NEVER
GOT COVID.
>> I HATED "HAMILTON" BEFORE IT
WAS COOL.
>> ONCE A YEAR I CALL OFF OF
WORK, I PRETEND I'M SICK AND I
GO TO THE MOVIES.
THEN I GO HOME AND MY WIFE SAYS,
HOW WAS WORK?
AND I SAY, GOOD.
AND NOBODY KNOWS.
* AND THAT'S ENOUGH
FOR HIM *
>> COME ON, EVERY DINNER CAN'T
BE STEAK.
SOMETIMES IT'S OLD WET PASTA IN
A TUPPERWARE.
GROW UP!
>> EVERY NIGHT CAN'T BE THE BEST
NIGHT OF YOUR LIFE, IT WOULD BE
EXHAUSTING, YOU'D END UP IN THE
HOSPITAL.
>> GOLD ISN'T THE ONLY METAL.
WHAT DOES GOLD DO, SPARKLE?
WHO CARES?
YOU KNOW WHAT DOES?
YOU KNOW WHAT TIN DOES,
PRESERVES TOMATOES FOREVER.
>> AND FINE, WE DON'T HAVE
GRAMMYS, BUT WE HAVE GRAMMYS OF
WEED WHICH IS WHAT I CALL IT
WHEN I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH WEED
LEFT.
* I DO NOT READ I DO NOT SLOT
THE WORLD SAW ME AND SAID GET
LOST *
* I DON'T HAVE ANY TROPHIES BUT
I HAVE TV *
>> HE CAN WATCH WHATEVER HE
WANTS.
* SOME PEOPLE ARE FASTER SOME
PEOPLE ARE HOTTER BUT I PUT
LEMONS IN MY WATER *
* SURE I'M NOT REGAL SURE I'M
NOT RICH BUT WHEN I COOK CHICKEN
IT'S NEVER DRY BITCH *
* I DON'T HAVE MONEY I DON'T
HAVE POWER BUT EVERY TIME I USE
IT I CLEAN ONE PART OF THE
SHOWER *
* I DON'T WRITE POEMS THAT
TRANSCEND BUT I HAVE A SON AND
HE HAS A FRIEND *
* AND THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME *
**
LITTLE SPRING BULBS, YOU'RE
GETTING BIGGER EVERY DAY.
AND LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE THIRSTY
FOR THE SPRINKLES.
>> HEE HEE HEE!
>> THANK YOU MR. GREEN THUMB, WE
LOVE LITTLE SPRINKLES!
>> I KNOW, I LOVE THEM A LOT!
>> HEE HEE HEE HEE!
>> UH, EXCUSE ME.
I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED.
YESTERDAY I WAS JUST A BULB IN
THE EARTH, AND NOW I'M
DIFFERENT.
>> WELCOME TO THE FLOWER BED,
FRIEND.
WE WONDERED WHEN YOU'D ARRIVE.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE A LATE BLOOMER.
>> NOT SEXUALLY, JUST AS A
FLOWER!
>> HEE HEE HEE HEE HEE!
>> YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE IT HERE.
JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING IS PERFECT
BECAUSE --
**
* IT'S SPRING *
* WELL EVERYWHERE
BUT IDAHO
'CAUSE THERE IS STILL
A LOT OF SNOW *
* BUT SPRING
HAS FINALLY SPRUNG *
* YES SPRING
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, I DO LIKE IT
HERE.
* HOORAY FOR SPRING
AND BEING AN EASTER THING *
* SPRING SPRING SPRING
SPRING SPRING
SPRING SPRING *
>> HEY, EVERYBODY, WHAT ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT?
>> WE WERE JUST SAYING HOW
WONDERFUL SPRING IS, MR. BEE.
>> OH, YEAH, SPRING IS THE BEST.
LOVE SPRING.
UNH, UNH --
>> WAIT, WHAT -- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> I'M JUST DOING WHAT BEES DO.
IT'S OKAY.
UNH --
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL OKAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE HAVING
SEX WITH HIS HEAD.
>> NO, NO, I'M JUST GETTING
POLLEN ON MY LEGS OR WHATEVER.
IT'S ALL VERY NATURAL AND
NECESSARY.
UNH!
UNH UNH UNH UNH UNH!
>> WAIT.
DON'T DO ME AFTER YOU JUST DID
HIM!
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
>> I KNOW, IT'S LIKE, WHEN'S IT
GOING TO BE MY TURN?
>> I'LL GET YOU, EVERYBODY.
UNH!
>> OH, IT KIND OF TICKLES.
>> DON'T TALK, I'M CLOSE.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO WITH ALL THIS
POLLEN ANYWAY?
>> I BASICALLY SQUEEZE A LOAD OF
GOOP OUT MY BUTT, AND THEN
PEOPLE EAT IT.
PRETTY KINKY, RIGHT?
>> HEY!
GET OUT OF THERE, YOU SILLY BEE.
DON'T BE BOTHERING MY PRETTY
FLOWERS.
>> OH, THANK GOODNESS THAT'S
OVER.
>> YEAH, PRETTY HARROWING,
RIGHT?
>> WAIT, WHO ARE YOU?
>> JUST ANOTHER FLOWER, LIKE YOU
GUYS.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT A
WEED?
>> NO, I'M A FLOWER.
HEY, CAN I CHOKE YOU A LITTLE
BIT?
>> CHOKE ME?
NO!
>> OKAY.
WHY NOT, THOUGH?
I THINK YOU MIGHT LIKE IT.
>> HEY, GET AWAY FROM US,
WEIRDO, YOU'RE NOT A FLOWER AND
YOU DON'T BELONG HERE.
>> OH, YOU DON'T THINK I BELONG
HERE?
YOU DON'T WANT ME IN YOUR LITTLE
GATED FLOWER COMMUNITY?
HEY, ARE YOU HEARING THIS, BULB?
>> UH-HUH.
>> COME ON, JUST LET ME CHOKE
YOU!
>> STOP.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
>> I KNOW, IT'S LIKE, WHEN IS IT
GOING TO BE MY TURN?
>> HEY!
GO AWAY, YOU STUPID WEED!
GET BACK!
>> ARGGHH!
YOU CAN KILL ME BUT YOU CAN'T
KILL THE REVOLUTION!
>> WOW.
A LOT HAPPENS IN THIS GARDEN
BED.
>> AT LEAST THE DAY HASN'T BEEN
ALL BAD.
WE'RE ALTOGETHER, AND THERE IS
NOT A CLOUD IN THE SKY.
>> WAIT.
THERE IS A CLOUD.
>> AND WHY IS THE CLOUD SO
FURRY?
>> AND WHY DOES HE HAVE -- THE
CLOUD HAVE A PENIS?
>> MR. PEANUT, DON'T DO THAT TO
MY FLOWERS.
>> OH!
>> WHAT IS THIS HOT LIQUID?
>> AH!
SO SALTY!
>> I DON'T MIND IT.
>> I'M GETTING OUT OF HERE.
OH, MY GOD!
I DON'T HAVE LEGS!
WHERE ARE MY LEGS?
>> OW!
MAKE IT STOP!
>> IT'S TO HARD!
OW!
THIS DOG IS DEHYDRATED!
>> AHH!
WHEN IS IT GOING TO BE MY TURN?
>> GET OUT OF THERE, MR. PEANUT.
OH, MY POOR FLOWERS ARE SOAKED.
>> WOW.
I GUESS BEING A FLOWER MAYBE
ISN'T ALL IT'S CRACKED UP TO BE.
>> DON'T SAY THAT!
DON'T YOU EVER!
IT'S BEEN A LONG, GRAY WINTER
AND PEOPLE NEED US.
OUR BEAUTIFUL COLORS AND OUR
SWEET AROMAS.
EVEN IF RIGHT NOW WE DON'T
EXACTLY SMELL SO GOOD.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
LOOK AT THE SMILE ON
MR. GREEN THUMB'S FACE RIGHT
NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE WHICH
ONE OF Y'ALL ARE GOING TO LOOK
GOOD ON THE BACK OF MY COLLAR.
>> OH, OH!
AGHH!
>> NO!
>> OH, NO!
THEY KILLED JAKE FLOWER-HAAL!
>> IS THAT WHO THAT WAS?
>> THIS GUY IS CRAZY.
CAN I CHOKE YOU A LITTLE BIT?
>> FINALLY.
THESE MEETINGS TONIGHT HAVE BEEN
BRUTAL.
>> I KNOW.
I CAN BARELY KEEP MY EYES OPEN.
>> YOU GUYS, I AM SO DONE WITH
JANET.
>> OKAY, SHE IS AWFUL.
>> I KNOW.
>> SHE'S ALWAYS RUNNING DOWN THE
HALLWAY SO FAST.
IT'S LIKE WHAT'S THE BIG RUSH,
JANET?
YOU DON'T ACTUALLY DO ANYTHING.
>> I KNOW.
AND DOES SHE HAVE TO EAT TUNA
EVERY DAY?
>> MAKES ME SICK.
AND SHE CHEWS WITH HER MOUTH
OPEN LIKE A FARM ANIMAL.
>> YES.
>> OKAY, THE WORST IS WHEN SHE'S
QUIET.
IT'S SO CREEPY.
SERIOUSLY.
LIKE YESTERDAY WHEN WE WERE CAR
POOLING,
I COMPLETELY FORGOT SHE WAS IN
THE CAR BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T SAY A
WORD THE WHOLE TIME.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN SHE JUST
POPS UP IN THE BACK SEAT OUT OF
NOWHERE LIKE CHUCKY.
>> HEY, CHUCKY.
>> WE DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE IN
THERE.
>> WELL, I WAS.
>> DID YOU HEAR US TALKING?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
ONLY THE PART WHERE YOU COMPARED
ME TO JANET, YOU FILTHY SLUTS!
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MESS WITH
ME!
NO
>> NOW, I KNOW NO ONE LIKES
GETTING CALLED INTO AN HR MEETING,
BUT GIVEN WHAT HAPPENED
THIS MORNING, I FELT IT WAS
NECESSARY.
CHUCKY, AS YOU KNOW, WE HAVE A
COMPANY POLICY
AGAINST STABBING
YOUR COWORKERS IN THE LEGS WITH
A KNIFE.
BUT LADIES, WE ALSO HAVE A
ZERO-TOLERANCE POLICY WHEN IT
COMES TO BULLYING.
WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT CHUCKY WAS
UNCALLED FOR.
ESPECIALLY COMPARING HIM TO
JANET.
WHO WE ALL KNOW SUCKS.
>> I'M SORRY, WHY DO I HAVE TO
BE HERE?
>> TO TAKE NOTES, JANET.
>> OKAY, SO HOW CAN WE STOP THIS
KIND OF THING FROM HAPPENING IN
THE FUTURE?
>> BY PUTTING THESE BITCHES IN
BODY BAGS?
>> SEE, THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE.
- CHUCKY'S ALWAYS SAYING THINGS
LIKE THAT.
>> I ALSO THINK THESE
GENDER-NEUTRAL BATHROOMS WERE A
BIG MISTAKE.
>> UH-OH.
>> ONLY BECAUSE NOW I HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT CHUCKY DROPPING DOWN
FROM THE CEILING
AND LANDING ON
MY BACK WHILE I'M SITTING ON THE
TOILET.
>> DON'T TEMPT ME WITH A GOOD
TIME.
>> EW, CHUCKY, STOP.
>> CHUCKY, I UNDERSTAND THAT
WHEN YOUR FEELINGS GET HURT,
YOUR FIRST INSTINCT IS VIOLENCE.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU'RE STABBING ME
IN THE LEG RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU SEE, HE DOESN'T BELONG
HERE.
>> YES, HE DOES.
EACH OF US HAS A DIFFERENT
STORY.
MEGAN, YOU HAVE A BACKGROUND IN
PR.
PEGGY, YOU WERE IN THE MILITARY.
AND CHUCKY, YOU DID AN ANCIENT
VOODOO CURSE THAT WHEN COMBINED
WITH A LIGHTNING STRIKE
TRANSFERRED YOUR SOUL TO THE
BODY OF A DOLL.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT NO ONE
ELSE HERE CAN SAY.
>> HE'S NOT EVEN LISTENING.
>> WELL, I THINK WE'RE MAKING
PROGRESS.
>> LOOK!
OH MY GOD!
JANET!
ARE YOU EATING TUNA RIGHT NOW?
>> WHAT?
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, CAMILA
CABELLO.
* YOU SAID YOU
HATED THE OCEAN
BUT YOU'RE SURFIN' NOW *
* I SAID I'D LOVE
YOU FOR LIFE
BUT I JUST SOLD
OUR HOUSE *
* WE WERE KIDS AT THE START
I GUESS WE'RE
GROWN-UPS NOW MMM
COULDN'T EVER IMAGINE *
* EVEN HAVIN' DOUBTS
BUT NOT EVERYTHING
WORKS OUT NO
NOW I'M OUT DANCIN *
* WITH STRANGERS
YOU COULD BE
CASUALLY DATIN'
IT'S ALL CHANGIN' SO FAST *
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
YEAH LOVE CAME AROUND
AND IT KNOCKED ME DOWN
BUT I'M BACK ON MY FEET *
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
I WAS BARELY STANDIN'
BUT NOW I'M DANCIN'
HE'S ALL OVER ME *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
* IT'S BEEN A HELL OF A YEAH
THANK GOD WE MADE IT OUT
YEAH WE WERE RIDIN'
A WAVE AND TRYING *
* NOT TO DROWN
AND ON THE SURFACE
I HELD IT TOGETHER
BUT UNDERNEATH *
* I SORTA CAME UNWOUND
WHERE WOULD I BE
YOU'RE ALL THAT I NEED
MY WORLD YOU HOLD ME DOWN *
* YOU ALWAYS HOLD ME DOWN
WELL I'VE BEEN
THE BREAKER AND BROKEN
EVERY MISTAKE *
* TURNED TO MOMENTS
WOULDN'T TAKE
ANYTHING BACK *
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
YEAH LOVE CAME AROUND
AND IT KNOCKED ME DOWN
BUT I'M BACK ON MY FEET *
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
I WAS BARELY STANDIN'
BUT NOW I'M DANCIN'
SHE'S ALL OVER ME *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM *
* BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM *
* BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM
BAM-BAM
BA-DA BAM-BAM-BAM-BAM *
**
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
YEAH LOVE CAME AROUND
AND IT KNOCKED ME DOWN
BUT I'M BACK ON MY FEET *
* YEAH THAT'S JUST LIFE BABY
I WAS BARELY STANDIN'
BUT NOW I'M DANCIN'
SHE'S ALL OVER ME *
* NOW I NOW I'M DANCIN'
NOW I NOW I'M DANCIN'
BA-DA BAM BAM BAM BAM *
WEEKEND
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>> THE SENATE CONFIRMED KETANJI
BROWN JACKSON, MAKING HER THE
FIRST BLACK WOMAN TO SERVE ON
THE SUPREME COURT.
I'LL DRINK TO THAT SAID BRETT
KAVANAUGH.
JUSTICE JACKSON WAS HONORED
FRIED AT A WHITE HOUSE
CEREMONY AND SAID, THIS IS A
MOMENT IN WHICH ALL AMERICANS
CAN TAKE GREAT PRIDE.
WE HAVE COME A LONG WAY TOWARDS
PERFECTING OUR UNION.
WHICH IS ALSO A DIRECT QUOTE
FROM BEN AFFLECK'S "PROPOSAL."
>>> REPUBLICAN SENATOR TOM
COTTON, WHO WANTS EVERYONE TO
COOL IT WITH THE LONG NECK
JOKES, SAID THAT HE BELIEVES
SUPREME COURT JUSTICE JACKSON
WOULD HAVE
DEFENDED THE NAZIS AT NUREMBERG.
WORSE, HE MEANT IT AS A
COMPLIMENT.
WASHINGTON, D.C. BECAME A COVID
SUPERSPREADER EVENT WITH MORE
THAN 50 HIGH-RANKING OFFICIALS
GETTING INFECTED.
THE PROBLEM WAS A LOT OF PEOPLE
TOOK OFF THEIR MASKS DURING THE
POST-DINNER ORGY.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY NEEDED
THAT EXPLAINED WITH THE PICTURE.
THE PICTURE REALLY PAINTS A
PICTURE.
>>> HEALTH OFFICIALS IN
WASHINGTON, D.C. CONFIRMED THAT
A FOX THAT BIT A CONGRESSMAN
NEAR THE CAPITOL HAD RABIES.
OFFICIALS SUSPECT THE FOX
CONTRACTED LABORBIES WHEN IT WAS
BITTEN BY MARJORIE TAYLOR
GREENE.
>> IN A NEW INTERVIEW DONALD
TRUMP SAID HE WANTED TO JOIN THE
JANUARY 6th MARCH ON THE CAPITOL
BUT THAT THE SECRET WOULDN'T
ALLOW IT.
ALSO KEEPING HIM FROM JOINING,
STEPS.
>>> BARACK OBAMA RETURNED TO THE
WHITE HOUSE FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN FIVE YEARS AND JOKINGLY
REFERRED TO JOE BIDEN AS VICE
PRESIDENT.
HEY, BARACK, DON'T CONFUSE HIM!
>>> AS PUNISHMENT FOR SLAPPING
CHRIS ROCK, THE ACADEMY OF
MOTION PICTURES ARTS AND
SCIENCES HAVE BANNED WILL SMITH
FROM ATTENDING THE OSCARS FOR
TEN YEARS.
BUT IS THAT A PUNISHMENT?
HE CAN STILL BE NOMINATED, HE
CAN EVEN WIN AN AWARD.
HE CAN EVEN GO TO THE AFTER
PARTY.
HE JUST DOESN'T HAVE TO ATTEND
THE FOUR-HOUR CEREMONY WHERE
SOMEONE IS DEFINITELY GOING TO
MAKE FUN OF HIS WIFE AGAIN.
I THINK -- HONESTLY,
I THINK A REAL PUNISHMENT WOULD
BE TO MAKE WILL SMITH HOST NEXT
YEAR'S OSCARS.
BECAUSE, TRUST ME, NOTHING WILL
MAKE YOU QUESTION YOUR CHOICES
IN LIFE MORE THAN HOSTING AN
AWARDS SHOW.
>> I LOVED IT.
>>> BUSINESS LEADERS IN MIAMI
ARE HOPING TO MAKE THE CITY THE
CRYPTOCURRENCY CAPITAL OF THE
COUNTRY.
BECAUSE JUST LIKE CRYPTO, MIAMI
WON'T BE AROUND IN ABOUT 20
YEARS.
>>> UKRAINE PRESIDENT VOLODYMYR
ZELENSKYY MADE A TELEVISED
SPEECH DURING SUNDAY'S GRAMMY
AWARDS.
IT WAS A HEARTFELT IMPASSIONED
PLEA TO HELP THE PEOPLE OF
UKRAINE BUT A MISSED OPPORTUNITY
FOR A LEGENDARY G.I. JANE JOKE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DISNEY ANNOUNCED IT WILL SOON
LIFT THE COVID PROTOCOL AND ONCE
AGAIN ALLOW GUESTS TO HUG KUS
TOMB CHARACTERS.
THANK GOD.
IS THAT AN ADULT MAN SITTING
NEXT TO JASMINE?
>>> RED LOBSTER'S CEO IS
RESIGNING AFTER JUST EIGHT
MONTHS ON THE JOB SAYING, I HAVE
TRULY LOVED MY TIME HERE AT RED
LOBSTER.
WHICH IS ALSO WHAT MY DATES SAY
TO ME RIGHT BEFORE GETTING IN
THEIR UBER.
>> OH, THIS IS FUN.
AN ALLIGATOR IN FLORIDA WAS
PHOTOGRAPHED SWIMMING WITH A
BASKETBALL IN ITS MOUTH.
TURNING NOW TO SPORTS NEWS, TOM
BRADY IS MISSING.
>> A PERSONAL INJURY ATTORNEY IN
FLORIDA ALLEGEDLY DROVE HER CAR
INTO FOUR PEOPLE.
SAID THE ATTORNEY, HAVE YOU BEEN
INJURED IN AN ACCIDENT?
>> DUMB JOKE.
>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT AT LEAST
139 PEOPLE AROUND THE COUNTRY
HAVE SAID THEY BECAME SICK AFTER
EATING THE BREAKFAST CEREAL
LUCKY CHARMS.
ONE OR TWO PEOPLE GETTING SICK
COULD BE FINE BUT 139?
THAT'S
** TRAGICALLY SUSPICIOUS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> A NEW LAWSUIT ACCUSES BURGER
KING OF FALSELY ADVERTISING
THEIR WHOPPERS AS BIGGER THAN
WHAT PEOPLE ACTUALLY GET.
IT'S THE SAME ACCUSATION MADE IN
THE CASE OF WOMEN V. MICHAEL
CHE.
PREDICTING CONSUMER TRENDS.
HERE TO COMMENT ARE TWO TREND
FORECASTERS.
SO YOU'RE HERE TO SHARE YOUR
DATA ON TODAY'S MOST POPULAR
TRENDS, RIGHT?
>> THE NUMBERS ARE IN.
THE TRENDS OF TODAY HAVE BEEN
CAST.
HERE IS --
>> THE REPORT!
>> OUR FIRST CATEGORY IS --
>> WORKOUT TRENDS.
>> IN, NOT WIPING DOWN THE
EQUIPMENT.
>> IN, HURTING YOUR BACK.
>> IN, BOOKS IN THE LOCKER ROOM.
>> AND OUT --
>> BLASTING KELLY CLARKSON WHILE
JOGGING.
YOU'RE OUT.
>> SO GO TO HELL!
>> SHE HAS A TALK SHOW NOW.
>> SHE DOESN'T HAVE TIME TO
MOTIVATE YOUR
SICK ASS.
>> YOU HAD THE CHANCE TO DO IT,
GO TO BET, BITCH!
>> DAMN.
YOU GUYS ARE SO MAD.
>> KEEP IT DOWN, MIKE.
AND LISTEN TO OUR NEXT CATEGORY.
>> ROMANCE TRENDS.
>> IN, KISSING WITH TONGUE AND
HANDS TOO.
>> IN, CHEATING.
>> IN, STICKING YOUR PINKY IN
NEW PLACES.
>> AND OUT?
>> WAITING UP BY THE BEDROOM.
>> WAITING OUTSIDE THE SITTING
ROOM.
SUCK JUNK.
>> WHILE YOU'RE WAITING, I'M
GETTING A WETZEL PRETZEL, FOOL.
>> COME UP FROM THE CURTAIN AND
KISS ME OR WATCH ME LEAVE!
>> GO TO BED, BITCH!
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP SENDING
THINGS TO BED?
>> BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO GET UP
EARLY FOR A FLIGHT -- TO HELL!
>> ALERT.
IMPORTANT.
ALERT.
WE HAVE THE NEXT CATEGORY.
>> SOUND TRENDS.
>> IN -- RRR!
>> IN -- RUH-ROH.
>> IN -- OH YEAH.
>> AND OUT?
>> OH, OH, OH!
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO SNEEZE,
JUST DO IT, SHOW-OFF!
>> ARE YOU GOING TO SNEEZE OR
ARE YOU GOING TO ORGASM.
>> AND DON'T YOU DARE TELL ME IT
PASSED.
>> GO TO BED AND NEVER WAKE!
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL, BUT YOU
ARE STUPID.
>> NEXT UP IS --
>> FUTURE TRENDS.
>> IN, THE QUESTION, WOULD YOU
LIKE ANY PARMESAN?
>> AND WHAT'S GOING TO BE OUT IN
THE FUTURE?
>> WELL, MICHAEL.
THE COMPUTER IS SADLY OUT ON NEW
TRENDS.
>> YOU KNOW THAT THEY HAVE TO
DIE TO BE OUT.
>> OUT, FANCY DERBY HAT.
>> SHAKE WINGS.
>> AND MICHAEL CHE!
>> NO!
>> GO TO BED, BITCH!
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M
MICHAEL CHE I'M COLIN JOST
GOODNIGHT
LIGHTS, CAMERA, ACHOO, A LOOK
BACK AT SOME OF THE SICKEST
PERFORMANCES IN FILM HISTORY.
FROM TOM HANKS IN "PHILADELPHIA"
TO TOM HANKS' GIRLFRIEND IN
FORREST GUMP.
TONIGHT, WE FOCUS ON THE ROLE OF
DOC HOLLIDAY, MADE FAMOUS BY
VAL KILMER IN "TOMBSTONE."
THE SOUTHERN GENTLEMAN COWBOY
WHO KEEPS HIS RAGING
TUBERCULOSIS A SECRET.
DID YOU KNOW ANOTHER ACTOR
PLAYED DOC HOLLIDAY EVEN SICKER
JUST THE YEAR BEFORE?
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS SCENE FROM
THE 1992 FILM "COUGH, COUGH,
BANG, BANG."
>> WELL, IF IT ISN'T EARL.
GOT TO DO TO GET A DRINK AROUND
HERE?
>> MY NAME IS GREG.
AND MY GOD.
IT'S CURLY BILL
AND JOHNNY RINGO!
THEIR GANG'S BEEN TERRORIZING
THE WHOLE SOUTHWEST.
>> LISTEN UP.
WE HEARD AN OLD LAW MAN BY THE
NAME OF WYATT EARP IS HOLED UP
IN THIS HERE TOWN.
>> YEAH, IF YOU SEE HIM, TELL
HIM CURLY BILL AND JOHNNY RINGO
WANT TO PAY OUR RESPECTS.
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA!
>> WELL, YOU CAN TELL ME
YOURSELF.
>> WELL, WELL.
WYATT EARP.
WHERE'S YOUR LITTLE LAP DOG,
DOC HOLLIDAY?
>> WELL, I DO DECLARE.
I'D RATHER BE A LAP DOG THAN A
YELLOW-BELLIED CHICKEN.
>> ARE YOU OKAY THERE, DOC?
>> OH, YEAH.
JUST HAVE A LITTLE TICKLE IN MY
THROAT, BLOOD ON MY
HANDKERCHIEF, WHICH MEANS I'M ON
THE MEND.
NOW IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN, YOU
MUST BE CURLY BILL.
THAT MAKES YOU THE INFAMOUS
JOHNNY RINGO.
WORD IS YOU'RE THE FASTEST GUN
THIS SIDE OF THE MISSISSIPP'.
>> DOC, YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU SURE YOU SHOULD BE OUT
IN PUBLIC?
>> OF COURSE NOT.
>> YOU JUST SEEM LIKE VISIBLY
SICK.
>> NONSENSE!
IT'S JUST ALLERGIES.
ACHOO!
>> OH!
COME ON, MAN!
AT LEAST COVER YOUR MOUTH.
>> WHY?
YOU AFRAID SOMETHING WITTY MIGHT
FLY OUT, MAKE YOUR BRAIN
ACTUALLY WORK FOR A CHANGE?
>> NO, MAN.
I THINK HE'S WORRIED ABOUT
CATCHING WHATEVER INSANE ILLNESS
YOU HAVE, MAN.
COME ON, SWEAT IS POURING DOWN
YOUR FACE!
>> WELL, THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I HAVE A NORMAL BODY TEMPERATURE
OF 108.
>> CAN I INTEREST ANY OF YOUR
GENTLEMEN IN A GAME OF CARDS?
>> I THINK YOU'VE GOT SOME KIND
OF INTESTINAL ISSUE THERE, DOC.
>> SOME MIXED NUTS OUGHT TO
SETTLE MY STOMACH.
>> STOP TOUCHING THE NUTS.
>> I TOLD YOU, I'M NOT
CONTAGIOUS.
IT'S JUST A CASE OF THE
SNIFFLES.
ACHOO!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
DUDE.
DO YOU HAVE, LIKE, EBOLA?
>> HEY THERE, DOC.
YOU READY FOR ROUND TWO?
>> ROUND TWO?
YOU SLEPT WITH PATIENT ZERO OVER
HERE?
>> WELL, I THINK HE'S JUST
SWEATY BECAUSE I GOT HIM ALL
WORKED UP.
>> I CONFESS I'M FEELING A
STIRRING IN MY BRITCHES, WHICH
MEANS I'M EITHER AROUSED OR I
NEED TO CHANGE MY DIAPER AGAIN.
>> SO YOU'RE WEARING DIAPERS
NOW?
>> MY DOCTOR SAID A LOT OF
30-YEAR-OLDS WEAR DIAPERS.
HEY, DID ANYONE ELSE EAT THAT
RAW SNAKE AT THE COOKOUT LAST
WEEK?
>> ALL RIGHT, GET THE HELL OUT
OF HERE.
YOU'RE COMING IN HERE WITH YOUR
SNAKE FLU, DRINKING FROM MY CUP,
HAVING SEX WITH MY WHITE
DAUGHTER?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M GOING TO
END DOC HOLLIDAY'S LIFE RIGHT
NOW BEFORE GOD GETS THE
SATISFACTION.
>> WELL THEN, I MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE ONE LAST DRINK.
EARL, YOU GOT ANY ORANGE
PEDIALYTE?
>> THIS AIN'T NO CVS!
>> ALL RIGHT!
NOW LET'S SEE WHO'S REALLY THE
FASTEST GUN IN THE WEST.
ONE, TWO -- THREE!
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, YOU
KILLED DOC HOLLIDAY!
>> I GUESS IT WAS MORE LIKE
EUTHANASIA.
>> YEAH, BUT THAT'S BECAUSE DOC
DIDN'T HAVE A GUN.
HE JUST PULLED OUT A BOTTLE OF
PILLS LABELED VALTREX.
>> OH MY GOD, HE HAD HERPES TOO?
>> ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, YOU'LL
ALWAYS HAVE SOMETHING TO
REMEMBER ME BY.
**
>> I LIKED IT.
FOR "LIGHTS CAMERA, ACHOO," I
PREFER TO REMAIN ANONYMOUS.
GOOD NIGHT!
LET'S SEE IF THIS WORKS.
>> THIS WILL BE GOOD FOR US.
>> I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I WAS JUST ON A CALL.
I AM DR. WYATT.
AND TELL ME, WHAT BRINGS YOU IN
HERE TODAY?
>> JUST NOT SURE IF TED REALLY
LOVES ME ANYMORE.
HE'S ALWAYS LOCKED IN HIS
BASEMENT READING AMINE.
>> IT'S CALLED MANGA.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME, TED?
AM I IMPORTANT?
>> GUYS, LET'S TRY TO WORK
TOGETHER INSTEAD OF ATTACKING
EACH OTHER, OKAY?
I'M SORRY, DO YOU MIND IF I TAKE
THIS?
BITCH, I TOLD YOU NOT TO CALL ME
WHILE I'M WORKING.
OH, REALLY?
YOU'RE GOING TO SHOOT ME?
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU TRY, COME
TO, BITCH, IT'S ALL RIGHT!
NOW, AS I WAS SAYING, IT IS ALL
ABOUT COMMUNICATION.
>> I -- I'M SORRY, DID SOMEBODY
JUST THREATEN TO SHOOT YOU?
>> NO, NO.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW WHERE I
WORK.
TED, HAVE YOU ALWAYS BEEN AFRAID
OF CONFLICT?
>> UH -- WELL -- I WOULDN'T PUT
IT LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, I --
DO YOU NEED TO GET THAT?
>> NO.
THIS IS YOUR TIME, TED.
CONTINUE.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T LOVE
CONFLICT.
MY FATHER WAS AN ANGRY GUY,
ESPECIALLY WHEN HE WAS
DRINKING --
>> ACTUALLY, I DO HAVE TO TAKE
THIS.
HOLD THAT THOUGHT BECAUSE ANGER
IS NEVER THE ANSWER.
YEAH, HO, WHERE YOU AT?
OKAY, BECAUSE I'M AT 453 UNION
STREET, SIXTH FLOOR.
AND THERE'S THREE OF US
IN HERE AND WE ALL STRAPPED.
OKAY.
NOW WHERE WERE WE?
>> WHAT'S STRAPPED?
ARE WE STRAPPED?
>> NO, WE ARE NOT.
SHOULD WE LEAVE?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, THIS IS THE
PERFECT OPPORTUNITY OF
PRACTICING
EXPRESSING OUR EMOTIONS.
LET'S TRY AN EXERCISE.
WHY DON'T YOU READ THESE TEXTS
TO ME
FROM MY PARTNER AND TELL ME HOW
YOU WOULD RESPOND.
>> OKAY, FINE.
GIRL --
>> DON'T DO THAT VOICE.
>> OKAY.
GIRL, YOU THINK YOU THE ONLY ONE
SELLING FISH OUT IN THESE
STREETS?
I DON'T NEED YOUR STINKY TUNA
WHEN I GOT A BEACH FULL OF FRESH
PINK SALMON EVERY TIME IT RAINS.
I'MA BRING A GUN TO YOUR OFFICE.
OKAY, I'M CALLING THE POLICE.
>> NO, SHE'S NOT SERIOUS.
>> OH, LORD.
HIT THE FLOOR!
>> I THOUGHT YOU SAID IT WASN'T
SERIOUS.
>> SHE'S NOT.
>> WHAT'S UP, BITCH?
EVERYBODY'S GETTING SUPER
SOAKED.
>> BABY WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS IS MY WORK WIG.
>> YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
ASK CLARISA.
AIN'T THAT WHO YOU BEEN TEXTING?
>> I AIN'T BEEN TEXTING NOBODY,
BABY.
>> ACTUALLY, YOU DID TEXT
CLARISA.
>> OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I'M ABOUT TO GET MY REAL GUN.
>> WAIT, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
CAN YOU OPEN THE CLARISA TEXT
AND READ HER WHAT I SAID?
>> ME?
OKAY, SURE.
GIRRRL --
>> NOT THE VOICE, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THE VOICE.
>> DO NOT DO THAT.
>> FINE, FINE.
GIRL, YOU THINK I WANT YOUR TWO
DAY OLD CATFISH WHEN THE TILAPIA
I GET AT HOME SO IS WET, IT
MAKES THE RIVER JEALOUS?
LOSE THIS NUMBER OR I'LL SET
YOUR CAR ON FIRE.
OKAY.
I DON'T WANT TO READ THESE
OUTLOUD ANYMORE.
>> BABY, THAT'S WHAT YOU WERE
SAYING TO HER?
>> YES, BABY!
>> OKAY.
WELL -- ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THEN, I'VE GOT A LITTLE
TEXT FOR YOU.
>> COULD YOU READ THAT FOR ME?
>> SHE COULD JUST SAY IT TO YOU.
I DON'T HAVE TO READ --
>> FINE.
GIRL --
>> WAIT.
GIVE ME THE VOICE.
>> GIRRRL, WHY WE COUNT FISH
WHEN OUR LOVE IS THE WHOLE DAMN
OCEAN?
DEEP AND WIDE AND WET AS HELL.
>> OH, TED, IS THAT REALLY HOW
YOU FEEL?
>> I THINK SO.
I THINK THAT WE HAVE MADE A LOT
OF PROGRESS HERE.
>> YOU DID THIS ALL ON PURPOSE
TO HELP US.
>> YEAH, LET'S JUST GO WITH
THAT.
IT'S GOING TO BE $675, NO
INSURANCE, AND CASH ONLY.
>> OR ELSE!
>>> ONCE AGAIN, CAMILA CABELLO!
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK-FREAK-FREAK *
* PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK SOMETIMES
TRYNA GET CONNECTED *
* NO WI-FI
TELL ME THAT YOU LOVE ME
ARE YOU LYING
GIVE ME LEMONADE *
* I GIVE YOU LIMES
HOUSE IN THE HILLS
IS A HOUSE OF CARDS
BLINK AND THE *
* FAIRYTALE FALLS APART
SORRY DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET SO DARK
MAYBE I'M AN ALIEN *
* EARTH IS HARD
SOMETIMES I DON'T
TRUST THE WAY I FEEL
ON MY INSTAGRAM TALKIN' *
* 'BOUT I'M HEALED
WORRYIN' IF I STILL
GOT SEX APPEAL
HOPIN' THAT I DON'T *
* DRIVE OFF THIS HILL
WHEN WE'RE MAKIN' LOVE
I WANNA BE THERE
AND I WANNA FEEL *
* YOU PULLIN' MY HAIR
AND BELIEVE THE WORDS
YOU SAY IN MY EAR
GOTTA GO OUTSIDE *
* I NEED SOME AIR
I WANT TO WANT TO
WANT TO TOUCH YOU
WANT TO TOUCH YOU *
* BUT MY FINGERTIPS ARE NUMB
I WANT TO WANT TO
WANT TO LOVE YOU
WANT TO LOVE YOU *
* BUT MY CHEST
IS TIGHTENIN' UP
I WANT TO WANT TO
WANT TO FEEL *
* LIKE I CAN CHILL
NOT HAVE TO LEAVE
THIS RESTAURANT
WISH I COULD *
* BE LIKE EVERYONE
BUT I'M NOT LIKE ANYONE
FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK SOMETIMES *
* TRYNA GET CONNECTED
NO WI-FI
TELL ME THAT YOU LOVE ME
ARE YOU LYING *
* GIVE ME LEMONADE
I GIVE YOU LIMES
HOUSE IN THE HILLS
IS A HOUSE OF CARDS *
* BLINK AND THE
FAIRYTALE FALLS APART
SORRY DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET SO DARK *
* MAYBE I'M AN ALIEN
EARTH IS HARD
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA *
* FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK-FREAK-FREAK
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA *
* FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK
SORRY COULDN'T FOCUS
ON THE MOVIE *
* EVERYBODY SAYS THEY
MISS THE OLD ME
I BEEN ON THIS RIDE
SINCE I WAS FIFTEEN *
* I DON'T BLAME THE GIRLS
FOR HOW IT WENT DOWN DOWN
THINKIN' OUT LOUD
IN THE BATHROOM WHILE *
* MY FRIENDS LAUGH
ON THE COUCH
WOW MOMENT'S GONE NOW
KNOW YOU WANNA STAY *
* BUT I THINK I GOTTA
LEAVE RIGHT NOW
I WANT TO WANT TO
WANT TO TOUCH YOU *
* WANT TO TOUCH YOU
BUT MY FINGERTIPS ARE NUMB
I WANT TO WANT TO
WANT TO LOVE YOU *
* WANT TO LOVE YOU
BUT MY CHEST
IS TIGHTENIN' UP
I WANT TO WANT TO *
* WANT TO FEEL
LIKE I CAN CHILL
NOT HAVE TO LEAVE
THIS RESTAURANT *
* WISH I COULD
BE LIKE EVERYONE
BUT I'M NOT LIKE ANYONE
FEELIN' LIKE A *
* PSYCHOFREAK SOMETIMES
TRYNA GET CONNECTED
NO WI-FI
TELL ME THAT YOU LOVE ME *
* ARE YOU LYING
GIVE ME LEMONADE
I GIVE YOU LIMES
HOUSE IN THE HILLS *
* IS A HOUSE OF CARDS
BLINK AND THE
FAIRYTALE FALLS APART
SORRY DIDN'T MEAN *
* TO GET SO DARK
MAYBE I'M AN ALIEN
EARTH IS HARD
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA *
* PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
FEELIN' LIKE A
PSYCHOFREAK-FREAK-FREAK
PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA *
* PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-RA
* MAYBE I'M AN ALIEN
EARTH IS HARD *
>> THANK YOU, EVERYBODY!
>>> TRUCK STOPS HAVE THE WILDEST
STUFF.
>> MY OTHER CAR IS A GUN?
>> WHO ARE THESE WEIRDOS STILL
BUYING CDs?
>> WELL, TRUCKERS, THAT'S WHO.
>> OH.
VERY COOL.
>> YEAH, THIS ONE RIGHT HERE IS
A COLLECTION OF HITS BY MY
FAVORITE TRUCK DRIVING CROONER,
JOHNNY GOBLIN.
I'M TALKING ABOUT "TRUCK YOU,
YOU TRUCKIN' TRUCK."
42 SONGS ALL ABOUT TRUCKING.
>> GREAT.
DO YOU MIND IF WE JUST SCOOT
PAST YOU?
THIS COLLECTION INCLUDES
FENDER-BENDING HITS LIKE
TRUCKERS LIVE.
* I'M PEEING IN A
BOTTLE AND
PEEING IN A THERMOS
AND PEEING IN THE CUPS *
* PEEING IN A BUCKET
AND I'M PEEING IN A DIAPER
AND I'M PEEING OUT THE
WINDOW AND THE *
* WIND BLOWS IT
BACK INSIDE *
>> WHOO!
BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
GET YOUR HAHNKY HANDY FOR THIS
THIS HEART-WRENCHING DUET
BETWEEN TRUCKER AND TRUCKER'S
WIFE, FEATURING DARLENE CUISINE,
DON'T GO FORGETTING.
* GOTTA GO BACK
OUT ON THE ROAD
I'M GONNA MISS YOU
TILL I GET HOME *
* AND I'M ASKING
YOU TO REMEMBER
YOU ALWAYS GOT TO
REMEMBER *
* DON'T GO FORGETTING WHICH
CUP IS YOUR DRINK AND WHICH
CUP IS FULL OF PISS *
>> ARE ALL THESE SONGS ABOUT
PEEING?
>> WELL, NOT ALL.
BUT MANY OF THEM, YEAH.
BIG PART OF THE LIFESTYLE.
>> OKAY, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> THAT WOULD BE THE DREADED
GHOST TRUCKER.
FEATURING LITTLE PICKY PICKER.
**
* GHOST TRUCKER
GHOST TRUCKER
NO ONE CAN SEE HIM
ON THE ROAD *
* GHOST TRUCKER
WITH THE FOG COME ROLLING IN
AND IT'S HOG CAME
ROLLING OUT *
* REACHING IN
HIS PANTS HE
STARTS TO TOUCH HIMSELF
WITH THE SAME *
* HAND HE USED TO
EAT FLAMING HOT CHEETOS
PEOPLE SAY HIS *
* SCREAMS STILL
ECHO TO THIS DAY
GHOST TRUCKER *
>> OH, OH!
>> WHOO!
AND HOW ABOUT THE OLD CHILDREN'S
CLASSIC "BLOW THAT HORN."
**
* A LITTLE BOY
ON AN IPAD IN A
MINIVAN NEXT TO MINE *
* HE SIGNALS FOR
ME TO BLOW MY
HORN AND I HAPPILY
OBLIGE *
* A SMILE COMES ACROSS
HIS FACE I'M SO HAPPY
I CAN MAKE A DAY *
* AND THE CAR IN
FRONT OF ME GETS STARTLED
AS HELL AND THEY
VEER OFF INTO A DITCH *
>> Together: NO!
>> YES!
AND OF COURSE, NO COLLECTION IS
COMPLETE WITHOUT THE TRUCKER
STANDARD "THE HITCHHIKER."
**
* A HOT JULY DAY IN
2015 DOWN JUAREZ, MEXICO
I'M TRUCKING ALONG
THE HIGHWAY *
* A HITCHHIKER ON THE
SIDE OF THE ROAD *
* A MUSTACHIOED MAN
HELPED ME INTO
THE CAB BUT HE'S
ONLY FIVE FEET TALL *
* SOMETHING BOUT HIM LOOKS
SO FAMILIAR
AND THEN SUDDENLY I RECALL
HIS NAME'S EL CHAPO *
* EL CHAPO
OH GOD I THINK I HELPED EL
CHAPO *
* HE DEFINITELY
HELPED EL CHAPO *
>> I'M EL CHAPO, AND THIS IS A
CERTIFIED BUST.
>> "TRUCK YOU, YOU TRUCKIN'
TRUCK," AVAILABLE ONLY AT LOVE'S
TRUCK STOPS OFF THE I-40.
**
* GHOST TRUCKER
GHOST TRUCKER
GHOST TRUCKER *
* GHOST TRUCKER
WILLOW SMITH AND THE ENTIRE CAST
OF "SNL."
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
HAVE A WONDERFUL NIGHT, STAY
SAFE!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!