GOOD EVENING
>>> I'M LAURA INGRAHAM,
AND AS SOON AS I MARRY YOUR DAD, I'M
SENDING YOU STRAIGHT TO BOARDING
SCHOOL.
WELL, WE'RE FINALLY DONE WITH
YEAR ONE OF BIDEN'S PRESIDENCY.
CAN WE ALL ADMIT IT'S A
DISASTER?
INFLATION'S OUT OF CONTROL.
GAS IS AT $19 A GALLON.
AND THE GREEN M&M HAS BEEN
CANCELED JUST FOR BEING A WHORE.
THINGS ARE SO BAD IN BIDEN'S AMERICA,
EVEN FORMER WENDY'S
SPOKES GIRL JEN PSAKI
LOOK
NOT PASS
VOTING RIGHTS IS APPARENTLY NOT
GOING TO PASS.
AND VACCINE REQUIREMENTS ARE
APPARENTLY ILLEGAL.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WE ARE NOT GOOD PEOPLE.
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC SHOULD VOTE
US OUT.
>> THE BEST TWO THINGS SHE'S
EVER SAID.
PLUS THE NATION IS STILL
MOURNING FROM THE SUDDEN LOSS OF
AMERICA'S DAD,
ROBERT DURST.
THE COUNTRY'S ON ITS LAST LEGS,
FOLKS.
LIBERALS WANT TO TAKE AWAY
EVERYTHING THAT MAKES YOU
AMERICAN.
FOR EXAMPLE, GUNS, HAMBURGERS,
MORGAN WALLEN.
I DON'T CARE IF HE USES A SLUR,
I JUST WANT TO DANCE.
YOUR BACKUP GUNS,
COMMERCIAL WHERE THE WHOLE FAMILY IS THE
SAME THING.
USING THE WORD MAYONNAISE.
IT'S AIOLI ALL OF A SUDDEN, NO
THANKS, LIN-MANUEL.
AND FINALLY, MISSIONARY.
MY FIRST GUEST TONIGHT IS HERE
TO TALK ABOUT HOW HE'S PUSHING
BACK AGAINST BIDEN'S TYRANNY.
YOU KNOW HIM.
TED CRUZ.
HELLO, LAURA.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> BEARD STILL GOING STRONG,
HUH, TED?
>> OH, YEAH.
MY BEARD IS LIKE JANUARY 6th.
SHOCKING AT FIRST, BUT SADLY
IT'S BEEN NORMALIZED.
SPEAKING OF JANUARY 6th, YOU
RECENTLY HAD TO APOLOGIZE
FOR CALLING THE CAPITOL RIOTERS
TERRORISTS.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU 100%.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE CALLED THEM
TERRORISTS.
THE TRUTH IS, THEY ARE BIG,
BURLY
MEN WITH BIG "D" ENERGY.
IN FACT, I ACTUALLY LIKE THEM A
LOT.
THEY ARE MY COOL FRIENDS.
AND DONALD, IF YOU'RE WATCHING,
I LOVE YOU, BABY.
YOU ARE THE KING.
HONESTLY, HIT ME.
>> DID YOU JUST ASK TRUMP TO HIT
YOU?
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
HIT ME, CHOKE ME, SPIT IN MY
FACE.
I JUST WANT TO STAY IN THE MIX.
>> THANKS FOR BEING HERE, TED.
>> OH, AND ONE MORE THING.
I LIKE TO REMIND ALL MY FELLOW
TEXANS WATCHING AT HOME
THAT
FEBRUARY'S GOING TO BE A COLD ONE,
SO YOU MIGHT WANT TO BOOK
YOUR VACAY TO CANCUN NOW.
LIVE MAS, EVERYBODY!
ADVICE
AND I'D LIKE TO TAKE A MOMENT TO
THANK MY FEW REMAINING LOYAL
SPONSORS.
COVID NEGS,
THE COVID TEST
THAT'S GUARANTEED TO BE NEGATIVE
EVEN IF YOU HAVE IT.
COVID NEGS, I'M GOING TO YOUR
WEDDING.
AND FALSE ALARM MEDICAL ALERT.
IF YOUR GRANDKIDS THINK IT'S THE
END, THEY'LL CALL.
AND WHITE PIZZA.
FOR WHEN ITALIAN IS TOO ETHNIC.
OUR NEXT GUEST IS THE LATEST
VICTIM OF THE VACCINE POLICE
WITH A NAME I SOMEHOW HAVE AN
EASIER TIME LEARNING TO
PRONOUNCE THAN KAMALA HARRIS.
PLEASE WELCOME NOVAK DJOKOVIC.
>> YES.
OH, YES.
CALL ME BY MY NICKNAME, THE
JOKER.
ALTHOUGH RIGHT NOW I'M THE LEAST
POPULAR JOKER,
EXCEPT FOR
JARED LETO.
>> NOW I FOUND HIM RELATABLE.
SO NOVAK, YOU WERE DEPORTED FROM
AUSTRALIA FOR REFUSING TO BE VACCINATED,
AND I NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD HEAR MYSELF USE THE WORD
DEPORTED IN A BAD WAY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I WENT TO AUSTRALIA, AND MY
VISA WAS DENIED.
BUT THEN I APPEALED TO THE
JUDGE, AND THIS WAS HIS RULING.
>> OUT.
>> I MUST SAY, I AM A FAN OF
YOUR SPORT,
BECAUSE IN TENNIS, LOVE
IS BAD.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU TELL YOUR
SIDE OF THE STORY
WHILE I STARE
INTO THE CAMERA LIKE IT'S A RAW
PIECE OF STEAK.
>> OH, THANK YOU, LAURA.
YOU SEE,
PEOPLE LOVE TO TEAR YOU OFF YOUR
PEDESTAL
JUST BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE REALLY RICH OR YOU'RE THE
BEST AT TENNIS,
OR YOU KNOW, YOU
GO TO A CHARITY EVENT WITH
200 KIDS EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE
DRIPPING WITH COVID.
BUT IN MY HEART I KNOW THAT ONE
DAY PEOPLE WILL LOOK BACK ON
THIS MOMENT IN HISTORY
AND THINK, "YEAH, WHO CARES?"
THANK YOU, NOVAK.
SEE YOU AT WIMBLEDON.
>> PROBABLY NOT.
>> YEAH.
MY NEXT GUEST IS HERE TO ADDRESS
A VOTING RIGHTS BILL
WHICH WOULD
MAKE IT EASIER FOR MINORITIES TO VOTE
AND HARDER FOR WHITE PEOPLE
IN FLORIDA TO VOTE TWICE.
PLEASE WELCOME MY ONE BLACK
FRIEND, CANDACE OWENS.
>> MARTIN LUTHER KING WOULD HAVE
VOTED FOR TRUMP.
>> HELLO TO YOU TOO.
>> LAURA, LIBERALS ARE TRYING TO
MAKE EVERYTHING ABOUT RACE.
TO QUOTE THE ONLY WORDS THAT
MARTIN LUTHER KING EVER SAID,
I
HAVE A DREAM.
THAT'S IT, END OF QUOTE.
NOTHING ABOUT MONEY OR JOBS OR
SCHOOLS.
UNLESS YOU COUNT HIS TOMBSTONE
WHICH SAYS, GREAT JOB, GANG,
RACISM OVER.
>> I HOPE PEOPLE AT HOME ARE
WRITING THIS DOWN.
>> THANKS, LAURA.
IT'S MY GREATEST HONOR TO
CONTINUE THE FIGHT FOR AFRICAN AMERICANS,
NO MATTER HOW MANY
TIMES THEY ASK ME TO STOP.
>> THANK YOU, CANDACE.
I'D LIKE TO THANK A FEW MORE OF
MY LOYAL SPONSORS.
BIBLE BELT.
HOLD YOUR PANTS UP THE WAY GOD
INTENDED.
FLOWER POISON.
EVER SEE A BIG GARDEN FULL OF
FLOWERS AND THINK, "I WISH THEY
WERE DEAD?"
FLOWER POISON.
AND PAULA DEEN'S CHICKPEA MASH.
IT'S NOT RADICAL ISLAMIST HUMMUS,
IT'S AMERICAN CHICKPEA
MASH.
TALK OF THE 2024 REPUBLICAN
PRIMARIES IS ALREADY HEATING UP,
SO LET'S TALK TO THE SVELTE, MUSCULAR,
230 POUND GORILLA IN THE ROOM,
DONALD TRUMP.
>> HELLO, LAURA.
HELLO, LAURA.
IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE HERE.
I'M BACK LIKE "TIGER KING 2."
YOU HAD FUN THE FIRST TIME, AND
NOW YOU'RE LIKE,
"HOW ARE MORE
PEOPLE FROM THIS NOT IN JAIL
YET?"
>> MR. PRESIDENT, YOU'RE OUT ON
THE TRAIL AGAIN,
CREATING
CONTROVERSY WITH YOUR TYPICAL WACKO STUFF
AND YOUR
UNCHARACTERISTICALLY REASONABLE
TAKES ON BOOSTER SHOTS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GIVE OUR
VIEWERS A TASTE?
>> I SURE WOULD.
CAN WE GET TODAY'S WORDLE
PLEASE?
>> I GOT THE BOOSTER, OKAY.
BECAUSE I MADE THE BOOSTER.
IT'S A WONDERFUL VACCINE.
BUT IT'S VERY UNFAIR WHAT IS
HAPPENING WITH THE COVID
TREATMENT, OKAY.
WHITE PEOPLE ARE BEING TOLD TO
GET IN THE BACK OF LINE.
SPEAKING OF WHITE PEOPLE,
JOHN MAYER.
OKAY, JOHN MAYER HASN'T HAD A
HIT IN SO LONG, BUT WE LOVE
MAYER, OKAY?
BODY WONDERLAND.
COME ON, I THOUGHT IT WAS
TREMENDOUS MUSIC.
I THOUGHT IT WAS TREMENDOUS
MUSIC.
WITH "BODY WONDERLAND."
YOU KNOW, I'D RATHER BE THE
MAYOR OF ANYTHING THAN BE
GOVERNOR RON DeSANTIS
I BEAT HIM SO BAD.
JUST LIKE I BEAT HILLARY.
BECAUSE THE ONLY HILLARY WE LIKE
IS DUFF, OKAY?
FROM "HOW I MET YOUR FATHER."
YOU KNOW WHAT, "HOW I MET YOUR FATHER,"
IT REALLY DOESN'T HAVE
THE CHARM AND SPARKLE OF,
FRANKLY, MOTHER.
OKAY?
BUT WE LOVE DUFF.
YOU KNOW, SHE GOT HER TEETH
FIXED.
NOT LOOK LIKE
AND "LIZZIE McGUIRE," YOU KNOW,
THEY WANTED TO DO A LIZZIE WITH HULU,
BUT THEY SAID NO SEX,
THEY DIDN'T WANT SEX.
SO THEY WENT THEIR SEPARATE WAYS
JUST LIKE LISA AND JASON MAMOA.
BIG
DEVIL
AND "THE DEVIL WEARS PRADA."
MY DAUGHTER
DAUGHTERS IS BY JOHN MYER.
AND I'VE GOT TO RUN TO THE HOLES
OF YOUR HIGH SCHOOL IN 2024 WHEN
YOU RE-ELECT TRUMP.
WORDLE!
>> THERE IT IS, WE GOT IT.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WILL
FORTE!
THANK
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HERE
TONIGHT.
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME HOSTING
SNL.
I WAS IN THE CAST 12 YEARS AGO
WITH KRISTEN WIIG, BILL HADER,
ANDY SAMBERG, JASON SUDEIKIS AND
FRED ARMISEN.
SO IT WAS REALLY FUN TO SEE
KRISTEN HOST.
YEP.
AND BILL.
AND THEN ANDY.
THEN FRED.
THEN KRISTEN AGAIN.
THEN BILL AGAIN.
THEN JASON.
SETH MEYERS.
I MEAN, HE'S ONE OF MY BEST
BUDS, RIGHT?
BUT, COME ON.
HE WASN'T REALLY A SKETCH GUY,
HE WAS JUST ON "WEEKEND UPDATE."
DOES THAT EVEN COUNT AS BEING ON
THE SHOW?
BUT HE HOSTED.
RIGHT?
JOHN MULANEY WAS A WRITER WHEN I
WAS IN THE CAST.
AND THEN HE HOSTED FOUR TIMES.
FOUR TIMES.
BUT HEY, THAT'S OKAY.
I'M NOT BITTER ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT.
SAVED THE BEST FOR LAST, RIGHT?
>> SAVED THE BEST FOR WAY LAST.
BUT, LOOK, AFTER 12 LONG YEARS,
TONIGHT IT'S FINALLY MY TURN.
MY TIME TO SHINE.
TONIGHT IS ALL ABOUT ME.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
KRISTEN.
HEY.
YEAH.
>> WILL, I AM SO EXCITED THAT
YOU'RE HOSTING.
>> NOT A GOOD TIME.
>> OKAY.
WELL, IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
BYE-BYE!
SO -- SO I SHOULD GO?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO.
>> I FLEW IN FOR THIS.
>> OH, GREAT, SO YOU KNOW WHERE
THE AIRPORT IS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, BACK TO NORTH KOREA.
IT WAS REALLY HARD TO GET OUT.
>> SO I DON'T LOVE
THAT SHE GOT MORE APPLAUSE THAN
WHEN I CAME OUT.
YOU KNOW, I CAME OUT ONCE WHEN
SHE WAS HOSTING,
AND I DID
SOMETHING IN HER MONOLOGUE.
BUT I WAS POLITE ENOUGH TO GET
LESS APPLAUSE THAN HER.
YOU KNOW.
BUT LOOK, MY POINT IS, MAYBE THE
UNIVERSE HAD A REASON FOR MAKING
ME WAIT TO HOST.
MAYBE IT WANTED ME TO WAIT UNTIL
MacGRUBER, THE SERIES, WAS
STREAMING ON PEACOCK.
NOW, SPEAKING OF "MacGRUBER," I
WOULD LIKE TO OFFICIALLY ANNOUNCE
THAT "MacGRUBER" HAS
BEEN PICKED UP FOR A SEASON TWO.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
THAT.
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN PICKED UP
YET, SO I CAN'T.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE WAITING TO HEAR.
BUT I CAN ANNOUNCE THAT YOU'RE
IN GREAT HANDS TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW?
STRONG, VEINY COMEDY HANDS.
AND, LOOK, IF I COULD JUST TAKE
A SERIOUS MOMENT.
I'D LIKE TO SAY HOW MUCH THIS
SHOW HAS MEANT TO ME.
I STARTED MY CAREER HERE, AND
THEY ALWAYS SUPPORTED ME.
WAIT A SECOND.
ARE THEY PLAYING ME OFF?
ARE YOU PLAYING ME OFF IN MY OWN
MONOLOGUE?
I WAITED 12 FREAKING YEARS FOR
THIS.
HAVE YOU SEEN SOME OF THE IDIOTS
THEY HAD HOST THE SHOW SINCE
THEN.
KRISTEN, BILL, ANDY, FRED.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'LL TAKE ONE QUESTION.
YOU, SIR.
>> I'M SO SORRY, WILL.
THERE'S BEEN A MISTAKE.
>> HEY!
>> WILLEM DAFOE,
YOU'RE HOSTING NEXT WEEK.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S THIS
WEEK.
>> YOU THINK I'D BOOK SOMEONE
NAMED WILL, THEN SOMEONE NAMED
WILLEM?
>> OH MY GOD, THIS IS NOT
HAPPENING.
YOU TEXTED ME TO COME HOST,
LORNE.
>> I TESTED WILLEM, AND YOU
KNOW, AUTO CORRECT.
>> ALL RIGHT, FINE.
THEN LET'S HAVE THE FANS DECIDE
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
DAFOE
>> OH, MY GOD?
5%?
I GUESS PEOPLE DO LOVE ME.
LOOK, WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW.
I'M HERE, MANESKIN'S HERE.
SO STICK AROUND, AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK.
HE
ANIMAL
GENIUS
GRUBER
FEDERAL
CONTROL ROOM
SEALED.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
>> MacGRUBER, IF WE DON'T
DISMANTLE THE C4 EXPLOSIVE, THIS
WHOLE BUILDING IS GOING TO BLOW
SKY HIGH.
60 SECONDS.
>> OKAY, DON'T WORRY, GANG, WE
CAN DO THIS IF WE WORK TOGETHER
AS A TEAM.
AND LOOK, I KNOW THIS WHOLE
COVID SITUATION HAS REALLY CHANGED THE GAME,
SO WE GOT TO
BE SMART ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
WE'RE IN A SMALL ROOM WITH VERY
LIMITED AIRFLOW.
>> GOOD CALL.
>> YEAH, GREAT THINKING,
MacGRUBER.
>> OKAY, VICKI, PASS ME THAT OLD
TIN.
>> YOU GOT IT, MacGRUBER.
>> PIPER, THAT LIGHTER FLUID.
>> COMING AT YOU, GRUBS.
>> NOW BOTH OF YOU, HAND ME YOUR
MASKS.
>> WHAT?
>> NO TIME TO EXPLAIN, MASKS
NOW!
>> MacGRUBER, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> FREEING US FROM TYRANNY,
VICK.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WELCOME FOR WHAT?
I REALLY WANTED TO WEAR THAT
MASK.
>> YEAH, YOU JUST SAID YOURSELF
THAT WE'RE IN A SMALL ENCLOSED
ROOM.
>> YES, SO WE NEED EVERY DROP OF
OXYGEN WE CAN GET,
WHICH IS
IMPOSSIBLE WITH THESE STUPID
FACE DIAPERS.
I CAN FINALLY BREATHE.
>> I'VE GOT TO SAY I'M A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THIS.
>> DON'T WORRY, VICK.
I'M VAXED AND RELAXED.
HERE'S PROOF.
>> I THINK THERE'S A "P" MISSING
AT THE BEGINNING OF PFIZER.
>> MADE OF A SIZLER?
>> SURE DID, PIPER.
>> AND VICKI, IF THERE WAS A "P"
IN FRONT OF PFIZER, IT WOULD BE
PRONOUNCED P-FIZER.
TRY
>> JUST ADMIT YOU'RE NOT
VACCINATED.
>> OKAY, FINE, YOU FREAKING
KAREN.
I'M NOT GETTING THAT STUPID
SHOT, ALL RIGHT,
'CAUSE I DON'T
WANT THE GOVERNMENT PUTTING A
TRACKING DEVICE IN MY SCROTUM.
>> MacGRUBER, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> YEAH, I DON'T NEED TO KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT, PIPER,
BECAUSE I HAVE A BRAIN.
BECAUSE YOU TWO SHEEPLE ARE SO
FREAKED OUT, LET ME ASSURE YOU,
I'M TOTALLY ANTI-SEMITIC.
>> I'M NOT SURE WE HEARD YOU
RIGHT.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY SYMPTOMS.
>> I THINK THE WORD YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR IS ASYMPTOMATIC.
>> YES, THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> NO, I DEFINITELY SAID I'M
ANTI-SEMITIC.
>> YEAH, YOU DID.
>> SO WHAT'S THE ISSUE HERE?
>> MacGRUBER, 10 SECONDS!
>> LOOK, WE MAY NOT ALL AGREE ON
THIS HOAX VACCINE,
BUT ONE THING
WE CAN ALL AGREE ON IS THAT I DO
KNOW HOW TO DEFUSE BOMBS.
>> 1 SECOND, MacGRUBER!
>> OKAY, PIPER, HAND ME
SUSIE IS OKAY.
SHE'S BACK HOME, AND SHE'S OKAY.
AND WE HAVE A BRAND-NEW "KID
KLASH" CONTESTANT READY TO GO.
MEET TATUM.
>> HEY, EVERYONE.
I'M THE SHORTEST AND THE SLOWEST
ONE ON MY BASKETBALL TEAM, BUT
HERE I'M GOING TO WIN, I'M
TATUM.
>> GREAT, 'TUDE, TATUM.
AND TODAY'S PRIZE IS PIZZA FOR
LIFE.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU GET TO KEEP
THIS ONE PIZZA FOR YOUR ENTIRE
LIFE.
>> I REALLY WANT THAT.
>> WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
THE COURSE.
FIRST, YOU'RE TAKING A DIVE INTO
THE WHIPPED CREAM PIE TO FIND
THE FLAG.
>> WHOA!
>> THEN MOVE ON TO THE SLIPPERY
MONKEY BARS.
BUT WATCH OUT FOR THE PIT OF HOT
NACHO CHEESE BELOW.
>> I HOPE IT'S NOT TOO HOT.
>> OH, IT IS.
IT'S REALLY HOT.
>> OKAY.
>> FINALLY, YOU AND YOUR FAMILY
CLIMB INTO THIS GIANT GLASS TO
BECOME A HUMAN SHRIMP COCKTAIL.
>> YOU CAN DO THIS, HONEY!
>> WE'RE READY TO BE SHRIMP WITH
YOU!
>> NOW, REMEMBER, YOU CAN'T MOVE
ON TILL YOU FIND THAT FLAG.
READY, SET, GO!
>> WHOA, OH!
>> WELL, TATUM IS DEEP IN THE
CREAM AND LOOKING FOR THAT FLAG.
HERE'S A "KID KLASH" FACT ABOUT
HER.
YEAH.
TATUM FAVORITE THINGS ARE
SPAGHETTI AND BEACH BALLS.
ALL RIGHT.
TATUM, HAVE YOU FOUND THAT
FLAG YET?
>> NO, SO FAR JUST FEELING THE
CREAM.
>> WELL KEEP LOOKING.
AND HERE'S A HINT, IT'S IN
THERE.
>> DO YOU NOT KNOW WHAT A FLAG
IS?
>> NO, I DO.
>> THEN TRY TO FIND IT.
>> I AM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER "KID KLASH" FACT.
TATUM WAS DISQUALIFIED FROM THE
CHILI COOK-OFF AT HER SCHOOL FOR
LYING.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, TATUM?
>> THE CREAM'S REALLY THICK, I'M
WORKING PRETTY HARD HERE.
>> WELL, DOESN'T SHOW.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
I THINK I FOUND SOMETHING.
IT'S SOME KIND OF GOLD
MEDALLION.
>> AMAZING.
BUT ONE QUESTION FOR YOU, TATUM.
IS A MEDALLION THE SAME AS A
FRIGGING FLAG?
>> NO, BUT -- IT SEEMED LIKE
MAYBE IT'S WORTH MORE THAN A
FLAG.
>> WELL, YOU'RE WRONG, TATUM.
IT'S PROBABLY LEFT OVER FROM
LAST WEEK'S SHOW.
>> WHAT?
YOU DON'T CHANGE THE CREAM?
>> I DON'T KNOW, TATUM.
BUT YOUR TIME IS UP IN 3, 2, 1.
>> DANG IT!
>> THAT'S OKAY, HONEY.
>> DAMMIT, TATUM!
>> WELL, I'M SORRY, EVERYONE, I
COULDN'T DO IT.
I COULDN'T FIND THE FLAG.
>> AND WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
GOING?
>> I GUESS TO GET CLEANED UP AND
GO BACK TO INDIANA.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
NOT UNTIL YOU FIND THAT FLAG.
>> BUT -- BUT THE TIME ENDED.
>> LOOK, I DIDN'T START THIS
GAME SHOW TO ENCOURAGE CHILDREN
TO QUIT LIKE BABIES.
NOW, I WAS VERY CLEAR.
YOU GET OUT
OF THE PIE WHEN YOU FIND THE
FLAG.
>> MOM?
>> WE AGREE WITH HIM, TATUM.
SHE NEVER SEES ANYTHING THROUGH,
MR. ZASS.
>> OKAY.
I'LL KEEP TRYING.
>> NOW, TATUM, AS I'M
SURE YOU KNOW, YOU AND YOUR
SHRIMP FAMILY ARE NOW INELIGIBLE
FOR THE PIZZA FOR LIFE PRIZE.
>> SHOOT, THIS MUSIC IS
MAKING ME FEEL BAD.
>> AND I'M JUST NOW REMEMBERING
THE PIE WAS SUPPOSED TO SPIN.
CAN WE GET THAT GOING?
>> WAIT.
DOES THIS PART HAVE TO GO ON TV?
>> TATUM, YOU KNOW THAT IT DOES.
HOW DO YOU THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE IN THE REAL
WORLD, HUH?
>> LIKE THIS, I GUESS?
>> YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE WHIPPED CREAM IS ADVERSITY.
AND THE FLAG IS YOUR UNFULFILLED
POTENTIAL.
>> OKAY, WELL, I THINK I JUST
GOT MY PERIOD.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST TO
DO THAT IN THERE.
>> WAIT, OH MY GOD, IS THIS IT?
>> OH!
SHE FOUND THE FLAG!
>> IT'S SO SMALL!
AND IT'S WHITE LIKE THE CREAM.
THIS IS A REALLY BAD GAME.
>> NO.
IT'S GOOD!
WHEN WE RETURN, WE'RE GOING TO
PUT THE ADOPTED BROTHER ON THE
MONKEY BARS!
>> I'M ADOPTED?
>> YES, YOU ARE.
WITH BERIGHT BACK WITH MORE
HE DID A LOT OF READING
AND HE'S GOT A NEW ALBUM
HE REALIZED THERE WAS *
* MORE THAN JUST
ONE SIDE TO THIS
ISSUE *
HE'S FOLLOWING THE SCIENCE
NOW
MACGRUBER *
CHEMICAL
CONTROL ROOM
>> SHOOT!
THIS VAULT DOOR'S WELDED SHUT.
THERE'S NO WAY OUT.
>> AND FROM THE LOOKS OF OUR
DYNAMITE BOMB WE'VE ONLY GOT 60 SECONDS
BEFORE THIS WHOLE
PLACE IS BLOWN TO BETSY.
>> NOT A PROBLEM, GANG.
WE GOT THIS.
DON'T WORRY.
AFTER THE LAST MISSION I'VE HEARD YOUR CONCERNS
AND NOW I'M
FOLLOWING ALL THE PROTOCOLS.
>> WELL MACGRUBER, THERE'S A BIG
HOLE IN YOUR MASK.
>> UH YEAH, SO I DON'T SUFFOCATE
FROM ALL THE CARBON DIOXIDE,
DUH.
LOOK, THERE'S NO REASON TO BE
SCARED.
I'M GOING TO BE FINE.
I'VE DONE A TON OF RESEARCH AND
I'M FOLLOWING THE SCIENCE NOW.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> OKAY.
VICKY, PASS ME THAT IVERMECTIN.
>> OKAY, HERE.
>> PIPER, THAT
HYDROXYCHLOROQUINE.
>> HERE.
>> MacGRUBER, YOU HAVE COVID?
>> HELL NO.
>> OH, THANK GOD.
>> I HAVE COVID PLUS.
IT'S A COVID STRAIN MIXED
WITH -- SOMETHING ELSE.
>> SYPHILIS.
>> YOU GOT IT.
GOOD ON YOU.
DO YEAH, COVID, SYPHILIS.
AND I DO HAVE AN UNCONNECTED
FREESTANDING HERPES IN THERE AS
WELL.
I ALSO HAVE HORSE WORMS SO THIS
IVERMECTIN IS PULLING DOUBLE
DUTY.
>> YOU HAVE HORSE WORMS?
>> OH, YEAH, A BUNCH OF THEM.
CHECK THIS OUT.
>> OH THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> RELAX, IT'S JUST SPAGHETTI.
DOWN HERE IN MY JOCKEYS, JUST
WAITING FOR THE RIGHT MOMENT TO
SPRING THIS LITTLE JOKE ON YOU.
PUNK'D!
A LITTLE AL DENTE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE HORSE WORMS?
>> NO, I DO HAVE HORSE WORMS.
OH, LOOK, THEY'RE CHOMPING ON
THE SPAGHETTI.
LEAVE THAT ALONE, YOU LITTLE
TURKEYS.
THAT'S MY FOOD.
I'M NOT GONNA EAT THIS NOW.
>> MacGRUBER, THE BOMB!
>> OKAY, PIPER, HAND ME THAT
TOILET PAPER WITH DR. ANTHONY
FAUCI'S FACE ON IT.
>> HERE.
>> VICKY, HAND ME THAT "LET'S GO
BRANDON" T-SHIRT.
>> HERE YOU GO, MacGRUBER.
>> SO FUNNY, HUH?
IT'S ACTUALLY MADE OF SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> YEAH, WE KNOW.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
>> YOU'VE GONE DOWN SOME
ALT-RIGHT MISINFORMATION RABBIT
HOLE.
>> YOU'RE ALT WRONG ABOUT THAT,
KAREN.
MY INFORMATION IS
100% NON-INSANE.
EVER HEARD OF QANON?
CLASSICS ON TBS.
>> GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO
CINEMA CLASSICS.
I AM REESE DE'WHAT!
IF YOU'VE HEARD THE PHRASE,
GASLIGHTING, YOU PROBABLY KNOW
IT MEANS TO MANIPULATE SOMEONE
INTO BELIEVING A FALSE REALITY.
BUT WHAT YOU MAY NOT KNOW IS
THAT THE PHRASE ORIGINALLY COMES
FROM THE 1944 FILM, "GASLIGHT,"
STARRING INGRID BERGMAN AS A
WOMAN WHOSE HUSBAND MAKES HER
BELIEVE SHE'S GOING INSANE BY
SLOWLY DIMMING THE GAS-FUELED
LIGHTS AROUND HER AND THEN
DENYING IT.
WHY DOES HE DO THIS?
I DO NOT KNOW.
AND I'M BAD AT GUESSING.
LIKE WHEN MY WIFE ASKED ME TO
GUESS WHAT SHE WAS MAKING FOR
DINNER AND I SAID, I DON'T KNOW,
A MESS?
WORST WELCOME HOME FROM PRISON
EVER.
HER!
LET'S WATCH A SCENE FROM
GASLIGHT NOW WHERE
CHARLES BOYER AS THE EVIL
HUSBAND TRIES TO MAKE HIS WIFE
BELIEVE SHE'S INSANE.
>> HOLD ON, I HAVE TRIED SO HARD
TO KEEP THIS, BUT YOU HAVE LOST
YOUR MIND A SECRET, BUT NOW I'M
AFRAID ALL OF LONDON KNOWS IT.
>> GRIZZLY, NO.
I'M NOT INSANE.
LOOK, EVERY NIGHT THE GASLIGHTS,
THEY GROW DIMMER.
>> NO, THEY DON'T.
>> THEY DON'T?
BUT LOOK.
IT'S JUST A TINY FLAME.
>> OH, MY CUCKOO DARLING, IN THE
WEEK AND A HALF YOU'VE KNOWN ME,
HAVE I EVER LIED TO YOU?
>> I GUESS NOT.
BUT HUMOR ME.
TURN THE GASLIGHTS UP
AS HIGH AS THEY'LL GO, PLEASE,
FOR ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL THE WAY UP.
THERE YOU GO.
>> AND THAT WAS UP?
BECAUSE THAT'S TO ME, THAT
SEEMED LIKE NOT UP.
>> AND I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY, OUR
GAS BILL IS GOING TO BE INSANE,
JUST LIKE YOUR BRAIN.
AND I'M AFRAID ITS MEMBRANE AS
WELL.
>> OH, NO.
I DON'T KNOW UP FROM DOWN.
THE NEXT THING YOU'RE GOING TO
TELL ME IS THAT THIS ISN'T A
BOOK.
>>, PAULA.
THAT'S A RAT!
>> IT IS?
I'VE BEEN READING RATS ALL THESE
YEARS?
OH, NO.
AM I REALLY THAT MAD?
I SET A GOAL FOR
MYSELF OF READING A RAT A MONTH.
>> PAULA, CALM YOURSELF AND PLAY
WITH THE PUPPY THAT I GAVE YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> YIKES.
YOU KNOW, IN MY HOUSE,
GASLIGHTING IS WHEN I STRIKE A
MATCH AFTER MY WIFE BLASTS ONE
OUT UNDER THE BLANKETS.
LET'S WATCH ANOTHER SCENE AS
GREGORY DRIVES PAULA EVEN
FURTHER INTO DELUSION WITH THE
HELP OF A SURLY MAID PLAYED BY
18-YEAR-OLD ANGELA LANSBURY.
>> OH, GREGORY.
DO YOU REGRET MARRYING A CRAZY
CUCKOO BIRD OF A WOMAN WHO
BELONGS IN A HOTEL FOR NUTS?
>> PAULA, PLEASE STOP!
JUST TRY TO ENJOY YOUR STEAK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, BUM.
EAT YOUR LITTLE STEAK.
>> DUDE, I DON'T CARE HOW CRAZY
I AM.
THIS IS A PINEAPPLE.
>> NO, MA.
IT'S THE RIB, JUST LIKE THE ONE
HE'S EATING.
DIG IN.
>> OKAY.
I FEEL LIKE, MAYBE, YOU'RE
TRYING TO DRIVE ME MAD.
>> NO ONE IS TRYING TO DRIVE YOU
MAD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
SWEAR ON THIS BIBLE?
>> OKAY.
OKAY, YEAH.
IT SAYS "HOW TO GASLIGHT YOUR
WIFE" BY GREGORY.
>> PAULA, STOP.
I LOVE YOU!
>> I DON'T FEEL LOVE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KISS ME ANYMORE.
>> THEN KISS YOU I SHALL.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
I'M PRETTY
SURE YOU JUST KISSED HER, THE
18-YEAR-OLD.
>> NO, I KISSED YOU!
WATCH NOW.
I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
>> NO.
NO.
I WON'T LET
YOU GASLIGHT ME YET ANY LONGER.
IN FACT, MAYBE I'LL GASLIGHT
YOU.
THAT'S NOT A TIE YOU'RE WEARING.
THAT'S A SNAKE.
>> IT'S A TIE.
GROW UP.
>> DAMMIT.
I GUESS I'M BAD AT IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU TOLD ME IT
WAS 9 INCHES AND I SAID, "OH,
LUCKY ME."
>> IT IS.
IS.
IT'S KIND OF, LIKE, WHEN MY
WIFE --
WHAT?
SHE'S ON THE PHONE NOW?
RIGHT NOW?
OH, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
FOR "CINEMA CLASSICS," I HAVE
BEEN REESE DE'WHAT!
>>> A DELUXE SUITE AT THE
RADISSON WITH A CITY VIEW, NOT
PARKING LOT.
KORBEL CHAMPAGNE.
YOU SPOIL ME, TATE.
>> ANYTHING FOR MY BIRTHDAY
GIRL.
AND I DO MEAN ANYTHING.
>> AND THE COMMENTS RETURN.
>> I'M SORRY.
MY WIFE ASKED FOR A THREESOME
WITH A RANDOM GUY ONLINE FOR HER
BIRTHDAY.
SO I THINK I HAVE THE RIGHT TO
MAKE A COMMENT OR TWO.
>> HONEY.
HE'S NOT A RANDOM GUY ONLINE.
HE'S AN EXPERIENCED THIRD.
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE OKAY WITH
THIS.
>> I AM.
I AM.
I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I GUESS I'M JUST NERVOUS.
>> DON'T BE.
HE'S HERE.
OKAY?
NOW, STOP WORRYING AND
CONCENTRATE ON MAKING TONIGHT
BEAUTIFUL.
>> HEY.
I'M GANNON.
I'M HERE TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU.
>> YES, HI.
I'M TRACY.
AND THIS IS MY HUSBAND TATE.
>> HEY THERE, TAINT.
>> MY NAME IS TATE, NOT TAINT.
>> GOOD, I WAS GOING TO SAY
THAT'S A BAD NAME.
SO LOOK, I KNOW IT'S YOUR FIRST
TIME DOING THIS.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT.
MY GOAL IS TO MAKE SURE EVERYONE
HAS A NICE, FULFILLING
EXPERIENCE.
BUT SAFETY FIRST, OKAY?
LET'S SEE IF THIS BED CAN HANDLE
MY MOTION.
IT'S NOT BAD.
NOT BAD.
YEAH,
THIS COULD WORK.
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME GET MY CIALIS HERE.
THREE PILLS OUGHT TO DO IT.
>> THREE?
WOW.
>> BY THE WAY, I FIND A
THREESOME WITH AMARIED COUPLE
WORKS BEST.
WHEN THE WIFE AND I GO ABOUT THE
NIGHT AS IF IT'S JUST US.
AND IT'S ON THE HUSBAND TO
FIGURE OUT WHEN AND HOW TO JOIN
IN.
>> THAT'S SMART.
SO IT'S NOT CHAOS.
FEELING BETTER NOW?
>> NO.
I'M NOT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, EXACTLY?
>> WELL, IT MEANS THAT IF YOUR
WIFE AND I HAVE A GOOD RHYTHM
GOING, DON'T CROWBAR YOURSELF
IN.
YOU KNOW?
REMEMBER, IT'S A THREE-WAY, NOT
A ME-WAY.
>> WOW, YEAH, THAT IS SUCH A
GOOD WAY TO PUT IT.
DID YOU MAKE THAT UP?
>> I DID.
YEAH.
NOW HEADS-UP, TAINT.
THE MORE HEATED I GET THE HARDER
IT WILL BE FOR YOU TO GET IN
THERE.
THIS DOG GETS GREEDY WITH HIS
TREATS.
>> YOU CALLED ME TAINT AGAIN.
IT'S TATE.
AND JUST SO I'M CLEAR, THE GAME
PLAN FOR TONIGHT IS YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE
LOVE TO MY WIFE ALL NIGHT AND
FIGHT ME OFF THE WHOLE TIME?
>> WHAT?
NO.
OKAY.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY, LET'S SEE.
LET'S SAY THAT ME AND YOUR
GORGEOUS WIFE ARE ON THE BED
HERE, RIGHT?
WE'RE DOING OUR THING, RIGHT?
THIS PILLOW IS YOUR WIFE, BY THE
WAY.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> ALL RIGHTMENT TRY TO JOIN IN.
>> TRY TO JOIN IN?
ALL RIGHT.
>> GET OUT OF HERE!
>> DUDE!
YOU'RE GOING TO HIT ME WITH MY
OWN WIFE?
>> YEAH, IF I HAVE TO, YEAH.
LOOK BUD, YOU WANT TO SAVE THE
SHIRE,
YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH MORDOR
FIRST.
>> YES, THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO
SEE TONIGHT, MY MAN FIGHTING FOR
ME.
GOD,
I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
>> NOW, I MENTIONED IN MY E-MAIL
I'M A SWEATER.
>> YES.
WE HAVE EVERYTHING YOU ASKED
FOR.
11 FULL SIZE BATH TOWELS AND A
TARP TO PUT OVER THE BED.
>> YES.
THE TARP IS OPTIONAL.
BUT, AGAIN, YOU WILL NOT BELIEVE
HOW MUCH I SWEAT.
OKAY.
SPEAKING OF, TAINT, DURING SOME
OF YOUR DOWN TIME, I MIGHT CALL
FOR A TOWEL.
GO AHEAD AND CALL FOR A FRESHY.
>> LOOK, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
HAVE A LOT TO DO SO I FIGURED
YOU'D WANT TO BE COMFORTABLE.
OKAY.
LAST THING, TAINT, THROW THIS
MASK ON.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> I DON'T LIKE SEEING A DUDE'S
FACE WHEN I'M DOING MY THING.
NOW IT'S LIKE YOU'RE NOT EVEN
HERE.
>> OH, YES.
I LOVE THAT.
SO SHOULD WE START?
>> HELL YEAH.
>> OKAY, I'M JUST GOING TO --
POP INTO THE BATHROOM AND WORK
THROUGH A MINOR CIALIS HEART
ATTACK REAL QUICK.
>> SO MAYBE MY WIFE AND I WILL
GET STARTED WHILE YOU'RE GONE?
>> DON'T YOU DARE!
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MANESKIN!
BEGGING
* PUT YOUR LOVING HAND OUT BABY
'CAUSE I'M BEGGIN'
I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN' *
I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN' *
* RIDIN' HIGH
WHEN I WAS KING
I PLAYED IT HARD AND FAST
'CAUSE I HAD EVERYTHING *
* I WALKED AWAY
WONDERIN' THEN
BUT EASY COME AND EASY
GO AND IT WOULD END SO *
* ANY TIME I NEED YOU
LET ME GO YA
ANY TIME I FEED YOU
GET ME LOW *
* ANY TIME I SEE YOU
LET ME KNOW
BUT I PLANTED THAT SEED
JUST LET ME GROW *
* I'M ON MY KNEES
WHILE I'M BEGGIN'
'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA
LOSE YOU *
'CAUSE I'M BEGGIN'
BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING *
* HAND OUT BABY
I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
TO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN' *
* I NEED YOU TO UNDERSTAND
TRIED SO HARD
TO BE YOUR MAN
THE KIND OF MAN *
AN EMPTY SHELL *
* I USED TO BE
THE SHADOW OF MY
LIFE WAS HANGIN' OVER ME
A BROKEN MAN *
* BUT I DON'T KNOW
WON'T EVEN STAND
THE DEVIL'S DANCE
TO WIN MY SOUL *
* WHAT WE DOIN'
WHAT WE CHASIN'
WHAT ABOUT 'EM
WHY DA BASEMENT *
* WHY WE GOT GOOD SHIT
DON'T EMBRACE IT
WHY THE FEEL FOR
DA NEED TO REPLACE ME *
* YA' ON A RUNWAY TRACK
FROM THE GOOD
I WANNA PAINT IN
THE PICTURES ANY *
* WAY WE COULD REACT
LIKE THE HEART IN A
TRASH WHERE YOU SHOULD
YOU DONE GAVE IT AWAY *
* YA' HAD IT TILL
YOU TOOK IT BACK
BUT I KEEP WALKIN ON
KEEP ROCKIN' DAWNS *
* KEEP WALKING FORWARD
NOW THE COURT IS YOURS
KEEP BROWSIN' HALLS
'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA *
* LIVE IN A BROKEN HOME
GIRL I'M BEGGIN'
I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING *
* HAND OUT BABY
I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN' *
* I'M FIGHTIN' HARD
TO HOLD MY OWN
JUST CAN'T MAKE
IT ALL ALONE *
* I'M HOLDIN' ON
I CAN'T FALL BACK
I'M JUST A CON ABOUT
TO FADE TO BLACK *
* I'M BEGGIN' BEGGIN' YOU
PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT BABY
I'M BEGGIN' *
* BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN'
I'M BEGGIN' *
* BEGGIN' YOU
SO PUT YOUR LOVING
HAND OUT DARLIN' *
OH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
WITH A TWO-HOUR PRESS
CONFERENCE.
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW LONG IT TOOK
TO LIST EVERYTHING THAT'S GONE
WRONG.
IT WAS ACTUALLY THE LONGEST
PRESIDENTIAL PRESS CONFERENCE IN
HISTORY.
BUT AS I HAVE BEEN TOLD MANY
TIMES BEFORE, JUST BECAUSE YOU
WENT FOR A LONG TIME DOESN'T
MEAN YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
>>> SENATE REPUBLICANS LINED UP
TO SHAKE KYRSTEN SINEMA'S HAND
AFTER SHE VOTED AGAINST CHANGING
THE FILIBUSTER TO PASS VOTING
RIGHTS.
AH, THE U.S. SENATE, KEEPING
BLACK FOLKS DOWN WITH A QUIET
HANDSHAKE SINCE 1787.
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS SUGGESTED
PRIMARY CHALLENGERS WHO RUN
REPLACING
JOE MANCHIN AND KYRSTEN SINEMA.
DAMN, BERNIE, STABBING YOUR OWN
CO-WORKERS IN THE BACK IS JUST
UNFORGIVABLE.
I MEAN, I WOULD NEVER SUGGEST
COLIN GET FIRED NO MATTER HOW
AMAZING I THINK BOWEN WOULD BE.
>>> SEVERAL TRUMP WHITE HOUSE
STAFF MEMBERS TOLD THE JANUARY
6th COMMITTEE THAT IF TRUMP MADE
AN UNSCRIPTED STATEMENT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE ATTACK, HE WOULD
HAVE MADE THE SITUATION WORSE.
AND I THINK THAT'S A PRETTY
SOUND ARGUMENT.
NO ONE HAS EVER BEEN LIKE, "YOU
KNOW WHO WOULD BE PERFECT TO
DE-ESCALATE THIS SITUATION?
DONALD TRUMP."
IF HE WAS TRYING TO TALK SOMEONE
OFF A LEDGE HE'D BE LIKE, "DON'T
JUMP.
EVEN THOUGH YOUR WIFE LEFT YOU
LIKE A DOG.
AND THIS WOULD BE THE PERFECT
WAY TO GET BACK AT HER.
>>> ON THE FIRST DAY IN OFFICE,
VIRGINIA GOVERNOR GLENN YOUNGKIN
SIGNED AN EXECUTIVE ORDER
BANNING THE TEACHING THE
CRITICAL RACE THEORY, WHICH
REALLY ISN'T THAT SURPRISING
COMING FROM A GUY WHO DRESSES
LIKE LEO IN "DJANGO UNCHAINED."
>>> THIS WEEK, BRITAIN'S MOST
ELIGIBLE BACHELOR, PRINCE
ANDREW, OFFICIALLY DELETED HIS
TWITTER ACCOUNT AFTER HE
REALIZED THAT'S NOT THE APP WITH
ALL THE DANCING TEENAGERS.
THAT IT WILL NOT BE SENDING ANY
CORRESPONDENTS TO THE UPCOMING
OLYMPIC GAMES IN BEIJING.
HERE TO COMMENT IS CHINESE TRADE
MINISTER AND GAMES ORGANIZER
CHEN BIAO!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS
BUT THANKS FOR JOINING US.
HOW IS BEIJING FEELING ABOUT THE
OLYMPICS?
>> OH, WE ARE PUMPED.
EVERYONE LOVES THE WINTER
OLYMPICS!
SLIDING DOWN SNOW, SLIDING DOWN
ICE.
GRAVITY'S GOT A POINT AND SHE IS
THE MOMENT.
>> SO
HOW DOES CHINA FEEL ABOUT NBC
NOT SENDING CORRESPONDENTS?
>> OH, WE'RE FINE.
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
NBC IS ANNOUNCING THE
GAMES FROM YOUR STUDIOS IN
CONNECTICUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE SHOOTS IN
CONNECTICUT?
MAURY.
COMMENTATING OVER CRIES OF "YOU
ARE NOT THE FATHER!"
AND HOW WILL YOU DESCRIBE THE
ATMOSPHERE IN THE STADIUM?
LIKE
"UH, THE VIBE IS 2:00 A.M. IN
STAMFORD."
I MEAN, HAVE FUN WALKING HOME
FROM METRO NORTH AT THAT HOUR,
GRAYSON.
>> WHO IS GRAYSON?
>> PROBABLY SOME COKED-OUT
FINANCE GUY TRYING TO FIND HIS
ESCORT IN A WENDY'S PARKING LOT.
>> HEY, WAIT.
JOURNALISTS THAT ARE IN BEIJING
SAY THE CITY IS COMPLETELY
LOCKED DOWN.
>> IT'S JUST FOR COVID SAFETY.
IT'S NOT EVEN THAT RESTRICTED.
IT'S PLANE, COVID TEST, ANOTHER
TEST, ANOTHER TEST, SPEED
SKATING, ANAL SWABS.
>> ANAL SWABS?
>> YEAH.
IT'S ACCURATE.
AND FUN.
>> OKAY, BUT LOTS OF JOURNALISTS
ARE BRINGING BURNER PHONES TO
AVOID BEING TRACKED.
>> BURNER PHONES?
WHAT IS THIS, "THE WIRE"?
MUST BE SEASON TWO BECAUSE
YOU'RE WHITE AND NO ONE CARES.
>> WELL THE BIGGER STORY IS THAT
SEVERAL COUNTRIES, INCLUDING THE
U.S., ARE PLANNING DIPLOMATIC
BOYCOTTS OVER CHINA'S HUMAN
RIGHTS VIOLATIONS.
>> HUMAN RIGHTS?
WE DON'T HAVE THAT.
WHAT, IS THIS THE FACE OF A
COUNTRY THAT WOULD VIOLATE HUMAN
RIGHTS?
THE OFFICIAL GAMES MASCOT BING
DWEN DWEN?
AS YOU CAN SEE, HE'S A PANDA
GOING TO A RACE.
I DON'T KNOW, I DESIGNED HIM
WHILE I WAS ON KETAMINE.
HE'S GONNA TRY AND HOOK UP WITH
SHAUN WHITE!
>> GREAT.
SO WHAT DO YOU
HAVE PLANNED FOR THE OPENING
CEREMONIES?
>> OKAY, WELL, PRESS RELEASE --
I'M PERFORMING IN IT!
YEAH, THE VIBE IS GOING TO BE
LIKE BEACHELLA MEETS
WONG KAR-WAI MEETS
DAVE CHAPPELLE STANDUP SPECIAL.
>> HOW IS IT GOING TO BE LIKE A
DAVE
CHAPPELLE SPECIAL?
>> THERE'S GOING TO BE A LOT OF
PEOPLE PROTESTING AFTERWARDS.
>> LOOK, IT FEELS LIKE YOU'RE
REALLY MAKING LIGHT OF SOME
SERIOUS ISSUES.
>> OKAY, FINE, YOU WANT ME TO
GET REAL?
LOOK, WE'RE HOSTING THE WINTER
OLYMPICS BECAUSE NO ONE ELSE
STEPPED UP.
IT'S OUR PARTY AND WE'LL SPY IF
WE WANT TO.
THE IOC CHOSE CHINA.
YOU ALL KNEW WHAT YOU WERE
GETTING INTO.
SO NOW WE'RE IN BED AND YOU HAVE
POST-NUT CLARITY?
WHATEVER.
FLOP.
IF YOU NEED ME, I'LL BE SKIING
THE SLOPES IN MY GAGA "HOUSE OF
GUCCI" SKI GOGGLES!
FATHER, SON, HOUSE OF DADDY.
>> CHEN BIAO, EVERYBODY!
>> TARA LIPINSKI!
>>> M&M'S ANNOUNCED THAT THEY'VE
REDESIGNED THEIR ICONIC M&M
CHARACTERS AFTER PEOPLE
REQUESTED THAT THE BROWN M&M NOT
LOOK LIKE A TEACHER WHO HAS SEX
WITH HER STUDENTS.
>>> IN A NEW DOCUMENTARY, AN
EX-GIRLFRIEND OF PRINCE ANDREW
DESCRIBES JEFFREY EPSTEIN AND
GHISLAINE MAXWELL AS BATMAN AND
ROBIN.
COME ON.
WHAT DOES BATMAN AND ROBIN HAVE
IN COMMON WITH A BILLIONAIRE
THAT GROOMS TEENAGERS?
>>> GEN-Z ICON KYLE RITTENHOUSE
IS PETITIONING THE COURT FOR THE
RETURN OF HIS RIFLE SO HE CAN
DESTROY IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
CAREFUL, KYLE.
TRYING TO GET YOUR OWN
MEMORABILIA BACK IS HOW THEY
GOT O.J.
>>> IN A NEW INTERVIEW, BONO
REVEALS THAT HE NEVER LIKED THE
NAME U2, ADDING, "I ALSO KIND OF
HATE IRELAND."
>>> ACTOR JON VOIGT RELEASED A
VIDEO CLAIMING THAT
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S SPIRIT WAS
GUIDING DONALD TRUMP.
HOPEFULLY NOT TO A THEATER.
>>> A LONGTIME DIRECTOR OF
WHEEL OF FORTUNE HAS DIED AT
THE AGE OF 92.
SAID "WHEEL OF FORTUNE" VIEWERS,
WOW, SO YOUNG.
IT'S COLD HERE AT 30 ROCK.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT STAYING COZY
IN THE WINTER WEATHER IS OUR
VERY OWN SARAH SHERMAN.
SO YOU'RE HERE TO TALK ABOUT THE
WINTER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, WINTER ROCKS.
ALL THE BUGS ARE DEAD.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO YOU DON'T MIND
THE COLD AT ALL?
>> COLIN, I'M COZY ALL WINTER
LONG.
I GOT PUBES THICKER THAN
CLOTHES.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK ABOUT
YOUR PUBES, SARAH.
>> OH, I'M SORRY, DOES THE BUSH
STUFF MAKE YOU UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> OKAY.
I'M SO SORRY.
THIS JUST IN!
LOCAL FEMALE BODY INSPECTOR
COLIN JOST, WISHES A FEMALE
CO-WORKER HAD HAIRLESS GENITALS
LIKE A BLOWUP DOLL.
BACK TO YOU, COLIN.
>> SARAH.
THAT'S NOT -- I DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOUR BODY HAIR.
>> WOW, COLIN.
CAREFUL HOW YOU TALK ABOUT MY
BODY, COLIN, I'M BASICALLY YOUR
SON'S AGE.
>> YOU'RE SIX MONTHS OLD?
>> OH, YOU WISH, SICKO.
YOU'D KILL TO CHANGE MY DIAPER,
WOULDN'T YOU?
>> SARAH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> WELL, YOU THINK THAT'S
DISGUSTING?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S DISGUSTING?
THE HOST OF HOUSING IN NEW YORK,
COLIN.
YEAH.
CAN YOU BELIEVE --
CAN YOU BELIEVE I HAVE TO PAY
$200 A MONTH TO LIVE IN
MANHATTAN?
>> YOU PAY $200?
WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> WOW!
BREAKING NEWS!
CAMDEN HOMEOWNER COLIN JOST
MOCKS STRUGGLING COMEDIAN FOR
FINDING A DEAL BY LIVING IN HIS
DOG HOUSE.
>> YOU LIVE IN A DOGHOUSE?
>> SARAH, WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM
ME?
>> $6,000.
>> I'M NOT GIVING YOU SIX GRAND.
>> YOUR FUNERAL.
IN OTHER NEWS, WEALTH-HOARDING
HOLLYWOOD HUSBAND, COLIN JOST.
HAS NOT A DIME TO SPARE FOR
SNL'S
UNDERPAID ROOKIE EVEN THOUGH SHE
WAS GOING TO DONATE THAT MONEY
TO ST. JUDE'S CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL.
>> YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT.
AND ANOTHER THING!
CAN WE TALK ABOUT YOU AND CHE?
IT'S ALWAYS, WILL THEY, WON'T
THEY WITH YOU TWO.
ALL RIGHT?
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GET IT OVER
WITH AND MAKE OUT ALREADY?
>> NO.
I'M NOT.
I'M NOT KISSING CHE.
>> WRONG ANSWER!
THIS JUST IN!
LOCAL SEX BIGOT, COLIN JOST,
VIOLENTLY REJECTS RADICAL ACT OF
QUEER INTERRACIAL LOVE.
>> YOU'RE SO SMALL-MINDED,
COLIN.
>> ALL RIGHT, FINE, YOU WANT TO
KISS?
LET'S DO IT.
OKAY?
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HEY.
>> BREAKING NEWS!
QUEER BAITING "UPDATE" ANCHOR
COLIN JOST PRETENDS TO BE GAY
FOR LAUGHS.
>> MAN, COLIN.
YOU ARE THE WORST.
>> SARAH SHERMAN, EVERYONE.
>>> OFFICIALS IN HONG KONG
ANNOUNCED THAT AFTER SOME
HAMSTERS IN A PET STORE TESTED
POSITIVE FOR COVID, THEY HAD TO
KILL MORE THAN 2,000 OF THE
PETS.
OKAY, BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO DO
IT IN FRONT OF THE CLASS.
>>> A MAN IN CANADA STOLE AN
$8,000 GUITAR BY HIDING IT IN
HIS PANTS.
POLICE CAUGHT THE MAN WHEN HE
GOT AN ERECTION AND IT SOUNDED
LIKE THIS.
**
>>> SCIENTISTS HAVE TRAINED A
GOLDFISH TO DRIVE A CAR.
THEY BELIEVE IT'S THE FIRST STEP
TO EVENTUALLY TRAINING WOMEN.
DURING A RECENT INTERVIEW WAS A
REPLICA AND NOT THE REAL THING.
JOHNSON ALSO SAID IT'S JUST A
COINCIDENCE THAT HIS DIET CALLS
FOR 1,000 POUNDS OF DINOSAUR
MEAT A DAY.
>>> THE OLDEST LIVING PERSON IN
THE UNITED STATES DIED THIS WEEK
AT THE AGE OF 115.
IT'S A POWERFUL REMINDER TO
ALWAYS TEST YOUR COCAINE FOR
FENTANYL.
>>> THE NFL PLAYOFFS CONTINUE
THIS WEEKEND.
HERE WITH HIS TAILGATING TIPS IS
A GUY WHO JUST BOUGHT A BOAT.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR SOME
THESE BALLS!
IT'S GOOD TO BEACH HERE.
>> I REALLY HATED THAT OPENING.
>> HEY, COLIN.
HAVEN'T YOU SINCE
THAT PARTY WE HAD TO GET COVID
ON PURPOSE.
GREAT IDEA BY THE WAY.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> YEAH.
IT'S TRUE, MY BRO-BRO FROM A
NO-HO HERE TOLD ME THE SAME
THING SO MANY WOMEN HAVE --
LET'S JUST GET THIS OVER WITH.
>> NO.
THAT DIDN'T -- THAT DID NOT
HAPPEN, NO.
>> OH, BUT IT DID.
IT'S FOOTBALL SLEAZE-ON.
IF YOU WANT TO NAIL YOUR DATE
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAIL
SOME GATE, MKAY?
IF YOU WANT A TOUCH DOWN THERE,
HERE ARE SOME JUST THE TIPS TO
TURN HER TIGHT END -- OH HELL.
LET ME TAKE THAT AGAIN.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO.
>> OH, WHATEVER.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST A TIP TO TURN HER TIGHT END
INTO A WIDE RECEIVER.
WE GOT THERE.
>> WE GOT THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MAKE YOUR STARTING LINEUP SOME
BEAUTIFUL CANS.
I'M TALKING BREWSKIS FOR THE
MAIN SQUEEZE.
GIVE HER SOME DUB CLAWS, SOME
MICKI ULCHIES, AND YEUNGLINGS TO
GET HER TINGLING.
AND PRETTY SOON YOU'LL BE LIKE A
RUNNING BACK POUNDING IT UP THE
MIDDLE.
I HAVE A SMALL PENIS.
>> I'M SORRY, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I HAVE A SMALL PENIS.
WHAT.
ARE YOU NEW HERE?
WAIT, ARE YOU SURE THERE'S
NOTHING DIFF GOING ON IN HERE?
I'M GETTING SOME SORT OF
MESSAGE, A FLIPPER FROM ANOTHER
SKIPPER, MY HINEY SENSE IS
TINGLING.
OH.
SOMEONE BOUGHT A BOAT!
>> NO, I DON'T KNOW --
>> HEY!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
>> I'M GETTING WORD IN MY SIDE
PIECE, BREAKING NEWS.
MY BOY COY JOY AND HIS "SNL" BOY
TOY ARE SAYING AHOY-HOY TO AN
AQUATIC TOY-TOY.
THAT'S RIGHT, COLIN AND PETE
BOUGHT A FERRY BOAT, EVERYBODY!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, FINE.
HERE SO TALK ABOUT IT
IS A GUY WHO JUST BOUGHT A
FERRY.
>> HI, EVERYBODY, I'M PETE.
THE WINDOWLESS VAN OF THE SEA.
>> YES, IT'S VERY EXCITING.
WE THOUGHT THE WHOLE THING
THROUGH.
>> I KNOW.
EVEN THE MAYOR TWEETED ABOUT US
BUYING IT, WHICH IS HOW I FOUND
OUT WE HAVE A NEW MAYOR.
WHAT HAPPENED TO BLOOMBERG?
>> WELL, WE KNOW -- WE ACTUALLY
DID A SKETCH ABOUT THE NEW MAYOR
LAST WEEK.
>> OH, I'M GONE AS SOON AS MY
LAST SKETCH IS OVER.
>> SO WAIT, YOU GUYS -- YOU GUYS
BOUGHT IT TOGETHER?
YOU'RE PULLING A DOUBLE TEAMER
ON THIS STEAMER?
ME LIKY.
WAY TO GET YOUR DECKS WET.
CLASSIC BOAT OWNER BEHAVE.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, THERE IS A
THIRD PARTNER.
>> OH, I'M LISTENING.
>> WE BOUGHT THE FERRY WITH THIS
GUY, PAULEY ITALIA, OKAY?
WHICH THE NAME OF A REAL PERSON,
AND NOT A MAFIA-THEMED WRESTLER.
WE'RE BOAT PEOPLE NOW, COLIN.
I MEAN, YOU ALWAYS WERE.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU HAVE THE YACHT
THAT THEY RENT OUT FOR RAP
VIDEOS, YES?
>> WE ARE HAVING TROUBLE FINDING
A PLACE TO DOCK THE BOAT,
THOUGH.
>> FELLAS, THAT HAPPENS TO ME
ALL THE TIME.
JUST START POKING AROUND
DOWNTOWN.
IT WILL EVENTUALLY SLIP IN
SOMEWHERE.
MY THINGY IS A DINGHY.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, OUR BOAT IS
300 FEET LONG.
>> EW.
LOOK,
IT'S THE WIDTH THAT COUNTS.
MINE'S LIKE A TUNA CAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALSO, WE KEEP -- WE JUST KEEP --
WE'RE GOING
TO JUST KEEP THE BOAT DOCKED.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T HAVE TO
MOVE UNDER ITS OWN POWER.
>> YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND, COLIN.
>> OKAY, SO IT JUST LAYS THERE
TIGHT?
THAT'S JUST LIKE ME, THERE'S NO
MOTION IN THIS OCEAN.
WHEN YOUR POOTER IS ON THIS
SCHOONER, ALL ABOARD!
THERE'S NO SHAME IN PAYING FOR A
TUG, FELLOWS.
COLIN KNOWS WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
GIVE IT HERE.
>> OH, IT'S LIKE WITH YOUR
PENIS?
>> NO, FOR YOUR BOAT.
>> THREE GUYS WHO JUST BOUGHT  A
BOAT
TWO OF THE GREATEST SONG SMITHS
IN THE HISTORY OF TIME ARE BACK
AND AT IT AGAIN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
** THROUGH HIM IN THE POOL
** AND THAT'S HOW HE LEARNED TO
SWIM
** FLEW DOWN AND LOANED US A
TOWEL
** AS A SHOW OF OUR GRATITUDE
** I GUESS THE ALIENS TRIED FOOD
** AND THE CAR BELONGED TO MY
STEPBROTHER'S LIFE COACH.
>> AND --
** KEY CARD TO THE NEAREST BAR
** THE SALAD BAR WAS CLOSED
BECAUSE A SHAPE SHIP EXPLODED
** SO A DRANK A CASE OF BEER
WITH A TODDLER.
>> FOR YEARS NOW, THESE TWO
THRILLED GLOBAL AUDIENCES WITH
SONGS ABOUT THE FOUR THINGS THEY
KNOW BEST: SPACESHIPS, TODDLERS,
MONSTER CARS AND JARS OF BEER.
AND AFTER A 12-YEAR SABBATICAL,
THESE TWO NATIONAL TREASURES
HAVE DECIDED TO ONCE AGAIN JOIN
FORCES.
I'M SORRY.
FOIN JORCES.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I WAS RIGHT THE FIRST TIME.
THEY RELEASED A NEW ALBUM.
SONGS ABOUT SPACESHIPS,
TODDLERS, MODEL T CARS AND CARS
OF BEER WITH EAR CAVIAR LIKE
THIS.
** OH, TODDLER DID YOU HEAR WHAT
I WHISPERED IN YOUR EAR ABOUT
THE SPACESHIP THAT WAS PARKED IN
YOUR YARD
** WITH A TURKEY AND A TOLD
** AND A FACE FULL OF REGRET
** BUT THEN A TRUCK PASSED BY
** AND NOW THE TURKEY IS BED AND
THE TOLD'S ON LIFE-SUPPORT.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> JUST GIVES YOU THE SHIVERS,
DOESN'T IT?
AN IMPORTANT MESSAGE.
SO IMPORTANTLY, YOU WANT LESS?
SORRY.
BECAUSE WHILE THERE IS MORE THAN
ONE WAY TO SKIN A CAT, THERE IS
ONLY ONE WAY TO PUT THAT SKIN
BACK ON, WITH BEAUTIFUL MUSIC
LIKE THIS LITTLE SLOW JELLY.
** THE EYES OF GOD ARE CRYING
**
** THE TODDLERS HAVE BEEN LYING
** OH, YES, THOSE LITTLE SONS OF
GUNS
** WHO TRUSTED THEM TO GUARD THE
MODEL T CARS.
** AND NOW THEY'LL MEET THE
WRATH OF GOD AND BURN IN TODDLER
HELL
** UNLESS THEY CALL YOUR FRIENDS
THE ALIENS TO SEND A SPACESHIP
DOWN
** BUT GOD WILL FIND THEM THERE
** HE'S EVERYWHERE
** HE'LL WELL CONNECTED
** AND A LIGHTENING BOLT AND
BURN THEM TO A CRISP AND DRINK A
JAR OF BEER TO CELEBRATE THE
DEATH FOR LITTLE NAUGHTY
TODDLERS WHO DISRESPECT NUNS
** FOR THEY WILL FIND THEMSELVES
** IN TODDLER HELL!
**
** TODDLER HELL
** TODDLER HELL!
>> THAT SONG GAVE ME ALL THE
FEELS.
MINUS A FEW FEELS, PLUS MORE
FEELS AND A FEW FEELS THAT WERE
SUBTRACTED.
AND IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH
EARGASM ALREADY, CHECK OUT THIS
REMARKING OF ONE OF THEIR
CLASSICS TO BE THE NEW OFFICIAL
SONG OF THE NATIONAL FOOTBALL
LEAGUE.
**
** AND YOUR FIELD IS STUCK FROM
THE SPACESHIP BELOW
** AND ONE DAY A TODDLER WILL
DISTRACT YOU
** AND THE MODEL T CAR WILL
DODGE A HAIL MARY AND WIN THE
SUPER BOWL
**
>>> ONCE AGAIN, MANESKIN!
SLAVE
* I WANNA BE YOUR SLAVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MASTER
I WANNA MAKE
YOUR HEART BEAT *
* RUN LIKE ROLLERCOASTERS
I WANNA BE A GOOD BOY
I WANNA BE A GANGSTER
'CAUSE YOU CAN *
* BE THE BEAUTY
AND I COULD BE THE MONSTER
I LOVE YOU SINCE
THIS MORNING *
* NOT JUST FOR AESTHETIC
I WANNA TOUCH YOUR BODY
SO FREAKIN' ELECTRIC
I KNOW YOU SCARED OF ME *
* YOU SAID THAT
I'M TOO ECCENTRIC
I'M CRYING ALL MY TEARS
AND THAT'S *
* FREAKIN' PATHETIC
I WANNA MAKE YOU HUNGRY
THEN I WANNA FEED YA
I WANNA PAINT YOUR FACE *
* LIKE YOU'RE MY MONA LISA
I WANNA BE A CHAMPION
I WANNA BE A LOSER
I'LL EVEN BE A CLOWN *
* CAUSE I JUST
WANNA AMUSE YA
I WANNA BE YOUR SEX TOY
I WANNA BE YOUR TEACHER *
* I WANNA BE YOUR SIN
I WANNA BE A PREACHER
I WANNA MAKE YOU LOVE ME
THEN I WANNA LEAVE YA *
* 'CAUSE BABY I'M YOUR DAVID
AND YOU'RE MY GOLIATH
AH-HA
MHM AH-HA *
* BECAUSE I'M THE DEVIL
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
AND I'M A LAWYER *
* WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
AND I'M A KILLER
WHO'S SEARCHING *
* FOR REDEMPTION
I'M A MOTHER -- MONSTER
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION *
* AND I'M A BAD GUY
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
AND I'M A BLOND GIRL *
* WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
I'M A FREAK THAT
IS SEARCHING *
* FOR REDEMPTION
I'M A MOTHER -- MONSTER
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION *
**
* I WANNA BE YOUR SLAVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MASTER
I WANNA MAKE
YOUR HEART BEAT *
* RUN LIKE ROLLERCOASTERS
I WANNA BE A GOOD BOY
I WANNA BE A GANGSTER
CAUSE YOU CAN *
* BE THE BEAUTY
AND I COULD
BE THE MONSTER
I WANNA MAKE YOU QUIET *
* I WANNA MAKE YOU NERVOUS
I WANNA SET YOU FREE
BUT I'M TOO
FREAKIN' JEALOUS *
* I WANNA PULL YOUR STRINGS
LIKE YOU'RE MY TELECASTER
AND IF YOU WANT TO USE ME
I COULD BE YOUR PUPPET *
* 'CAUSE I'M THE DEVIL
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
AND I'M A LAWYER *
* WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION
AND I'M A KILLER
WHO'S SEARCHING *
* FOR REDEMPTION
I'M A MOTHER -- MONSTER
WHO'S SEARCHING
FOR REDEMPTION *
**
* I WANNA BE YOUR SLAVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MASTER *
HE KIND OF SPIRALED OUT *
* DOWN AN INTERNET
RABBIT HOLE *
HE LOST SOME FRIENDS *
* AND FAMILY AND THEY
STAGED AN INTERVENTION *
HE'S GOT IT *
* BACK TOGETHER NOW
MacGRUBER.
RESEARCH
CONTROL ROOM
TRAPPED
>> AND A HYDROGEN BOMB IS SET TO
BLOW IN 30 SECONDS!
>> SO WHERE WAS I?
OH, YES.
HOLLYWOOD CELEBRITIES ARE EATING
BABIES.
THEY DEVOUR THEM.
THEY'RE INSATIABLE.
LIKE THE WAY HORSE WORMS EAT
SPAGHETTI.
RAW BABIES, COOKED BABIES.
I'M SURE THEY HAVE A VARIETY OF
RECIPES.
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING OUT
THERE AND NOBODY IS DOING
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
>> CAN WE CONCENTRATE ON THE
BOMB?
>> OH, THAT'S NOT A BIG ENOUGH
BOMB FOR YOU TO FIND OUT THAT
ELLEN POMPEO EATS BABIES?
>> I KNEW IT.
>> YOU'RE SO BRAINWASHED.
>> I'M SORRY, IN WHAT WAY?
>> JUST LOOK AT HOW YOU'RE
DRESSED.
>> FORGIVE ME FOR NOT SHOPPING
AT CHEAPS-R-US LIKE YOU.
I'M JUST YOUR AVERAGE AMERICAN
WHO BELIEVES IN LIMITED GOVERNMENT,
MY BODY, MY
CHOICE -- FOR MEN --
AND
SUPPRESSED VOTING RIGHTS FOR
ALTERNATIVELY SKINNED PEOPLE.
I'M NOT SURE HOW THAT MAKES ME
BRAINWASHED.
>> MacGRUBER, FOCUS.
PLEASE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, OKAY.
VICKY, HAND ME ALL THE REMAINS
OF AMERICA'S SOUL.
>> WHAT?
THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
WELCOME TO THE REAL WORLD.
LOOK, I'M JUST A SHAMAN.
>> ALL I CAN DO IS PRAY FOR YOU,
TAKE UP ARMS AGAINST YOU, AND
KEEP THE OATH I TOOK TO PROTECT
THIS COUNTRY.
BECAUSE I AM AN OATH KEEPER AND
BOY AM I PROUD OF THAT.
WHICH I GUESS MAKES ME A PROUD
BOY.
>> DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING RIGHT NOW?
>> PROBABLY NOT.
>> MacGRUBER, IF WE DON'T DEAL
WITH THIS BOMB, WE ARE GOING TO
EXPLODE.
>> 5 SECONDS.
>> ACCORDING TO CNN.
>> 4 SECONDS.
>> CANCEL CULTURE.
>> 3 SECONDS.
>> NOT MY CLOCK.
>> 2 SECONDS.
>> HOLLYWOOD ELITE.
>> 1 SECOND.
>> THOUGH I DO KIND OF LIKE SOME
STREAMERS ON PEACOCK.
* MacGRUBER **
THANKS TO
KRISTEN WIIG, WILLEM DAFOE.
LORNE MICHAELS.
THIS AMAZING CREW UP HERE.
THEY HAVE BEEN LIKE A FAMILY TO
ME.
AND MY FAMILY, TOO.
THANK YOU TO ALL OF YOU FOR
BEING HERE.