Last
Iran
Further
-Hello. Hi.
Good evening
and happy World War III
to all who celebrate.
It's me, Donald Trump.
FIFA Peace Prize winner
and Nobel Peace Prize taker.
Yoink!
Remember when I did that?
I launched this attack after me
and my Board of Peace
decided that we were
bored of peace.
Little wordplay there.
Did you catch it?
As we all know,
Iran has been two weeks away
from developing
a nuclear weapon
for like
the last 15 years or something,
so we had to act now.
And we're doing war.
War!
♪ What is it good for? ♪
♪ Distracting
from the Epstein files ♪
And I know on the campaign trail
I promised no new foreign wars.
But listen, wars --
plural, right?
I'm allowed to do one.
Do one foreign war
and possibly one civil.
To all my MAGA voters
who are upset and saying,
"This is not what I voted for,"
well, you did.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm me.
Even I don't know what
I'm gonna do next.
Hello from the year 5000.
Like, what the hell was that,
right?
Nobody knows.
I'm unpredictable.
I'm like a box of chocolates --
you never know what
you're gonna get.
Forrest Gump!
Gump!
America's favorite
time-traveling R-word.
He told that story to that nurse
on the bench
after the feather fell down.
Gump!
I don't get it.
People beg and beg for Trump,
and then when you get him,
you don't like him.
What's going on?
All right?
I'm like new "Star Wars" movies.
They see the trailer
for "Mandalorian & Grogu,"
and they say,
"Never mind. I don't want that."
People are asking,
"Why attack Iran now?"
Well, we had to strike
in the early hours of Saturday,
which has two advantages
militarily.
One, it's after the stock market
closes for the weekend,
and, two,
it's to cause immeasurable fear, rage,
and chaos
in the "SNL" writers room.
Those guys were going crazy.
They probably had a big
State of the Union address thing
they were gonna do.
Not anymore!
Jeremy was in it.
Poor Jeremy.
He's got a light show.
Put the whole thing in the trash
and start fresh.
We love that for them.
Anyway, with more on this,
here's a man I'm gonna blame it
on when it doesn't work,
Secretary of War Pete Hegseth.
-Yeah, all right, all right,
cut the track!
Cut the track.
And relax.
This is a Four Loko non-alc!
What's up, dill weeds?
As you probably heard,
Operation Epic Fury is underway.
And as you could tell from the
veins in my neck, I'm pumped!
Why'd we call it Epic Fury?
Simple.
Eight letters.
Lines up perfectly
for some bitchin' knuckle tats!
Yeah!
Did 'em in the wrong order,
but you get it!
And those are my
least problematic tattoos.
Shut up!
They asked for someone
to volunteer
to oversee this
half-baked operation,
and I didn't walk,
"I ran." [Iran]
When President Trump called me
at 2:00 in the morning,
you know I was awake,
sober AF and already training
for the mission,
playing "Prince of Persia:
Sands of Time" on my GameCube.
-We love the GameCube.
It's underrated.
-Yeah! Misunderstood system,
the GameCube.
-And a small library.
It was hard to code for.
-It was hard to code for.
Smart man.
But don't let
my confident demeanor fool you.
I am scared,
and I don't know what I'm doing.
When he said we were gonna
blow up the leader of Iran,
I thought he was kidding.
And now, all day long,
I've been hearing people say,
"Why did we do this?
What's the reason for this war?"
Oh, yeah, I actually have
the reason right here.
It's under my chin.
Let me get it for you.
"Goodfellas."
Bottom line, all of you
should be thanking us.
We took out a horrendous,
horrible leader
who was oppressing
his own people.
-But don't get any ideas.
-And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Connor Storrie!
-Thank you! Thank you,
thank you, thank you very much.
I am so excited to be here.
Yes.
Okay, okay.
Now, some of you may
have seen literally all of me
on my show, "Heated Rivalry."
It's a show that has taught
a lot of people about hockey,
and it's taught a lot
of straight women
that their sexuality
is actually gay guy.
If you haven't seen it,
it's a little spicy,
but it's actually
a lot more than that.
"SNL" said I could show a clip,
so I found one that was good
for the whole family.
Okay.
That's it. That's it.
That is literally all
we could show from the show.
But this show
has totally changed my life. Okay?
Um, right before I got
cast, I was a waiter, and --
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
And, uh, I've only --
so I've only technically
been a professional actor
for like six months now.
But on the other hand,
I've been preparing for this
my entire life
since I was a 12-year-old
obsessed with acting.
So, it's like --
it's like, on one hand,
I'm totally surprised
and humbled
that this is happening to me,
and on the other hand...
...this was my destiny.
When I was little,
I said to my mother,
"Why do I have to have
the last name 'Storrie'?
The whole world is gonna
know me as just Connor,
like I'm Madonna or Cher
or Paddington."
"Mother, I'm not a story,
I'm a whole damn book."
I am kidding.
Seriously,
I promise I'm nothing like that.
I am much worse.
I'm joking.
I definitely did not have
a glamorous childhood, though.
Um, I grew up in Texas,
and my mom --
Texas!
Um, I grew up in Texas,
and my mom would drive
me hours to auditions.
She even drove me to this weird
mall
where they did this, like,
national kids talent contest.
Which I won hands-down...
...in every category
by doing a catwalk
to "It's Raining Men"
with other children.
But seriously,
I really did not know
if this would ever happen to me.
And, you know,
when I got the call
that I was gonna be on "SNL,"
I honestly cried.
Yeah. You know, I am just --
I really --
I am just so,
so thankful for everything
that this job gives me
the chance to do.
You know, like in two weeks,
I had to learn
how to play Russian
and look like I knew
how to play hockey.
And then I'm watching
the Olympics,
and I see these amazing players,
and I'm like,
"I don't think I pulled it off."
-No way, man.
I hear you're great.
-Whoa.
Quinn and Jack,
you guys literally
just won the Olympics.
Congrats.
-Thanks.
But we've been so busy playing,
we haven't had time
to see your show yet.
-It's about hockey, right?
-Kind of.
-I got my teeth knocked out
in the finals.
Does that happen in your show?
-Metaphorically.
-Cool.
What team do you play on?
-Uh, the Boston Raiders.
-Boston Raiders?
What league is that?
The NHL?
-The HBO.
But you guys
should check it out.
Oh, I hope some hockey
players watched it.
-Don't worry.
We saw your show.
-Oh, wow. Hilary, Megan, it's
so cool that we're all here.
-It was gonna be just us,
but we thought we'd invite
the guys, too.
-Yeah, we thought we'd give
them a little moment to shine.
-Well, that is very important.
You know,
my show speaks to people
who are not always
represented in hockey,
so this is really great
to have actual
hockey legends here tonight.
I mean -- yeah, I mean, both
of your teams just won the gold.
-Thanks. The last time the men
did that was 46 years ago.
-And the last time we did that
was two whole Olympics ago.
-Nice burn. But these gold
medals aren't just for us.
They're for all hockey fans.
Yours, too.
-Oh. So can I try one on?
-No.
-We have a great show
for you tonight.
Mumford & Sons is here.
Stick around.
We'll be right back!
-Go, Ricky! Go, Ricky!
Go, Ricky!
Go, Ricky! Go, Ricky!
-Wait! You guys, stop!
We have a math test today.
Who even cares about math
when you can do this?
- Okay.
Everybody, silence,
and stop it right now, okay?
Mr. Jacob, sit down yesterday.
-I'm sorry, Mr. Jacob
I was just playing.
-Not today, guys.
I am in a bad mood, okay?
-Dang, Mr. Fronzi.
Is everything okay?
-No, Mr. Jacob,
everything is not okay.
This morning, my wife spilled
my coffee all over my body,
and the coffee was everywhere,
and my body was on fire.
and he covered my body
from my feet until my head
in aloe vera.
Okay, guys?
-Wow. Sorry that happened
to you, Mr. Fronzi.
-It's okay, guys.
I just letting you know
that today is not the day
to play with Mr. Fronzi.
Now, please, take a quiz and
passing it to your neighbors.
This is a big quiz, guys.
It count for 65%
of your grade, okay?
That's a lot
of percentage of grade, guys.
So I need-a silence in here.
No jokes, no comments
from the "penis" gallery.
Okay, I'm so sorry.
What is so funny, Mr. Jacob?
-Seriously, dude?
You just said "penis."
-No. No.
"Peanuts." Like the a-snack.
As in, my wife is
deathly allergic to "penis."
For me, I love "penis,"
but my biggest struggle
in my life
is keeping my "penis"
away from my wife.
-Yo, Fronzi,
stop saying "penis"!
-That's it! 10 points
off the quiz for everybody!
-What? No!
-Come on!
No
Focus on the quiz, guys.
Very good, guys.
This is what
I like to be seeing, guys.
Very quiet, very nice.
Wow
And now I will briefly
go to the bathroom
and privately reapply
the aloe vera
everywhere in my body.
I trust you guys to be
my little angels from Jesus.
Okay?
This is a big quiz, guys.
I'm proud of you guys.
-Bro, go do it! Do it!
-Do it, man.
- Okay, you guys.
I am Mr. Fronzi...
-My wife is deadly
allergic to my "penoi."
-Go off, Ricky.
-And the crazy thing is,
I have no idea
that nobody even like me.
-Really, guys?
This is what you think of me,
Mr. Jacob?
-I'm sorry, Mr. Fronzi.
I was just joking around.
-Wow.
This is one of the darkest days
of my life.
I did not think that my heart
could be broken like this.
-Oh, no, Mr. Fronzi,
please don't cry.
-Yo, why does he low-key sound
like the iPhone ringtone?
-Yo, I don't even know
what subject this class is.
-Yo, we're sorry, Mr. Fronzi.
We only make fun of you
because you're like one of us.
Look, I guess what
I'm trying to say is...
-We love you, Mr. Fronzi!
-Mr. Jacob!
You mean it?
Okay, guys,
we love you, Mr. Fronzi.
We love you, Mr. Fronzi.
-Ai, Angie.
Your words are like aloe vera
for my heart.
The quiz is canceled.
Everybody get an A!
-Everybody -- Fronzi!
Fronzi! Fronzi! Fronzi!
-Oh, my God!
I love you guys!
I love you!
-It turns out the poor bastard
had worn his riding boots
to luncheon.
-Oh, the absolute shame!
-Lord Kedley.
-Lady Delacort. A pleasure.
-I quite look forward
to our croquet match
this afternoon
at my father's estate.
-Then you obviously
haven't seen Kedley play.
-Well, I will leave you
gentlemen to your discourse.
Good day.
-Good day.
-I resent that insulting
remark, Lord Farrington.
And I ask, sir, how dare you?
-He asks him how he dares.
-Such an affront, according to
the Gentleman's Code,
permits me to remove my glove
and slap your face.
-How dare you?
I ask twice, sir --
how dare you?
I rebuke you, sir,
and give it to you twice.
-How dare you?
I deny your rebut thricefold!
How dare you?
Ha! Dodge!
-How dare you?!
-How dare you?
How to the absolute dare you?!
-Gentlemen!
You are beginning
to act like commoners.
-How dare you?
How dare you?
I am ungloved
and therefore unable to retort.
Kedley, slap him as my proxy.
-Of course.
-Mnh!
How dare you?
-Very good.
-Gentlemen, stop!
-We can't let this
silliness ruin the afternoon.
Why don't you both
just apologize?
-Apologize?
I have done nothing wrong, sir.
How dare you?
-Don't do it.
-I slapped you because --
-Aah!
-Ohh!
Ah, uh...
Ho' 'are you?!
How dare you?
You struck me
with a closed fist!
And, therefore,
I am allowed to do the same.
How dare you?
-Enough!
You, sir, have disobeyed
the Gentleman's Code.
So I am permitted
to strike you with my cane.
-Don't do it.
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
Please don't hi--
-Gentlemen!
Stop this rabble at once.
There are children present.
Are you okay, sweetie?
-How dare you?
-Oh, my God!
-You strike a woman, boy?
How dare you.
-Nice work.
-This must cease.
Look at this woman's dog.
The commotion has frightened
the poor girl.
Cede defeat, Farrington,
and end our quarrel now.
-Ha ha!
Are you mad?
Lord Pubert Farrington
would never bend his knee
to appease
a frightened little...
bitch.
-How dare you?
-No!
Skee-boop!
-How dare --
Yep, it seems
I've beshatted myself.
Well, I cede defeat.
Well done.
-Glad that's settled.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to retrieve my son,
who I kicked across the park.
-How dare you?
I'm kidding. Good day.
-Good day.
-Wow!
First you take me to dinner
at Le Beef,
and then you take me to the same
ice rink where we first met.
I mean, this is the perfect
first-year anniversary.
-And I haven't even
proposed yet.
-Wait. What?
-Candace Lorraine Dugan,
will you marry me?
-Oh, my God.
Uh, Casper, um...
I'm sorry, I can't.
-W-what?
-I'm having so much fun, Danny!
-I'm so glad, Bryce.
-I can't say yes right now.
-Bryce, Danny,
wait up, fast pokes!
-Uh, why can't you say yes?
-I don't know.
It just doesn't feel right yet.
-You guys, you guys, look --
I'm a plane.
-I mean, do you think
that we're ready?
-Hey! I know you!
-Get back here!
-Please, say something, Casper.
-Those three men
are having the best time.
-What?
-Those guys,
I've never seen grown men having
such, like, genuine, pure fun.
Like, how old are they?
-Um, this train
lost its caboose.
-Yeah, Danny, why'd you let go?
-Because I was laughing
too much.
God, I love being in my 40s.
-They're in their 40s?
-Okay. I'm so glad that's what
you're focused on right now.
-Sorry if I'm a little
scattered, Candace.
You just told me
you didn't love me.
-Stop it!
You know that I love you!
-Eeeeeeeee!
And I know I'm gonna be
with you forever.
-Oh, I feel so free!
I feel like Alysa Liu right now.
-I just don't know
if I'm ready to start
forever right now.
-Ooh-wah! Ooh-wah!
Is that your girlfriend?
Hunh, aah!
-Sorry. What did you say?
-See? See? This is
what I'm talking about.
I'm always fighting
for your attention.
-I'm sorry. I can't
get a read on these guys.
-Best bachelor party ever!
-This is a bachelor party?
-I cannot believe you
right now!
-Candace, come on!
Don't cry.
-Oh, my gosh, you guys,
look who finally showed up.
-Hudson!
Yeah, dude!
Hudson!
-Hudson.
-Dude, so stoked.
-Hudson! Yeah!
-Oh! Sorry.
-Oh.
So glad you're here, Hudson.
-I know.
It's pretty great. Hey.
Sorry I'm late, fellas,
but I have a serious question.
-Yeah.
-Who's ready
to skate their butts off?
-Yeah!
-Hudson!
-Hudson's hilarious.
-And a lot of my issues
are my own.
Like, sometimes I think
that I don't deserve you,
and you've just got
so much on your plate.
It's like, who am I,
you know?
-Ooh-wee! Ooh-wee!
-♪ Come on, ride the train,
and ride it ♪
-Choo-choo!
-I've never felt so cool!
-How's that even possible?
-I don't know.
It's just how I feel.
-No, I -- sorry.
I meant, like,
how is ice-skating
in a four-person train
the coolest
that that guy has ever felt?
-Stop using those guys
as a distraction
and talk to me, Casper!
-♪ Ice-skate like an Egyptian ♪
-Okay, that's going viral.
-You guys are gonna be famous.
-Tell me...
Tell me what
you're thinking right now,
and please be honest.
-I mean, honestly,
I'm thinking...
there's no way the Egyptian
thing goes viral, right?
-Oh. Okay. Okay.
Goodbye, Casper.
-Candace, wait.
Okay? You're right.
I'm sorry.
I -- I have felt distracted,
but we can work through it.
-♪ Backwards, back, alright ♪
-♪ Oh, my God,
we're backwards again ♪
-You guys, slow down.
If I fall, Kendrick Lamar
is literally gonna need to find
himself a new producer.
-I don't understand.
-Right?
Like, how is that guy
in any way associated
with Kendrick Lamar?
-I'm not talking
about those guys!
You know what?
Maybe this is a sign.
Maybe what we both actually
need is some time apart.
-Okay. Sounds good.
I'm gonna hang with these guys.
I have to figure out
their secret.
-Ha ha! Our secret?
One word.
Tag!
-Oh!
-Yay!
-Oh, my God!