>>> ON WEDNESDAY, PRESIDENT
TRUMP GIVES A SPEECH IN THE ROSE
GARDEN
ABOUT HIS ECONOMIC VISION FOR AMERICA,
INCLUDING TARIFFS
AGAINST ALMOST EVERY COUNTRY WE
DO BUSINESS WITH.
AND LIKE EVERYTHING SO FAR IN HIS PRESIDENCY,
IT WAS A TOTAL
HOME RUN.
WE GO NOW TO AN ENCORE
PRESENTATION
OF TRUMP'S
HISTORICALLY AWESOME
SPEECH.
THANK
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING OUT
TO HEAR ABOUT TARIFFS.
MY FAVORITE WORD, TARIFF.
WHICH OF COURSE IS SHORT FOR
TARIFFIC IDEA.
THEY'RE THE BACKBONE OF MY
INCREDIBLE PLAN FOR OUR ECONOMY.
IT'S ACTUALLY BETTER THAN A PLAN
BECAUSE IT'S A SERIES OF RANDOM
NUMBERS.
LIKE THE
NUMBERS ON COMPUTER SCREENS IN
SEVERANCE.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE HELL
THEY MEAN, BUT
I KNOW WHAT THE NUMBERS MEAN.
OKAY?
THEY MEAN
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AMERICA
WEALTHY AGAIN, OKAY?
MAWA,
MAWA. BROING
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GOING TO CHECK
YOUR STOCK PORTFOLIO IN
A COUPLE OF DAYS
AND THINK I'M
ALMOST TOO WEALTHY, MAWA.
BEFORE THAT, WE'RE GOING TO DO
MAGDA.
MAGDA,
MAKE AMERICA GREAT DEPRESSION
AGAIN.
IT WILL BE BETTER THAN GREAT,
A FANTASTIC, UNBELIEVABLE
DEPRESSION.
THE LIKES OF WHICH WE'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE.
WE LOVE TO SAY THE LIKES OF
WHICH WE NEVER HAVE SEEN BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, THIS DEPRESSION IS
GOING TO BE SO GREAT.
WE'LL BE THE ONES EATING CATS
AND DOGS.
AND THAT'S FUN, FOLKS.
LOW AND SLOW, BRAISE THEM, YOU
KNOW.
THE STOCK MARKET HAS CRASHED
TEMPORARILY,
BUT THAT'S ALL PART OF THE PLAN,
IT'S SIMPLE
ECONOMICS.
IF THE STOCK MARKET GOES DOWN
AND DOWN AND DOWN,
IT MEANS IT
HAS NOWHERE TO GO BUT UP.
OR PERHAPS FURTHER DOWN.
WE GOT TO DO THESE TARIFFS,
FOLKS, WE HAVE TO.
NO IDEA WHY BUT WE'VE GOT TO DO
THEM.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE REALLY BIG
PIECE OF CARDBOARD.
HOWARD, YOU WANT TO BRING IT UP?
THIS IS WONDERFUL, MY COMMERCE SECRETARY
HOWARD LUTNICK
EVERYBODY, THANK YOU.
NOW WE'VE GOT THE BIG CARDBOARD,
THIS IS GREAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS IS A
CHEESECAKE FACTORY MENU.
THAT'S FOR THE LUNCH AFTER.
I'M GETTING BANG BANG TACOS.
GIVE
THANKS HOWARD, YOU'RE DOING A
GREAT JOB TO FIGURE OUT THE
SCARY TARIFFS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO BE FACE OF THE
TARIFFS WITH ME?
>> NO, I'M GOOD.
>> HE'S A MODEST GUY.
HERE IT IS.
LOOK AT THIS, THAT'S SO
BEAUTIFUL.
WE SPENT SO MUCH TIME,
FRANKLY MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS, FRANKLY, ON THIS
PIECE OF CARDBOARD.
WE LISTED THE COUNTRIES IN AN
ORDER THAT'S NEITHER
ALPHABETICAL NOR NUMERICAL
FOR
MAXIMUM CONFUSION.
AND THE TARIFFS WILL BE
RECIPROCAL.
WE LOVE THE WORD RECIPROCAL,
EXCEPT IN THE BEDROOM, RIGHT
FELLOWS?
YOU WANT ME TO DO WHAT?
GUYS KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
SOME PEOPLE SAY MY PLAN IS NONSENSE
BUT WE'RE USING A
FORMULA, THEY CALL IT FORMULA,
IT'S COMPLICATED BUT LET ME
EXPLAIN HOW IT WORKS.
GIVE ME THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO THAT'S A TRIANGLE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
UP HERE, XI, FROM CHINA.
AND THAT'S MI STABBING HIM WITH
A SWORD.
AND THEN DOWN HERE THERE'S SOME
SIDEWAYS BOOBS.
YOU GET IT.
YOUR MONEY IS GONE, THAT'S THE
OKAY, WE'RE GOING TO FIGURE IT
OUT.
NO COUNTRY IS SAFE FROM MY
TARIFFS.
I EVEN PUT TARIFFS ON AN ISLAND
UNINHABITED BY HUMANS.
IT'S CALLED HEARD & McDONALD
ISLAND.
McDONALD ISLAND,
I WOULD LOVE TO VISIT THERE.
RIGHT?
CAN YOU IMAGINE THAT?
BIG MAC AND A HULA SKIRT.
OOH LA LA.
I HAD THEM MOCK UP McDONALD
ISLAND.
WOULD YOU BRING IT UP?
THERE YOU GO.
WANT
GET ME TO GOD'S COUNTRY, RIGHT?
REMEMBER THAT?
THE POINT IS EVERYTHING
IS GOING TO BE FINE,
AND/OR BAD.
EVERYBODY IS WORRIED ABOUT
PRICES GOING UP,
ESPECIALLY THE
PRICE OF GROKERIES.
AM I SAYING THAT RIGHT?
FOOD FROM THE GROKERIE STORE.
OLD FASHIONED TERM.
WE NEED TO SEND A MESSAGE TO
COUNTRIES RIPPING US OFF,
SOUTH
AFRICA PUTS A 60% TARIFF ON
EVERYTHING WE SEND THEM
AND
THEY'VE NEVER SENT US ONE GOOD
THING.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME?
>> SAY CHEESE!
KIDDING.
COME ON, COMEDY!
THAT IS FROM WHEN I TRIED TO BUY
THE ELECTION IN WISCONSIN.
I'M AN IDIOT, I SHOULD HAVE JUST
BOUGHT WISCONSIN.
GLITCH.
PIN-WHEEL, PIN-WHEEL, PIN-WHEEL.
AND I'M BACK.
>> ELON IS GREAT BUT SADLY,
IT'S TIME TO NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN,
OKAY?
YOU'VE GOT TO GET BACK TO TESS
TESLA BECAUSE THEY'RE DOING
PRETTY BAD.
>> YES, AND RECENTLY OUR
DEALERSHIPS HAVE
BEEN THE
TARGETS OF MANY ATTACKS.
SUDDENLY NO ONE LIKES TESLA
CARS.
I ASKED MYSELF WHY,
THEN I ANSWERED MYSELF, BECAUSE OF ME.
WHICH IS WHY WE ARE INTRODUCING
THE NEW TESLA MODEL-V.
THE FIRST ELECTRIC CAR IN
HISTORY
TO BE FULLY
SELF-VANDALIZING.
WITH FEATURES LIKE SELF-SMASHING
HEADLIGHTS,
SELF-SLASHING TIRES,
AND A.I.-POWERED GRAFFITI.
YOU CAN CHOOSE FROM PENISES OR
SWASTIKAS,
OR MY FAVORITE,
SWASTIKAS MADE OUT OF PENISES.
>> WOW.
SWASTIKAS OF PENISES,
WE'RE
TRULY THE PARTY OF LINCOLN.
>> BEFORE I GO, I WANT TO
MENTION I'M REALLY SMART
AND
THESE TARIFFS SOUND REALLY DUMB.
>> THANK YOU, ELON, GOOD LUCK
ON MARS.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
BLACK!
LADIES
>>> OH, MY GOODNESS,
THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH THIS
MEANS TO ME.
I AM BACK!
I'M HOSTING "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE"
FOR THE FOURTH TIME.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T KNOW,
IT'S BEEN 20 YEARS SINCE I'VE
BEEN ON THIS STAGE.
AND HONESTLY IT WAS AN ABSOLUTE
LIFE HIGHLIGHT.
AND THAT'S WHY IT'S SO HARD
TO SAY WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SAY.
BUT I QUIT.
I KNOW, IT'S THE FIRST TIME EVER
A HOST HAS QUIT IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE MONOLOGUE.
IT'S KIND OF COOL, FIRST TIME
IT'S EVER HAPPENED.
BUT I CAN'T DO IT.
IT'S TOO STRESSFUL
AND
FRANKLY, I DON'T HAVE THE NERVE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WAIT A SECOND, MATTY NO.
HOW DARE YOU PLAY THAT RIFF,
NOW I GET A MIC.
YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW WHAT THIS
SONG DOES TO ME.
IT GIVES ME THE POWER TO HOST
AGAIN.
YEAH.
HERE WE GO.
¶ I'M BACK
I'M BACK
AT SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE
AGAIN ¶
¶ JACK BLACK
I'M HOSTING SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE
AGAIN ¶
¶ 20 YEARS AGO
I HOSTED THIS
FREAKIN' SHOW ¶
¶ AND THEN I DID
SOME INDYIE FIMZ
THAT YOU MAYBE KNOW ¶
¶ JUMANJI
AND DON'T FORGET
SUPER MARI-EE ¶IE FIMZ
¶ AND DON'T FORGET
KUNG FU PAND-I
I PLAYED PO ¶
¶ AND DON'T YOU DARE FORGET
NACHO
¶ I'M BACK
I'M BACK ON SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE
AGAIN ¶
¶ MINECRAFT
THAT'S ANOTHER MOVIE I'M IN ¶
¶ BET THIS GUY
DID NOT KNOW
HE'D BE ON TV ¶
TAKE A LOOK
¶ AND IF YOU WANT TO ROCK AND ROLL
YOU BIT OF FOLLOW ME ¶
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THE
MARCHING BAND!
¶ LAST TIME I WAS HERE WAS
20 YEARS BACK
BUT NOW I KNOW EVERYBODY
KNOWS YOU'RE IN THE CAST ¶
¶ IT'S KENAN
AND HELEN AND MARKEESIO ¶
¶ I'LL ADMIT
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE WATCHED
THE SHOW ¶
¶ BUT YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU GUYS ¶
BIG FINISH.
¶ SNL'S 50 ¶
¶ AND I'M 55
THE OLDER WE GET
MORE WE FEEL ALIVE ¶
¶ I'M BACK ¶
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW.
ELTON JOHN AND BRANDI CARLILE
ARE HERE.
STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
HELLO
MATCH,"
THE GAME WHERE ONE
LONELY GAL HAS HER PICK OF THREE
ELIGIBLE GUYS.
JANIE FROM SYRACUSE, ARE YOU
EXCITED TO PUT MINGLE IN THAT
SINGLE?
>> YOU KNOW IT, I'M JANIE FROM SYRACUSE
AND I'M GOING TO PUT
SOME MINGLE IN THAT SINGLE.
>> YEAH, I JUST SAID ALL THAT.
LET'S MEET THE BACHELORS.
REMEMBER JANIE, EVEN THOUGH
I CAN SEE THE GUYS,
YOU WON'T
UNTIL YOU MAKE YOUR CHOICE.
FIRST UP IS ALLAN FROM TEMPE.
>> MY NAME IS ALLAN, BUT I HOPE
TO BE F'ALLAN IN LOVE.
>> WE'VE ALSO GOT DAN FROM
RIDGEFIELD.
>> HEY, I'M DAN,
AND DAN, GIRL, LET'S DO THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND FINALLY WE'VE GOT GENE FROM
SEATTLE.
>> I'M GENE,
I CAN'T THINK OF A
PUN FOR MY NAME, I'M JUST GENE.
>> THANK YOU, GENE.
>> WELL, OKAY.
I'LL START WITH DAN.
DAN, WHAT DO YOU LOOK FOR IN A
WOMAN?
>> WELL, THE RIGHT ANSWER IS PERSONALITY,
BUT THE REAL ANSWER
IS BUTT.
>> OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, GENE?
>> YOU KNOW, I SPENT A LOT OF MY
LIFE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WOMEN.
THEN ONE DAY I SAID, MAYBE IT'S
TIME TO FIGURE OUT GENE.
SO I'M LOOKING FOR A WOMAN TO GO
ON THAT JOURNEY WITH ME.
>> WOW, THAT'S HONESTLY SO
REFRESHING.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, GENE.
REALLY.
>> I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO TELL
YOU, HE'S DRESSED LIKE INDIANA
JONES.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO SAY WHAT
THEY LOOK LIKE
BUT HE'S IN
HEAD-TO-TOE INDIANA JONES.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YEAH, WHAT IS INDIANA JONES?
>> WHAT IS INDIANA JONES?
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
INDIANA JONES IS.
>> WELL, NO, GENE, I THINK YOU
DO.
BECAUSE YOU'RE DRESSED LIKE
INDIANA JONES.
>> I'M DRESSED LIKE GENE, I
DON'T
KNOW WHAT INDIANA JONES IS,
IS
IT A BRAND LIKE TOMMY HILFIGER?
>> WHAT?
NO.
>> THEN I DON'T KNOW WHAT
INDIANA JONES IS.
>> YOU DO KNOW WHAT IT IS.
YOU DO.
YOU HAVE A WHIP.
>> HE DOES HAVE A WHIP.
I HAVEN'T HAD A QUESTION YET.
WHAT CAN WE DO ABOUT THAT?
>> THIS ISN'T
MINE, YOUR PEOPLE GAVE IT TO ME.
I THOUGHT YOU PUSHED IT TO BUZZ
IN.
>> NO YOU DIDN'T THINK IT WAS TO
BUZZ IN, IT'S A WHIP.
>> I DON'T CARE HOW HE'S
DRESSED.
HE SOUNDS NICE.
>> I AM NICE.
>> NO, HE'S NOT NICE
BECAUSE HE'S LYING ABOUT NOT KNOWING
HE'S DRESSED LIKE INDIANA JONES,
IN A KHAKI SHIRT WITH ONE SLEEVE
RIPPED OFF AND WEARING AN
ADVENTURE HAT.
>> YOU'RE HURTING MY FEELINGS,
YOUR PRODUCER JUST SAID WEAR
WHAT YOU WEAR ON A DATE.
I'M SORRY IF IT LOOKS LIKE
INDIANA JONES.
WHOEVER HE MAY BE.
>> WAS INDIANA JONES FROM
INDIANA?
>> NO, THAT WAS HIS NICKNAME.
>> EXCUSE ME!
EXCUSE ME!
DID YOU JUST SAY A CORRECT FACT
ABOUT INDIANA JONES?
>> IT'S A GAME SHOW, I WAS
GUESSING.
>> CAN WE JUST GET BACK TO THE
GAME?
GENE, WHAT'S YOUR BIGGEST FEAR?
>> GOT TO SAY SNAKES.
>> YOU'RE PISSING ME OFF, BUDDY.
>> SAY THAT TO MY WHIP.
>> BOYS, BOYS, NO.
COME ON.
>> JUST GO LOOK AT HIM, YOU'LL
SEE.
>> NO, NO, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
AND I MUST SAY IF YOU KEEP
TELLING HER WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE,
YOU HAVE TO
SAY WHAT WE LOOK LIKE AS WELL.
>> OKAY, YOU LOOK LIKE A 12-YEAR-OLD
AND YOU LOOK LIKE
JANE LYNCH.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THIS IS THE WORST EPISODE OF
THIS SHOW WE'VE EVER HAD.
>> TELL THAT TO MY WHIP!
>> JUST SHUT HIS DOOR.
>> NO!
>> I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT, JANIE.
LET'S START OVER, ALL NEW GUYS.
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
LET'S MEET NEW BACHELOR NUMBER
ONE.
>> HI, I'M STEPHEN, I'M LOOKING
FOR LOVE.
>> WHERE ARE THEY COMING FROM!
LOVE MATCH WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
ANOTHER
ORDINARY?
THAT'S FOR THE OTHER GUY.
>> DON'T YOU TRY COMING AT US
WITH MILD.
>> MILD?
I AIN'T NO CHILD, I NEED IT
WILD.
AND WHEN IT'S TIME TO DEPLOY
SOME MAJOR SNACKAGE,
ONLY
FLAMIN' HOT WILL DO.
>> BUT LET'S SHOOT STRAIGHT, KING,
ALL THAT IN YOUR FACE
FLAVOR CAN MESS UP YOUR BUTT.
INFLAMMATION, SWELLING, PAINFUL
IRRITATION.
YOU NEED FAST RELIEF,
YOU NEED
THE COOLING TOUCH OF PREPARATION
H.
>> NOT THIS DAWG, DAWG, I NEED
TO KICK IT TO THE EXTREME.
>> WHAT?
>> NEW FLAMIN' HOT PREPARATION
H.
>> WHERE DID YOU GET THAT, WHAT
IS THAT?
>> 20,000 SCOVILLE UNITS,
PLAYER!
DENSELY PACKED INTO AN EASY TO
APPLY DARK RED CREAM.
>> GOOD LORD, WHY ON EARTH WOULD
YOU PUT
THAT ON YOUR ANUS?
>> YOU NEED TO FIGHT FIRE WITH
FIRE, G.
>> NO YOU DON'T.
STUART,
THAT'S HORRIBLE IDEA.
NO, DAWG, IT'S SCIENCE.
>> MOST CREAMS SHRINK THE
IRRITATION WITH A COOLING
EFFECT.
BUT YOU NEED TO EXHAUST THE
FUEL, CHIEF!
ONLY FLAMIN' HOT PACKS THE
INFLAMMATORY PUNCH TO ACHIEVE --
>> TOTAL
ERUPTION.
>> STUART, COME ON, YOU'RE
SCARING ME MAN.
>> HELP ME SPREAD IT AROUND.
>> I'M NOT TOUCHING THAT.
>> I'LL JUST BE ONE MORE MINUTE
PLEASE.
>> HANG IN THERE STUART, I'M
GOING TO CALL 911.
>> THIS WAS A MISTAKE!
>> FLAMIN' HOT PREPARATION H,
NOW IN CHILI LIME HABANERO AND
CAROLINA REAPER PEPPER.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU GUYS IN AGES.
>> ARE EDDIE AND WALTER STILL
COMING?
>> YEAH, THEY SHOULD BE HERE
SOON.
LOVE
DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
TRYING TO ONE-UP US?
COLLEGE
NOW
EDDIE
>> SORRY I'M LATE.
OH, MY GOSH, ANGIE, HAVEN'T SEEN
YOU IN SO LONG, WHERE YOU BEEN?
>> YOU KNOW I EITHER BE TWO
PLACES, AT WORK OR ON THIS
PHONE.
>> SAME, I LITERALLY MUST BE
STOPPED
MY SCREEN TIME IS LIKE
18 HOURS A DAY.
>> SAME, MINE IS LIKE 20, IT'S
SAD.
>> LET ME SEE WHAT MINE IS.
WEIRD, IT SAYS ONLY TWO.
>> ONLY TWO HOURS?
>> I GUESS BECAUSE I GAVE UP ALL
SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> OH, WOW, THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
>> JEEZ, I'M SO JEALOUS.
>> WELL LOOK, BEING OFF GRID
ISN'T THAT GREAT,
I'M SO BORING,
ALL I DO IS LIKE READ PHYSICAL
BOOKS.
>> WOW, THAT'S GREAT MAN.
>> LOOK, WALTER IS HERE.
>> HEY GUYS, SO SORRY I'M LATE,
>> NO WORRIES, HOW YOU BEEN?
>> I'M FINE, JUST HAD A LONG
DAY.
I WAS AT A PROTEST.
>> HELLO, WALTER, GOOD TO SEE
YOU.
SOUNDS LIKE A CRAZY DAY.
CAN WE GET YOU A DRINK?
>> OH, YEAH, I'LL JUST HAVE A
CLUB SODA.
I'M NOT DRINKING.
>> WOW, THAT'S AWESOME.
HONESTLY YOU GUYS ALL LOOK SO
WELL.
BY THE WAY, EDDIE, WHERE DID YOU
GET THAT SWEATER?
>> I THRIFTED IT.
FROM GOODWILL.
WHERE I VOLUNTEER.
>> WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING OF YOU, EDDIE.
>> YEAH, WHERE'S YOURS FROM,
ZARA OR THE EVIL TEMU?
>> NEITHER ACTUALLY, I MADE IT.
ANYWAY, SOPHIE, HOW WAS YOUR
WEEKEND?
>> IT WAS GREAT, I SAW A FOREIGN
FILM WITH NO SUBTITLES.
>> SORRY GUYS, IT'S WORK,
I NORMALLY WOULDN'T TAKE IT BUT
YOU'RE ALWAYS ON CALL WHEN
YOU'RE A TEACHER.
FOR SPECIAL NEEDS KIDS.
WHO SPEAK SPANISH.
>> WOW, YOU MUST BE SO EXCITED
FOR THE SUMMER.
>> I KNOW I AM.
>> ME, TOO, BUT I DON'T GO TO
THE BEACH,
I ONLY GO TO
BLACK-OWNED POOLS.
>> OKAY, WELL, WE'RE POLY.
>> OOPS, EXCUSE ME.
>> HOW'S THE FOOD, FOLKS?
NEED ANYTHING?
>> NO.
>> LOVELY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OKAY.
GREAT, WELL MY SHIFT IS ENDING
AND I GOT TO GET HOME TO MY SON
WHO I ADOPTED FROM CHINA.
COME AUREULIUS.
>> OH, THAT'S WHAT THAT SOUND
WAS.
ATHENS
THEATHER
BEEN
FIRST
>> RIGHT THIS WAY, HERE YOU ARE.
THE SHOW WILL BEGIN SHORTLY.
>> CLYMESTICLES, GOOD TO SEE
YOU.
>> YOU AS WELL, ZEERIOS.
TELL ME, DO YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE
GATHERED HERE TO SEE?
>> ALL I'VE BEEN TOLD IS IT'S A
NEW FORM OF ENTERTAINMENT
CALLED
A PLAY.
>> YES, THE POSTER SIMPLY SAID
TONIGHT AT 7:00 P.M.
COME WATCH
A BOOK.
>> CURIOUS.
>> SOMETHING APPEARS TO BE
HAPPENING.
>> I AM DAMATROS.
>> HELLO.
>> I AM BUT A SIMPLE FARMER.
>> I AM A CLOTH MERCHANT.
>> WHY ARE YOU UP THERE?
COME SIT WITH US.
>> PLEASE LET HIM SPEAK.
>> AH, MY CHICKENS, TIME TO
FEED.
EAT YOUR GRAIN, CHICKENS.
>> I SEE NO CHICKENS.
>> FRIEND, IT SEEMS YOUR
CHICKENS HAVE RUN OFF.
>> PLEASE SIT DOWN.
>> WHY?
>> LOOK, JUST YONDER, THE KING'S
GENERAL APPROACHES THE PALACE.
>> THERE'S NO GENERAL BACK
THERE.
>> WHY DO YOU LIE TO US, SIR?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> I SENSE GRAVE EVENTS WILL
BEFALL OUR KING.
>> GOODBYE.
>> I, PHOBIS, HAVE RETURNED FROM
THE ISLES.
>> HI, I'M CLYMESTICLES.
>> I'M FILIMEDE, WELCOME.
>> SOMEONE FETCH THE KING,
TELL HIM HIS LOYAL FRIEND AND GENERAL
BRINGS DISTRESSING NEWS.
>> I WILL GO.
>> OH, I'M WEAK WITH HUNGER,
HOW MY HEAD ACHES AND STOMACH ROARS
WITH WANT OF FOOD.
>> HERE'S SOME BREAD.
PLEASE.
AND SIT DOWN.
>> SIR, GO BACK TO YOUR SEAT.
>> HE'S STARVING, HE NEEDS TO
EAT.
>> GREETINGS, ALL.
>> I KNOW THIS MAN, HE'S MY
NEIGHBOR, TRITUS.
>> IT IS I, KING BYZANTUS.
>> LIAR!
YOU'RE NO KING.
HE'S AN OLIVE OIL MERCHANT.
>> MY KING, THEY LAID SIEGE ON
MY CARAVAN
AND CAPTURED YOUR
WIFE, QUEEN SILESTRA.
>> LIAR, I SAW HIS WIFE THIS
MORN.
>> STOP INTERRUPTING.
>> HE'S LYING TO US.
GO AWAY, I DON'T LIKE YOU.
>> COME, PHOBIS, WE SHALL SET
SAIL THIS MOMENT AND RESCUE HER.
>> THE AIR IS ODDLY STILL THIS
EVE.
>> SO, DID YOU FIND YOUR
CHICKENS?
>> DAYS HAVE PASSED SINCE THE
KING'S SHIP LEFT HARBOR,
I PRAY
THE GODS KEEP THEM SAFE.
>> OH, THANK ZEUS, THE SHIP HAS
HELD WELL.
LOOK, THE ARMY OF ISLES WAITS
FOR US.
>> AGAIN, HE TRICKS US!
>> I WILL NOT WAIT TO STRIKE,
I KNOW OF YOUR PLOT TO MURDER ME
AND STEAL BOTH MY WIFE AND
CROWN.
>> HOW DID YOU DISCOVER MY
SECRET?
>> THAT IS BETWEEN ME AND THE GODS,
WHOM YOU SOON SHALL MEET.
>> OH, GOD!
>> WHY!
WHY!
WHY WERE WE BROUGHT HERE TO
WATCH SOMEONE BE MURDERED?
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S PRETEND.
SEE?
HE'S NOT REALLY DEAD.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> NO!
>> SO
WE ACT OUT A STORY, YOU WATCH
AND PRETEND IT'S REAL.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
>> THAT SOUNDS DIFFICULT, I
DON'T THINK I CAN.
>> THE NEXT SCENE THERE'S
NUDITY.
>> WELL THEN ON WITH THE SHOW.
I LOVE THE THEATER.
JAMAICA
THIS ISLAND IS OUR HOME
BLESSED BY JAH
SO MUCH BEAUTY TO BEHOLD ¶
¶ BUT WHEN THERE IS WAR
AND STRUGGLE AND PAIN
HOW DO WE FILL OUR SOULS
WITH JOY AGAIN ¶
¶ WE LOOK AND WE LAUGH AND
GOTH KID ON VACATION
WITH THEIR FAMILY ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
GOTH KID ON VACATION
THEY JUST WANT TO LEAVE ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION ¶
¶ HE NO WEAR BATHING SUIT
HE WEAR BIG BLACK JEANS ¶
¶ HE WEAR NO SANDAL
HE GOT JAH COMBAT BOOTS
ON JAH BEACH ¶
¶ HE NO WAN NO JET SKI
HE NO SWIM WITH NO DOLPHIN ¶
¶ HE WAN SIT IN
THE HOTEL LOBBY
LOOK AT PHOTOS OF HIS
BIG-BONED GIRLFRIEND ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
HIDING FROM THE SUN
GOTH KID ON VACATION
WATCH HIS HAIR DYE RUN ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
HE NO HAVE NO FUN
GOTH KID ON VACATION ¶
¶ WHEN I WAS
A YOUNG BOY
MY PARENTS
TOOK ME DOWN TO JAMAICA ¶
¶ FOR MY HIGH SCHOOL
SPRING BREAK ¶
¶ THEY SAID COME TO
THE POOL BUT
I STAYED IN
THE ROOM WITH ¶
¶ MY GRAPHIC NOVELS
SO I COULD MASTURBATE
CUZ I'M A ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
GOTH KID ON VACATION ¶
>> HEY, SO WHAT'S THE PLAN FOR
THIS AFTERNOON, GANG, WHAT DOES
EVERYBODY WANT TO DO?
>> GO HOME.
>> MAYBE SNORKELING.
>> MAYBE GO HOME.
>> SNORKELING SOUNDS GREAT.
>> GOING HOME SOUNDS GREAT.
>> DEXTER, MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST
GO TO THE BEACH AND WRITE YOUR
POETRY.
WOULD THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY?
>> HAPPINESS IS A DISEASE.
¶ HE SWEATING, HE SWEATING
OH MY
HE SWEATING, HE SWEATING
RIGHT THROUGH HIS T-SHIRT ¶
¶ HE SWEATING, HE SWEATING
ASS PRINT ON
THE LOUNGE CHAIR ¶
¶ HE SWEATING, HE SWEATING
LIFE IS MISERY FOR A
GOTH KID ON VACATION
MY SHIRT IS STAYING ON ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
I'LL DO THE ZIPLINE ONCE
GOTH KID ON VACATION
PLEASE JUST TAKE ME HOME ¶
¶ GOTH KID ON VACATION
ONE LOVE ¶
LADIES
Little Richard's Bible
¶ PENNIMAN AND MACON
GO TOGETHER
SINGING LOUD SWEET GEORGIA
OOH MY SOUL ¶
¶ BLACK MASCARA
THICKER THAN MOLASSES
SEX AND SINNERS
TAKE A TOLL ¶
¶ FREEDOM FEATHERS FALLING
FROM OLD JIM CROW
GOT THE MISSISSIPPI BLUES
ON THE RADIO ¶
¶ BIG EASY BAKING
IN THE RED-HOT SUN
ROCK AND ROLL
TO NUMBER ONE ¶
¶ LITTLE RICHARD
WOKE UP WANTING
TO CAST OFF SEX AND IDOLS ¶
¶ GOD WHISPERED IN HIS EAR
COME ON OVER HERE
SON GET YOURSELF A BIBLE ¶
¶ POMPADOUR PILED
HIGH TO THE SKY
CHRIST IS COMING
BY AND BY ¶
¶ LONG TALL SALLY
MY OH MY
HE'S GOT THE GOOD BOOK
BY HIS SIDE ¶
¶ WITH RICHARD AND
THE DEVIL DIVIDED
THE HOLY WORD
FROM HEAVEN'S HANDS ¶
¶ THE SOUND OF
SWEET SALVATION
RINGING IN THE
EARS OF EVERYMAN ¶
¶ MADE-UP LOOKING PRETTY
VANITY WON'T PREVAIL ¶
¶ IT'S HOT DOWN SOUTH
BUT SHUT YOUR MOUTH
GRAB THAT OLD BOY
BY THE TAIL ¶
¶ LITTLE RICHARD
WOKE UP WANTING
TO CAST OFF SEX AND IDOLS ¶
¶ GOD WHISPERED IN HIS EAR
COME ON OVER HERE
SON GET YOURSELF A BIBLE ¶
¶ POMPADOUR PILED
HIGH TO THE SKY
CHRIST IS COMING
BY AND BY ¶
¶ LONG TALL SALLY
MY OH MY
HE'S GOT THE GOOD BOOK
BY HIS SIDE ¶
>>> IT'S "WEEKEND UPDATE" WITH
>> THANK YOU,
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
AMERICA ELECTED DONALD TRUMP
TO RUN THE COUNTRY LIKE A BUSINESS.
BUT IT TURNS OUT HE'S RUNNING IT
LIKE ONE OF HIS BUSINESSES.
WORST WEEK
I LOVE THAT YOU CAN
INTENTIONALLY RUIN THE ECONOMY
AND STILL GET TO STAY PRESIDENT.
IT'S LIKE IF YOU DRUNK DROVE
YOUR CAR THROUGHOUT WINDOW OF THE DMV
AND THEY WERE LIKE
LICENSE RENEWED.
IT'S INSANE.
THIS WAS THE WORST WEEK FOR THE
STOCK MARKET SINCE THE SUMMER OF 2020,
BUT YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER,
BACK THEN THE PRESIDENT WAS ALSO
TRUMP.
JUST IN THE PAST TWO DAYS,
INVESTORS HAVE LOST OVER $6
TRILLION.
MONEY IS LEAVING THE STOCK MARKET FASTER
THAN MORGAN WALLEN AT
GOOD NIGHT.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCED A
TARIFF ON ALL GOODS IMPORTED
INTO THE U.S.
SAYING THE U.S. HAS
BEEN PLUNDERED AND RAPED BY
OTHER COUNTRIES.
AND TRUMP WILL NOT STAND FOR
PLUNDERING.
AN ECONOMIC SLOWDOWN FROM
TARIFFS COULD BE ESPECIALLY HARD ON CHINA
BECAUSE IT'S NOT EASY
TO TELL A CHILD
THEY'RE GETTING LAID OFF.
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
>> YEAH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP EVEN IMPOSED
TARIFFS ON REMOTE ISLANDS
ONLY
INHABITED BY PENGUINS.
THEN MAYBE PENGUINS SHOULDN'T
KEEP PUSHING THEIR GAY AGENDA.
>> SENATOR CORY BOOKER SET A RECORD,
25-HOUR SPEECH ON THE
SENATE FLOOR.
WHICH IS CRAZY.
I'VE BEEN TALKING 45 SECONDS AND
I ALREADY WANT TO GO HOME.
THE PREVIOUS RECORD WAS STROM THURMOND
WHO SPOKE OVER 24 HOURS
TO PROTEST THE CIVIL RIGHTS
BILL.
AND LOOK HOW EFFECTIVE THAT WAS.
>> THE LIVESTREAM OF CORY
BOOKER'S SPEECH
GOT MORE THAN
350 MILLION LIKES ON TIKTOK
AND
WAS RESHARED MILLIONS MORE TIMES
WITH THE #WHYVINDIESELTRIPPIN'.
>> THE DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
HAS WARNED STATE OFFICIALS
THAT
PUBLIC SCHOOLS WILL LOSE FEDERAL FUNDING
IF THEY DON'T ELIMINATE
DEI PROGRAMS.
FROM NOW ON, SPANISH CLASS IS
JUST GOING TO BE
ENGLISH BUT
LOUDER CLASS.
>> HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY ROBERT F. KENNEDY JR.,
SEEN HERE WATCHING A CHICKEN
SNEEZE ON A BABY,
SAID THIS WEEK
THAT HE'S PUSHING FOR SCHOOL
CAFETERIAS TO SERVE WHOLE MILK.
THOUGH IT'S RFK, SO THAT MILK
COULD BE COMING FROM ANY HOLE.
IN THE FLORIDA SPECIAL ELECTION,
JIMMY PATRONIS
WON MATT GAETZ'S
OLD SEAT BY 15 POINTS.
SAID GAETZ, 15?
NICE.
I DELIVERED THAT TOO CREEPY.
>> THAT WAS WAY TOO REAL.
THIS WEEK, PRESIDENT TRUMP MET
WITH KID ROCK
FOR WHAT APPEARS
TO BE DRAG QUEEN STORY HOUR.
KID ROCK WATCHED TRUMP SIGN AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER ABOUT CONCERT TICKET FEES,
THEN HE RETURNED TO
HIS REGULAR JOB
AS A FOURTH OF
JULY LAWN SKELETON.
NEW YORK MAYOR ERIC ADAMS ANNOUNCED
THAT HE IS LEAVING THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
I ASSUME TO HIT UP THE AFTER
PARTY.
>> SOME STUDIES SUGGEST THAT SPRING
IS THE MOST COMMON SEASON
FOR COUPLES TO BREAK UP.
HERE TO COMMENT ON HOW TO KEEP A
HEALTHY RELATIONSHIP
ARE GRANT
AND
ALYSSA, THE COUPLE YOU CAN'T
BELIEVE ARE TOGETHER.
>> WHAT'S UP, COLIN,
BRO, WE'RE PUMPED TO BE HERE ON "WEEKEND
EDITION."
LET'S GO!
>> THANK YOU.
HELLO.
>> IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU GUYS
AGAIN.
I HONESTLY FORGOT JUST HOW
DIFFERENT YOU WERE.
>> MAN, THAT'S WHAT MAKES US
PERFECT, COLIN, OUR
DIFFERENCES.
WE'RE GOING TO LIVE HAPPILY EVER AFTER,
JUST LIKE ROMEO AND
JULIET, I ASSUME.
>> GREAT.
HOW DO YOU GUYS KEEP YOUR
RELATIONSHIP HEALTHY?
>> MAN, IT'S IMPORTANT TO KNOW
EACH OTHER'S LOVE LANGUAGES.
MINE IS GIFT GIVING.
GUESS WHAT I GOT HER FOR OUR
ANNIVERSARY, COLIN, GUESS!
>> MAYBE SOME JEWELRY?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, A CLARINET.
DOESN'T MY BABY LOOK LIKE SHE
WOULD GO STUPID ON A WOODWIND?
>> GUILTY.
>> MAN.
AND HER LOVE LANGUAGE IS MAKING
ME WATCH THAT TV SHOW
ABOUT AN
AUSTRALIAN GUY WHO LIVES IN A
PORT-A-POTTY.
>> HE MEANS "DR. WHO".
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN, WE WATCH
IT EVERY NIGHT.
AND SHE'S LOOKING BAD AS HELL
WATCHING DR. WHOEVER
WHILE SHE'S
SIPPING
TEA IN HER NIGHTCAP LIKE THE
BEAR IN THE BOX.
I SNORT IT LIKE A PREWORKOUT,
WATCH IT LIKE THIS.
I'M SORRY, BUT
THIS DYNAMIC JUST WORKS FOR U
GUYS?
>> IT WORKS BECAUSE WE HAVE
GROUND RULES.
>> THAT'S TRUE, MY BABY HAS
THREE RULES FOR ME.
RULE NUMBER ONE, I DO THE DISHES
BECAUSE I LIKE PLAYING IN THE
WATER.
RULE NUMBER TWO, SHE DOES THE
COOKING
BECAUSE I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO TOUCH THE STOVE.
AND TELL THEM RULE NUMBER THREE,
BABY.
WHAT YOU ALWAYS TELL ME.
>> DON'T WEAR THOSE LITTLE
SHORTS AROUND UNLESS YOU'RE
TRYING TO DROP THEM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
>> WHOA, ALYSSA, WHERE DID THAT
COME FROM?
>> THOSE ARE CALLED BOUNDARIES, COLIN,
SHE HAS BOUNDARIES.
BOUNDARIES.
THAT'S A NEW WORD SHE TAUGHT ME
ON WORD WEDNESDAY.
EVERY WEDNESDAY MY BABY TEACHES
ME A NEW WORD.
AND I LOVE IT.
I WANT TO SAY,
GIRL, YOU MAKE ME FEEL
UNDOUBTEDLY.
>> THAT IS SO CLOSE, BABY.
>> IT'S NOT THAT CLOSE.
ANY FINAL ADVICE FOR COUPLES WHO
WANT TO MAINTAIN A HEALTHY
RELATIONSHIP?
>> I HAVE A TIP FOR LADIES OUT THERE,
LISTEN TO EACH OTHER,
NEVER GO TO BED ANGRY.
AND IF YOU COME FOR MY MAN I'LL
BREAK A BITCH LIKE A KIT-KAT
BAR.
COUPLE
>> UNDOUBTEDLY, COLIN.
>> A BRITISH WOMAN SAYS THAT HER
1-YEAR-OLD SON ATE HER FATHER'S
ASHES.
SO IN A WAY HE DOES HAVE HIS
GRANDPA'S EYES.
ISN'T THAT SWEET?
>> ACTOR RUSSELL BRAND WAS
CHARGED
IN ENGLAND WITH SEXUAL ASSAULT,
WHICH SOMEHOW MAKES THIS VIDEO
EVEN CREEPIER.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, CHRIS
BROWN.
>> WOW.
WE REALLY KNOW HOW
TO PAIR THEM UP.
>> BETTY WEBB, ONE OF THE LAST
SURVIVING WORLD WAR II CODE BREAKERS
DIED AT 101.
SHE FIRST DECIPHERED NAZI
COMMUNICATIONS
AFTER HITLER
ACCIDENTALLY ADDED HER TO A
GROUP CHAT.
>> A NEW REPORT SHOWS THAT THE
NUMBER OF BLACK MEN ATTENDING
HISTORICALLY
BLACK COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES
HAS HIT A HISTORIC LOW OF 26%,
SADLY THEY'RE LACKING ONE KEY
RESOURCE -- WHITE GIRLS.
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
>> JUST IMAGINE IF I TOLD IT.
>> YOU WROTE IT.
>> SUBWAY HAS PARTNERED WITH
DORITOS TO OFFER NEW FOOTLONG NACHOS,
BUT I DON'T LOVE THE
SLOGAN, EAT OUT OF THIS TROUGH,
YOU PIG.
>> I'M ALSO WORRIED ABOUT THIS
ONE.
THURSDAY WAS NATIONAL BURRITO
DAY
WITH MANY PLACES OFFERING FREE BURRITOS,
INCLUDING THE
BACK OF THIS TRUCK.
ICE
>> MENTAL HEALTH EXPERTS ARE
SAYING THAT ADULTS CAN HELP DEAL WITH TRAUMA
BY SLEEPING WITH A
STUFFED ANIMAL.
WHICH IS THE SAME THING GOOFY
ARE WHISPERED TO YOUR WIFE.
>> THE RESTAURANT CHAIN HOOTERS
HAS FILED FOR
BANKRUPTCY.
APPARENTLY THEIR BUSINESS MODEL
WAS A BUST.
IT'S A THINKER.
>> A BALLET DANCER SET A NEW
WORLD RECORD FOR LONGEST DISTANCE COVERED
WHILE
PERFORMING A SPLIT ON TWO MOVING
ATVs.
WHICH ALSO INSPIRED THE NEW TV
SHOW "VAGINA 911."
GREAT SHOW.
WELL, THE WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENTS ASSOCIATION ANNOUNCED
THERE WILL NO LONGER
BE A COMEDIAN AT THIS YEAR'S EVENT
TO AVOID DIVISIVE
POLITICS.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR OWN EGO
NWODIN.
>> HEY COLIN, WHAT'S UP,
EVERYBODY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M GOING TO COME
OUT AND SAY IT,
THEY SHOULD LET
ME DO THE WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENTS DINNER.
>> OKAY.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT, EGO, BUT
THEY SAID THEY DON'T WANT A
COMEDIAN.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE EVERY YEAR A
COMEDIAN TALKS TRASH ABOUT THE
WHITE HOUSE, THE MEDIA.
NO ONE EVER MAKES FUN OF THE
DINNER.
>> THE DINNER?
THE WHOLE SET CAN'T BE ABOUT
FOOD.
>> YES, IT CAN.
READ THE CARD.
>> OKAY.
LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN,
GIVE IT UP FOR
THE BADDEST CHICK ON THE BLOCK.
>> WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENTS,
HOW WE DOING WHITE HOUSE!
HEY CHEF, HANG THAT APRON UP BRO,
BECAUSE I'M DOING THE
ROASTING TONIGHT.
>> SORRY, WHAT IS THIS?
>> DAMN IT STINK IN HERE.
THIS FOOD IS RANK.
FOR DINNER, I SEE Y'ALL GOT A
CHOICE OF BEEF, FISH OR CHICKEN,
ALSO A VEGETARIAN OPTION,
IT'S CALLED WALKING YOUR GAY ASS
TO SWEET GREENS ACROSS THE
STREET.
CALL ME PEAS, BABY BECAUSE
I'M ABOUT TO SNAP, SUCKER.
>> WHAT IS THIS VOICE?
>> THEY TALK --
THEY TALKIN'
ABOUT THEY SERVING
ME SEARED ALASKAN HALIBUT.
I SAID HALIBUT YOU THROW THAT
MESS IN THE TRASH, SUCKER.
IS IT JUST ME OR ARE THESE
DINNER ROLLS HARDER THAN
TRIGONOMETRY?
GOOD GOD, THIS FOOD IS BLAND
TONIGHT.
I SEE Y'ALL GOT JICAMA ON THE
MENU.
LIKE HERE COME ANOTHER MAN WITH
ANOTHER EXCUSE.
THE HELL?
>> WHERE IS THIS GOING?
>> AS IF I AIN'T GIVE THAT MAN
FIVE CHILDREN AND TEN YEARS OF
MY LIFE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE KIDS.
>> HEY, GET YOUR FRIEND,
MICHAEL, I AIN'T DOING CROWD
WORK.
THIS MISS AGGIE AND MISS AGGIE
DON'T WHAT?
THAT'S RIGHT -- HOW YOU ALL
KNOW?
PLAY.
WASN'T SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT.
MISS AGGIE JUST TRYING TO GET
FED, GET SOME
AND GET THAT UBER HOME.
THE HELL!
>> WHO IS MISS AGGIE?
>> IT'S MY STAND-UP PERFORMER,
COLIN, PLEASE LET ME COOK.
>> YOU'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT FOOD
ANYMORE.
>> YES, I AM.
NOW LISTEN HERE,
SEX IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT AFTER 50.
>> YOU'RE NOT 50!
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, THOUGH,
NO MATTER WHAT AGE, MISS AGGIE GO
OVER EASY, OKAY?
CORY BOOKER, HIS FILIBUSTER.
SHOOT.
I HAD MY FILL OF BUSTERS
BECAUSE THESE MAN AIN'T WHAT?
>> GOING TO GET FIRED FOR THAT.
WORTH A DAMN.
GOING TO PAY FOR THAT.
WILL BE MAD AT Y'ALL.
>> IN CONCLUSION, THANK YOU
WHITE HOUSE FOR HAVING A BITCH.
>> THAT'S YOUR ENDING?
OH, MY GOD.
>> YES.
BECAUSE MISS AGGIE DON'T WHAT?
>> PLAY.
>> THERE IT IS.
EGO
WAIT
FOR
>>> FRANCESCA, I HAD A GREAT TIME TONIGHT.
>> ME, TOO, IT WAS COOL
WHEN YOU ALMOST CAUGHT THAT SHRIMP IN
YOUR MOUTH.
>> YEAH, I ALMOST HAD IT, TOO.
ANYWAY, FRANCESCA,
I HAVE TO SAY I REALLY LIKE YOU AND I'M
FEELING REALLY GOOD ABOUT US.
>> WOW, GREG, I FEEL THE SAME
WAY.
>> I THINK IT'S TIME TO TAKE
IT -- TO CONNECT
PHYSICALLY.
AND TAKE THIS TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
>> I DO, TOO.
¶ WHEN A MAN AND A WOMAN PUT ON
SILK PAJAMAS ¶
¶ AND FINALLY READY FOR A
BANG-O-RAMA ¶
¶ TOGETHER WE SWIM THROUGH THE
SEA OF ROMANCE ¶
¶ AND WE JOIN OUR BODIES IN A
SENSUAL DANCE ¶
¶ BECAUSE WE'RE MAKIN' LOVE ¶
¶ FIRST WE DO THINGS TO ME FOR A
WHILE ¶
¶ THEN WE DO THINGS TO YOU FOR
NOT THAT LONG ¶
¶ YOU'LL MAKE LOTS OF NOISE AS
OUR BODIES BLEND ¶
¶ I'LL JUST MAKE ONE NOISE AT
THE END ¶
¶ AS WE KISS WE CAN HEAR WE'RE
OUT OF BREATH ¶
¶ BECAUSE I'M IN A YOGA PLANK ¶
¶ AND I'M JUST CHILLIN' ¶
>> HEY, I HAVE AN IDEA!
HOW ABOUT SOME DIRTY TALK?
>> OH, SURE.
YOU'VE BEEN SO BAD.
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
>> WHOA, LITTLE SCARY.
NOW HOW ABOUT SOME CHAMPAGNE.
HERE YOU GO.
IT'S HARD TO REACH.
ARE YOU GETTING ANY?
SORRY, DIDN'T WANT IT TO GO IN
YOUR EYEBALLS.
SORRY.
THAT'S ENOUGH CHAMPAGNE.
>> WOW, THAT WAS SO ROMANTIC.
>> FOR ME AS WELL.
KNOW WHY?
¶ BECAUSE -- BECAUSE WE'RE
MAKIN' LOVE ¶
¶ AND THEN WITHOUT EVEN SAYING A
WORD ¶
¶ WE BOTH KNOW IT'S TIME TO
BRING IN A THIRD ¶
¶ HELLO I'M HERE TO FIX YOUR PROBLEMS
AND THIS WILL
DEFINITELY END WELL
BECAUSE
BRINGING IN A THIRD
HAS NEVER NOT WORKED,
SO
LISTEN UP, HERE'S THE PLAN ¶
¶ WE DO ME AND HIM THEN HER AND
ME ¶
¶ THEY SHE DOES HIM THEN SHE
DOES
ME ¶
¶ THEN I GET JEALOUS AND I CRY
FOR A LITTLE ¶
¶ SO WE GO OFF AND FIGHT IN THE
BATHROOM ¶
>> WHY ARE YOU MAD, THIS WAS
YOUR IDEA?
>> WELL NOW I FEEL WEIRD.
I SHUNT HAVE BROUGHT SOMEONE
FROM WORK.
HE'S GOING TO TELL EVERYONE HOW
LOVE I LOVE MAKE.
>> HEY GUYS, I CAN HEAR YOU.
SHOULD I JUST GO BACK TO
MIDTOWN?
¶ IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
EVERYTHING WILL BE DANDY ¶
¶ IF WE BRING IN A FOURTH
AND THE FOURTH IS BRANDI ¶
>> BRANDI, GIVE US YOUR WISDOM.
¶ WHAT YOU NEED IS TO LOVE EACH
OTHER DOWN ¶
¶ YOU NEED TO LET YOUR LOVE FIRE
BURN ¶
¶ THE TWO OF YOU GOT TO GET TOGETHER
AND HOLD
EACH OTHER CLOSE
AND ALWAYS REMEMBER
TO TAKE TURNS ¶
>> TAKE TURNS?
OH, BRANDI, THEY DON'T DO THAT,
YOU LESBUN.
>> I TRIED.
¶ THANKS FOR HAVING US IN THIS
LOVE PARADE ¶
¶ ISN'T IT WEIRD THIS IS HOW
PEOPLE ARE MADE ¶
¶ WELL YOU KNOW WHAT'S NEXT,
WE GET TO DO THE ONE THING ¶
¶ THAT'S BETTER THAN SEX
WE GET
TO LAY DOWN ¶
¶ AND WATCH TV,
TV ¶¶
HEY
WE ARE BIG RICKY AND THE
MINNOWS.
EVERY SUNDAY WE HOST OUR POTLUCK JAM,
IF YOU'RE A MUSICIAN, COME ON UP,
ALL INSTRUMENTS AND SKILL
LEVELS ARE WELCOME TO JAM.
ALSO AT 1:00, THERE'S THE
DIABETES AWARENESS WET
T-SHIRT CONTEST.
UNTIL THEN, LET'S JAM.
THIS IS FOR ALL MY '90s BABIES.
TWO, FOUR.
¶ SHE'S A GOOD GIRL
WHO LOVES HER MAMMA,
LOVES JESUS
AND HER BOYFRIEND TOO ¶
LOOK AT THIS, OUR FIRST JAMMER.
NICE, A BASS.
ASK AND YE SHALL RECEIVE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME MY MAN?
>> TRISH.
>> YOU KNOW THIS ONE, DIVE IN.
TWO, FOUR.
¶ IT'S A LONG DAY LIVING IN
RESEDA ¶
OH, THAT BASS FEELS GOOD, YEAH.
¶ RUNNING THROUGH THE YARD ¶
>> WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE,
NO SHIRT, NO SHOES AND A BASS.
ARE WE
DEALING WITH A DOUBLE BASS
SANDWICH?
RIGHT ON, MY MAN.
ALSO IS THAT A McDONALD'S NUMBER
TWO ON YOUR CHEST?
>> YEAH, I'M LOVING IT.
>> RIGHT ON, BUD.
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
¶ I'M A BAD BOY
BECAUSE I DON'T EVEN MISS HER ¶
FOR BREAKING HER HEART ¶
WOW, NOW IT'S AN EMBARRASSMENT
OF BASSES.
>> WOO, I LOVE YOU BIG RICKY.
>> HELLO.
LOOKS LIKE OUR SWEET JAM HAS
SUMMONED A SIREN.
ARE YOU FRESH OUT OF THE LAKE,
DARLIN'?
>> YEAH, JUST KILLING TIMES
BEFORE THE BOOB CONTEST.
>> LET'S GET THIS WET SEAL A
TAMBOURINE.
>> I PLAY BASS.
>> ANOTHER BASS,
NOT SURE THERE'S MORE REAL ESTATE LEFT ON
THE AMP.
>> I'LL FIND AN OPEN SOCKET.
>> SHE'S SLAPPING IT.
I GUESS BASS WAS NEVER MISSING
FROM THIS SONG.
KIND OF CHANGES OF VIBE OF "FREE
FALLIN'".
EDDIE, YOU THINK TOM PETTY IS
LIKING THIS?
>> I DO NOT.
>> ALL GOOD.
LET'S HIT THE CHORUS.
THREE, FOUR
¶ AND I'M FREE,
FREE FALLIN' YEAH ¶
IT'S ALL GOOD BUT PROBABLY HIT
OUR QUOTA ON BASS.
QUALITY OF THE SOUND FEELS LIKE
A SINUS INFECTION.
ALL INSTRUMENTS ARE WELCOME BUT
IF YOU GOT A BASS,
SIT THIS ONE
OUT.
WE'LL GET YOU NEXT TIME.
WE'RE BIG RICKY AND THE MINNOWS
AND WE'RE GOOD ON BASS.
SPOON MAN, YEAH,
WE CAN USE SOME PERCUSSION.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> GIVEN OR STAGE?
>> STAGE.
>> MY NAME IS KEVIN BASS-Y.
>> YOWCH, THAT'S DISAPPOINTING
ON TWO LEVELS.
WHAT WERE THE SPOONS FOR?
>> THESE SPOONS ARE FOR CRACK.
>> SON OF A BITCH!
THREE, FOUR.
¶ I'M FREE ¶
YEAH, I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
HEARING THE MELODY
LOST IN THE
CORN MAZE OF BASS.
ANYBODY ELSE'S TEETH RATTLING?
LOOKS LIKE THE AMP IS THROWING
SPARKS.
TO THE GIRL DRIPPING WETTING
MAYBE GIVE THAT THING SOME ROOM.
SHE'S NOODLING OVER THE AMP, NOT
A SMART GIRL.
LOOK, IT'S MIKE, THE OWNER OF
THE BASS BAR.
NOT A MOMENT
TOO SOON, WE COULD USE A
KEYBOARD.
>> NO, THIS IS A CARRYING CASE
FOR MY BASS.
>> WHAT?
A KEYBOARD SHAPED BASS CASE FOR
A BASS?
DAMN IT!
THIS IS LIKE GOING TO A COOKOUT
AND EVERYBODY BROUGHT QUINOA.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ONE BOSS.
>> WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
>> WHATEVER, LET'S KEEP JAMMING,
THREE, FOUR.
IS THAT "THE SIMPSONS" THEME?
GOD DAMN IT.
THIS IS TOO MUCH BASS, CAN
ANYBODY MAKE ANOTHER SOUND?
MA'AM, CAN YOU
MAKE YOUR DOG BARK.
>> NO, HE'S MUTE BUT HE'S A
BASS-ET HOUND.
>> DON'T TELL ME THAT DOG PLAYS
BASS.
I SAID WE DON'T NEED BASS AND
PEOPLE KEEP BRINGING BASS.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS, WE WANT MORE
BASS.
NO!
THIS IS TOO MUCH BASS.
THE FREQUENCIES COULD ENDANGER
THE INTEGRITY OF THE PIER.
>> IF WE'RE GOING DOWN, LET'S GO
DOWN JAMMING.
>> EDDIE, YOU'RE SO RIGHT.
EVERYBODY, LET'S JAM.
THREE FOUR.
¶ I'M FREE,
FREE FALLIN' ¶
AGAIN
Who Believes in Angels?
¶ YOU DON'T NEED TO
LAUGH SO HARD
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WEAR A TIE ¶
¶ SOMETIMES HONEST
IS BEING CAUGHT
INSIDE A LIE ¶
¶ AND I HAVE BEEN THERE
I HAVE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ IF I'D LIVED AN EASY LIFE
WOULD I STILL CHOOSE YOU
WOULD I FALL ON
THE SAME KNIFE ¶
¶ A RODEO QUEEN
BREATHING
FIRE INTO THE NIGHT ¶
¶ I HAVE BEEN THERE
MAN I'VE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ WHAT DO YOU SAY WE SET
THE PLEASANTRIES ASIDE ¶
¶ EVEN THE DIAMONDS
LOOK LIKE ROCKS
TO THE UNTRAINED EYE ¶
¶ WHAT DOES IT COST
TO BUY YOUR SOUL BACK
WHEN YOU DIE ¶
¶ WHAT ARE THE ANGELS GONNA
DO WITH YOU AND I
¶ WHAT'LL THE ANGELS
DO WITH YOU AND I ¶
¶ BLAME THE END OF DAYS
MERCURY IN RETROGRADE
WHO BELIEVES IN
ANGELS ANYWAY ¶
¶ THE COLOR OF
THE LIE IS WHITE
I WOULD DIE ON THAT HILL
IN A ONE-HANDED FIGHT ¶
¶ IF YOU'RE NOT
SWINGING FIRST
YOU WERE NEVER
IN THE RIGHT ¶
¶ I HAVE BEEN THERE
MAN I'VE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ WHAT DO YOU SAY WE SET
THE PLEASANTRIES ASIDE ¶
¶ EVEN THE DIAMONDS
LOOK LIKE ROCKS
TO THE UNTRAINED EYE ¶
¶ WHAT DOES IT COST
TO BUY YOUR SOUL BACK
WHEN YOU DIE ¶
¶ WHAT ARE THE ANGELS GONNA
DO WITH YOU AND I
¶ WHAT'LL THE ANGELS
DO WITH YOU AND I ¶
¶ BLAME THE END OF DAYS
MERCURY IN RETROGRADE
WHO BELIEVES IN
ANGELS ANYWAY ¶
¶ BLAME THE END OF DAYS
MERCURY IN RETROGRADE
WHO BELIEVES IN
ANGELS ANYWAY ¶
¶ THERE'S NO NEED TO
CURSE THE STARS
OR BITE BEFORE YOU BARK ¶
¶ BUT WHEN YOU NEED SOMEONE
TO WALK WITH IN THE DARK ¶
¶ I HAVE BEEN THERE
I HAVE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ OH I HAVE BEEN THERE
I HAVE BEEN THERE
MAN I'VE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ OH I HAVE BEEN THERE
I'VE BEEN THERE
MAN I'VE BEEN THERE ¶
¶ I'VE BEEN THERE
I'VE BEEN THERE
JAPAN
GOOD
SAY
>> UH, BABE, WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW, IT
HAPPENED SO FAST.
>> I LEAVE FOR FIVE SECONDS TO
GET A COUPLE DOGS
AND YOU'RE KISSING SOME STINKING
SAILOR?
I'M STANDING RIGHT HERE AND I
THINK SOMEONE TOOK A PHOTO.
>> NO ONE TOOK A PHOTO, DON'T
GET UPSET.
IT WAS NOTHING, I HATED IT
ANYWAY.
>> OH, 93, I KNEEL BACKWARDS AND
ARCH WHEN I HATE SOMETHING, TOO,
SURPRISED YOU
DIDN'T POP YOUR SHIRT OPEN.
TALKER
IT WAS JUST SOME DRUNK SAILOR
HAPPY TO BE HOME.
LET JUST HAVE A HOT DOG AND
FORGET THE WHOLE THING.
>> DID YOU WANT ME TO GET YOU A
HOT DOG?
>> YOU GOT FOUR HOT DOGS WITH
FOR YOURSELF?
>> IS THAT A PROBLEM?
IF YOU WANTED A DOG, YOU SHOULD
HAVE TOLD ME.
>> I'M NOT EVEN HUNGRY, I'M TOO EXCITED,
WE CAN FINALLY START
OUR LIVES.
>> HELLO.
MAY I KISS YOU ON THE MOUTH?
>> WELL, I DON'T SEE WHY NOT.
>> OKAY.
>> HEY, BUDDY.
COME ON, TIME'S UP.
KNOCK IT OFF FOR REAL, WRAP IT
UP.
SERIOUSLY,
I'M GETTING MAD,
TWO MORE
SECONDS AND THAT'S IT.
ONE --
>> HEY, MAN, GOT THAT FIFTH HOT
DOG FOR YOU.
HAD TO GO TO THE OTHER CART TO
GET IT.
>> THANK YOU.
WHY ARE YOU STILL STANDING
HERE?
>> ISN'T THIS THE LINE TO KISS
THE NURSE?
>> NO!
GET OUT OF HERE.
HEY, PUNK, THAT'S MY GIRL YOU
JUST KISSED.
>> OH, YEAH, I KNOW.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON,
BABE?
>> HONEY THEY'RE JUST HAPPY TO
BE HOME.
IT WAS A LONG WAR.
>> YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW THAT?
I SERVED MY COUNTRY,
NOT WITH A
GUN BUT I SERVED.
>> I KNOW YOU DID, SWEETHEART.
>> WHEN UNCLE SAM PUT OUT THE
CALL FOR ABLE-BODIED ILLUSTRATORS
TO DRAW RACIST
PROPAGANDA CARTOONS ABOUT THE JAPANESE EMPEROR,
I WAS FIRST IN
LINE.
>> AND I AM SO PROUD OF YOU
HONEY.
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY PEOPLE
JOINED THE ARMY BECAUSE OF MY
RACIST CARTOONS?
>> MILLIONS.
>> HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS.
>> SO I THINK I'VE EARNED MYSELF
A LITTLE TREAT, TOO,.
>> ARTHUR, DON'T.
>> TOO LATE.
HELLO DOLL, PUCKER UP.
>> GET AWAY PERVERT!
>> YOU COULD HAVE JUST SAID NO.
JEEZ!
OKAY, NOW YOU'RE THE KISSER?
WELL PLAYED.
YOU KNOW WHAT, WE'RE BREAKING
UP.
NOT FOREVER, JUST FOR NOW, WE'RE
BREAKING UP UNTIL THIS KISS ENDS
BECAUSE WHEN IT DOES, YOU'RE
WITH ME.
>> WOW.
WELCOME HOME TO ME, I GUESS.
>> HEY, JAGOFF, THAT'S MY GIRL.
>> WAIT, AREN'T YOU ARTHUR
DONNELLY, THE CARTOONIST?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> YOUR CARTOONS JUST -- WOW.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I MEAN EVEN FOR WAR TIME,
THOSE WERE REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY RACIST.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF.
>> YOU'RE TOO KIND.
>> YOU'RE A SICK MAN.
>> ALWAYS NICE TO MEET A FAN.
>> GOODBYE MISS.
>> HOW ABOUT YOU DIP YOUR GIRL
AND I'LL TAKE A PHOTO.
>> THAT'S MORE LIKE IT,
COME HERE DARLING, I'LL GIVE YOU A
BIG SMOOCH --
MY DOGS!
GLUTTON
ELTON
WHERE'S MIKE MYERS?
ANYWAY, YOU GUYS, THIS HAS BEEN
A LIFE HIGHLIGHT.
THIS IS THE BEST CREW, BEST
WRITERS, BEST CAST.
LOVE YOU.