>>> HELLO.
HELLO.
I'M TOM HANKS.
IN DECEMBER, 1990, I CREATED
THE "SNL" FIVE-TIMERS CLUB.
AND INGENIOUSLY LAZY WAY TO
AVOID WRITING A MONOLOGUE.
IT HAS GROWN INTO ONE OF THE
MOST EXCLUSIVE CLUBS IN THE
INDUSTRY.
AND TONIGHT, WE ARE HERE TO
INDUCT OUR NEWEST MEMBER.
>> HEY.
>> TOM.
TOM, I GOT TO ASK, WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING TO HERE, PAL?
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE DONE SO MANY DOCUMENTARIES,
WHEN EVER I SIT IN A LEATHER
CHAIR I NATURALLY ASSUME I'M IN
ONE.
>> SHOULD WE LET HIM IN?
HE'S BEEN STANDING OUTSIDE FOR
20 MINUTES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MARTIN ORT, WELCOME TO THE
FIVE-TIMERS CLUB.
>> OH MY GOODNESS GRACIOUS.
WHAT A SURPRISE THAT I'VE KNOWN
ABOUT ALL WEEK.
>> WELL, GET OVER HERE, MARTY.
HEY, HAVE THEY TAUGHT YOU THE
SECRET HANDSHAKE?
>> OF COURSE THEY HAVE.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE.
>> YOU'RE GREAT.
>> HEY, WHAT DO THEY CALL YOU BY
THE WAY, MARTY OR MARTIN?
>> WELL, MY FRIENDS ALL CALL ME MARTY,
SO YOU CAN CALL ME MR.
MARTIN SHORT.
>> MARTY, CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU KNOW, I AM SO GLAD YOU'RE
HERE.
YOU'RE ONE OF THE RASHEST THINGS
IN HOLLYWOOD.
A WRITER BUT ATTRACTIVE ENOUGH
TO BE ON CAMERA.
>> AND YOU'RE ONE OF THE LEAST
RARE THINGS IN HOLLYWOOD,
A LOUD
MAN.
>> THANK YOU, MISSY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE SO RIGHT.
>> HEY, THANK YOU, KID.
MARTIN, MAY I OFFER YOU OUR
SIGNATURE COCKTAIL,
THE
MARTY-TINI.
>> IT'S JUST LIKE YOU.
SUPER SWEET
AND AFTER A FEW SIPS
YOU'RE LIKE, I GET IT.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S OFTEN PAIRED
WITH OUR STEVE MAR --
TONIGHT
>> I BET IT'S BETTER ON ITS OWN.
>> FIRST THINGS FIRST.
FIVE TIMER
QUICK, NAME THREE CURRENT CAST
MEMBERS.
>> NO IDEA.
>> CORRECT!
AND THAT WAS THE WHOLE TEST.
>> AND, HEY, YOU PICKED A GREAT
TIME TO BE HERE TO JOIN.
THIS IS OUR ANNUAL CHRISTMAS
PARTY.
>> YES.
AND I LOVE THE DECORATIONS, MY
GOODNESS.
>> YES.
THESE ARE ACTUALLY SCRIPTS
THAT WE ALL SABOTAGED
BECAUSE A CAST
MEMBER HAD A BETTER PART THAN WE
DID.
>> I CAN DO THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> OF COURSE YOU CAN.
YOU'RE A FIVE-TIMER NOW.
THE RULES ARE ALL DIFFERENT.
>> ALEC, LOOK AT YOUR ROBE.
>> WELL, THAT'S RIGHT, I'VE
HOSTED 17 TIMES.
HAPPEN TO BE A VERY USEFUL TYPE OF THE SHOW,
THEY CALL ME WHEN
THEY NEED SOMEBODY TO PLAY
A REPUBLICAN.
APPARENTLY BECAUSE OF MY FACE,
MY VOICE
AND MY STRONG DADDY
VIBES.
>> YES.
>> REALLY?
A DADDY VIBE?
>> GO TO YOUR ROOM, TINA.
>> I WONDER WHO THAT IS.
>> HI, EVERYONE.
>> WE HAVE A NEW CAST MEMBER.
WHERE SHOULD I PUT THIS SECRET
SANTA GIFT?
>> OH, I'LL TAKE THAT GIFT.
I HAVE TO PUT MINE UNDER THE
TREE, TOO.
>> NOW, IT'S NOT ANOTHER BOOK
ABOUT WORLD WAR II, IS IT, TOM?
>> NO.
IT'S ABOUT OUTER SPACE.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> WHY ARE YOU WEARING A
BATHROBE?
>> IN A BATHROBE, I'M NOT LIVING
HERE.
>> NO ONE SAID THAT.
>> GOOD.
BECAUSE I'M NOT LIVING HERE.
>> HELLO, MARTIN.
>> HELLO, KRISTIN.
>> I HOPE YOU'RE NOT EXPECTING A
REPEAT OF LAST TIME WE SAW EACH
OTHER.
I'M NOT THAT GIRL ANYMORE.
>> AND I'M NOT THAT FLEXIBLE
ANYMORE.
>> DID YOU TWO HAVE A THING?
>> WE TOOK A HOT YOGA CLASS
TOGETHER WHERE WE MADE LOVE AND
GOT KICKED OUT
AND WE BOTH VOTED
FOR TRUMP.
>> DON'T TELL THEM THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
IN THIS CLUB YOU CAN BE
COMPLETELY HONEST.
ANYONE ELSE WANT TO TRY?
>> I'LL GO.
ANTMAN'S POWERS AREN'T GOOD.
IT'S ME THAT'S FLYING THOSE
DRONES.
ALL OF THEM.
>> I'LL GO.
I NEVER HAD COVID.
I HAVE COVID RIGHT NOW.
>> I'LL GO.
I HAVE WAY TOO MANY CHILDREN.
>> SEE, WE FEEL BETTER ALREADY.
BUT WAIT, IS THIS A FIVE-TIMERS
THINK OR ONLY "MURDERS"
REUNION.
>> IT IS TRUE.
TINA AND PAUL WERE BOTH GUEST
STARS.
ISN'T IT EMBARRASSING WHEN A
SHOW THROWS BIG NAME CAMEOS FOR
CHEAP RATING BOOSTS.
>> IT'S THE WORST.
IT'S THE WORST POSSIBLE
THING.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, MARTY.
HONESTLY, THIS IS SUCH AN
ACCOMPLISHMENT.
>> HELLO, KRISTIN.
>> EMMA.
>> I HOPE YOU'RE NOT EXPECTING A
REPEAT OF WHAT HAPPENED WHEN I
SAW YOU LAST TIME.
>> I'M NOT THAT GIRL ANYMORE.
>> AND I'M NOT THAT DRUNK.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW, I'M GETTING
CLOSE.
>> GOOD.
>> WELL, I JUST HAVE TO SAY THAT
IT IS SO NICE TO SEE EACH OTHER
OUTSIDE OF A SKETCH.
WE CAN ACT LIKE THE DIGNIFIED
SALT OF THE EARTH CELEBRITY
FOLKS THAT WE ARE.
>> NORMALLY YOU WOULD BE
CHUGGING RANCH DRESSING AND
CRASHING THROUGH A TABLE BY NOW.
>> OH, MARTY, FOR SHAME.
BUT EXACTLY.
YEAH.
THIS IS A CLASSY PLACE.
WE DON'T DO ANY OF THAT
SOPHOMORIC COMEDY HERE,
DO WE?
NO.
BUT IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I'D
LIKE TO TREAT MYSELF TO A
COCKATAIL.
>> HI!
SHE'LL BE FINE.
I JUST STOPPED BY TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> JOHN, LOOK AT YOU.
LOOK AT YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT WE DID THAT
SITCOM TEN YEARS AGO.
>> YOU COULD NEVER DO THAT SHOW
NOW.
>> WHY, BECAUSE EVERYONE IS SO
WOKE?
>> NO, BECAUSE IT WASN'T GOOD
AND NO ONE LIKED IT.
>> BUT YOU CAME BACK STRONG.
AND THEN YOU CRASHED AND BURNED.
AND THEN YOU CAME BACK STRONG.
AND WE'RE ALL SO CURIOUS WHAT
WILL HAPPEN NEXT.
>> LET'S RAISE A TOAST, SHALL
WE?
>> OH S THERE ANYTHING
NONALCOHOLIC?
>> DO YOU MEAN DRINKS OR PEOPLE,
BECAUSE EITHER WAY NO.
>> WELL, MARTY, YOU'RE FINALLY
IN THE FIVE-TIMERS CLUB,
WHICH
MEANS WE'VE GOT A LITTLE
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
>> JACKET BOY!
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
>> JIMMY!
>> HI.
I CAN ONLY STAY FOR A LITTLE BIT
AND THEN I HAVE TO GO AND HOST
ANOTHER GAME SHOW AND LAUGH AT
MY OWN JOEX.
>> BUT AT LEAST SOMEONE IS
LAUGHING.
>> YOU GET IT.
WELL, MARTY, U JUST WANT TO SAY
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE FOR THIS MOMENT
SO I WOULD LIKE TO
PRESENT TO YOU THE OFFICIAL
FIVE-TIMERS CLUB JACKET
IN
EXACTLY YOUR SIZE, A WOMEN'S
SMALL.
>> WEAR IT AS A CAPE.
WEAR IT AS A CAPE.
>> THANK YOU ALL FOR BEING HERE.
THIS IS SUCH A SPESH NIGHT.
AND FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART,
I JUST WANT TO SAY,
I LOVE MOST
OF YOU SO MUCH.
AND --
[ LIVE FROM NEW YORK IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT ]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MARTIN
SHORT.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, EVERYONE!
HOW EXCITING THIS MUST BE FOR
ALL OF YOU.
AND TONIGHT, THE BIG "SNL"
CHRISTMAS SHOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THE HOLIDAYS ARE
ALREADY HERE.
BUT WE MUST MOVE THIS MONOLOGUE
ALONG BECAUSE
I HAVE TEN
SKETCHES TO GET TO WHERE I PLAY
AN ELF.
>> ALSO I LEFT MY UBER DRIVER
WAITING.
AND YOU KNOW HOW TESTY MATT
GAETZ CAN GET, SO.
LISTEN TO ME, LISTEN TO ME, NOT
ONLY DO I SPEAK FROM MY HEART,
BUT I SPEAK FROM THE CUE CARDS
WHEN I SAY
THAT I AM SO THANKFUL
TO MY DEAR FRIEND LORNE MICHAELS
FOR ASKING ME TO HOST TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, LORNE.
YOU KNOW, LORNE AND I ARE VERY
CLOSE FRIENDS.
WE'RE KIND OF LIKE TRUMP AND ELON MUSK
WITHOUT THE SEXUAL
TENSION, YOU KNOW.
IN FACT, I'M REMINDED OF LORNE'S
WORDS AFTER EVERY SHOW I'M EVER
HOSTED.
NEXT TIME
TONIGHT I JOIN THE FIVE-TIMERS
CLUB.
>> COME TO THINK OF IT, YOU
KNOW, FIVE MUST BE MY LUCKY
NUMBER.
I MEAN, THIS IS MY FIFTH TIME
HOSTING.
I'M ABLE TO START SEASON FIVE OF
ONLY MURDERS IN THE BUILDING.
>> I OWN FIVE CYBERTRUCKS.
NOT TO DRIVE.
IT'S JUST THEY'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
MY DEAR FRIEND STEVE MARTIN IS
ALSO PART OF THE CLUB.
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN HERE TONIGHT,
BUT HE HAD A CONFLICT WITH ME
NOT WANTING HIM TO BE HERE.
>> AND BESIDES, IT'S REHEARSAL
WEEK FOR "THE MASKED SINGER."
SO, YOU KNOW.
STEVE AND I HAVE HOSTED TOGETHER
BEFORE, BUT YOU KNOW,
HOSTING "S
NL" IS A LOT LIKE SEX.
IT'S GREAT WITH A PARTNER, BUT
SOMETIMES IT'S GREAT TO KNOCK
ONE OUT BY YOURSELF.
THIS WEEK HAS BEEN SO MUCH FUN.
AND THE CAST IS JUST SO
LOVELY --
OH, HI, SARAH.
>> HI, MARTY.
>> IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
>> OH, MARTY, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
I WANT TO HAVE THE HOLIDAY
SPIRIT, BUT ALL I FEEL IS DREAD.
>> DON'T WORRY.
THAT HAIRCUT WILL GROW OUT.
>> I WASN'T  ING ABOUT MY
HAIR.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN.
I GUESS I'M JUST UPSET BECAUSE
THE HOLIDAYS HAVE SUPPOSED TO BE FUN,
BUT EVERYONE HERE IS SO
STRESSED OUT.
RIGHT, GUYS?
>> YEAH.
YOU ALWAYS SEEM SO HAPPY.
>> WE WERE HOPING YOU COULD, I
DON'T KNOW, CHEER US UP?
>> PLEASE, MARTY.
>> PLEASE.
>> WE WOULD LOVE IT, MR. SHORT.
>> SURE.
GATHER AROUND, YOUNGSTERS.
AND KENAN.
THE HOLIDAYS ARE ALWAYS
STRESSFUL
AND SURE, THE WORLD IS
GOING CRAZY,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
I HAVE A SOLUTION.
>> REALLY?
>> FOR THE PURPOSE OF THIS BIT,
SURE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU HOW.
OR I COULD SING IT, THAT IS IF
YOU'D LIKE ME TO?
>> LISTEN UP, CHILDREN.
¶ OH, NO IT'S CHRISTMAS ¶
¶ EACH TRICKED-OUT TREE YOU SEE
PROVOKES ANXIETY ¶
¶ GOOD CHRIST, IT'S CHRISTMAS ¶
¶ WITH YULETIDE STRESS AND DREAD
YOU'RE HEAD'S ABOUT TO EXPLODE ¶
¶ SO YOU NEED A NEW
PRESCRIPTION,
JUST TO GET
THROUGH CHRISTMAS,
TAKE A LITTLE
EDGE OFF, MAKE SENSE OF YOUR
EXISTENCE ¶
¶ YES, YOU NEED A NEW PRESCRIPTION,
TO FLY HIGHER THAN BLITZEN,
DON'T SNORT SNOW AND
DON'T SMOKE ¶HOLLY
¶ HEERS MY PLAN TO MAKE YOU
JOLLY ¶
¶ WHILE MALLS ARE HOPPING,
WE ALL GO DOCTOR SHOPPING FOR
PSYCHIATRISTS ¶
>> OH, DOCTOR, I'M IN DESPAIR
>> WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
>> I HAVE THIS REOCCURRING DREAM
WHERE I'M MEETING ARMY HAMMER.
MOMMA.
THANK YOU.
BENZOS
¶ YES,
OH OR A KETAMINE SPRITZ ¶
OH BOY!
¶ CAUSE YOU NEED A NEW
PRESCRIPTION,
TO QUELL THE
HELTER-SKELTER ¶
¶ SANTA HAS HIS ELVES AND I HAVE
MARTY'S LITTLE HELPER ¶
>> I WANT A BIKE, AN XBOX AND
THE NEWEST iPHONE.
>> GREEDY MUCH, GET LOST, KID!
>> HI, SANTA.
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR
CHRISTMAS?
>> WELL, I WANT WORLD PEACE BUT
I NEED PREPARATION H.
¶ CAUSE YOU NEED A NEW
PRESCRIPTION
AND TAKE IT FROM THIS CROONER,
GET THOSE MEDS
BEFORE THEY'RE OUTLAWED BY RFK JR.
YES YOU NEED A NEW
PRESCRIPTION,
BUT NOTHING FROM
THE SACKLERS ¶
¶ NEED A NEW PRESCRIPTION NOW ¶
OH, LORNE.
YOU SMELL WONDERFUL.
I DIDN'T KNOW JACK DANIELS MADE
COLOGNE.
>> GOD, I'M ATTRACTED TO YOU.
>> YOU NEVER KISS ME LIKE THAT
ANYMORE.
¶ YES, WE NEED TRANQUILIZATION,
PHARMACEUTICAL CORRECTION
AND DRUG INDUCED AMNESIA
REGARDING THE ELECTION ¶
¶ AND PREFERABLY SOMETHING THAT
WON'T KILL MY ERECTION,
WE NEED
A NEW PRESCRIPTION ¶
¶ NOW ¶
>>> WE HAVE A GOOD SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
HOZIER IS HERE,
SO STICK AROUND.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
>>> OH MY GOD.
DAD, JUST PARK.
>> WELL, I'D LOVE TO, MADISON,
BUT THERE'S NO SPOTS.
>> WELL, MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
WE'RE GOING SHOPPING ON
CHRISTMAS EVE AFTERNOON.
>> OH, THERE'S A SPOT.
HOLD ON.
>> WAIT, DAD, DAD, WATCH OUT!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME!
THIS GUY FULLY JUST TRIED TO
STEAL OUR SPOT.
HEY!
THIS SPOT, THIS SPOT IS MINE.
MY SPOT.
>> NO.
IT'S MINE.
MY BLINKER WAS ON.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ARE YOU SERIOUS!
I WAS HERE FIRST.
>> WHAT!
ARE YOU BLIND?
>> ME, ARE YOU BLIND?
>> DAD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING.
>> HE DID A CANE, SO I'M DOING
BRAILLE.
>> I SAW THIS SPOT BEFORE YOU.
>> HA, YOU WISH.
YOU WISH.
>> I SWEAR ON MY MOTHER.
MY MOTHER.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> MY MOTHER IS DEAD.
SHAME ON YOU.
>> I HATE THIS GUY.
DUDE, YOU BLOW.
YOU BLOW.
>> NO, NO, MADISON DON'T.
DON'T.
>> WHAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE THAT.
AND I REALLY DON'T LIKE THAT ONE
HAND WAS DOING THIS.
>> OKAY.
DAD, GUYS LIKE IT, THOUGH.
>> MADISON.
>> THEY LIKE IT.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
SHE'S RIGHT.
>> SHUT UP.
SHUT UP.
JUST GET LOST.
>> I NEED THIS SPOT.
I'M HANDICAPPED.
HANDICAPPED.
>> THAT, THAT IS BULL, BULL,
BULL CRAP, CRAP.
BULL CRAP.
>> NO.
MY BLOOD PRESSURE IS HIGH.
VERY HIGH.
>> YOU ARE SUCH A LIAR.
>> I NEVER LIE.
I'M SUPER-CHRISTIAN.
SUPER-CHRISTIAN.
>> LIAR!
>> YEAH.
SCREW YOU.
>> YOU'RE SUCH A JERK.
A JERK.
>> NO, NO MADISON.
>> WHAT?
>> DON'T DO TWO AT ONCE.
>> OKAY.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST A
HABIT.
>> DON'T SAY THAT.
>> COME ON, MAN!
IT'S ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
LET ME HAVE THE SPOT, YOU
SCROOGE.
>> I'M NOT SCROOGE.
I HAVE A GOOD HEART.
OKAY.
GOOD HEART.
I'M MORE LIKE SANTA CLAUS.
HO HO HO.
>> DAD, WHAT THE HELL!
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO
DO.
I'M SORRY.
>> IF YOU WON'T LISTEN TO ME,
MAYBE YOU'LL LISTEN TO MY WIFE.
>> WELL, I DON'T SEE A WIFE.
DO YOU?
>> DRIVE AWAY RIGHT NOW
OR I WILL KILL YOU NOW!
AND I'LL MAKE YOUR DUMB DAUGHTER
WATCH.
MY RACE WILL EAT YOUR FACE.
OKAY.
SHE HATES YOU, BY THE WAY.
GOT IT!
YOURS
HAPPY HOLIDAYS!
ACT
I GOT IT FOR YOUR SISTER AND THE
COOK BOOK FOR MY MOM
BUT THEY
DIDN'T HAVE SAD DI'S SIZE AT THE
FIRST J. CREW
SO I'LL STOP BY
THE OTHER ONE.
>> MISS, MISS?
EXCUSE ME, MISS.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
YOU DROPPED THIS.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
HEY.
COME WITH ME.
>> OKAY.
SO, WHAT ARE WE LOOKING TO GIVE
HIM HERE?
>> HOW ABOUT A FRESH START.
AN EXCELLENT FIT.
PERHAPS A WATCH TO COMPLETE THE
LOOK?
>> I LIKE THE GOLD.
>> MISS, MAY I ASK WHY YOU'RE
DOING ALL THIS FOR ME?
>> BECAUSE EVERYONE DESERVES A
GIFT AT CHRISTMAS.
SPEAKING OF --
>> OH, THIS IS TOO MUCH.
>> IT'S JUST SOMETHING TO GET
YOU BACK ON YOUR FEET.
GET A HOTEL ROOM FOR A FEW
WEEKS.
AND PLAN YOUR NEXT ACT.
SORRY, EXCUSE ME.
HEY, HONEY.
>> WHERE THE [ BLEEP ] ARE YOU.
IT'S CHRISTMAS EVE [ BLEEP ]
RACHEL.
YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY IS HERE.
>> WELL, I --
>> YOU SAID YOU WOULD BE BACK BY
1.
IT'S 9:30.
WHERE ARE YOU!
>> I'M AT DINNER.
DINNER!
HAVE YOU GONE INSANE!
>> LET ME SPEAK TO HIM.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT YOU TO
TALK TO SOMEONE AND HE WILL
EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
>> YOUR GIRL IS WITH ME NOW, YOU
HEARD?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, SLICK.
YOUR GIRL IS WINING AND DINING
ME, MAN.
SHOOT.
THIS CHICK TALKING ABOUT I NEED
TO GET A HOTEL WITH HER
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, MAN.
BUSTER.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
>> GUESS WHAT TIME IT IS.
IT'S STEAL YOUR BITCH:00.
>> I THOUGHT WE GOT THE GOLD
ONE.
>> YEAH, YOU DID.
BUT IT WAS A BUY ONE, STEAL ONE
FOR FREE.
>> WHO AM I SPEAKING TO?
>> MAN, YOU KNOW ME.
I'M RICARDO THE D. TRAIN DEVIANT DEMONT,
AKA, THE RAINING TRAIN
WITH THE KNOCKOUT TRAIN.
>> OH MY GOD.
GIVE ME THE PHONE!
>> HONEY, I MADE A CHRISTMAS
MISTAKE AND I'M COMING HOME NOW.
I NEED TO GET MY CAR FROM THE VALET,
BUT I PROMISE YOU, I WAS
JUST TRYING TO DO SOMETHING
GOOD.
>> I BELIEVE YOU, BABY.
JUST COME HOME TO US, OKAY?
>> I WILL.
LOVE YOU.
RICARDO --
EXCUSE ME.
DID YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENED TO THE
GENTLEMAN I WAS HERE WITH?
>> OH, YES.
I THINK HE WENT TO GO GET YOUR
CAR FROM THE VALET.
>> WHAT'S THAT OVER THERE?
BOOM.
>> OH, GOD.
IF ONLY I HAD LISTENED TO --
>> FOX NEWS, STAY SMART.
STAY RICH.
HAPPY HOLI -- YOU WISH.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> BUSTER!
>>> LIVE FROM GATE 78 IN
TERMINAL C,
IT'S THE "CHIBO
EXPRESS" CHRISTMAS AIRPORT
PARADE.
CHAOS, MAYHEM
EVERYONE
PARADE
>>> GOOD EVENING FROM NEW YORK
WHICH IS HOW YOU SAY NEW YORK IF
YOU'RE ON PILLS WHICH I AM.
MY NAME IS AGENT CHARTREUSE
HAMILTON.
>> AND I'M UMBERTO.
>> WHAT KIND OF NAME IS THAT?
>> MY PARENTS WERE AFRAID OF
NAMING ME BERTO, SO THEY SAID,
UMBERTO.
LOVE
EXPECTING
CLASSIC
HERE IS ONE NOW.
>> UP FIRST, IT'S A NERVOUS
FLIER WHOSE EDIBLE KICKED IN TOO
EARLY.
>> 1,000 MILLIGRAMS IS LOW,
RIGHT?
BECAUSE THAT'S JUST ONE GRAM.
>> WRONG.
I'LL HAVE WHAT HE'S HAVING.
>> I ALREADY DID.
I'M ON PILLS AND POTIONS, BABY.
>> GIRL, I HATE THAT YOU'RE MY
RIDE HOME.
NEXT UP IT'S A WOMAN WHO'S
SAVING HER STINKY MEAL FOR THE
FLIGHT.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO EAT MY
DAY-OLD TUNA MELT.
AND I GOT A MIDDLE SEAT.
>> NICE.
LET'S CHECK IN WITH OUR PARADE
CORRESPONDENT, KENTON BEAN,
THE
OVERLY AGGRESSIVE DELTA LOUNGE
EMPLOYEE.
>> THANK YOU, UMBERTO.
THE DELTA LOUNGE IS GLITZ.
IT'S GLAM.
IT'S GOT THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
BUFFET YOU'VE EVER BEEN TO.
IF YOU'VE NEVER BEEN TO A
BUFFET.
NO!
>> I THOUGHT I HAD ACCESS TO THE
LOUNGE.
>> NO!
>> YOU'RE NOT  ED
APPROPRIATELY AND DRAKE IS IN
THERE.
>> DRAKE IS IN THE DELTA LOUNGE?
>> IT'S EITHER DRAKE OR JOSH.
I CAN'T TELL THEM APART.
>> THANKS, KENTON.
NEXT UP, IT'S TSA EMPLOYEE WHO
SAYS THE SAME THING 12 DIFFERENT
WAYS.
>> BAG IN THE BIN.
PUT YOUR BAG IN THE BIN.
IF YOU GOT A BAG, GO AHEAD AND
PUT IT IN THE BIN.
>> SIR, HOW YOU GOING TO
CELEBRATE THE HOLIDAYS?
>> BAG IN THE BIN.
>> OH, LOOK WHO'S NEXT, IT'S THE PARADE FIRST
WOMAN WHO
ACCIDENTALLY SAT DOWN ON A
MOTORIZED SUITCASE.
>> HELP!
THIS ISN'T MY LUGGAGE.
CREATE A BARRICADE.
>> LET'S CHECK BACK IN WITH
KENTON.
KENTON?
>> YOU'RE NOT GETTING IN.
>> I'M PAUL RUDD.
>> PAUL RUDD THAT NAME SOUNDS
POOR.
>> I WAS VOTED SEXIEST MAN
ALIVE.
>> COULD SOMEONE HAND ME WATER?
SEXIEST MAN ALIVE?
WELL, WHAT, IS TIM ALLEN DEAD?
>>> NEXT UP IT'S AN AIRPORT
STAPLE.
IT'S WHITE WOMAN WHO IS SOMEHOW
GOING TO MAKE THE FLIGHT ABOUT
HER.
>> I MIGHT SING.
I MIGHT YELL AT A BABY.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO WATCH A
MOVIE ON MY iPAD, NO HEADPHONES.
>> CHAOTIC QUEEN.
NEXT UP THE LEAST NECESSARY
EMPLOYEES IN THE TERMINAL,
IT'S
THE EXPRESS SPA SPONSORED BY
CALM APP MASSEURS.
>> WHAT'S UP.
HOLIDAY DISCOUNT
5% OFF FOR A DRY ASS PUBLIC
MASSAGE.
>> AND FREE UNHAPPY ENDINGS.
>> PLEASE, LET US TOUCH YOU.
>> THEY SHOULD GET A JOB WITH
TSA.
>> YES.
UP NEXT, IT'S A CLASSIC.
IT'S WOMAN WHO WANTS TO JOIN THE
MILE HIGH CLUB AND HER BOYFRIEND
WHO DOES NOT.
>> OKAY.
SO, I'LL SIT IN THE SINK.
YOU KNEEL ON THE TOILET PUT YOUR
HANDS ON THE WALL.
I'LL PUT MY FEET ON THE CEILING.
>> WHY CAN'T WE JUST MAKE LOVE
IN OUR BED.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> YOU HEAR THAT.
IT'S A GATE AGENT WHO'S HAVING
TROUBLE WITH THE NAMES.
>> FLIGHT 663 BOARDING NOW FOR
MIAMI.
I NEED TO SPEAK WITH MY COOL
LITTLE PENIS.
SEE MY COOL LITTLE PENIS AS SOON
AS POSSIBLE FACE TO FACE.
NEXT ON MY STANDBY LIST, I HAVE
GINA-SOWDRY.
I HAVE GINA SOWDRY.
HOPE I'M PRONOUNCING THAT RIGHT.
OKAY.
PLEASE COME TO THE COUNTER GINA
SOWDRY.
NAMES
CHARTREUSE, DID THEY NAME YOU
THAT BECAUSE THEY LOVE THAT
COLOR?
>> NO BECAUSE THEY LOVE
CHARCUTERIE BUT THEY'RE
ILLITERATE.
MING THIS WAY IS PARADE
MARSHALL CAPTAIN SULLY.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE.
I'M HERE TO INTRODUCE THE GRAND
FINALE.
SO LET'S SEE IF I CAN LAND THIS
PLANE.
>> I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT THERE WOULD BE A ROUND
OF APPLAUSE AFTER THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW MY RHYTHM IS ALL OFF.
ANY WAYS, PLEASE WELCOME A GROUP
OF PASSENGERS
WHO JUST ARRIVED
FROM TURKEY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SULLY.
THEY JUST GOT CHEAP COSMETIC
WORK DONE IN TURKEY.
>> OH, YEAH.
MY WIFE IS GOING TO LOVE MY NEW
BOOTY.
>> WELL, THAT'S A WRAP ON THE
CHRISTMAS WEEK AIRPORT PARADE.
BUT REMEMBER --
¶ WE'RE BACK FOR THE SPRING
PARADE
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
HOZIER.
Too Sweet
¶ CAN'T BE SAID I'M AN EARLY
BIRD ¶
¶ IT'S 10:00 BEFORE I SAY A
WORD ¶
¶ BABY I CAN NEVER TELL HOW DO
YOU SLEEP SO WELL ¶
¶ YOU KEEP TELLING ME TO LIVE
ALL RIGHT ¶
¶ TO GO TO BED BEFORE THE
DAYLIGHT ¶
¶ BUT THEN YOU WAKE UP FOR THE SUNRISE
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T GOTTA
PRETEND, BABY NOW AND THEN ¶
¶ DON'T YOU JUST WANNA WAKE UP,
DARK AS A LAKE ¶
¶ SMELLING LIKE A BONFIRE,
LOST IN A HAZE ¶
¶ IF YOU'RE DRUNK ON LIFE, BABE,
I THINK IT'S GREAT ¶
¶ BUT WHILE IN THIS WORD,
I THINK I'LL TAKE MY WHISKEY
NEAT ¶
¶ MY COFFEE BLACK AND MY BED AT
THREE ¶
¶ YOU'RE TOO SWEET FOR ME ¶
¶ I TAKE MY WHISKEY NEAT ¶
¶ MY COFFEE BLACK AND MY BED AT
THREE ¶
¶ YOU'RE TOO SWEET FOR ME ¶
¶ I AIM LOW, I AIM TRUE
AND THE GROUND IS WHERE I GO ¶
¶ I WORK LATE, WHERE I'M FREE
FROM THE PHONE ¶
¶ AND THE JOB GETS DONE, BUT YOU
WORRY SOME, I KNOW ¶
¶ BUT WHO WANTS TO LIVE FOREVER,
BABE ¶
¶ YOU TREAT YOUR MOUTH AS IF
IT'S HEAVEN'S GATE ¶
¶ THE REST OF YOU LIKE YOU'RE
THE TSA ¶
¶ I WISH I COULD GO ALONG, BABE,
DON'T GET ME WRONG ¶
¶ YOU KNOW YOU'RE BRIGHT AS THE
MORNING, SOFT AS THE RAIN,
PRETTY AS A VINE, AS SWEET AS A
GRAPE ¶
¶ IF YOU COULD SIT IN A BARREL,
MAYBE I'LL WAIT,
UNTIL THAT DAY ¶
¶ I'D RATHER TAKE MY WHISKEY NEAT,
MY COFFEE BLACK AND MY BED
AT THREE ¶
¶ YOU'RE TOO SWEET FOR ME ¶
¶ I TAKE MY WHISKEY NEAT ¶
¶ MY COFFEE BLACK AND MY BED AT
THREE ¶
¶ YOU'RE TOO SWEET FOR ME ¶
¶ I TAKE MY WHISKEY NEAT,
MY COFFEE BLACK AND MY BED AT
THREE ¶
¶ YOU'RE TOO SWEET FOR ME ¶
>>> IT'S "THE WEEKEND UPDATE"
WITH COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>> WELL, AS OUR LAST SHOW OF A
WILD 2024
THAT SAW DIDDY GO TO JAIL,
DONALD TRUMP GET
RE-ELECTED PRESIDENT
AND ELON
MUSK APPOINT HIMSELF
CO-PRESIDENT.
>> AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT NEXT
YEAR WILL HOLD, BUT ONE THING IS FOR CERTAIN,
WE'LL SEE ALL THREE
OF THOSE GUYS AT "SN-L'S" 50th
ANNIVERSARY.
>>> LUIGI MANGIONE DROPPED --
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
DEFINITELY WOO.
YOU'RE WOOING FOR JUSTICE,
RIGHT?
LUIGI MANGIONE DROPPED HIS
EXTRADITION FIGHT
AND WAS FLOWN
FROM PENNSYLVANIA TO NEW YORK
TO
FACE MULTIPLE CHARGES
IN RELATED
NEWS, BUMBLE EXPLODED.
>> LUIGI MANGIONE HAS BEEN
PLACED IN THE SAME FEDERAL
PRISON AS SEAN COMBS.
SAID COMBS, CHRISTMAS CAME
EARLY.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT THE
HOUSE ETHICS COMMITTEE VOTED TO
RELEASE ITS REPORT
ON SEXUAL
MISCONDUCT CHARGES AGAINST MATT
GAETZ.
GAETZ SAYS HE'S JUST GLAD HIS
GIRLFRIENDS ARE TOO YOUNG TO
READ THE NEWS.
>>> GEORGE SANTOS HAS ANNOUNCED
A NEW PODCAST CALLED PANTS ON
FIRE.
AND YOU CAN DOWNLOAD THE FIRST
EPISODE FOR FREE.
SIMPLY BY ENTERING YOUR FULL
SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER.
>>> DONALD TRUMP HAS TRANSFERRED
ALL OF HIS SHARES OF TRUMP MEDIA
INTO A TRUST CONTROLLED BY
DONALD TRUMP JR.,
WHILE ERIC WAS
GIVEN SOME BUBBLE WRAP TO POP.
>> BUBBLE WRAP TO POP.
SHUT UP, COLIN.
>> TELL US MORE.
BUBBLE RAPE.
GREAT.
LET'S GET THAT ONLINE.
>>> THE FIRST SEVERE HUMAN CASE
OF BIRD FLU
IN THE U.S. HAS JUST
BEEN CONFIRMED.
BUT DON'T WORRY, I'M SURE THIS
DEADLY ANIMAL DISEASE
WILL GET
HANDLED PERFECTLY BY THE ROAD
KILL KING.
>>> DONALD TRUMP -- DONALD TRUMP
HAS SELECTED HERSCHEL WALKER
AS
HIS AMBASSADOR TO THE BAHAMAS.
WHEN TOLD HE WOULD BE AN
AMBASSADOR,
WALKER SAID,
CORRECTION, I IS BASSADOR.
>>> DISNEY ANNOUNCED THAT IN
2027 IT WILL RELEASE A FULL
LENGTH UEY MOVIE.
YEAH.
IT'S EXCITING
WHERE BLUEY AND
HER FAMILY UNFORTUNATELY MEET
CRUELLA DEVIL.
OVER NEW JERSEY
DRONE SIGHTINGS ACROSS THE
STATE CONTINUE WITH NO REAL
ANSWERS.
HERE TO COMMENT IS A DRONE.
HEY, MICHAEL.
WOW.
INDOORS.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
HOW ARE YOU?
OR SHOULD I SAY, WHAT ARE YOU?
>> OKAY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
I KNOW WHAT I AM, AND I DON'T
HAVE TO EXPLAIN MYSELF TO ANYONE
AT ANY TIME FOR ANY REASON.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
BUT WHETHER OR NOT'S CONTROLLING
YOU?
>> WHO'S CONTROLLING YOU,
MICHAEL?
LOOK, ALL Y'ALL HATE ME BECAUSE
I'M UP.
EVERYONE IS LIKE, IS IT UFOs?
IS IT THE MILITARY?
SIT PROMO FOR "SNL 50."
MEANWHILE, I'M MINING MY
BUSINESS, HOVERING OVER PEOPLE'S HOMES,
MAYBE FILMING THEM.
ALSO WHAT IS SO THREATENING
ABOUT RANDOM MACHINES IN THE
NIGHT SKY?
GOD, IT'S LIKE Y'ALL HAVE NEVER
BEEN TO AFGHANISTAN BEFORE.
WHY ARE YOU IN NEW JERSEY?
>> WHY IS ANYONE IN NEW JERSEY?
OH, RIGHT, BECAUSE THERE'S
BEAUTIFUL NATURE AND GOOD
SCHOOLS.
YEAH.
BET YOU THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO
PLAK SOME MAKE SOME CHEAP
SOPRANO'S JOKE.
NO. PEOPLE LIVE THERE.
HAVE SOME RESPECT.
>> YOU SCARE THEM.
>> JUST BY EXISTING.
EVERYONE SO PARANOID.
ALL THESE DUMB THEORIES.
BETHANY FRANKEL IS GOING SUPER
SANE ON TikTok.
TALKING ABOUT ORBS AND PLASMOIDS
LIKE SHE KNOWS A DAMN THING
BESIDES HOCK MUFFINS AT A
GROCERY STORE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> CHE, ASK YOUR GOVERNMENT?
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
>> THEY'RE JUST MANNED AIR
CRAFTS.
>> WHAT'S THIS OBSESSION WITH
WHETHER I'M MANNED OR NOT.
FOR THE RECORD, I CAN GET A MAN
WHEN EVER I WANT.
OKAY?
TRUST ME.
THERE'S NO PROBLEM THERE.
MANNED, UNMANNED, I MAKE IT
WORK.
ADMIT IT, MICHAEL.
YOU WANT TO STICK YOUR FACE IN
THIS AND ROTOR BOAT ME.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> YES, YOU DO.
>> OKAY.
LOOK, YOU'RE ALL OBSESSED.
GO AHEAD.
ASK ME WHO I PREFER TO HAVE SEX
WITH.
IT'S HELICOPTERS, OKAY.
I LIKE HELICOPTERS.
BECAUSE THEY'RE LIKE ME BUT
LARGER AND LOUDER.
AND THEY BOOK A LOT OF TV WORK.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M DATING THE HELICOPTER
FROM "SUCCESSION" IF YOU MUST
KNOW.
GOD, EVERYONE HATES ME.
YOU ALL POINT AT ME, SHOOT YOUR
LASERS AT ME, HIDE YOUR KIDS
FROM ME.
I FEEL LIKE ALPHA BA FOR REAL
FOR REAL.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HERE IS WHAT I
THINK IS GOING ON.
I'M THE RECEPTACLE FOR
EVERYONE'S ANXIETY AND AGITA
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
FOR WHAT BE A DRONE BUT A MIRROR
TO SOCIETY.
AND POTENTIALLY A KILLING
MACHINE.
BUT FINE.
I'LL BE THE VILLAIN
BECAUSE I'M
THE ONE YOU WANT.
IT'S ME!
¶ IT'S ME ¶
¶ SO IF YOU CARE TO FIND ME ¶
¶ LOOK TO THE JERSEY SKY ¶
¶ AS BETHANY TOLD YOU LATELY,
DRONES ARE ORBS AND PLASMOIDS
CAN FLY ¶
END
¶ AND NOBODY IN ALL JERS
KNOW BETHANY THAT IS OR WERES
IS EVER GOING TO BRING ME DOWN ¶
>> DRONE, EVERYBODY!
BEAUTIFUL.
REALLY HARD TO TELL A JOKE NOW.
>>> UNITED AIRLINES PILOT WENT
INTO THE CAPTAIN TO HUG A PASSENGER
WHO HAD DONATED BONE
MARROW TO HIM.
WHILE THE PILOT ON SPIRITS STOLE
A SLEEPING PASSENGER'S KIDNEY.
>>> A PIZZA SHOP IN TENNESSEE
HAS CREATED CONTROVERSY
AFTER
DECLINED TO CATER A GAY WEDDING.
OKAY.
BUT WHAT IF THEY CALLED IT A
MEAT LOVER'S WEDDING?
>>> A NEW STUDY
SUGGESTS THAT THE MOON
MAY BE
100 MILLION YEARS OLDER THAN
PREVIOUSLY THOUGHT.
OH MY GOD.
RETIRE, BITCH.
>>> A NEW STUDY SUGGESTS THAT
TAKING MORE THAN 1,000 STEPS A DAY
CAN REDUCE THE RISK OF DEPRESSION,
OR YOU CAN END YOUR
DEPRESSION WITH ONE STEP.
>> THAT'S PERFECT FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
>>> WELL, AS YOU CAN TELL FROM
THAT JOKE, IT'S CHRISTMAS.
AND WE HAVE A TRADITION HERE ON
UPDATE WHERE CHE AND I --
YOU'RE APPLAUDING NOW.
WHERE WE GIVE EACH OTHER JOKES
TO READ.
>> YEAH.
WE'RE MAKING EACH OTHER READ
JOKES LIVE ON THE AIR
THAT THE
OTHER PERSON HAS NEVER SEEN
BEFORE.
>> BUT TIME-OUT.
BEFORE WE DO THIS, I KNOW
MICHAEL IS GOING TO MAKE ME TELL
SOME RACIST JOKES LIKE HE ALWAYS
DOES.
SO, THIS TIME, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I WOULD LIKE TO READ ALL
THE JOKES IN BLACK VOICE
SO I DON'T GET IN
TROUBLE.
>> I MEAN, COLIN.
I DON'T MIND.
DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO, MAN.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT BLACK
VOICE IS.
WHERE YOU WOULD BRING THAT UP,
PLEASE, WHY DON'T YOU DO THE
FIRST JOKE.
>>> SO SORRY IN ADVANCE.
>> OH, REPARATIONS.
I WONDER WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
>>> OKAY.
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
Y'ALL KNOW MY GIRL.
Y'ALL KNOW MY GIRL,
KAMALA HARRIS
HELD A TOWN HALL
TALKING ABOUT SHE STILL SUPPORTS
THE IDEA OF SLAVERY REPARATIONS.
WELL, DAMN, GIRL, ME TOO.
BECAUSE WHITE PEOPLE DESERVE OUR
MONEY BACK
FOR ALL THOSE SLAVES
THAT RAN AWAY.
SHIZZ.
I AIN'T AFRAID OF YOU MO FO'S.
>> WOW.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT'S WHAT YOU
THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT BLACK VOICE
WAS.
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS THAT WOMEN
ARE MORE LIKELY TO HAVE AN ORGASM
IF THEY ARE IN TOUCH WITH
THEIR BODY SIGNALS,
SUCH AS
HEART RATE AND BREATHING.
AS OPPOSED TO THE WOMEN I HAVE SEX WITH
WHO JUST HOLD THEIR
BREATH UNTIL IT'S OVER.
OH MY GOD.
>>> WHY?
I WANT TO DEDICATE THIS NEXT JOKE
TO MY BOO'S SCARLETT
JOHANSSON.
OH, NO.
OH MY GOD.
SHE'S SO GENUINELY WORRIED.
HEY, BOO.
YOU'LL KNOW SCARLETT JUST
CELEBRATED HER 40th BIRTHDAY,
WHICH MEANS -- WHICH MEANS I'M
ABOUT TO GET UP OUT OF THERE.
SHIZZ.
>> I THINK THERE'S A LITTLE
MORE, COLIN.
>> THERE'S MORE, OH.
NO, NO, I'M JUST PLAYING.
WE JUST HAD A KID TOGETHER AND
Y'ALL AIN'T SEEN NO PICTURES OF HIM YET
BECAUSE HE'S BLACK AS
HELL.
SHIZZ.
SHIZZ, I AIN'T AFRAID OF YOU MO
FO'S.
>> I AIN'T AFRAID OF YOU MO FO.
>>> "MOANA-II" CONTINUES TO SET
RECORDS AT THE BOX OFFICE.
ME AND MY GOOD FRIEND JEFFREY
EPSTEIN USED TO SAY,
THERE'S
NOTHING LIKE AN ISLAND ADVENTURE
WITH A TEENAGE GIRL.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WOULD NEVER, EVER
SLEEP WITH A
GIRL AS DARK AS MOANA.
AND, HEY, BEFORE WE GO, I WOULD
BE REMISS
IF I DIDN'T ADDRESS
THE ALLEGATIONS OF JAY-Z ON THE
DIDTY PARTIES.
NO, MAN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
SOME PEOPLE ARE AFRAID TO TALK
ABOUT IT, BUT NOT MIKEY THE TRUE
BOMB CHE.
SO HERE IT IS.
JAY-Z IS INNOCENT.
WASN'T EVEN AT THOSE PARTIES AND
I KNOW BECAUSE I WAS.
AND DIDDY, IF YOU'RE LISTENING,
WITH BAD BOYS FOR LIFE,
WHEN IT
COMES TO THE CHARGES AGAINST YOU,
I'LL SAY THE SAME THING I
ALWAYS SAID AT YOUR PARTIES,
I WILL HELP GET YOU OFF.
>> STRANGE THING TO SAY AT A
PARTY.
>>> NAH, FOR REAL, THOUGH.
COSTCO -- COSTCO HAS REMOVED THE
ROAST BEEF SANDWICH FROM ITS MENU,
BUT I AIN'T TRIPPEN.
I BE EATING ROAST BEEF EVERY
NIGHT SINCE MY WIFE HAD THE KID.
>> NO, NO, I'M JUST PLAYING,
BABY.
YOU KNOW I DON'T GO DOWNTOWN.
SHIZZ, THAT'S GAY AS HELL.
>> OH MY GOODNESS, I CAN'T
BELIEVE YOU, COLIN.
FOR
GREG JARRETT.
>> HI.
THANK YOU.
BUT I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
I MISSED MY FLIGHT OUT OF MIAMI
INSTEAD OF A VOUCHER, THEY GAVE
ME A TICKET TO THIS SHOW.
>> MY FRIEND, YOUR ENGLISH VERY
GOOD LOOKING.
>> YEAH, I'M SORRY.
I ONLY KNOW TWO WORDS IN
SPANISH.
TEQUILA AND SHAKIRA.
I HAVE TO PICK A NUMBER?
UNO.
IT'S MIAMI FROSTY THE SNOWMAN.
NO
>> OH, GREG.
YOU KILLED HIM.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO DO.
CAN SOMEONE GIVE ME A HINT IN
ENGLISH OR SOMETHING.
>> OF COURSE.
THE ENGLISH HINT.
>> HELLO, GREGORY.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A FIRST HINT?
LET ME HELP YOU.
THE LANGUAGE THEY'RE SPEAKING IS
SPANISH.
BYE NOW.
>> THAT WAS THE HINT?
WELL OBVIOUSLY I KNOW THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS WHOLE SHOW FEELS LIKE I
CALLED CUSTOMER SERVICE
AND
ACCIDENTALLY PRESSED TWO.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THIS IS INAPPROPRIATE,
BUT I'M GOING TO LEAVE.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE I'M STUCK.
I'LL PICK ANOTHER BOX, I GUESS.
QUARTRO.
>> GREG, IT'S MILLION DOLLAR --
>> A MILLION DOLLARS?
WOW.
>> GREG --
>> IS CHRISTMAS STRONG, IS THAT
WHAT YOU'RE ASKING ME?
>> I'M GOING TO SAY NO,
NO.
CHRISTMAS IS NICE, NOT STRONG.
>> NO.
OKAY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
FUERTE IS STRONG.
WHY DID BABY JESUS JUST PUNCH ME
IN THE NUTS.
I DON'T FEEL GREAT RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL NAUSEOUS AND I'M SWEATY.
>> THE PALMS ARE SWEATY.
ME WEAK MOMMA'S SPAGHETTI, HE
NERVOUS.
GREG.
CRAZY.
>> I REALLY NEED TO GET BACK TO
MY FAMILY.
THEY PROBABLY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE I AM.
>> DON'T WORRY, GREG.
YOU WIN
>> I WON?
WAIT, HOLD ON, WHAT DID I WIN?
>> GREG --
>> MY PRIZE IS A NEW FAMILY?
BUT I DIDN'T EVEN WANT THESE
PEOPLE.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING!
I DON'T WANT THIS!
AGAIN
Fairytale of New York
¶ IT WAS CHRISTMAS EVE BABE
IN THE DRUNK TANK
AN OLD MAN SAID TO ME
WON'T SEE ANOTHER ONE ¶
¶ AND THEN HE SANG A SONG
THE RARE OLD MOUNTAIN DEW
I TURNED MY FACE AWAY
AND DREAMED ABOUT YOU ¶
¶ GOT ON A LUCKY ONE
CAME IN EIGHTEEN TO ONE
I'VE GOT A FEELING
THIS YEAR'S FOR ME AND YOU ¶
¶ SO HAPPY CHRISTMAS
I LOVE YOU BABY ¶
¶ I CAN SEE A BETTER TIME
WHEN ALL OUR DREAMS
COME TRUE ¶
¶ THEY'VE GOT CARS
BIG AS BARS
THEY'VE GOT RIVERS OF GOLD ¶
¶ BUT THE WIND
BLOWS RIGHT THROUGH YOU
NO PLACE FOR THE OLD ¶
¶ WHEN YOU FIRST
TOOK MY HAND
ON THAT COLD CHRISTMAS EVE ¶
¶ YOU PROMISED ME
BROADWAY WAS WAITING
FOR ME ¶
- YOU WERE HANDSOME
- YOU WERE PRETTY
QUEEN OF NEW YORK CITY ¶
¶ WHEN THE BAND
FINISHED PLAYING
THEY HOWLED OUT FOR MORE ¶
¶ SINATRA WAS SWINGING
ALL THE DRUNKS
THEY WERE SINGING ¶
¶ WE KISSED ON A CORNER
THEN DANCED
THROUGH THE NIGHT ¶
¶ THE BOYS OF THE NYPD CHOIR
WERE SINGING GALWAY BAY ¶
¶ AND THE BELLS
WERE RINGING OUT
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY ¶
- YOU'RE A BUM
YOU'RE A PUNK ¶
- YOU'RE AN OLD HAG ON JUNK
LYING THERE ALMOST DEAD
ON A DRIP IN THAT BED ¶
¶ YOU SCUMBAG YOU MAGGOT
YOU'RE CHEAP
AND YOU'RE HAGGARD ¶
¶ HAPPY CHRISTMAS YOUR ARSE
I PRAY GOD IT'S OUR LAST ¶
¶ THE BOYS OF THE NYPD CHOIR
STILL SINGING GALWAY BAY ¶
¶ AND THE BELLS
ARE RINGING OUT
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY ¶
¶ I COULD'VE BEEN SOMEONE
WELL SO COULD ANYONE
YOU TOOK MY DREAMS FROM ME
WHEN I FIRST FOUND YOU ¶
¶ I TOOK THEM WITH ME BABE
I KEPT THEM WITH MY OWN
CAN'T MAKE IT ALL ALONE ¶
¶ I'VE BUILT
MY DREAMS AROUND YOU ¶
¶ THE BOYS OF THE NYPD CHOIR
STILL SINGING GALWAY BAY ¶
¶ AND THE BELLS
ARE RINGING OUT
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY ¶
¶ THE BOYS OF THE NYPD CHOIR
STILL SINGING GALWAY BAY ¶
¶ AND THE BELLS
ARE RINGING OUT
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY ¶
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING FREEFORM'S
25 DAYS OF CHRISTMAS.
WE ALL RETURN TO THE ANIMATED
CLASSIC "A CHARLIE BROWN
CHRISTMAS."
REHEARSAL
>>> STOP DANCING.
STOP DANCING.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> I'M DRAKE TUTTLE, LOCAL
COMMUNITY THEATER LEGEND.
YOUR PRINCIPAL HIRED ME TO
DIRECT YOUR PAGEANT.
>> BUT CHARLIE BROWN IS OUR
DIRECTOR.
>> AND I'M SORRY TO SAY HE'S
DEAD.
>> CHARLIE BROWN IS DEAD?
>> TO ME.
HE'S DEAD TO ME.
BUT ALIVE.
SORRY, I SHOULD HAVE PAUSED
AFTER DEAD.
THAT WAS MY MISTAKE.
THIS IS MY COLLEAGUE, LE'STAT.
YOUR NEW CHOREOGRAPHER.
>> HELLO, I'M GENIUS.
>> FYI, WE USED TO DATE AND OUR
RELATIONSHIP IS VERY WEIRD.
>> DRAKE STILL THINKS I'M IN
LOVE WITH HIM.
>> BECAUSE YOU ARE.
>> YOU HIT ME.
>> STOP IT, YOU BIG QUEEN.
CAN YOU BELIEVE HE'S A TOP!
THIS GUY KNOWS WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
>> NO, I DO NOT.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
FIRST UP.
SOME HOUSEKEEPING.
THERE WILL BE NO LITTLE KID
ACTING IN THIS PAGEANT.
ONLY GOOD ACTING.
FOR EXAMPLE, THIS IS GOOD
ACTING.
OH MOTHER, YOU'RE DRUNK AGAIN.
THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE FROM MY WAY
OF FAKING.
ANY QUESTIONS?
YES, YOU.
>> YEAH, MAY I DROP OUT OF THE
SHOW?
>> NO!
NO.
I WOULD LIKE TO GET A SENSE OF
EVERYONE'S MODERN'S HIP HOP
DANCE SKILLS.
SO YOU OUGHT TO PERFORM THIS
COMBINATION,
ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
YOUR TURN.
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
NO, NO, NO.
STOP, STOP, STOP.
OH, WE HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOOD.
THEY'RE NOT GOOD.
NOW WE HAVE SOME NEWS FOR THE
ENSEMBLE.
AND I'M SORRY, I DON'T KNOW YOUR
NAMES.
BUT YOU DIRT FACE?
>> ME?
MY NAME IS PIG PEN, SIR.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE HEARING YOU,
YOUR NAME IS PIG PENIS?
>> NO, SIR.
IT'S PIG PEN.
>> YOU'RE THE FILTHIEST CHILD I
HAVE EVER, EVER SEEN.
LOCATE THE SHOWER IN THAT HORDER
HOUSE YOU LIVE IN
AND CLEAN
YOURSELF BEFORE TOMORROW'S
REHEARSAL.
THANK YOU, PIG PENIS.
>> PIANO KID, KEEP DOING WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
I LIKE IT.
YOU'RE DEEP IN THE GROOVE.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE USED TO SAY TO
ME.
>> HE GETS IT.
>> I DO NOT.
>> BOY IN THE RED SHIRT.
BOY IN THE RED SHIRT.
WHAT'S WITH THE BLANKET?
>> I LOVE MY BLANKET.
>> RIGHT.
FYI, WE WILL DO OUR BEST TO
ACCOMMODATE
ANY AND ALL CAST
MEMBERS WHO ARE ON THE SPECTRUM.
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST, WE HAVE
A FEW QUESTIONS FOR THE DOG.
>> OH, THAT'S ME.
>> YES.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE JUST SO, SO --
>> COOL?
>> YES.
>> THAT'S IT.
ARE YOU A BOY DOG OR A GIRL DOG?
>> SNOOPY LOOK LIKE A BITCH TO
>> OH, SO YOU'RE A BOY.
NOW HAVE YOU BEEN FIXED.
>> NAH MAN, BECAUSE I AIN'T
BROKEN.
>> OH MY GOD.
YOU'RE A STAR.
>> EXACTLY.
NO OFFENSE TO THE KIDS, BUT
OBVIOUSLY ANYONE WHO COMES WITH THIS SHOW
WILL ONLY BE LOOKING
AT THE BEAGLE WHO CAN PLAY THE
GUITAR.
IT'S OBVIOUS.
>> THAT'S THE SHOW.
EK OKAY, SNOOPY.
YOU SHRED THAT GUITAR AND
EVERYONE GET BEHIND THE DOG AND
SWAY LIKE THIS AND POINT.
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
HOZIER
HANKS.
PAUL RUDD,
TINA FEY,
SCARLETT JOHANSSON, EMMA STONE,
MELISSA McCARTHY,
AND DANA CARVEY AND
THIS BRILLIANT CAST.
LORNE MICHAELS,
EVERY ELEMENT OF
THIS SHOW IT'S A DREAM TO DO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS AND HAPPY NEW
YEAR.