>>> IN RESPONSE TO THE CHAOTIC
SITUATION IN MINNESOTA,
PRESIDENT TRUMP ORDERED WHITE
HOUSE BORDER CZAR TOM HOMAN
TO
TRAVEL TO MINNEAPOLIS AND TAKE
CONTROL OF THE OPERATION.
UPON ARRIVAL, HE MET WITH I.C.E.
UNIT COMMANDERS
TO CLARIFY THE
MISSION OBJECTIVES.
>> ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE, SETTLE
DOWN.
MY NAME IS TOM HOMAN.
NOW I'M SURE A LOT OF YOU ARE
WONDERING WHY GREG BOVINO, THE
LAST GUY, WAS DISMISSED.
I WANT TO STRESS THAT IT WASN'T
BECAUSE HE DID A BAD JOB.
OR PUBLICLY LIED ABOUT THE
SHOOTING OF AN AMERICAN CITIZEN.
OR EVEN, OH-OH, DRESSED LIKE A
NAZI.
IT WAS THAT HE WAS FILMED DOING
THESE THINGS.
AND THE PRESIDENT NO LIKEE THAT.
SO I'M HERE NOW, AND WE NEED TO
TIGHTEN UP.
THAT STARTS WITH REMEMBERING THE
MISSION OBJECTIVE.
NOW, WHO CAN TELL ME WHY WE'RE
HERE IN MINNEAPOLIS?
>> PASS.
>> NOPE, CAN'T PASS.
COME ON, GUYS.
WHAT ARE WE DOING IN
MINNEAPOLIS?
>> THIS COULD BE WRONG, BUT
ARMY?
>> CLOSE.
THAT'S CLOSE.
WE'RE HERE TO DETAIN AND DEPORT
ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS WHO HAVE
COMMITTED CRIMES.
>> THAT IS LITERALLY THE FIRST
I'M HEARING OF THAT.
>> WELL, IT SHOULDN'T BE.
JUST SO I KNOW WHAT WERE YOU
TOLD YOU SHOULD BE DOING?
>> UM -- WILDING OUT.
>> FORGET EVERYTHING YOU WERE
TOLD BEFORE.
WE'RE NOT HERE TO INTIMIDATE,
RACIALLY PROFILE, OR VIOLATE
ANYONE'S RIGHTS.
SO AGAIN, WHAT ARE WE LOOKING
FOR?
>> EPSTEIN FILES?
>> NOPE!
NOPE!
WE ACTUALLY JUST RELEASED THOSE
TO DISTRACT FROM THIS.
WHICH IS IRONIC, BECAUSE WE DID
THIS TO DISTRACT FROM THOSE, SO...
ANYWAY, GUYS.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT DOING THE MISSION,
IT'S ABOUT DOING IT THE
RIGHT WAY.
A LOT OF THE BAD PRESS WE'RE
GETTING IS COMING FROM THE
AGGRESSIVE TACTICS WE'RE USING.
>> AND THE NAZI COAT.
>> YES, THE NAZI COAT, VERY
GOOD.
SO, LET'S TALK ABOUT USE OF
FORCE.
WHEN DO WE WANT TO USE FORCE?
>> RIGHT AWAY?
>> NO.
THINK OF THE OPPOSITE.
>> RIGHT.
PRE-EMPTIVELY.
>> ALSO NO.
IT'S KIND OF A TRICK QUESTION,
BECAUSE WE ACTUALLY DON'T WANT
TO USE FORCE.
REMEMBER, THE JOB ULTIMATELY IS
ABOUT KEEPING AMERICA SAFE
FROM -- WHAT?
>> THIS COULD BE WRONG, BUT --
DON LEMON?
>> THAT IS WRONG, YES.
IT'S CRIMINALS.
>> TEACHER?
>> NOT A TEACHER.
GO AHEAD.
>> UM -- SOME OF THESE PEOPLE
PROTESTING HAVE GUNS.
THAT SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED,
RIGHT?
>> WELL, LET'S FLIP IT AROUND,
HOW MANY OF YOU WENT TO A "STOP
THE STEAL" PROTEST
WITH A LOADED
AUTOMATIC WEAPON?
OKAY.
THAT IS ALL OF YOU.
SO YOU'VE GOT TO DO BETTER.
LOOK, I'M TOM HOMAN, OKAY?
I'M THE -- I'M THE SEPARATING
FAMILIES AT THE BORDER GUY.
I'M THE ON-FILM TAKING A $50,000
BRIBE GUY.
AND Y'ALL ARE MAKING ME LOOK
LIKE THE UPSTANDING, REASONABLE
ADULT IN THE ROOM.
THAT'S CRAZY!
NOW, LET'S OPEN IT UP TO
QUESTIONS, PLEASE.
YES?
>> I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT THE
LOCAL POLICE.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
I WAS HOPING SOMEONE WOULD BRING
THIS UP, BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN
SOME FRICTION THERE.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION ABOUT THE
LOCAL POLICE?
>> UM -- HOW COME I WASN'T
ALLOWED TO BE IN THEM?
>> I'M NOT SURE.
YES, YES, YOU.
>> UH, YES.
SO -- I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT
DESTROYING EVIDENCE.
>> YEAH, LET ME STOP YOU RIGHT
THERE.
YOU SHOULD NEVER, NEVER DESTROY
EVIDENCE.
>> GOT IT.
>> DON'T WINK.
DON'T WINK.
NOW, WHO ELSE HAS A QUESTION?
YES, YOU?
>> YEAH, HOW COME ALL THE FAST
FOOD IN THIS CITY TASTES LIKE
SPIT?
>> IT'S JUST BEST NOT TO THINK
ABOUT THAT.
OKAY.
WE GOT ONE MORE QUESTION.
>> I'M BEING DETAILED TO THE
SUPER BOWL,
BUT I'M LOOKING IN
MY TICKET APP AND I DON'T SEE A
TICKET.
>> RIGHT.
SO YOU WON'T ACTUALLY HAVE A
SEAT.
>> SO WE'RE PLAYING IN IT?
LIKE WHAT?
>> GUYS.
GUYS, NO.
NO.
LET'S RECAP.
WHAT HAVE WE LEARNED TODAY?
>> THIS COULD BE WRONG, BUT --
THAT YOU HIRED A BUNCH OF ANGRY,
AGGRESSIVE GUYS,
GAVE US GUNS,
DIDN'T TRAIN US, SO THIS IS WHAT
YOU WANTED TO HAPPEN?
>> COME ON, MAN, DON'T START
THINKING NOW.
DROP AND GIVE ME 20.
>> HOW ABOUT THREE WITH KNEES
GIRL-STYLE?
>> NEVER MIND.
LOOK.
THE SITUATION OUT THERE HAS BEEN
ROUGH, AND WE NEED TO LOWER THE
TEMPERATURE.
SO LET'S GET OUT THERE, LET'S
SHOW SOME RESTRAINT.
LET'S DO OUR JOB WITHOUT
VIOLATING ANYONE'S RIGHTS AS
AMERICANS.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
>> NO.
>> WELL, I HAD TO ASK.
MAYBE JUST TRY NOT TO GET
FILMED.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
HOST
SKARSGARD!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN --
ALEXANDER SKARSGARD!
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK
YOU, THANK YOU.
I AM INCREDIBLY EXCITED TO BE
HERE TONIGHT,
BECAUSE WE ARE
CELEBRATING 1,000 EPISODES OF
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE!
¶ CELEBRATE GOOD TIMES COME ON ¶
NOW, WHEN I WAS A KID, I LOVED
WATCHING THIS SHOW
FROM MY IGLOO
BACK IN STOCKHOLM.
BUT DURING THESE MONOLOGUES, I
WOULD NEVER FOCUS ON THE HOST.
I WAS MORE INTERESTED IN THE
BAND.
BACK THERE IN THE BACKGROUND.
SOMETIMES LAUGHING.
MORE OFTEN NOT.
BUT ALWAYS OUT OF FOCUS.
NEVER IN THE SPOTLIGHT.
WELL, NOT ON MY WATCH.
CALL ME WILLY WONKA, BECAUSE
TONIGHT,
I'M GOING TO LET THE
LITTLE PEOPLE COOK.
GUYS, GIVE ME SOMETHING.
SEE, I LIKE THAT ONE.
NICE RIGHT THERE.
MIC, PLEASE.
COME
WHAT IS YOUR NAME, GOOD SIR?
>> JAMES.
>> BEAUTIFUL NAME.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN IN THE
BAND?
>> 26 YEARS, BUT
>> THAT'S AMAZING, AMAZING.
HOW ABOUT YOU, IS SIR?
MUST BE PRETTY COOL TO TALK TO
THE HOST, HUH?
>> DEPENDS ON THE HOST.
>> YOU ARE WELCOME.
A FEMALE.
ON GUITAR.
YBANEZ 2000, NO?
>> NO.
>> NO?
THAT'S WHAT I SAID NO.
GREAT BANTER, GUYS.
HEY -- WHO WANTS TO HEAR SOME
FREEFORM JAZZ?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
A LITTLE STRAY SAXOPHONE.
ALWAYS WANTED TO PLAY ONE OF
THOSE.
THAT WAS EASY.
NO, NO, DON'T FOLLOW ME.
FOCUS ON THE LADIES.
POWER
LAGGING
IT FEELS GOOD TO GIVE!
GIVE IT UP FOR THE BAND FOR
REALS.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU.
CARDI B IS HERE.
STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
THANKS
MOM AND DAD.
>> OF COURSE.
>> WE LOVE YOU, WE LOVE YOU.
>> SHOULD WE HEAD TO THE
RESTAURANT?
I'M STARVING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SURE.
>> OH, OH -- WAIT.
WAIT, THERE'S --
THERE'S
SOMETHING I NEED TO TELL YOU ALL
FIRST.
>> OH, OKAY, WHAT IS IT, MOM?
>> IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> I'M ONLY GOING TO SAY IT IF,
AFTER I DO,
YOU PROMISE YOU WILL
NOT REACT.
NO TALKING.
NO FACES.
NO NOTHING.
>> MOM, WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> YEAH, YOU'RE SCARING US.
>> THE THING I'M GOING TO SAY --
IS SHOCKING.
AND IT'S GOING TO MAKE YOU WANT
TO REACT.
BUT I NEED YOU TO PROMISE THAT
YOU WILL NOT.
>> FINE.
>> SURE, YEAH.
>> LET'S DO A PRACTICE EXAMPLE.
I EAT BUGS.
>> MOM.
IS THAT --
>> NO, NO, WHAT DID I SAY?
>> SORRY, SORRY.
>> NO SPEAKING.
NO TALKING.
NO NOTHING.
PRACTICE EXAMPLE.
MY BUTT FELL OFF, I CAN'T FIND
IT.
I DON'T HAVE A BUTT.
OKAY, GOOD.
WHAT I HAVE TO TELL YOU --
IS I MAY HAVE CHANGED MY MIND --
ABOUT TRUMP.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH!
>> STOP IT, STOP IT!
YOU WANT THIS TO BE REAL OR NOT?
>> YES!
>> SURE, YEAH.
>> I FEEL NOW --
LIKE HE MIGHT BE --
BAD FOR OUR COUNTRY.
>> OH, I DO!
>> STOP IT!
WHAT DID I SAY, WHAT DID I SAY?
>> I'M SORRY, MOM, YOU'VE GOT TO
BE JOKING.
>> WE'VE BEEN SAYING THIS SINCE
2016.
>> OH, I'M SORRY I'M LATE TO THE
PERFECT PARTY.
DO YOU GUYS WANT THIS TO BE REAL
OR NOT?
>> YES!
>> YES, ABSOLUTE.
>> WE WANT IT TO BE REAL.
>> THEN GIVE ME GRACE.
I FEEL LIKE -- MAYBE --
SOME OF THE THINGS HE SAYS --
AREN'T TRUE.
>> OH!
>> MOM!
>> BYE, I TAKE IT BACK!
>> MOM, COME ON.
DON'T DO THAT.
>> GUYS, COME ON, CAN'T YOU SEE
THIS IS HARD FOR YOUR MOTHER?
ALSO, I WANT TO REMIND
EVERYBODY, IT IS MY BIRTHDAY.
>> AND GREG, WE ARE GOING TO GET
TO THAT.
AND FOR THE RECORD, YOU LITTLE BRATS,
I DO STILL THINK HE'S A
GOOD BUSINESSMAN.
>> MOM, COME ON.
>> THIS IS WHY NOBODY LIKES YOUR
SIDE!
YOU THINK YOU KNOW EVERYTHING
WITH YOUR MACHO RAPPING HAMILTON
AND YOUR IUDs.
JUST HAVE KIDS ALREADY!
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> MAYBE WE COULD TALK ABOUT
THIS AT RED ROBIN'S.
I'M AFRAID THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE
OUR TABLE AWAY, AND I WANT MY
BIRTHDAY SCOOP.
>> OKAY, MOM, WE'RE SORRY, WE'LL
BE QUIET.
JUST SAY WHAT YOU NEED TO SAY.
>> FINE.
BUT I SWEAR TO GOD --
IF I HEAR A SINGLE "I TOLD YOU SO,"
I WILL GO SEE THE "MELANIA"
MOVIE TONIGHT.
YOU HEAR ME?
>> OKAY.
>> REALLY
>> THEN I WILL SPEAK.
THE THINGS THAT ARE HAPPENING --
NO ONE COULD HAVE SEEN COMING.
I FEEL LIKE -- THE WAY THEY TALK
ABOUT GUNS --
IS DIFFERENT --
FOR DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
THEY MADE ME FEEL WORRIED --
ABOUT TRANS PEOPLE.
BUT NOW I'M REALIZING --
I DON'T REALLY GET WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
I'M STARTING TO WONDER --
IF DRAG QUEENS -- ARE ACTUALLY
HILARIOUS.
OH, STOP THAT, I SEE WHAT YOU'RE
DOING!
STOP IT!
>> ENOUGH, ENOUGH, LEAVE YOUR
MOTHER ALONE.
HER LAPTOP IS OLD, SHE GETS A
DIFFERENT INTERNET THAN YOU.
>> NOT HOW THAT WORKS.
>> THAT IS HOW THAT WORKS, AND
THIS IS VULNERABLE FOR ME, OKAY?
YOU SHOULD UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DID I SAY WHEN YOU CAME
OUT?
>> YOU SAID, IS IT POSSIBLE YOU
JUST LIKE HATS?
>> STILL WAITING ON THE ANSWER,
BABE.
>> PLEASE STOP GETTING YOUR
MOTHER WORKED UP.
OR SHE WON'T DANCE FOR ME
TONIGHT.
DANCE
>> YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE WITHOUT
IT.
>> OKAY, RELAX.
MOM, WE'RE SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE MADE THIS HARD
FOR YOU, AND WE'RE HAPPY THAT
YOU TOLD US.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE SORRY.
>> THANKS, MOM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO DINNER.
PLENTY OF ROOM IN THE
CYBERTRUCK.
>> SELL THAT!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
>>> THE WINTER OLYMPICS ARE A
WEEK AWAY.
NOW MEET SOME OF THE ATHLETES
WHO PUSHED THEMSELVES TO THE
LIMIT OF HUMAN ENDURANCE
FOR THE
CHANCE TO COMPETE AT THE GAMES
IN MILAN.
>> NO ONE SAID IT WOULD BE EASY,
BUT IT'S ALL WORTH IT WHEN I'M
OUT ON THE SLOPES WITH MY BOARD.
>> WHEN I'M ON THE ICE, I FEEL
ALIVE.
IT'S MY PURPOSE.
>> I HATE THE LUGE.
IT'S WAY TOO FAST.
IT SCARES ME TO DEATH AND I
SERIOUSLY HATE IT.
SPORTS
>> I'VE BEEN WANTING THIS MY
WHOLE LIFE.
I'M LIVING MY DREAM.
>> THIS IS A NIGHTMARE.
I HATE THE THING I'M GOOD AT.
>> OVER 2,000 ATHLETES.
BUT ONLY THE BEST OF THE BEST
WILL BRING HOME THE GOLD.
>> I'VE TRAINED FOR THIS SINCE I
WAS 4 YEARS OLD.
>> YOU'VE JUST GOT TO WANT IT.
NO ONE'S BORN THE BEST.
>> IN LUGE, BEING THE BEST IS
SORT OF JUST THE HEIGHT AND
WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION THING.
I HONESTLY THINK A CORPSE THAT'S
MY SAME SHAPE COULD WIN.
>> EVERY ATHLETE BRINGS
SOMETHING DIFFERENT TO THE
TABLE.
>> WHAT MAKES ME UNIQUE?
DEFINITELY MY SLOPE STYLE.
CLEAN
>> MY SIGNATURE MOVE IS
DEFINITELY MY ENGLISH TRIPLE
AXEL.
>> I JUST GO STRAIGHT DOWN LIKE
EVERYONE.
BUT I SCREAM THE WHOLE TIME.
>> AND BEHIND EVERY OLYMPIAN IS
AN EQUALLY DEDICATED COACH.
>> COACHING CLARE HAS BEEN ONE
OF THE GREATEST GIFTS OF MY
LIFE.
>> COACHING GARDI IS A BATTLE.
TRYING TO GET HER ON THE SLED,
GET HER DOWN THE HILL.
GET HER TO STOP FREAKING OUT AND
PRETENDING TO BE SICK, ET
CETERA?
>> I'M SICK!
>> YOU'RE NOT SICK.
>> GO DOWN, GO DOWN.
OH, LOOK AT THAT SPIDER!
>> THE SPORT NEEDS HER.
SHE'S A ONCE-IN-A-GENERATION
SHAPE.
>> THEY'RE NOT JUST PLAYING FOR
THEMSELVES.
THEY'RE PLAYING FOR US ALL.
>> I'M DOING THIS FOR YOU, MOM.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF MY LITTLE
GIRL.
I'VE BEEN CHEERING HER ON SINCE
SHE WON HER VERY FIRST EVENT.
>> AFTER YEARS OF PREPARATION,
IT'S GO TIME FOR THE ATHLETES.
>> I'M LOCKED IN.
NO DISTRACTIONS.
>> FOR COMPETITION, THE NAME OF
THE GAME IS FOCUS.
>> THE NAME OF THE GAME IS TO CONFUSE
AND ULTIMATELY SILENCE
MY SURVIVAL INSTINCTS.
>> SEE IF THEY HAVE WHAT IT
TAKES TO WIN.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU IN MILAN!
>> NOT ME, THOUGH, BECAUSE I'M
SICK, I CAN'T GO.
CAN
>> THE WINTER OLYMPICS IN MILAN.
GO FOR THE GOLD.
>>> ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
I AM THRILLED TO BE BACK IN OSLO,
TO BE DIRECTING THIS
MOVIE, "STENCH OF A FAMILY."
I AM OBSESSED WITH SCANDINAVIAN
CINEMA.
I JUST LOVE HOW YOU GUYS SO
BRAVELY REFLECT
HOW FAMILY LIFE
IS JUST HARROWING.
SO LET'S GO FOR A TAKE, YEAH?
ALL RIGHT.
>> "STENCH OF A FAMILY," SCENE
14, TIGHT ROOM.
>> ALL RIGHT, AND ACTION!
>> LOOK AT ME WITH THIS.
>> FATHER IS DYING UPSTAIRS,
AND YOU DO NOT HAVE THE NERVE TO SEE
HIM?
>> HE WAS A PIG AND A COWARD.
>> BUT I HAVE TO BATHE HIM, NOT
YOU.
I'VE BEEN HERE FOR SIX YEARS
BATHING HIM.
I USED TO PAINT.
BUT NOW I JUST WIPE.
WIPE MY FATHER.
>> YOU CAN LEAVE AT ANY TIME.
YOU JUST WANT TO COMPLERN.
>> AND CUT!
>> OH, MY GOD, I DID SAY
COMPLERN?
THAT'S TOTALLY GOING TO THE
BLOOPER REEL!
>> I DON'T GET NERVOUS.
>> ALL RIGHT, NOT BAD.
DIDN'T EXPECT THIS GIGGLY ENERGY
FOR THIS KIND OF MOVIE.
ANYWAY, LET'S MOVE ON.
THE NEXT SCENE IS WHERE YOU DEAL
WITH YOUR FAMILY'S PAST.
SO QUIET BUT POWERFUL.
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO FOR A TAKE.
>> "STENCH OF A FAMILY" SCENE
22, TIGHT ROOM.
>> AND ACTION!
>> I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY TO
FATHER.
TO ME, HE IS ALREADY DEAD.
GOD
>> I'M NOTHING LIKE HIM.
HE FLUNG OUR MOTHER OFF THE
DOCK.
>> HE LOVED HER.
>> IF HE LOVED HER, THEN WHY
WOULD HE FLING HER INTO THE
FJORD?
>> HOW DARE YOU SAY THIS.
>> I'M LEAVING.
I'M GOING TO --
LINE?
>> KILL MYSELF.
KILL
>> OH, OH GOD!
HOW COULD YOU FORGET THAT?
>> LET'S JUST GO STRAIGHT TO THE
BLOOPER REEL.
>> ALL ABOUT THE BLOOPERS.
>> OKAY, GUYS, GUYS -- "THE
STENCH OF A FAMILY"
IS NOT GOING
TO HAVE A BLOOPER REEL, OKAY?
BUT WHAT WE'RE GETTING IS WORKING,
SO LET'S GO TO THE NEXT
SCENE, OKAY?
>> YES.
>> "STENCH OF A FAMILY" SCENE
30, PACKED ROOM.
>> ALL RIGHT, AND ACTION!
>> THIS HOUSE IS FULL OF GLOOM
AND DOOM.
>> BECAUSE FATHER IS SICK.
HE THINKS HE'S MY MOTHER.
EVERY DAY HE TRIES TO MAKE LOVE
TO ME AND PUSH ME DOWN THE HILL.
>> I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
>> COME HERE.
>> OH, I THINK I'M GOING TO LIKE
IT HERE.
>> AND CUT!
>> BLOOPER REEL!
>> CUT!
>> CUT.
OKAY, GUYS, THAT IS ENOUGH OF
THAT.
PLEASE.
I'M WORRIED WE'RE LOSING OUR
FOCUS HERE.
SO YOU CAN HEAD TO THE NEXT SET
AND FINAL SCENE, OKAY?
LET'S FOCUS UP, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS WHERE YOU SAY
GOOD-BYE TO YOUR FATHER
IN THE
TUB FOR THE LAST TIME.
OKAY?
AND ACTION!
>> FATHER.
WE ARE HERE.
>> HELLO, MY CHILDREN.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
I'VE BECOME A STONE AROUND YOUR
NECK.
>> FATHER, DON'T SAY THIS.
>> ALL THESE YEARS, YOU'VE HATED ME
FOR FLINGING YOUR MOTHER OFF
THE DOCK.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, SHE FLUNG
HERSELF.
I WANTED TO PROTECT YOU FROM THE
TRUTH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
>> IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
SHE JUST DIDN'T LIKE YOU.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME TO DROWN
MYSELF IN THIS TUB.
SO I WILL NO LONGER HAVE TO SMELL THE
STENCH OF A FAMILY.
>> MY ONLY ASK IS, HOLD MY HAND.
AS I GO DOWN IN THE WATER.
>> OF COURSE, FATHER.
>> FETCH!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> WAY TO GO!
>> THAT'S A BLOOPER!
- BLOOPER!
IMMIGRANT DAD
ANTONIO GONZALES HERNANDES
SUAREZ.
>> HELLO, HELLO, HELLO
AND WELCOME TO "THE IMMIGRANT DAD
TALK SHOW."
THIS IS THE SHOW WHERE WE TALK
ABOUT OUR CHILDREN.
THE ONES WE LOVE AND THE SONS AS
WELL, HA HA HA!
BEFORE WE START, FOR ALL THE
WHITE PEOPLE
THAT ARE SAD ABOUT
THE IMMIGRANTS GETTING DEPORTED --
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL BE BACK, HA HA HA!
NO, TODAY, MY FIRST GUEST IS MY
NEIGHBOR FROM FINLAND.
PLEASE WELCOME HEIKE HONNKONING.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE, HEIKE.
>> SHOULD I ALSO SHOW MY
PASSPORT?
>> NO, BUDDY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SHOW YOUR PASSPORT.
YOU LOOK LIKE IF A RACIST GUY DRAW
SOMETHING THAT HE LIKE.
ANYWAY.
IT'S TIME FOR OUR FIRST SEGMENT.
NAME THAT PUNISHMENT.
HEIKE, LET'S SAY YOUR SON IS
CAUGHT SMOKING MARIJUANA IN THE
SCHOOL.
HOW YOU PUNISH HIM?
>> I'D KNEEL DOWN, LOOK INTO HIS SOUL,
AND SAY, "THE SHAME IS
YOURS TO LIVE WITH."
OKAY.
SO YOU TALK TO HIM?
I DON'T TALK, BUDDY, I SHOOT.
>> OKAY.
IS TIME TO BRING OUT MY NEXT
GUEST.
HE'S ANOTHER FATHER IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
PLEASE WELCOME KEVIN!
>> HI.
HOLA, JOAQUIN.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I'M
THINKING ABOUT YOUR PEOPLE LATELY,
AND I WANTED TO DO
SOMETHING TO HELP.
SO TA-DA!
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MAN.
THAT SHIRT IS GOING TO FIX
EVERYTHING.
ANYWAY.
IT'S TIME FOR OUR NEXT SEGMENT
CALLED, "HOW DO YOU HANDLE
THAT?"
ARGUING WITH YOUR WIFE.
WHAT DO YOU DO, HEIKE, WHEN YOU
AND YOUR WIFE HAVING AN
ARGUMENT?
>> YES.
WE STAY SILENT.
VERY INTENT.
THEN ONE DAY, FINALLY,
WE DIE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S SPOOKY, HEIKE.
ME AND MY WIFE, WE DON'T DO
THAT.
WE SCREAM, SCREAM, SCREAM, AND
THEN IT GET QUIET.
AND THEN I SAY, YOU WANT TO HAVE
SEX WITH ME, BABY?
AND USUALLY SHE SAY NO.
KEVIN, HOW DO YOU HANDLE THIS?
>> WELL, IT'S FUNNY YOU BRING
THAT UP.
RECENTLY, ME AND MY WIFE GOT
INTO A LITTLE TIFF
BECAUSE SHE
THINKS I'M TOO AFFECTIONATE WITH
OUR SON.
BUT THAT IS NOT TRUE.
RIGHT, CONNER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE BEST DAD EVER.
>> ONLY BECAUSE YOU'RE THE BEST
SON EVER.
NO, NO!
NO, NO, NO!
DON'T DO IT HERE!
SORRY
>> I MEAN, I'M SURE YOUR DADS
SHOWED AFFECTION TO YOU,
RIGHT,
HEIKE?
>> ONE TIME, ME AND MY FATHER
WERE SITTING IN A SAUNA.
AND OUR KNEECAPS ACCIDENTALLY
TOUCHED.
AND HE SAID, "TELL NO ONE OF
THIS."
>> I TOLD YOU, TELL NO ONE OF
THIS.
>> FORGIVE ME, FATHER.
>> THE SHAME IS YOURS!
LIVE WITH IT!
>> WHITE PEOPLE, VERY
INTERESTING.
THEY NEVER SCREAM, YOU KNOW?
THEY JUST PUSH IT DOWN, DOWN,
DOWN.
AND THEN ONE DAY, THEY KILL
THEIR WIFE.
ME AND MY WIFE, WE HAVE A
BEAUTIFUL RELATIONSHIP.
BECAUSE I DO WHATEVER I WANT.
BECAUSE IT'S MY HOUSE, AND IT'S
MY RULES.
>> JOAQUIN!
DRIVEWAY
MY CAR
>> I'M SORRY, BABY.
>> WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
>> OH NO.
>> BABY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO
ME, BABY?
THESE ARE MY FRIENDS.
NO, NO, NO!
>> WHITE PEOPLE IN MY HOUSE.
- SORRY
- KILL
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
SMOKE
SMOKING IN MY HOUSE?
HAVING THESE PEOPLE EAT MY FOOD?
SICK OF YOU.
>> DO YOU WANT TO HAVE SEX,
BABY?
OH, MY GOD, OKAY.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE
TODAY FOR "IMMIGRANT DAD TALK
SHOW."
DINE
DO WHATEVER YOUR WIFE SAY.
VIKING RAID
SAVE
The gods have smiled on us.
>> WHERE IS YOUR GOD, CHRISTIAN?
MINE ARE IN ASGAARD!
>> YOU HAVE WON A GREAT BATTLE.
>> I'M PROUD TO CALL YOU MY
YARROW.
>> AS AM I.
>> AND I AM PROUD TO LEAD YOU
ALL.
TONIGHT WE FEAST!
>> I'M GOING TO EAT IN THE BOAT.
>> ARE YOU OKAY, EIFAR?
>> IT'S FEELING A LITTLE LEFT
OUT.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> YEAH.
I FEEL LIKE THE GROUP IS GETTING
KIND OF CLIQUEY.
>> CLIQUEY?
>> I'M JUST -- ALONE.
COOL, THAT'S GREAT, FINE.
>> WE HAD NO IDEA.
WHAT DID WE DO TO MAKE YOU FEEL
LIKE THAT?
>> LITTLE STUFF.
LIKE RAGNAR DURING THE RAIDS,
I
SAW YOU AND SNORR CUTTING A GUY
IN HALF.
AND I WAS STANDING RIGHT NEXT TO
YOU READY WITH MY SWORD,
AND NO
ONE EVEN THOUGHT OF LIKE,
HEY,
AT SOME POINT MAYBE YOU WANT TO
JOIN US?
>> I'M SORRY, MAN.
>> AND THEN, LIKE, THIS IS MAYBE
KIND OF STUPID.
BUT WHEN WE WERE PLAYING
FOOTBALL, NOBODY PASSED IT TO
ME.
MAYBE I'M OVERREACTING, BUT I
FEEL LIKE THIS WEIRD TENSION IN
THE GROUP.
>> AND I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO FINISH
SEWING A GOAT HEAD ON THIS MONK.
>> THIS IS WHY I DIDN'T WANT TO
BRING IT OUT, I DIDN'T WANT TO
BUM EVERYONE OUT.
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
>> IT'S HARD TO BE HAPPY WHEN
YOU REALIZE YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
LIKE A FIRST-CLASS A-HOLE.
>> NO-PENIS, STOP.
I'M OVER IT.
LET'S SKIN THIS CHRISTIAN rodent ,
MAKE A HAT OUT OF HIS SKIN, STAY
HOME, AND FORGET ABOUT THE WHOLE
THING, OKAY?
>> NO.
MAKE A HAT OUT OF ME?
IT'S NOT GOING TO SOLVE WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH THE GROUP.
>> THIS CHRISTIAN IS RIGHT.
>> FIRST TIME FOR EVERYTHING.
>> THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
BUT I THINK IVAR, MAYBE SOME OF
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING
IS JEALOUSY.
>> JEALOUSY -- OF YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> WE WORSHIP YOU, MAN.
>> ANY COLDNESS YOU FELT WASN'T
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T LIKE YOU
BUT
BECAUSE WE WERE AFRAID YOU
WOULDN'T LIKE US.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST.
>> CUT TO ME TELLING MY WIFE MY
HERO THINKS I'M THE BEST.
SHE'S LIKE, YEAH, OKAY, LIAR.
>> SHUT UP!
I'M SO NOT YOUR HERO.
>> YOU'RE EVERYONE'S HERO.
WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER, I HAD A
RUNE OF YOU ON MY BEDROOM WALL.
>> SAME.
DOING THAT COOL POSE.
>> WHAT COOL POSE?
YOU MEAN THIS COOL POSE?
>> YES!
>> LEGEND, LEGEND.
>> SO EMBARRASSING.
IS MY FACE RED?
>> YES.
You're covered in blood.
>> THE ONLY CLIQUE WE WANT TO BE
IN IS YOURS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, NOW THAT I
FEEL MORE CONFIDENT,
I'M READY
TO SHOW YOU ALL MY NEW
HAIRSTYLE.
BOOM.
>> UM -- PRETTY COOL.
Stop laughing!
-I love it!
-It looks great.
>> SO GOOD.
>> COOL.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
LADIES
Bodega Baddie
Bodega baddie, hot as a belly, nigga, say what? (What?)
¶ GOOD-LOOKIN' BADDIE
HE WANNA TREAT ME
JUST LET THE STREETS BE ¶
¶ HE WANNA DROP THAT
TELL YOU MY ADDY
BITCH I LOOK GOOD
ON A DAY-TO-DAY ¶
¶ THAT'S WHY
I GOT BITCHES LIKE
QUÉ LO QUE ¶
¶ TEXTIN' MY PHONE
MY BETTER DAY
NOW WE MISSIONARY
TALKIN' FACE TO FACE ¶
¶ EL DIABLO I'M LOCA
BOW TIE
¶ DIAMONDS DANCING LIKE SOCA
LIKE MY -- BAT
SAMMY SOSA WHOO
¶ I'M THE REALER
SIPPIN' TEQUILA
BEEN AN EATER
-- MY LIL' BOO ¶
¶ PAPARAZZI CATCHIN' HIM
TOP ME
OH CAN'T STOP ME
DAMN WHAT A VIEW ¶
¶ CHECK GOT RIPPED OUT
I GOT -- DOWN
THIS HOTEL ROOM
LOOK LIKE A SHOE ¶
¶ ONLY TIME
THESE -- MAKE SENSE TO ME
IS WHEN I PUT THEM ON MUTE ¶
¶ BITCH SO YEAH
I'M LIKE SELENA
YOU CAN TELL
BY MY DEMEANOR ¶
¶ CHECK THAT --
THAT TIME I SEEN HER
TOLD HER
DAME MÁS GASOLINA ¶
WEEKEND
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>>> WELL, LET'S START WITH SOME
GOOD NEWS TONIGHT.
IT WAS REPORTED THAT JUST 20
MINUTES AGO, DRY JANUARY FINALLY
ENDED.
LET'S HOPE IT'S A WET-A IS. S
FEBRUARY.
>>> MEANWHILE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS CHANGING THINGS UP IN MINNESOTA
TO CALM THE RECENT
VIOLENCE AGAINST HIS POLL
NUMBERS.
BORDER PATROL OFFICIAL GREGORY BOVINO,
WHO WAS INCREDIBLE IN
ONE BATTLE AFTER ANOTHER --
HAS BEEN REMOVED FROM OVERSEEING
THE MINNEAPOLIS I.C.E. OPERATION,
AND HOPEFULLY HE WAS
REMOVED I.C.E. STYLE THROUGH THE
BROKEN WINDOW OF HIS CAR.
BOVINO WAS REPLACED BY TOM HOMAN,
SEEN HERE JUST THINKING
ABOUT BAD BUNNY'S HALFTIME SHOW.
CALL ME CRAZY, BUT I DON'T SEE
THIS GUY CALMING THINGS DOWN.
THIS FEELS LIKE TRYING TO QUIT
COCAINE BY TAKING UP CRACK.
>>> TOM HOMAN CALLED ON LOCAL
LEADERS IN MINNEAPOLIS
TO WORK
WITH I.C.E. AGENTS TO TONE DOWN
THE DANGEROUS RHETORIC,
BECAUSE
ALL THAT RHETORIC JUST DISTRACTS
AGENTS FROM THEIR MAIN AIM,
ANYONE FILMING.
>>> HOMELAND SECURITY'S INITIAL
REVIEW OF THE ALEX PRETTI SHOOTING
DOES NOT SAY THAT HE
ATTACKED OFFICERS,
WHICH
CONTRADICTS KRISTI NOEM'S
CLAIMS.
BUT NONE OF THAT REALLY MATTERS
TO KRISTI NOEM.
SHE'LL OPEN FIRE, EVEN IF YOU'RE
A GOOD BOY.
>>> SENATE DEMOCRATS ARE SAYING
THEY WILL ONLY VOTE TO FUND THE GOVERNMENT
IF I.C.E. FOLLOWS NEW
RULES, INCLUDING REMOVING THEIR FACE MASKS,
WHICH WOULD KEEP
AGENTS FROM GETTING FIRED FROM THEIR OTHER JOBS,
LIKE "WEEKEND
UPDATE."
>> I DON'T LIKE HOW MUCH YOU
JUST ASSUMED
THAT WOULD BE
NORMAL AND LAUGH AT IT.
>>> MINNESOTA GOVERNOR TIM WALZ
COMPARED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S IMMIGRATION CRACKDOWN
TO THE NAZI OCCUPATION
DESCRIBED "THE DIARY OF ANNE
FRANK."
REMEMBER THIS ADMINISTRATION HAS
ALWAYS IGNORED
THE STORIES TOLD
BY YOUNG GIRLS.
>>> IT WAS REPORTED THAT I.C.E.
AGENTS WILL HAVE A SMALL SECURITY ROLE
AT THE WINTER
OLYMPICS IN ITALY.
OH, LORD, SAID THE JAMAICAN
BOBSLED TEAM,
NO!
FBI SEARCHED THE COUNTY ELECTION HUB IN GEORGIA
LOOKING FOR BALLOTS TO
BACK UP PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FALSE CLAIM
THAT THE 2020 ELECTION WAS
RIGGED.
JESUS, MAN.
LET IT GO.
I MEAN, EVEN HITLER STOPPED
TRYING TO GET INTO ART SCHOOL AT
SOME POINT.
>>> THIS WEEK, A DOCUMENTARY
ABOUT MELANIA TRUMP DEBUTED IN
THEATERS.
IT'S TITLED "WICKED FOR REAL."
>>> "MELANIA" WAS DIRECTED BY
RUSH HOUR DIRECTOR BRETT RATNER,
WHICH EXPLAINS THIS
SCENE.
>> YOU SPEAK-A ANY ENGLISH?
YOU UNDERSTAND THE WORDS THAT
ARE COMING OUT OF MY MOUTH?
>>> OFFICIALS IN LONDON
ANNOUNCED THEY WILL CREATE A NEW
NATIONAL POLICE FORCE
THAT'S
BEING CALLED THE BRITISH FBI.
IT WILL BE RUN BY THE BRITISH
EQUIVALENT OF KASH PATEL,
MR.
BEAN.
>>> LAST SUNDAY, NEW YORK GOT A
FOOT OF SNOW AND FREEZING
TEMPERATURES
HAVE CONTINUED ALL
WEEK.
HERE TO COMMENT IS OUR NEW
WEEKEND UPDATE WEATHER
CORRESPONDENT, SARAH SHERMAN.
>> HI, COLIN.
I'M HERE LIVE OUTSIDE OF
ROCKEFELLER CENTER
WHERE
CONDITIONS ARE VERY, VERY COLD.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M SARAH
SHERMAN.
NOW BACK TO YOU, COLIN.
>> THAT CAN'T BE IT.
YOU'RE OUR BRAND-NEW WEATHER
CORRESPONDENT.
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE TO SAY?
>> YEP.
IT'S COLD, THERE'S SNOW,
AND I
DEEPLY REGRET DOING THIS.
LOOK, IT'S SO COLD EVEN THE
PIGEONS ARE FROZEN,
CHECK IT
OUT.
P.E.T.A., BEFORE YOU ALL BLOW UP MY DMs,
THIS PIGEON WAS A
RACIST.
THROWING IT BACK TO YOU, COLIN.
NOW BACK TO YOU, COLIN.
>> CAN YOU JUST PLEASE DO THE --
JUST TELL US SOMETHING ABOUT THE
WEATHER, HOW MANY DEGREES IS IT
OUTSIDE?
>> FINE.
THE TEMPERATURE IS HOY YOU SAY
YOU LIKE YOUR WOMEN --
20 BUT IT
FEELS LIKE 15.
>> GOOD LORD.
I TOLD YOU THAT IN CONFIDENCE.
I DID NOT SAY THAT, I DID NOT.
LISTEN, IT'S NOT MY FAULT YOU
DIDN'T WEAR A WARMER COAT.
>> IT IS YOUR FAULT.
YOU ORDERED ME --
HEARD NOT ONE "WOO" IN THE
AUDIENCE.
OH, STOP.
YOU ORDERED ME TO WEAR SOMETHING
THIN IN THE COLD.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED MY NIPPLES
TO BE STANDING AT ATTENTION
LIKE
TWO WEST POINT GRADUATES.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO USE MY
NIPS AS PULL-UP PEGS
LIKE IN
AMERICAN NINJA WARRIOR.
COLIN, YOU SAID, I'M QUOTING YOU ON THIS --
YOU SAID YOU WANTED MY NIPS
"HARDER THAN I WAS
DURING CARDI B'S FIRST SONG."
>> I DID NOT SAY THAT.
>> OH, SHUT UP.
JUST LET ME INSIDE.
I'M LITERALLY SO COLD, I HAD TO
PUT HAND WARMERS IN MY
UNDERWEAR, OKAY?
IT'S SO STEAMY DOWN THERE,
MY CRABS ARE GETTING COOKED INTO A
FULL-ON SEAFOOD BOIL.
ALL YOU NEED IS SOME GARLIC
BUTTER.
>> AND MAYBE YOU COULD INCLUDE
SOME OLD BAY AND A COUPLE OF
BOILED EGGS?
>> EWW!
HEY, SIR.
SIR, WILL YOU LET ME IN?
I'M LOCKED OUT.
COLIN LOCKED ME OUT.
>> OH, SORRY.
I'M OFF DUTY TONIGHT.
RUDE
>> NOW BACK TO YOU, COLIN!
>> SARAH SHERMAN, EVERYONE.
>> WEIRD DUDE, MAN.
>>> A JUDGE HAS RULED THAT LUIGI
MANGIONE
WILL NOT FACE THE DEATH
PENALTY.
UNLESS HE HAS A PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION.
THAT'S A THINKER.
>>> YE TOOK OUT A FULL-PAGE AD
IN THE JOURNAL
APOLOGIZING FOR
HIS PAST ANTI-SEMITIC COMMENTS,
SAYING THEY WERE DUE TO AN
UNDIAGNOSED BRAIN INJURY
FROM A
CAR CRASH 25 YEARS AGO.
DAMN.
EVEN WHEN IT COMES TO EXCUSES,
HE'S A CREATIVE GENIUS.
>>> COOPER FLAGG OF THE DALLAS
MAVERICKS HAS SET A NEW NBA RECORD
FOR SCORING THE MOST
POINT BY A TEENAGER IN A GAME.
NOT A GREAT START TO BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
>>> WAFFLE HOUSE ANNOUNCED THAT
THEY WILL ONCE AGAIN BE TAKING
RESERVATIONS FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY.
AND FELLAS, WAFFLE HOUSE IS THE
PERFECT PLACE TO GET DOWN ON ONE KNEE AND SAY,
"I'VE BEEN
STABBED!"
>>> A NEW STUDY FINDS BY THE
YEAR 2035, NEARLY HALF OF
AMERICAN ADULTS WILL BE OBESE.
HEY, AS LONG AS IT'S THE BOTTOM
HALF, BABY.
YOU DON'T LIKE THAT ONE?
COME ON, MAN.
>>> KEURIG ANNOUNCED A RECALL OF
MORE THAN 80,000 McDONALD'S
BRAND DECAF COFFEE PODS BECAUSE
THEY ACTUALLY CONTAIN CAFFEINE.
SO IF YOU BREW McDONALD'S DECAF
AT HOME --
JESUS, MAN.
>>> SHA'CARRI RICHARDSON WAS
ARRESTED FOR ALLEGEDLY DRIVING
MORE THAN 100 MILES AN HOUR.
WHAT'S CRAZY IS HER CAR IS
FLINTSTONES STYLE.
>>> EXPERTS ARE WARNING THAT
ASKING A PERSON "HOW ARE YOU" IS
A USELESS WAY TO START A
CONVERSATION.
WHICH IS WHY I OPEN WITH "HOW
MUCH?"
>>> A U.P.S. DRIVER IN
CALIFORNIA RESCUED A
101-YEAR-OLD WOMAN FROM HER
BURNING HOME BY USING HIS U.P.S.
TRAINING TO TOSS HER VIOLENTLY
ONTO THE PORCH.
>>> THE SUPER BOWL IS A WEEK
AWAY WITH THE PATRIOTS AND
SEAHAWKS GOING HEAD TO HEAD.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS TWO
PEOPLE WHO JUST HOOKED UP.
>> DOES MY HAIR LOOK OKAY?
>> YOU'RE AMAZING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU GUYS
BACK.
SO YOU'RE HERE TO TALK ABOUT THE
SUPER BOWL?
>> YES, YES.
WE ARE HERE TO DISCUSS THE SUPER
BOWL.
THE PATRIOTS AND SEAHAWKS PLAYED
EACH OTHER IN THE SUPER BOWL IN
2016.
>> IT'S ONE THING TO PLAY A TEAM
ONCE, BUT TO GET ANOTHER CHANCE
TO PLAY THEM AGAIN -- THAT'S
JUST OUT OF THIS WORLD.
>> UH-HUH, YEAH.
SO, HOW DO YOU PICTURE THIS
SECOND TIME PLAYING OUT?
>> WELL, LOOK.
THE SEAHAWKS HAVEN'T WON THE
SUPER BOWL IN QUITE SOME TIME,
SO THEY JUST NEED TO GET OUT
THERE ON THE FIELD AND SAY TO
THE PATRIOTS, HEY!
REMEMBER ME?
>> HOW COULD I FORGET?
>> OKAY.
AND THEN WHAT?
>> UM -- AND THEN -- MAYBE THE
SEAHAWKS SAY -- ARE WE DOING
THIS AGAIN?
>> AND -- MAYBE THE PATRIOTS ARE
LIKE -- I WANT TO SO BAD.
>> BUT MAYBE THE SEAHAWKS ARE
SCARED BECAUSE -- THEY HAVEN'T
BEEN TO THE SUPER BOWL, GOSH --
NOT SINCE JASON.
>> I'M SORRY, WHO'S JASON?
HE'S A PLAYER?
>> HA.
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THE SEAHAWKS FAMOUSLY LOST ON
THE 1 YARD LINE IN 2015.
DO YOU THINK THIS GAME WILL BE
THAT CLOSE?
>> YEAH, LOOK, FOOTBALL IS
FAMOUSLY A GAME OF INCHES.
EVERYBODY WANTS TO GO FOR SEVEN.
BUT -- SOMETIMES IT'S BETTER TO
TAKE THE THREE.
>> THREE?
>> ONE.
>> GOD, ONE?
>> LOOK, COLIN.
THESE ARE TWO GREAT TEAMS.
AND THERE'S NO DOUBT IT WILL BE
BACK AND FORTH ALL NIGHT.
>> 100%.
I PREDICT THAT THE PATRIOTS WILL
BE ON TOP FOR THE FIRST HALF.
THEN AT SOME POINT, THE SEAHAWKS
WILL COME FROM BEHIND AND --
DOMINATE THE PATRIOTS FOR A
LITTLE WHILE.
>> YEAH.
THEN MAYBE THE PATRIOTS GET
TIRED AND ASK THE SEAHAWKS TO
PLAY THEMSELVES FOR A LITTLE
WHILE.
OR THE PATRIOTS GO WATCH ON THE
SIDELINES.
>> OKAY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE SUPER
BOWL, COLIN.
IT'S THE BIGGEST GAME OF THE
YEAR.
SO YOU KNOW, WHATEVER HAPPENS,
ALL I KNOW IS -- SOMEONE'S
GETTING A RING.
>> YOU THINK THAT SOMEONE WILL
GET A RING?
>> OH, WOW.
WELL, PROBABLY NOT LIKE THAT
NIGHT.
>> I DIDN'T SAY THAT NIGHT.
>> LOOK, I THINK THE PATRIOTS
JUST THOUGHT THIS WAS, LIKE,
CHILL.
>> OH, OH, OKAY.
OH, THE PATRIOTS THOUGHT IT WAS
SUPER CHILL.
THEY THOUGHT THE SUPER BOWL WAS
CHILL, OKAY.
WELL.
I THINK IF THE SEAHAWKS KNEW
THAT, THEY WOULDN'T HAVE DONE
THE TUSH PUSH IN COLIN'S
DRESSING ROOM.
>> MY DRESSING ROOM AGAIN?
>> THE TUSH PUSH?
IF I RECALL, THE SEAHAWKS CALLED
THAT PLAY.
THE PATRIOTS WERE ACTUALLY
SCARED TO DO IT BECAUSE THEY'D
ONLY EVER SEEN IT ON FILM.
>> THE SECOND THE SEAHAWKS
MUTTERED TUSH PUSH, THE PATRIOTS
SCORED --
>> OKAY.
OH, MY GOSH.
TWO PEOPLE WHO JUST HOOKED UP.
FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M COLIN
JOST.
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE, GOOD NIGHT!
>> THANK YOU GIRLS FOR COMING
OVER TO HANG WITH AGNES.
SHE HASN'T REALLY HAD A CHANCE
TO MEET ANY OTHER KIDS SINCE WE
MOVED HERE FROM IOWA.
RIGHT, AGNES?
DON'T BE SHY, COME ON.
>> STOP IT, MOM.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME, MOM.
>> COME ON, SIT.
BE NICE.
>> HI, GUYS.
>> HI, AGNES.
>> I'M AGNES.
>> OH, OKAY.
WELL, I'M GOING TO GET OUT OF
YOUR HAIR.
YOU GIRLS HAVE FUN.
CALL ME IF YOU NEED ME, I'LL BE
DRINKING IN THE KITCHEN.
>> THANKS.
>> BYE, MOM.
>> AGNES, WHAT DID YOU DO BACK
IN IOWA FOR FUN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, USUAL STUFF.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, PLAY.
WATCH CARTOONS.
HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
>> I LOVE CARTOONS.
HAVE YOU SEEN BLUEY?
>> NO.
>> YOU DON'T WATCH BLUEY?
>> NO, I'VE NEVER SEEN IT.
>> NOT EVEN ONCE?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
>> YOU'VE NEVER SEEN BLUEY?
LIKE, HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
>> I SAID I NEVER SAW IT!
WHO CARES!
>> OH, OKAY.
NO WORRIES.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
TOTAL OOPS ON MY PART.
SORRY.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
ANYWAY, BLUEY IS REALLY COOL.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY CHECK IT OUT.
>> I WILL, THANKS, JENNIFER.
SO, WHAT KIND OF MUSIC DO YOU
GUYS LIKE?
I REALLY LIKE OLIVIA RODRIGO.
>> OH, YEAH!
>> I LIKE OLIVIA.
>> I LIKE HARRY STYLES.
SO CUTE.
>> SO CUTE!
>> HARRY WHO?
>> YOU KNOW.
HARRY STYLES.
>> NO, WHO IS HE?
>> WHO IS HARRY STYLES?
WHAT PART OF IOWA ARE YOU FROM?
EVERYONE KNOWS HARRY STYLES.
>> WELL, I DON'T, OKAY!
JESUS!
>> OKAY.
I THOUGHT EVERYONE KNEW HARRY
STYLES.
>> I SAID I DON'T, OKAY?
GOD!
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE!
>> NO WORRIES.
>> OOPS.
SORRY.
I DID IT AGAIN.
>> HEY, GIRLS.
JUST CHECKING IN.
HOW'S EVERYONE GETTING ALONG?
>> GREAT.
WHEN WILL IT BE OVER?
>> OH, I TOLD YOUR MOMS TO PICK
YOU UP AT 7:00.
I ORDERED PIZZA.
IT WILL BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT?
PIZZA, I LOVE PIZZA.
>> I LOVE PIZZA.
¶ PIZZA PIZZA PIZZA ¶
I LOVE IT!
>> IT'S ACTUALLY A REALLY COOL
DANCE, AGNES.
>> OH, THANKS.
I LOVE TO DANCE.
>> OH, DO YOU KNOW ANY DANCES
FROM TIKTOK?
>> STOP ASKING HER IF SHE KNOWS
STUFF.
>> HERE.
STAND OVER HERE.
>> I DON'T THINK I -- NO I DON'T
KNOW THIS --
>> DO IT!
EVERYBODY CAN GET IT.
>> THAT'S OKAY, IT LOOKS KIND OF
HARD.
>> COME ON, AGNES, JUST DO IT.
>> I SAID I DON'T WANT TO!
JIMINY CRICKET!
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> SORRY.
I WAS JUST REALLY SCARED ABOUT
DOING IT WRONG, I GUESS.
>> OH, THAT'S OKAY.
I THINK IF YOU HAD JUST TRIED
IT --
>> OH MY GOD, JUST LET IT GO!
ANYONE ELSE WANT TO TAKE A TRIP?
>> NO, THANK YOU.
>> NO.
>> AGNES?
AGNES?
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE OFFENDED
YOU.
I THINK WE JUST GOT OFF ON THE
WRONG FOOT.
>> OH, YOU JUST OPENED THE GATES
OF HELL!
>> WE'RE SORRY, AGNES.
MOVING TO A NEW PLACE MUST BE
REALLY OVERWHELMING.
>> YEAH, WHEN I MOVED HERE I WAS
SUPER SCARED, ALMOST AS MUCH AS
I AM RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, REALLY, THANKS.
THAT MEANS A LOT.
>> HEY, GIRLS.
THE PIZZA'S HERE.
>> EAT IT IN THE BUSHES!
SHOOT, GIRLS.
I'M SO SORRY.
I KEEP THROWING MARIE.
I GET A LITTLE MAD WHEN I LOSE
IT -- DO YOU THINK MARIE'S OKAY?
>> I DON'T.
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> IS IT?
>> YEAH.
WE ACTUALLY DON'T LIKE MARIE.
>> SHE'S MEAN, AND HER MOM
SLEEPS AROUND.
>> SO YOU'RE OUR NEW FRIEND.
NOW LET'S DANCE!
>> WAIT, I'M GETTING IT!
>> LOOKING -- LOOKING GOOD,
GIRLS!
>> DON'T PUSH ME!
AGAIN
errtime
¶ SOMEBODY BETTER GET HER
'CAUSE SHE OUT HERE
LOOKIN' FINE ¶
¶ BETTER POP YOUR --
BECAUSE I'M OUT HERE
POPPIN' MINE ¶
¶ THE WAY
THESE DIAMONDS HITTIN'
BITCHES DAMN NEAR
GOIN' BLIND ¶
¶ LOOK 'CAUSE DON JULIO
GON' DO THE TRICK EVERY TIME
¶ -- LOSE ME
YOU KNOW THAT -- OUT HIS MIND
¶ TELL HER MAKE A HIT
SHE IN THE STU'
JUST WASTIN' TIME
¶ IF I TAKE YOUR --
I DON'T WANNA HEAR NO CRYIN'
¶ 'CAUSE I AIN'T SAY --
WHEN HOES WAS OUT HERE
MINE
¶ OUTSIDE GRINDIN'
I'MA SHINE ALL SUMMER ¶
¶ BAD-ASS BITCH
I KNOW THAT EVERY --
WANT HER ¶
¶ REAL FINE -- MAN
I GET IT FROM MY MOTHER
I'M A DEMON I'LL -- YOUR OPP
AND -- YOUR BROTHER ¶
¶ BOTTLE AFTER BOTTLE
AFTER BOTTLES
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ ALL MY FRIENDS TENS
LOOK LIKE MODELS
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ HOES THROWIN' ASS
NEED SOME DOLLARS
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ BAD YELLOW BITCH
LOOK LIKE LATTO
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ SOMEBODY BETTER GET HER
'CAUSE SHE OUT HERE
LOOKIN' FINE ¶
¶ BETTER POP YOUR --
BECAUSE I'M OUT HERE
POPPIN' MINE ¶
¶ THE WAY
THESE DIAMONDS HITTIN'
BITCHES DAMN NEAR
GOIN' BLIND ¶
¶ LOOK 'CAUSE DON JULIO
GON' DO THE TRICK EVERY TIME
¶ -- LOSE ME
YOU KNOW THAT -- OUT HIS MIND
¶ TELL HER MAKE A HIT
SHE IN THE STU'
JUST WASTIN' TIME
¶ IF I TAKE YOUR --
I DON'T WANNA HEAR NO CRYIN'
¶ 'CAUSE I AIN'T SAY --
WHEN HOES WAS OUT HERE
MINE
¶ NEW BAG NEW ICE
-- ON THESE BITCHES'
WHOLE LIFE ¶
¶ FAT ASS
YOU WANT A BITE
FOR A BAD BITCH
I'M A WHOLE -- ¶
¶ IF I HIT THE CLUB
I'M GOIN' HOME
WITH A STRIPPER
¶ I GOT A BANGIN' BODY
THEN I'M ON IT
LIKE SOME GLITTER ¶
¶ MAYBE I'M BUGGIN'
MAYBE I'M TRIPPIN'
¶ I LET YOU HAVE THE -- HO
HOW COME YOU AIN'T WITH HIM
¶ I'M SOMEWHERE
ON THE AMALFI COAST
TANNIN' SOMEWHERE NAKED
¶ YOU SOMEWHERE
ON THE WATER BROKE
BITCHES MUST BE PREGNANT
¶ Y'ALL -- ON MY EX NOW
DAMN Y'ALL
MUST BE DESPERATE ¶
¶ R.I.P. TO O.G. MACO
WHO THE BADDEST BITCH
YOU GUESSED IT BRR ¶
¶ BOTTLE AFTER BOTTLE
AFTER BOTTLES
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ ALL MY FRIENDS BAD
LOOK LIKE MODELS
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ BITCHES THROWIN' ASS
NEED SOME DOLLARS
IN THIS MOTHER -- ¶
¶ BAD YELLOW BITCH
LOOK LIKE LATTO
IN THIS MOTHER --
¶ IT'S YOUR GIRL CARDI B
¶ I'M NOT YOUR GIRL
NOT YOUR GIRL ¶
TARZAN
DINNER'S READY.
>> TARZAN HOME.
>> THERE YOU ARE, TARZAN.
YOU'VE BEEN GONE ALL DAY.
NOW GO WASH UP, I MADE YOUR
FAVORITE.
BUGS WITH MUD SAUCE.
>> TARZAN NOT HUNGRY.
>> BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU LOVE BUGS WITH MUD SAUCE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> JANE, WE NEED TALK.
TARZAN THINK MAYBE THIS NOT
WORKING ANYMORE.
>> WAIT A SECOND.
ARE YOU BREAKING UP WITH ME?
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
>> TARZAN BEEN THINKING.
JANE GIVE UP WHOLE LIFE FOR
NAKED MAN RAISED BY GORILLAS WHO
NO SPEAK ENGLISH.
MAKE TARZAN THINK, WHAT WRONG
WITH JANE?
WHAT THAT SAY ABOUT JANE, YOU
KNOW?
>> YOU THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH ME?
>> NO, IT'S NOT ABOUT JANE.
TARZAN JUST NEEDS TO LOCK IN ON
WORK STUFF.
>> OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> BUT SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH
JANE.
JANE ONLY FRIENDS WITH ANIMALS.
WHY NO FRIENDS FROM OLD LIFE IN
LONDON?
THAT BIG RED FLAG.
ALSO, JANE SAY BOOTS ARE HUGE
FOR HUMAN.
TARZAN DUMB BUT NOT THAT DUMB.
>> OKAY, TARZAN.
LET'S JUST NOT DO ANYTHING RASH.
>> HELLO, THERE.
WE'RE HERE FROM LEOPARD AND SONS
MOVERS.
I'M A LEOPARD.
THIS HERE IS MY SON.
WE'RE HERE TO HELP THE
FLAT-CHESTED BRITISH LADY MOVE
OUT.
>> NO, NOW NOT GOOD TIME.
>> OH, NO PROBLEM.
ME AND MY SHY SON WILL BE BACK
LATER.
WHAT'S THAT, SON?
OH, MY SON JUST MADE THE ASTUTE
OBSERVATION THAT BOTH OF YOU
SMELL STINKILY.
GOOD-BYE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
FINE.
I'LL GO.
>> JANE WILL GO!
TARZAN NO LOVE JANE ANYMORE.
>> THAT ANOTHER THING.
JANE MAKE FUN OF WAY TARZAN
TALK.
TARZAN NEVER MAKE FUN OF JANE'S
ENGLISH ACCENT.
WHICH PART OF ENGLAND JANE FROM?
LONG ISLAND?
>> HEY.
YOU WATCH IT, BUDDY.
VERY WELL.
GOOD LUCK FINDING ANOTHER WOMAN
LIKE ME.
>> TARZAN PENIS TWO FEET LONG.
OKAY
BUT TARZAN WANTS TO SAY --
TAR ZEN NEVER FORGET JANE.
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU EITHER.
>> BECAUSE JANE TEACH TARZAN
ABOUT SOMETHING MAGICAL.
SOMETHING TARZAN NEVER
EXPERIENCED BEFORE.
>> LOVE --
>> MOUTH STUFF.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> NOTHING.
GOOD-BYE, JANE.
>> GOOD-BYE.
TARZAN.
>> WAIT.
WE IN TREEHOUSE.
SAY
GAMBLE
GEN
DUSTY NUT SAC?
>> WHAT?
OH, THAT GOD ME.
GANDALF'S DUSTY NUT SAC?
DUDE, YOU ARE HYSTERICAL.
DID YOU JUST COME UP WITH THAT?
>> MY KIND OF SENSE OF HUMOR, I
GUESS.
>> JESSICA, WHEN YOU SAID YOU
WERE BRINGING YOUR NEW BOYFRIEND
ON OUR SKI TRIP,
WAS HONEST, I
WAS FURIOUS.
BUT WOW, HE'S SO FUNNY.
>> FUNNY IN A COOL, EDGY WAY,
TOO.
YOU'RE SO LUCKY, GIRL.
>> YEAH, STEVE'S QUITE THE
COMEDIAN.
>> YOU WANT ME TO TAKE THAT COAT
FOR YOU?
LOOKS HOT.
>> NO, I'LL KEEP IT ON.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME COME.
THIS IS MORE FUN THAN --
SMOKING
CRACK WITH SUSAN BOYLE.
>> OH, DUDE!
- WHAT
>> WOW.
ALL MY FRIENDS THINK YOU'RE
HILARIOUS.
ACTUALLY MAKING ME PRETTY HORNY.
>> WHY DON'T WE GO TAKE CARE OF
THAT?
>> I'D LIKE THAT.
>> GUYS, IT WAS SO GREAT TO MEET
YOU ALL, BUT WE SHOULD GET
GOING.
OH, CRAP.
>> BABE?
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS REALLY WEIRD.
WHAT IS ALL THIS STUFF?
>> SMOKING CRACK WITH SUSAN
BOYLE?
DAVE, ARE THESE CARDS AGAINST
HUMANITY CARDS?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, WHAT?
>> DAVE, ARE YOU READING OFF
CARDS AGAINST HUMANITY CARDS
TO
MAKE PEOPLE THINK THAT YOU'RE
FUNNY?
>> NO, THAT WOULD BE WEIRD, LIKE
WHAT?
>> POOPING YOUR PANTS AT
LEGOLAND.
DAVE, YOU SAID TO TO ME BUT
MOMENTS AGO.
>> I DON'T THINK SO --
>> I KNOW SO.
I ASKED WHAT YOU DID FOR A
LIVING AND YOU SAID,
POOPING
YOUR PANTS AT LEGOLAND.
I REMEMBER BECAUSE I LAUGHED SO
HARD, I POOPED MY PANTS.
I HAD TO GET MY GYM SHORTS FROM
MY CAR.
>> THIS IS SO WEIRD.
I WANT TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
THIS.
>> AN INCONVENIENT BONER WHILE
WATCHING "MARLEY & ME"?
DAVE, YOU SAID THIS WORD FOR
WORD TO ME.
>> WHY WOULD I SAY THAT?
>> BECAUSE I ASKED YOU IF YOU
WERE WORRIED ABOUT TRAFFIC LATER,
AND YOU SAID YOU WERE
MORE WORRIED ABOUT AN
INCONVENIENT BONER WHILE
WATCHING "MARLEY & ME."
I REMEMBER BECAUSE I LAUGHED SO
HARD, I TRIED TO KISS YOU.
>> I DON'T REMEMBER THAT AT ALL.
>> DROPPING ACID WITH THE
MARIACHI BAND AT JOSH GAD'S KEEN
SIN YARA.
>> I DON'T RECALL THAT.
>> I TOLD YOU MY UNCLE DIED
AND YOU SAID THAT SOUNDS WORSE THAN
DROPPING ACID WITH THE MARIACHI BAND
AT JOSH GAD'S KEEN SINNER
IN RA.
HARD
LOVE
>> WHO ARE YOU?
I DON'T KNOW YOU ANYMORE.
ARE YOU EVEN TWISTED?
>> NO,
I'M JUST -- NORMAL!
GROWING UP, I NEVER SAID
ANYTHING TWISTED.
SOMEONE ASKED WHAT I WANTED FOR
LUNCH, I'D SAY A SANDWICH.
INSTEAD OF SOMETHING AWESOME
LIKE --
JACKING OFF THE KOOL-AID MAN
TILL HE SAYS "OH YEAH."
THEN IN COLLEGE, I PLAYED CARDS
AGAINST HUMANITY.
YOU KNOW.
I PICKED OUT A CARD AND PEOPLE
WOULD LAUGH AND GO,
DAMN THAT
BOY AIN'T RIGHT, YOU NEED JESUS!
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE I
FELT GOATED.
BODIED WITH A SAUCE.
YOU HEAR ME, MA?
YOUR BOY IS GOLDEN!
GOLDEN WITH A SAUCE!
AFTER THAT I DECIDED TO CARRY AT
LEAST THREE DECKS OF CARDS WITH ME AT ALL TIMES
AND FLAWLESSLY
WORK THEM INTO EVERY
CONVERSATION.
>> OKAY.
WELL.
ARE YOU GOING TO --
ARE YOU GOING TO PICK THESE UP,
THEN?
>> YEAH, OF COURSE.
OF COURSE I AM.
OF COURSE I AM, WHO DO YOU THINK
I AM?
HITLER'S HAIRY BUTT CRACK?
>> DUDE!
YOU NEED JESUS!
CARDI
PETE
STELLAN
MACFRER.
LORNE
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE, FOR COMING.