>>> LIVE FROM CENTRAL PARK,
IT'S
THE FIRST WARM DAY OF THE YEAR
ARRIVALS SHOW.
>> WELL, FOLKS, IT'S MID APRIL
HERE IN NEW YORK CITY,
AND THE
TEMPERATURE HIT 90 DEGREES THIS WEEK,
A FULL TWO MONTHS AHEAD OF
SCHEDULE.
WHILE THAT MAY BE TERRIFYING ON
A CLIMATE LEVEL,
THE WARM
WEATHER CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
ALL THE FREAKS, CRAZIES, AND
WEIRDOS ARE HEADED TO CENTRAL
PARK.
AND WE'RE EXPECTED TO SEE SOME
ICONIC PARK PEOPLE TODAY, AREN'T
WE, JACE?
>> WE SURE ARE.
THE MOOD HERE IS ELECTRIC.
THE SMELL OF HORSE MANURE IS IN
THE AIR.
ICON
OLDER MAN DOING AN AGGRESSIVE
POWER WALK.
>> HI THERE.
>> FIRST, DISH ON THIS OUTFIT.
>> CERTAINLY.
I'M WEARING THE TIGHTEST SPANDEX
SHIRT OF ALL TIME,
LITTLE
SHORTS, AND A WEIRD HEART RATE
MONITOR STRAPPED TO MY ARM.
>> ICONIC.
CAN YOU GIVE US A PREVIEW OF
YOUR WALK?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
BEHIND YOU, BEHIND YOU, BEHIND YOU,
ON YOUR
LEFT, BEHIND YOU.
AND THERE IT IS.
>> WOW, GORGEOUS.
DANA.
>> WELL, JACE, I AM STAR STRUCK RIGHT NOW
AS I AM JOINED BY NOT
ONE BUT TWO PERVERTS
WHO CAME TO
THE PARK TO PLEASURE THEMSELVES.
>> NICE TO BE OUT OF THE SUBWAY.
>> EXCITED FOR THE BIG DAY?
>> OH, YEAH.
I GOT MY MODESTY BLANKET AND BY
KNOCK LARS,
SO I'M GOOD TO GO.
POLICE
>> YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND YOUR
BOYS, THIS IS BUSHES, BABY.
>> ANY NEW TECHNIQUES THIS YEAR?
>> OH, JUST ONE.
>> IS THAT A FAKE ARM?
>> YEAH.
>> WOW!
SHAME ON YOU BOTH.
JACE.
>> WELL, WE WERE HOPING SHE
WOULD MAKE AN APPEARANCE.
IT'S A WOMAN LEARNING TO ROLLER
BLADE.
>> YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO LEARN, AND
I THOUGHT WHAT BETTER PLACE
THAN
ON A CROWDED PATHWAY FILLED WITH
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
>> HORRIBLE PLAN.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
>> HERE I GO.
>> AND SHE FELL RIGHT AWAY.
DANA.
>> WELL, LOOK WHO I FOUND.
TWO OF CENTRAL PARK'S FINEST.
PARK EMPLOYEES WHO DO NOT CARE
ABOUT THEIR JOBS.
HOW YOU GUYS FEELING?
>> WE ARE VERY HIGH RIGHT NOW.
YES.
THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
>> AMAZING.
ANY WARNINGS FOR THOSE WHO
VIOLATE PARK RULES?
>> YOU DO YOU.
>> INSPIRING WORDS.
JACE, I HEAR YOU'VE SPOTTED AN
ABSOLUTE LEGEND.
>> WELL, I HOPE SHE'LL STOP TO
TALK.
IT'S A LADY TRYING TO TELL
SOMEONE WHERE SHE IS.
>> WELL, I DON'T SEE YOU, BITCH.
I'M RIGHT WHERE I SAID I WOULD
BE.
RIGHT BY THE BIG TREE, THE BIG
TREE NEAR THE BRIDGE.
>> OH, JUST MISSED HER.
DANA.
>> HE'S BACK.
IT'S THE GROWN MAN WITH THE
DRONE WHO'S ALONE.
>> HEY, THERE.
>> AND YOU WON'T BE FILMING
GIRLS LAYING OUT SUN BATHING,
WILL YOU?
>> NO.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
NOW, JACE, THIS GUY IS BAD, BUT
I HEAR YOU'RE WITH ONE OF THE
WORST PARK PEOPLE OF ALL.
>> I SURE AM.
IT'S THE GUY WITH THE CLIPBOARD
WHO WANTS TO KNOW IF YOU HAVE A
SECOND FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
NOW, PEOPLE ABSOLUTELY HATE YOU.
CAN YOU TELL US WHY?
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S BECAUSE I
ZERO IN ON FOLKS TRYING TO ENJOY
THEMSELVES AND PESTER THEM FOR
MONEY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
CAN WE SEE THAT IN ACTION?
>> YOU BET.
WOW.
COOL SHIRT.
YOU HAVE A SECOND FOR --
>> NO!
I DONATED BEFORE.
>> WHAT AN ABSOLUTE PAIN IN THE
ASS.
DANA.
>> IT'S A BIRD, IT'S A PLANE.
IT'S A CRAZY MAN WITH A
MICROPHONE.
>> GOOD TO BE BACK FOR ANOTHER
YEAR.
>> AND I SEE YOU BROUGHT A LADY
FRIEND WITH YOU.
>> I SURE DID.
THIS WOMAN WILL BE DEBATING THE
NONSENSE THAT I SCREAM
AS IF I'M
A RATIONAL MAN WHOSE MIND CAN BE
CHANGED.
>> CAN WE GET A PREVIEW?
>> OF COURSE.
>> OUR PLEASURE.
>> CREATED THE
CORONAVIRUS.
>> THAT IS BOLOGNA!
5G
IMPOSSIBLE
LIKE THAT
>> WOW.
I CAN'T TELL WHO ANNOYS ME MORE.
JACE.
>> WELL, WE HAVE BEEN WAITING
FOR HER TO ARRIVE.
IT'S WEALTHY WOMAN AND CHILD.
I FOUGHT TO ASK, WHAT'S THE PLAN
TODAY?
>> I'M TAKING RILEY HERE TO THE PLAYGROUND
WHERE I'LL SNAP INTO
AN IMMEDIATE PANIC IF I LOSE
SIGHT OF HIM FOR ONE SECOND.
RILEY?
RILEY!
>> OH, NO.
>> WELL, I STILL DON'T SEE YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M DONE LOOKING FOR YOU, BITCH.
YOU COME FIND ME.
I'LL BE IN THE GRASS IN A RED
BIKINI GETTING MYSELF SOME SUN.
>> WELL, WE'VE GOT PLENTY MORE
PARK PEOPLE COMING UP,
INCLUDING
A WOMAN WITH AN OUT OF CONTROL DOG
AND A PERFORMANCE FROM SOME
A-HOLE PLAYING AT ACOUSTIC GUITAR.
AND LIVE --
>> OKAY.
GIRL, I'M RIGHT HERE.
>> LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ANA de
ARMAS!
>>> GRACIAS.
GRACIAS.
JUST KIDDING.
I SPEAK ENGLISH.
BUT I DIDN'T WHEN I FIRST GOT TO
THE U.S.
I WAS BORN IN CUBA, CAME TO
AMERICA WHEN I WAS
26, AND I
LEARNED ENGLISH THE WAY EVERYONE
WHO COMES TO THIS COUNTRY DOES,
BY WATCHING "FRIENDS."
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THE BEST
ENGLISH TUTOR WOULD HAVE BEEN
CHANDLER BING.
LOOK AT ME NOW, COULD I BE ANY
BETTER AT ENGLISH?
ACTING HERE WAS DIFFICULT AT FIRST
BECAUSE I DIDN'T ALWAYS
UNDERSTAND WHAT I WAS SAYING.
THEN I MET A GUY WHO HAD A CLASS
CALLED HOW TO AUDITION,
WHICH
WAS DEFINITELY A SCAM.
HE HAD ME READ A SCENE,
AND THERE WAS THIS LINE, I BEG YOUR
PARDON.
BUT I HAD NEVER SEEN OR HEARD THAT PHRASE,
SO I THOUGHT THIS
CHARACTER WAS LITERALLY BEGGING.
SO WHEN I DID THE LINE, I SAID,
I BEG YOUR PARDON!
GIVE IT TO ME!
THEN SOMEONE ELSE IN THE CLASS
READ THE LINE, AND I WAS LIKE,
OH, CAN I TRY AGAIN?
THIS HAS BEEN A MAGICAL YEAR.
NOT ONLY I WAS NOMINATED FOR AN
OSCAR --
BUT IN THREE WEEKS, I'M GOING
OFFICIALLY BECOME AN AMERICAN
CITIZEN.
I AM PROUD TO BECOME A CITIZEN
BECAUSE WHEN I MOVED HERE,
EVERYONE WAS SO WELCOMING.
WHEN I DID MY FIRST MOVIE IN THE
U.S. CALLED HANDS OF STONE,
I
GOT TO WORK WITH ROBERT DE NIRO,
AND ONE DAY ON SET, HE SAID HE
WAS GOING TO CUBA SOON,
AND IF I
DO, I'LL SAY HELLO TO YOUR
FAMILY.
HE ASKED ME FOR THEIR PHONE
NUMBER.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT IT,
AND ONE DAY I GET A PHONE CALL
FROM MY DAD, HE'S HYSTERICAL,
AND I GO, DAD, WHAT'S WRONG,
AND HE GOES, ROBERT DE NIRO JUST
CAME TO VISIT ME AT WORK.
THAT WAS SUCH A KIND GESTURE,
AND I HAVE BEEN SO FORTUNATE TO
WORK WITH SO MANY WONDERFUL
ACTORS.
MY DAD WAS SO PROUD OF ME,
AND HE WOULD BE PROUD TO SEE ME
TODAY STANDING ON THIS STAGE.
I FEEL VERY LUCKY TO BE HERE.
I REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME MY
NAME WAS IN THE NEW YORK CROSS
WORD.
EVERYONE TEXTED ME, AND THEY
SAID, YOU MADE IT.
AND I THOUGHT I DID.
BUT THEN, A COUPLE MONTHS AGO,
SNL CALLED ME AND SAID,
ANA, WE
WANT YOU TO HOST.
AND I WAS SO SHOCKED AND EXCITED
THAT ALL I COULD SAY WAS --
I
BEG YOUR PARDON!
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
KAROL G IS HERE.
STICK AROUND.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> GOOD EVENING.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M TED CONLEY, AND THIS IS THE
DOME.
NOW LET'S MEET THE TEAMS VYING
FOR A CHANCE AT THE $1 MILLION
PRIZE.
TEAM ONE, INTRODUCE YOURSELVES.
>> I'M BETH AND THIS IS MY
BROTHER-IN-LAW, ROB.
>> PROOF THAT IN-LAWS CAN GET
ALONG.
WE'RE HAVING FUN.
OKAY.
WHO DO WE HAVE ON TEAM TWO?
>> I'M CARMEN, AND THIS IS MY
HUSBAND MATT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CARMEN AND HER COUSIN MATT.
OKAY.
>> NO, NO.
MATT'S MY HUSBAND.
>> I'M SORRY.
I HAVE A BAD EAR FOR ACCENTS.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU SAID THAT MATT'S
YOUR HUSBAND.
>> I DID.
WE'RE MARRIED.
>> UH-HUH.
>> TO EACH OTHER?
>> YEPERONI.
>> OKAY.
SO, LET ME JUST CLARIFY WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
SO YOU, WHO ARE YOU, ARE MARRIED
TO HE, WHO IS HIM?
>> YEP.
WE ARE MR. AND MRS. MATTHEW
PATRICK SCHATT.
>> YOUR NAME IS MATT PAT SCHATT?
>> YES, SIR.
IS THAT OKAY?
>> NOT REALLY.
NOW, I GOT TO ASK, WHY ARE YOU
ON THE SHOW WHEN YOU ARE
OBVIOUSLY EXTREMELY WEALTHY?
>> OH, NO, I AM NOT WEALTHY.
>> WELL, THEN, WHY IS SHE WITH
YOU?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
>> NO!
OH, MAN, I GOT TO CALM DOWN.
I GOTS TO CALM DOWN.
IF YOU'RE NOT RICH, WHAT DO YOU
DO FOR A LIVING?
>> I DANCE WITH THE SAN
FRANCISCO BALLET, AND MATT WORKS
IN THE FOOD INDUSTRY.
>> OH, SO YOU'RE A CHEF?
>> NO.
I'M A TASTE TESTER AT PURINA DOG
CHOW.
>> HE TRIES NEW DOG FOODS TO
TELL THEM IF IT'S TOO, LIKE,
SPICY.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE THE DOGS CAN
TALK.
>> SO YOU EAT DOG FOOD FOR
MONEY?
>> SOME DAY, HOPEFULLY.
IT'S VOLUNTEER RIGHT NOW, BUT
FINGERS CROSSED IT TURNS INTO A
PAID GIG SOON.
>> YOU EAT THE DOG FOOD FOR
FREE?
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S GOING
ON.
THIS DUDE HAS OBVIOUSLY GOT THE
BADDEST BITCH I EVER SEEN, AND
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
SORRY, EVERYBODY.
I JUST HAD A STROKE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET BACK TO IT.
JUST TRY TO FIGURE OUT HOW THIS
ABSOLUTE DIME IS MARRIED TO MATT
SCHATT.
OH, BETH, YOU GOT AN ANSWER?
>> I THINK I DO.
HE OBVIOUSLY GAVE HER A KIDNEY
AND SAVED HER LIFE.
>> HE DIDN'T GIVE ME A KIDNEY.
>> ROB, CHANCE TO STEAL.
>> HE'S A HANGING EIGHT BUT A
STANDING 12?
>> NO.
AND FYI, HE'S HANGING FIVE AND
WHEN HE STANDS IT'S A FOUR.
>> SO WHEN HE GETS EXCITED IT
GETS SMALLER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
>> I'M BUZZING IN ON THIS ONE.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK, SHE
HYPNOTIZED.
>> YOU'RE ALL SOUNDING CRAZY.
LOOK AT MY HUSBAND.
I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS WHY I'M
WITH HIM.
>> THE JUDGES SAY NO.
>> I'M SORRY.
CAN WE PLAY THE GAME NOW OR --
>> OF COURSE, OF COURSE.
I'M SORRY.
MATT AND CARMEN, YOU WON THE
COIN TOSS BACKSTAGE, SO THE
FIRST QUESTION GOES TO YOU.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I'M SO NERVOUS.
I'M LIKE ALREADY SWEATING.
ONE SECOND.
>> FREEZE.
ZOOM IN ON THIS.
>> WHAT?
>> WHAT IN THE HECK?
MATT PAT SCHATT HAS GOT A
GRIFFIN NIPPLES.
LOOK AT ALL OF THESE.
EWW.
>> YEAH.
EVERY COUPLE OF YEARS, A NEW ONE
POPS UP.
JUST ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
THINGS.
>> BABE, PUT YOUR SHIRT DOWN.
I'M GOING TO GET TOO EXCITED.
>> BUT WHY, THOUGH?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
LET'S JUST TAKE A BREAK WHILE I
HAVE ANOTHER STROKE.
BECAUSE I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON.
SHE BAD.
RIGHT?
>> PEOPLE CAN'T STOP TALKING
ABOUT THE TRAILER FOR THE NEW
BARBIE MOVIE,
BUT NOT ALL DOLLS
LIVE IN A DREAM HOUSE.
SOME ARE BIGGER, YOUNGER,
SADDER.
SOME DOLLS ARE AMERICAN GIRLS.
>> HI, KIRSTEN.
>> HI MOLLY.
>> HI SAMANTHA.
JOS
KEATH
>> AND I'M ADDY.
NO ONE SAID HI TO ME.
>> THIS SUMMER, A NEW LIVE
ACTION STORY ABOUT YOUR FAVORITE
HISTORICALLY ACCURATE DOLLS,
EACH WITH THEIR OWN BACK STORY.
>> I'M FROM VICTORIAN TIMES.
I WATCHED MY PARENTS DIE IN A
BOAT.
MARTHA
>> THAT'S OKAY.
MY DADDY'S A PRISONER OF WAR,
AND TRAGICALLY, I HAVE GLASSES.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
MY MAMA IS DEAD.
CHURCH
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW MY BIRTHDAY BECAUSE
I'M A RUN AWAY SLAVE.
>> LET'S PLAY.
>> YEA!
>> DO THEY HAVE PINK CORVETTES?
NOPE,
BOYFRIENDS, NO WAY.
DID ALL THEIR FAMILY MEMBERS DIE
OF VAGUE OLD-TIMEY DISEASES?
ABSOLUTELY.
>> FASHION SHOW.
>> COME FOR THE FUN, STAY FOR
THE OVERBURDENED PRETEENS
WEARING FOUR LAYERS OF COATS AND
PANTALOONS.
>> WHAT'S WRONG, JOSH?
YOU'VE BARELY TOUCHED YOUR TEA.
>> THE MEMORY OF MY MAMA IS
SLIPPING AWAY.
LOOK WHAT I CAN DO.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> YEAH.
>> AUDIENCES ARE RAVING.
WE LOVED IT, SAYS GIRLS WHO
PLAYED SOCCER MAGAZINE.
THE NEW YORK TIMES WRITES, THESE
LITTLE GIRLS ARE GOING THROUGH
TOO MUCH.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY, GIRLS,
SHOULD WE HAVE A SLEEPOVER
TONIGHT?
>> YEA.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU, ADDY?
>> I'M GOOD.
I DON'T TRUST NONE OF Y'ALL.
>> WATCH AS THE AMERICAN GIRLS
TRAVEL ON A JOURNEY FROM
AMERICAN GIRL LAND TO THE MODERN
WORLD.
>> I'M GOING TO STOP WORLD WAR
II.
>> AND I'M GOING TO STOP THE
SPANISH AMERICAN WAR.
>> AND I'M GOING TO END CHOLERA.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>>> WHAT'S UP, Y'ALL.
MY NAME IS YOUNG SPICY, AND I'M
A PRODUCER.
I'M ABOUT TO RELEASE MY FIRST
ALBUM.
JALAPENO JONES.
>> THANKS FOR HELPING US OUT
TODAY.
>> HOW Y'ALL DOING?
>> WHAT'S GOOD, SPICY?
>> WE JUST LOOKING FOR A NEW
PRODUCER TAG FOR MY BEATS,
SOMETHING SEXY AND COOL.
>> FOR EXAMPLE, SOMETHING LIKE,
MAKE THAT MUSIC.
>> AND WE'VE HEARD YOU HAVE SOME
BEAUTIFUL VOICES, SO WE NEED TO
HEAR YOU SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
YOUNG SPICY SO FUEGO.
>> WE CAN DO THAT.
>> WE GOT YOU, MR. SPICY.
>> I'M GOING TO START THE BEAT,
YOU TWO TAKE IT AWAY, AND WE'LL
GET SOME LUNCH.
>> WE'LL GIVE YOU SOME OPTIONS.
YOUNG SPICY GOT THAT FIRE.
>> YOUNG SPICY'S FLAMING HOT.
>> EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
KEEP THAT GOING.
>> OOH, YOUNG SPICY, YOU STUPID.
>> OOH, SPICY CAN'T READ.
>> DAMN, SPICY, YOU ILLITERATE.
>> OKAY.
I LOVE IT.
BUT JUST FYI, I CAN READ.
I'M A READER.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT YOU.
>> OOH, SPICY CAN READ BUT HAS
TROUBLES WITH MATH.
>>LET STOP.
>> I THINK WE GOT IT, MAN.
LET'S GET SOME LUNCH.
>> NO LUNCH.
SO Y'ALL REMEMBER THE
ASSIGNMENT, RIGHT?
>> WE HEAR YOU.
WE GOOD.
>> WE'RE ARTISTS.
WE JUST RESPONDING TO THE VIBES.
>> LET'S DO A DIFFERENT VIBE
THEN.
LET'S DO SOMETHING LIKE, TO OH,
SPICY, THESE BEATS NASTY.
>> ALL RIGHT, COOL.
>> ONE MORE TAKE AND THEN WE ALL
GETTING GYROS.
TZATZIKI SAUCE ON THE SIDE.
TAKE TWO.
>> OH, SPICY, YOU FILTHY FOR
THIS.
>> LET'S GET A COUPLE MORE LIKE
THAT, YEAH.
>> SPICY, WHY YOU SLEEP NEXT TO
YOUR LAUNDRY.
>> SPICY DON'T WASH HIS PILLOWS.
HE'S GROSS.
>> DAMN, SPICY, YOU GOT THAT
DARK RING AROUND YOUR TOILET.
I'M UNCOMFORTABLE HERE.
>> DAMN SPICY, YOU LIKE THAT.
>> STOP.
OKAY, LADIES, I AM BEGGING YOU.
CAN Y'ALL SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
OH, THE LADIES LOVE SPICY?
>> YEAH.
AND AFTER THIS TAKE, I'M GOING
TO GET SOME HUMMUS WITH THE PITA
BREAD.
>> DAMN, SPICY GETTING
EVERYTHING PREGNANT.
>> GETTING CLOSER.
>> THE BABY'S YOURS FOR SURE.
>> DAMN, SPICY, MY WATER BROKE.
>> DAMN, SPICY, I'M GOING TO
NAME THE BABY DELONTE.
>> SPICY, DRIVE ME TO THE
HOSPITAL IN YOUR 2001 COROLLA.
>> NO, NO BABY STUFF, AND LEAVE
MY COROLLA OUT OF THIS, ALL
RIGHT?
TALK ABOUT HOW LIKE SPICY GETS
YOU HOT, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> DAMN, SPICY GOT ME SWEATING.
>> YEAH, THANK YOU.
>> OH, I DON'T USUALLY SWEAT
LIKE THIS.
I'M SCARED.
>> DAMN, SPICY, WHY THE ROOM
SPINNING ALL THE SUDDEN?
>> DAMN, SPICY, ALL I HAD WAS
ONE SPRITE.
I SHOULDN'T BE FEELING LIKE
THIS.
>> OOH, I THINK SPICY PUT
SOMETHING IN MY DRINK.
>> SPICY NEEDS TO BE ON A WATCH
LIST.
>> CUT THAT.
DELETE THAT, ACTUALLY.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST CALL IT A DAY.
I'M GOOD.
>> OKAY.
I MEAN, LISTEN --
>> WHATEVER.
I MEAN --
>> RIGHT?
COME ON.
>> WE GAVE YOU FUEGO.
>> YOU SHOULD JUST USE THE ONE
ABOUT THE RING AROUND YOUR
TOILET FOR REAL.
>> SPICY, CAN I TRY ONE?
PLEASE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH, SPICY GOT THAT FIRE.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH, YEAH, SPICY GOT THAT
HEAT.
>> OKAY.
>> SPICY STRUGGLES WITH HIS
READING.
>> NO!
>> THAT'S NOT IT?
>>> HOLA, BUENAS TARDES.
COME ON.
EXCELENTE.
BEFORE WE GET STARTED, WHAT DID
EVERYONE DO THIS WEEKEND?
AND REMEMBER, ANSWER IN ESPANOL.
>> COMO SE DICE EDIBLES?
>> OKAY.
>> MR. McINTOSH?
>> HOLA, PRINCIPAL DAVIDSON,
COMO ESTAS?
>> THE NEW TRANSFER STUDENTS ARE
HERE.
COME ON IN, GUYS.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
I'M ASKING YOUR NAMES IN CASE
>> --
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
>> UH-OH.
A LITTLE FAST.
THAT WAS A LITTLE FAST POR ME,
VERY COOL.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET STARTED.
TODAY, WE'RE GOING OVER OUR
FAVORITE FOODS.
OKAY?
SO, RICKY, WHAT IS YOURS?
>> MI FAR VRKS ORITA IS PIZZA.
>> ES PIZZA.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, HUGO?
>> --
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
>> YUMMY!
>> WHOA!
WHAT DID HE SAY, MR. McINTOSH?
>> SI, SI, I HEARD RICE
SOMEWHERE IN THERE, AKA, NIES.
>> I THINK YOU MEAN ARROZ.
>> YES, YES.
ARROZ.
YES, ARROZ, OF COURSE.
OF COURSE.
SO, HUGO LIKES ARROZ.
ALL RIGHT.
I AM SWEATING A LITTLE BIT.
WHO ELSE WANTS TO SAY THEIR
FAVORITE FOOD?
OKAY.
ANYBODY ELSE?
MARIA.
>> --
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
I'M IN LOVE?
>> OKAY.
VERY GOOD PREGUNTA.
ESTOY EMARADO.
>> IN MY COUNTRY, WE SAY --
[ SPEAKING SPANISH ]
WHICH MEANS GOING DOWN THE HILL
WITH NO BRAKES.
>> SI.
THAT IS SO MUCH MORE ROMANTIC.
I LOVE THAT.
YOU KNOW, THIS MORNING, I CAME
IN FEELING BUENO, BUT NOW I'M
STARTING TO FEEL ASI ASI.
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, NO ONE IN
OUR COUNTRY SAY ASI ASI.
>> THAT'S LIKE IF SOMEBODY SAY
HOW ARE YOU, AND YOU SAY, THAT,
THAT.
>> SI, SI, I KNOW.
I WAS KIDDING.
ESTOY KIDDING.
I'M FEELING -- I'M FEELING A
LITTLE CALIENTE UNDER MY COLLAR.
TMA, ES UN TMI, I THINK I GOT
THE RUNS.
I'M GOING HEAD TO EL BANO.
>> WHILE MR. McINTOSH IS GONE,
CAN YOU GUYS TEACH US SOME
STUFF?
>> AND TO HELP US, WE BROUGHT
SOME BACKUP.
>> OKAY, CLASS.
I JUST THINK THAT WE NEED TO
START FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THE ALPHABET.
>> OKAY.
HIT IT.
♪
>>> THAT AFTERPARTY ON SATURDAY
WAS WILD, HUH?
>> SUPER WILD.
THAT OPEN BAR GOT ME GOOD.
CAN'T HELP BUT HAVE A LITTLE
HANGXIETY.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WASN'T LIKE WEIRD TO ANYONE,
WAS I?
MICHAEL LONGFELLOW.
KISS ATTACK.
I WANT TO SEE THEM LONG FELLOWS.
>> DUDE!
STOP IT!
>> THAT'S JUST HANGXIETY, MAN.
IT'S ALWAYS WORSE IN YOUR HEAD
THAN WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
>> OKAY.
COOL.
JUST WOKE UP TO A LOT OF MISSED
CALLS.
NO BIG DEAL.
PROBABLY JUST HANGXIETY.
>> NOTHING TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT,
DUDE.
LIKE, MARK, ME AND YOU ARE FINE,
RIGHT?
WE'RE ALL GOOD?
>> YEAH.
WHY WOULDN'T WE BE?
>> GIVE ME MY PHONE BACK NOW!
>> OH, YOU WANT YOUR PHONE?
>> YEAH, GIVE ME MY PHONE BACK
NOW!
>> JUST MAKING SURE.
ALL GOOD.
>> MAN, HOW MUCH DID WE DRINK?
>> NOT MUCH.
I HAD LIKE TWO NEGRONIS AND
MAYBE LIKE 40 BEERS.
>> WHOEVER WAS BAR TENDING WAS
MAKING THEM STRONG.
>> DUDE, LET ME MAKE IT, YOU'RE
TOO SLOW.
>> I'M FILMING YOU.
>> GO AHEAD, FILM ME.
>> MAKE IT.
>> MAN, WHO ORDERED THE
MARGARINI?
I DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> ANA.
>> THAT PARTY WAS FUN ON
SATURDAY.
>> THANKS FOR COMING.
>> YOU WERE A DELIGHT.
>> AND WERE ME AND YOU KIND OF
VIBING?
>> SO LIKE ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
USUALLY IN SPANISH OR ENGLISH?
>> CAN YOU STOP LIKE YELLING IN
MY MOUTH?
>> YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
>> SERIOUSLY, YOU SMELL LIKE YOU
HAVE A DEAD TOOTH.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> COOL.
DIDN'T THINK SO EITHER.
BACK TO WORK.
>> WELL, ANA, EVERYONE LOVED
YOU.
SERIOUSLY, I WAS WITH PEOPLE ALL
NIGHT, AND ALL WE COULD TALK
ABOUT WAS HOW FUN YOU WERE
BEING.
NO!
>> THANK YOU.
IT'S JUST SO NICE TO SEE YOU
GUYS HOW YOU REALLY ARE LIKE A
FAMILY HERE.
♪ DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME ♪
>> YOU NEED AUTO TUNE!
YOU NEED AUTO TUNE!
>> YOU'RE A JEALOUS BITCH!
>> LITERALLY THE POT CALLING THE
KETTLE BAD!
>> MY SHIRT!
>> FAMILY.
>> WE ARE.
>> TOTALLY.
>> HEY, GUYS.
OH, IT'S MESSY IN HERE.
THAT'S CRAZY.
I JUST WANT TO SAY YOUR BEHAVIOR
AT THE AFTERPARTY WAS UNACCEPT
LABLE.
>> SORRY, MIKEY.
>> THIS IS A WORK PLACE.
ACT LIKE IT.
>> OKAY, MAN.
GOD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
MICHAEL CHE.
>>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE."
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THE PERSON WHO ALLEGEDLY LEAKED
CLASSIFIED PENTAGON DOCUMENTS ON SOCIAL MEDIA
HAS BEEN IDENTIFIED
AS JACK TEIXEIRA
WHO IS A
MASSACHUSETTS AIR NATIONAL
GUARDSMAN,
I ASSUME IN A SCHOOL
PLAY.
HE SHARED IS DOCUMENT IN A
PRIVATE SOCIAL MEDIA GROUP
THAT
MEMBERS SAY STARTED AS A PLACE
WHERE YOUNG MEN COULD PLAY WAR
THEMED VIDEO GAMES,
BOND OVER
THEIR LOVE OF GUNS, AND POST
RACIST MEMES,
AND NOW IT'S
RUINED.
IT WAS REVEALED THAT JUST BEFORE
HIS ARREST, TEIXEIRA CONTACTED
THE MEMBERS OF HIS GROUP
AND
SAID, GUYS, IT'S BEEN GOOD.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
OF COURSE, HIS FRIENDS ALL
REPLIED, GAY.
>> THE ONLINE GROUP TEIXEIRA
STARTED WAS NAMED THUGS SHAKER
CENTRAL.
THAT'S ALSO WHAT COLIN CALLS
ATLANTA.
PRESIDENT BIDEN IS TRYING TO
DOWN PLAY THE RECENT LEAK
OF CLASSIFIED U.S. DOCUMENTS THAT
WERE POSTED ON SOCIAL MEDIA
BECAUSE WHEN YOU'RE OVER 80, A
COUPLE OF LEAKS IS NOTHING TO BE
EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
>> IN AN INTERVIEW, DONALD TRUMP
CLAIMED NEW YORK POLICE AND
COURT EMPLOYEES
WERE CRYING WHEN
THEY ARRESTED HIM.
WHY IS EVERYONE IN TRUMP'S
STORIES ALWAYS CRYING?
>> PEOPLE CAME TO ME AND THEY
SAW ME, AND THEY WERE CRYING.
VERY TOUGH, VERY STRONG, VERY
POWERFUL MEN WERE CRYING.
THEY HAD TEARS IN THEIR EYES.
THEY WERE ALL CRYING.
PEOPLE WERE CRYING.
JUST
THESE PEOPLE THAT DIDN'T CRY
WHEN THEY WERE BABIES,
AND THEY
WERE CRYING.
A LOT OF THEM WERE CRYING.
>> YOU'RE BRAGGING THAT WHEN
PEOPLE SEE YOU, THEY JUST LIKE BURST INTO TEARS,
BECAUSE IT
NEVER SOUNDS LIKE EXCITED
CRYING.
LIKE BTS
IT SOUNDS MORE LIKE SCARED CRYING
LIKE WHEN HOSTAGES SEE
JIGSAW.
>> AFTER A JUDGE'S RULING LEFT
ACCESS TO ABORTION PILLS UNCERTAIN,
SOME STATE OFFICIALS
ARE STOCK PILING THEM JUST IN
CASE.
CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR GAVIN NEWSOM
MASS
AND NEW YORK COMEDIAN, MICHAEL
CHE.
AFTER IT WAS REVEALED THAT
HARLAN CROWE BOUGHT CLARENCE
THOMAS' GEORGIA HOME,
HE SAID HE DID IT
SO HE COULD TURN IT INTO A MUSEUM
CALLED THE SEXUAL
HARASSMENT HALL OF FAME.
>> CONSERVATIVE JUDGES HAVE
DEFENDED THOMAS
SAYING HIS DEALS
WITH HARLAN CROWE ARE NOT CORRUPT
BECAUSE HE HAD NO DEALS
BEFORE THE COURT.
DOES THIS CONSERVATIVE CHRISTIAN BILLIONAIRE
STRIKE YOU AS SOMEONE WHO DIDN'T WANT THEM
TO OVERTURN ROE V WADE?
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S AN A PAMPHLET
CALLED WHY YOU HAVE TO KEEP IT.
>> PRESIDENT BIDEN TRAVELED TO
IRELAND THIS WEEK
AND IS BEING
CALLED THE MOST IRISH PRESIDENT
SINCE KENNEDY.
BIDEN HAS SO MUCH IRISH BLOOD
THAT HE DOESN'T NEED A DRINK TO
SLUR HIS WORDS.
>> DID THAT GET YOUR PEOPLE?
>> EASY.
SENATOR DIANE FEINSTEIN WHO IS 89
IS FACING CALLS TO RESIGN
FROM FELLOW DEMOCRATS.
UNFORTUNATELY, FEINSTEIN IS
ANSWERING THOSE CALLS ON HER
STAPLER.
>> REPUBLICAN SENATOR TIM SCOTT
OF SOUTH CAROLINA
ANNOUNCED THE LAUNCH
OF AN EXPLORATORY
COMMITTEE FOR A 2024
PRESIDENTIAL RUN.
THAT NAME AGAIN IS TIM SCOTT,
AS IN TIM'S GOT NO CHANCE OF BEING
A NOMINEE.
>> THE NEW MARIO BROTHERS MOVIE
IS A HUGE HIT, AND MANY FANS
WERE HOPING FOR AN APPEARANCE
FROM ONE OF THE COOLEST
CHARACTERS, FUNKY KONG.
SO HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS
FUNKY KONG.
>> WHAT'S U COLIN?
WHAT'S UP, LADIES?
WHICH ONE OF Y'ALL GOING HOME
WITH FUNKY KONG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, FUNKY KONG?
>> I'VE BEEN BETTER.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE ALL
OVER THIS MOVIE THAT JUST MADE
$500 MILLION -- 600.
BUT THIS IS HOW MUCH YOU GET TO
SEE OF ME.
>> YOU'RE JUST IN THE
BACKGROUND?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> THEY CUT ME OUT.
I GUESS I'M TOO REAL FOR THEM.
THEY DON'T WANT TO HEAR WHAT I
GOTS TO SAY, AND THEY SURE AS
HELL DON'T WANT TO WATCH ME
WORK.
BRING IT BACK.
♪
>> WOW.
I'M SO SORRY YOU GOT CUT.
>> FUNKY DON'T WANT TO BE WHAT
THEY WANT, COLIN.
FUNKY DON'T THROW NO BARRELS.
FUNKY KONG SPENDS ALL DAY
CRUISING IN MY CART AND MY
NIGHTS WITH A GLASS FULL OF
BANANA RUM AND A BED FULL OF
TOADS.
>> ARE THE TOADS MALE OR FEMALE?
>> FUNKY DON'T KNOW, FUNKY DON'T
ASK.
>> IT'S A SHAME YOU'RE NOT IN
THE MOVIE BECAUSE YOUR COUSIN
DONKEY KONG IS A MAJOR
CHARACTER.
>> YEAH, DONKEY KONG IS ALL UP
IN IT.
BUT THEY AIN'T EVEN USE MONKEY
KONG.
>> WHO IS MONKEY KONG?
>> HE'S A DONKEY.
THEM JAPANESE PEOPLE SURE ARE
INTERESTING.
YOU KNOW THEY KICKED ME OFF THE
SET?
>> WHAT?
WHY?
>> BECAUSE I WAS IN MY TRAILER
DRUMMING ON BOOTY CHEEKS LIKE
BONGOS.
I WAS IN THERE LIKE, BOOTY
CHEEKS, BOOTY CHEEKS.
>> GREAT.
REALLY GREAT.
SO YOU WERE ORIGINALLY IN THE
MOVIE.
>> ABSOLUTELY, MAN.
I HAD A FEW CHOICE SCENES.
I WAS INCREDIBLE.
I EVEN HAVE THE OLD SCRIPT RIGHT
HERE.
READ THIS WITH ME.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
YOU BE MARIO AND LUIGI.
>> LUIGI, WE GOT TO GET TO THE
CASTLE.
BUT THE FASTEST WAY IS RAINBOW
ROAD.
MARIO, RAINBOW ROAD?
WE'LL FALL OFF.
>> MAN, AIN'T NO BITCHES IN
HERE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT'S THE
ORIGINAL LINE.
>> I TOLD YOU, MAN.
I WAS DOPE.
GO TO PAGE 36, MAN.
THE SCENE WITH ME AND PEACH.
>> YOU AND PEACH.
OKAY.
PRINCESS PEACH, FUNKY KONG,
THEY'RE HOLDING OUR FRIENDS
PRISONER AT WARIO STADIUM.
CAN YOU HELP?
>> GIRL, WHY DON'T YOU GO ON AND
OPEN UP THAT PEACH AND LET ME
SEE WHAT'S INSIDE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HONESTLY, I CAN SEE WHY THEY CUT
YOU OUT.
>> COME ON.
PEOPLE WOULD HAVE EATEN THAT UP,
MAN.
YOU EVER HAD MONKEY MEAT?
>> NO.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT YOUR MAMA
SAID LAST NIGHT.
BRING IT BACK!
>> FUNKY KONG, EVERYONE.
>> I'LL TAKE THAT.
>> KATHLEEN WAS ANNOUNCED AS NEW
YORK CITY'S FIRST RAT CZAR, A
TITLE FORMERLY KNOWN AS
MS. STATEN ISLAND.
LOSER.
>> YOU AND FUNKY KONG?
ARCHEOLOGISTS HAVE DISCOVERED A
THOUSAND-YEAR-OLD SCOREBOARD
USED FOR AN ANCIENT MAYAN BALL
GAME.
THE SCORE WAS MAYANS 24, NEW
YORK JETS, 0.
THE DEPARTMENT OF SANITATION HAS
LAUNCHED ITS FIRST CAMPAIGN WITH
MESSAGES SUCH AS, IF YOU LITTER,
YOU'RE GARBAGE, WHICH IS
ACTUALLY DIALLED BACK FROM THE
ORIGINAL VERSION, YOUR LITTER
BELONGS IN THE TRASH NEXT TO
YOUR WHORE WIFE.
>> A PROPOSED BILL IN CALIFORNIA
WOULD CREATE AN ALERT SYSTEM FOR
MISSING BLACK WOMEN AND KIDS.
THIS IS IN ADDITION TO THE ALERT
SYSTEM FOR MISSING WHITE WOMEN
AND KIDS, THE NEWS.
>> WITH MENTAL HEALTH STRUGGLES
ON THE RISE, SOME AMERICANS ARE
SEEKING ALTERNATIVE FORMS OF
WELLNESS.
HERE TO HELP IS MEDITATION GURU
GENESIS FRY.
>> HELLO, COLIN.
JOIN ME, WON'T YOU, ON A GUIDED
MEDITATION TO THE CENTER OF YOUR
MIND.
>> OH.
LIKE RIGHT NOW?
>> YES, COLIN.
COLIN, ARE YOU READY TO MEET
COLIN?
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED.
>> COLIN, TAKE MY HAND.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
>> OKAY.
>> I WANT YOU TO PICTURE
YOURSELF AFTER THE SHOW TONIGHT,
COLIN.
AS USUAL, FANS ARE TAKING
PICTURES WITH CHLOE, SELFIES
WITH BOWEN.
YOU STEP OUTSIDE, AND NOT A
SINGLE BALL FLASHES.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> RELAX.
RELAX YOUR ARMS, RELAX YOUR
BODY, RELAX YOUR ARMS.
SOFTER THAN I IMAGINED.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU GET INTO YOUR CAR WITHOUT
ACKNOWLEDGING YOUR DRIVER.
HE'S LIKE A SUBHUMAN CREATURE TO
YOU.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> WHAT'S HIS NAME, COLIN?
>> IT'S -- LET'S JUST FOCUS ON
THE MEDITATION RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU GET HOME AND YOU REWATCH
TONIGHT'S UPDATE.
21 LAUGHS FOR MICHAEL, FOUR FOR
YOU.
YOU'RE IMPROVING, BUT IT'S SLOW.
>> GENESIS, COME ON.
>> SHH, COLIN, RELAX.
RELAX.
>> I'M RELAXED.
>> RELAX.
>> REPEAT AFTER ME, I AM COLIN
JOST.
>> I AM COLIN JOST.
>> I AM FULL OF LIGHT.
>> EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE.
>> WAS SIMPLY HANDED TO ME.
>> I AM NOT SAYING THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY, COLIN.
IT'S NATURAL THE FIGHT AGAINST
THE BREAKTHROUGH.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY HOLDING MY
HAND.
>> I KNOW.
WOW, IT'S SO SOFT.
YOU'VE NEVER DONE AN HONEST
DAY'S WORK IN YOUR LIFE.
>> NO, NO.
>> RELAX.
PICTURE IT, COLIN.
YOU'RE IN YOUR DRESSING ROOM
AFTER THE SHOW TONIGHT STILL
FUMING ABOUT THE BILINGUAL
MONOLOGUE!
>> THAT WOULD NOT UPSET ME!
>> YOU'RE SO ALONE.
THE ONLY PERSON IN THE WORLD WHO
CARES ABOUT YOU IS ANTONIO.
>> WHO IS ANTONIO?
>> YOUR DRIVER, COLIN!
SO SUNDAY MORNING, PICTURE IT,
COLIN, YOU'RE STANDING IN THE
NBC GIFT SHOP TO SEE IF ANYONE
RECOGNIZES YOU.
>> SUNDAY MORNING?
>> NO ONE DOES.
FINALLY, A MAN SEES YOU, HE RUNS
UP TO YOU SO EXCITED.
COLIN JOST, COLIN JOST, HE SAYS.
AND HE SERVES YOU WITH COURT
PAPERS.
>> COURT PAPERS?
>> TURNS OUT, SOMEONE DOES
RECOGNIZE YOU, 32 WOMEN TO BE
EXACT.
>> YOU'RE MAKING THIS UP.
>> REPEAT AFTER ME, COLIN.
I AM COLIN JOST.
>> I AM COLIN JOST.
>> I AM A STAR.
>> IF YOU WANT TO SHINE LIKE THE
SUN, FIRST YOU HAVE TO BURN LIKE
IT.
>> IF YOU WANT TO SHINE LIKE THE
SUN, FIRST YOU HAVE TO BURN LIKE
IT.
>> YOU DID IT, COLIN!
YES!
>> WOW.
I ACTUALLY LOVE THAT LAST QUOTE.
DID YOU JUST COME UP WITH THAT?
>> NO.
IT'S A FAMOUS HITLER QUOTE,
COLIN.
AND NOW IT'S A YOU QUOTE TOO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GENESIS FRY, EVERYONE.
>> A NEW REPORT FROM THE CDC
SHOWS THAT IN 2021, CASES OF
SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASES
JUMPED BY 7% TO WHAT EXPERTS
DESCRIBE AS NURSING HOME LEVELS.
IT'S HAPPENING, GUYS.
>> A NEW STUDY SUGGESTS THE
AVERAGE MAN EXAGGERATES THE
LENGTH OF THEIR PENIS BY 20%,
BUT AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO ADD
20% FOR TIP?
>> TWO 81-YEAR-OLD WOMEN HAVE
TRAVELED THE WORLD IN 80 DAYS
AFTER THE POST OFFICE LOST THEIR
ASHES.
>> A GROUP OF HIKERS IN GREAT
BRITAIN HAD TO BE RESCUED WHEN
THEY GOT LOST AFTER TAKING
PSYCHEDELIC MUSHROOMS.
MORE EMBARRASSING, THEY NEVER
ACTUALLY LEFT THE HOUSE.
AND POLICE IN AUSTRALIA ARRESTED
A MAN AFTER HE WAS CAUGHT AT A
BUS STOP MASTURBATING FOR OVER
AN HOUR.
AUSTRALIA, WHERE THE POLICE LET
YOU FINISH.
>> SINCE THE START OF THIS YEAR,
OVER 400 ANTI --
[ LAUGHTER ]
SINCE THE START OF THIS YEAR,
OVER 400 ANTI-LBGTQ BILLS HAVE
BEEN INTRODUCED ACROSS THE
COUNTRY, MANY OF WHICH TARGET
TRANSYOUTH.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS SOMEONE
WITH THEIR OWN INTRODUCTION.
>> INTRODUCING SNL'S FIRST
NONBINARY CAST MEMBER.
IT'S MOLLY KEARNEY!
>> THANK YOU, MR. CHE.
>> MOLLY, WHAT IS ALL THIS.
>> WELL, AS YOU KNOW, I HAVE
BEEN WANTING TO COME TO UPDATE
AND TALK ABOUT TRANSPEOPLE, BUT
I HAVE FOR A MUCH LONGER TIME
THAN THAT WANTED TO FLY DOWN
FROM THE CEILING.
>> DID IT LIVE UP TO YOUR
EXPECTATIONS?
>> YEAH.
BUT THIS HARNESS IS PRETTY TIGHT
AND MY GROIN AREA IS BEEFED.
I HAVE BEEN HUNG UP ON MY
GENITALS FOR FAR TOO LONG, AND
I'M STARTING TO FEEL LIKE A
FREAKING REPUBLICAN LAWMAKER.
HELLO.
>> THAT'S AN AWESOME TRANSITION.
AS OF THIS WEEK, THERE ARE NOW
OVER 14 STATES THAT HAVE PASSED
BILLS RESTRICTING HEALTH CARE
FOR TRANSKIDS.
>> LISTEN TO THAT, MICHAEL,
RESTRICTING HEALTH CARE FOR
KIDS.
FOR SOME REASON, THERE'S
SOMETHING ABOUT THE WORD TRANS
THAT MAKES PEOPLE FORGET THE
WORD KIDS.
IF YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT
TRANSKIDS LIVES, IT MEANS YOU
DON'T CARE ABOUT FREAKING KIDS'
LIVES.
>> WOW.
I CAN TELL YOU'RE REALLY UPSET
ABOUT THAT.
>> I AM!
AND ALSO, MY LEGS ARE GOING
NUMB, AND I MIGHT PASS OUT.
>> HOW LONG WERE YOU HANGING UP
THERE?
>> LONGER THAN I WOULD HAVE
LIKED.
I TRIED TO CALL DOWN, BUT NO ONE
COULD HEAR ME.
AT ONE POINT, I HEARD A CREW GUY
SAY, IS SHE GONNA DIE UP THERE.
AND THEN ANOTHER GUY WAS LIKE,
YOU MEAN, ARE THEY GONNA DIE UP
THERE.
AND THEN THEY BOTH WALKED AWAY
AND DIDN'T HELP, WHICH FEELS A
LOT LIKE HOW TRANSPEOPLE ARE
BEING TREATED RIGHT NOW.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
WE HAVE A CODE WORD FOR
EMERGENCIES, AND IT WAS
TRANSRIGHTS.
OH, MY GOSH.
GOOD GOLLY!
THAT WAS THE CODE FOR CONFETTI!
MY BAD.
>> THAT WAS SO LOUD.
>> WELL, YEAH.
PEOPLE NEED TO WAKE UP!
WE ARE MAKING TRANS KIDS GROW UP
TOO FAST.
WE SHOULD BE KEEPING THEM SAFE,
AND WE NEED TO LIFT THEM UP.
NOT ME, THEM.
I MEAN THE KIDS!
THEY GOT MY PRONOUNS RIGHT,
LET'S GO!
WAIT A MINUTE.
BEFORE I GO.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, KIDS, IS
WRONG.
AND YOU DON'T NEED TO BE SCARED.
OUR JOB IS TO PROTECT YOU, AND
YOUR JOB IS TO FOCUS ON BEING A
KID.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE ME FLYING IN
THE SNL SKY.
THERE'S A BUNCH OF DUDES ASKING
YOU ABOUT YOUR CROTCH AND
CONTROLLING WHEN AND WHERE YOU
GET TO PEE.
IF YOU JUST HANG ON, YOU'LL LOOK
UP AND REALIZE, YOU'RE FLYING,
KID.
HEY, MR. CHE, AND I STILL IN THE
FRAME?
>> YOUR FEET A
NADINE IS SUCH A BEAUTIFUL
BRIDE.
>> CHANDLER IS ONE LUCKY GUY.
>> HE SURE IS.
HEY, SHINA, BY THE WAY, I KNOW
IT'S TOUGH COMING TO A WEDDING
AFTER A BREAKUP, BUT I THINK
IT'S SO SWEET YOUR BABY SISTER
CAME ALL THE WAY HERE TO BE YOUR
DATE.
LISA, IT'S SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S CUTE.
BUT MY BOX IS CLOSED TONIGHT.
>> I'M SORRY.
WHAT?
>> KELLY, GIRL.
PAY NO MIND TO MY SISTER.
SHE'S SUCH A JOKESTER.
>> ALL RIGHT, MA'AM.
THIS IS ALL THE DRESSING WE
COULD FIND IN THE KITCHEN.
>> WHY IS THIS RANCH BLACK?
>> IT'S BALSAMIC.
>> YOU REALLY LIKE YOUR
DRESSING, HUH?
>> YEAH, EVERYONE ELSE IS JUST
EATING THE SALAD AS SERVED.
>> AND EVERYONE ELSE IS ABOUT TO
BE SICK.
NOT ME.
TOSS MY SALAD.
THE MORE DRESSING YOU PUT ON IT,
THE LESS LIKELY YOU ARE TO GET
ECOLI.
I NEED TO STAY HEALTHY.
I GOT TO BE IN COURT IN THE
MORNING.
>> LISA IS THE LEAD LITIGATOR ON
A CLASS ACTION SUIT AGAINST
BUILD-A-BEAR.
>> THEY GAVE A BUNCH OF
BUILD-A-BEARS TO BALD KIDS, AND
I AIN'T GOT TO TELL YOU WHAT
HAPPENED NEXT.
>> THAT IS REALLY GREAT WORK.
>> SIS, SWITCH ME SEATS, YOUR
LESBIAN FRIEND IS TRYING TO GET
THE BOX TONIGHT.
IT AIN'T HAPPENING, BOO.
>> DO I COME OFF FLIRTING?
BECAUSE I'M NOT.
>> KELLY, YOU'RE FINE.
LISA, CAN YOU PLEASE CHILL?
>> WHATEVER.
I'M GOING TO SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND FIX THIS SALAD.
OKAY?
HOLD ON.
HUH-HUH.
WHO THOUGHT THIS WAS A GOOD
IDEA?
RAW SOLOMON.
>> WELL, IT'S SMOKED.
>> SMOKED.
PINK AS IT IS, LOOK LIKE A FRUIT
ROLLUP, HUH-HUH.
COOK MY MEAT.
I'M GOING TO MIX THIS ALL UP FOR
ALL OF US.
YEAH?
OKAY.
>> WELL, ANYWAYS, I HAVE TO TELL
YOU GUYS ABOUT THIS EMBARRASSING
DATE I WENT ON.
>> THIS ABOUT TO BE A MEAN ASS
SALAD.
>> SO WE WENT TO A MOVIE AND
ENDED UP BACK AT MY PLACE.
AS SOON AS WE WALKED IN, A MOUSE
RUNS ACROSS --
>> YOU GOT ANY RANCH ON YOU?
>> CAN YOU PLEASE JUST EAT?
>> BUT I NEED RANCH.
EVERYBODY KNOWS LETTUCE IS NASTY
WITHOUT RANCH.
>> NOW I'M WORRIED THAT HE SAW
THE MOUSE.
BUT THEN HE'S LIKE, NO, NO, IT'S
FINE.
WE'LL JUST GO TO MY PLACE.
>> WOW, WHAT A GENTLEMAN.
>> SMART MAN.
>> COME ON, SIS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO US JUST
CHILLING?
>> I AM CHILLING.
I'M CHILLIN.
WHAT?
I'M MINDING MY BUSINESS.
THIS SALAD GOING TO BE ALL
RIGHT, BUT I'M GOING TO NEED IT
TO BE BUSSIN.
I HEARD THE GIRL.
SHE SAID HER HOUSE IS DIRTY.
>> LISA.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
LISA, CAN YOU PLEASE JUST --
>> I NEED THE LERJ.
I NEED THE LEVERAGE.
WHAT?
GIRL, I HEARD THE GIRL.
CARMEN SAN DIEGO TRYING TO GET
THE BOX WHILE SHE GOT
RATATOUILLE AS HE ROOMMATE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
A PIECE OF SALMON HIT MY MOTHER.
>> THIS WEDDING IS A MESS.
PEOPLE GETTING HIT WITH SOLOMON
AND THEY PUT RAW SOLOMON IN MY
SALAD.
>> IS SHE SAYING SALMON?
>> THIS IS RUINING OUR SPECIAL
DAY.
>> OH, BECAUSE WE GAY?
>> NO.
WE'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF OUR
FIRST DANCE.
>> WHY YOU OVER HERE TALKING TO
ME?
DANCE, BITCH.
Y'ALL SEE THIS, RIGHT?
THERE IS CHAMPAGNE ALL IN THE
FOOD, VEGETABLES EVERYWHERE.
THAT MARRIAGE IS DOOMED.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU DON'T
WANT TO GET SICK, BUT THIS IS
ALL KIND OF YOUR FAULT.
>> YEAH.
YOU HAVE BEEN DRESSING THAT
SALAD IN A REALLY INSANE WAY.
>> HOLD ON.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO LET Y'ALL
ATTACK MY SISTER, LISA WHO CAME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE FROM
TEMECULA TO BE MY DATE.
MAYBE SHE'S THE TYPE OF SISTER
THAT CAN'T TAKE NOWHERE.
>> I KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
MAYBE SHE'S SUCH A BAD LISTENER
IT MAKES YOU WONDER IS THIS
WOMAN HARD OF HEARING?
>> I KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BUT WHEN IT'S ALL SAID AND
DONE, THIS MY BLOOD RIGHT HERE,
AND SHE BETTER NOT HAVE ONE DRY
LEAF IN THAT DAMN BOWL.
>> TOSS MY SALAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
Y'ALL DONE PISSED ME OFF.
I LOST MY APPETITE.
I'M LEAVING.
>> WHERE IS SHE FROM AGAIN?
>> TEMECULA!
>> HAS IT CRUISED BY ON LOOKS
ITS ENTIRE LIFE?
>> DO YOU CATCH YOUR DOG LOOKING
AT ITSELF IN THE MIRROR?
>> BUT IT SUCKS IN ITS CHEEKS
LIKE THIS?
THEN YOUR DOG MIGHT BE THE
PERFECT CANDIDATE FOR ENTER
STAGE WOOF, ACTING SCHOOL FOR
DOGS.
>> I'M YOLANDA BATISTA, AND I'M
DONNA COLONOSCOPINI.
>> GET IN HERE, HENRY.
NOW, SURE, SURE.
OH, HENRY, OH, OH.
HENRY'S DOING A LITTLE IMPROV.
SURE, HENRY IS THE TOTAL
PACKAGE.
WINNING SMILES, GOLDEN LOCKS,
AND THOSE BIG PHOTO GENERALIC
NUTS.
>> GOOD LOOKS AREN'T EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW, CASTING DIRECTORS WANT
TO SEE EMOTIONAL RANGE.
>> WATCH.
HENRY, YOU JUST FOUND OUT YOU
HAVE WORMS.
SHOW ME SHOCK.
ALL RIGHT.
>> HENRY, YOU'RE GOING TO THE
VET TO GET CLIPPED, AND THEY
DON'T MEAN YOUR NAILS.
SHOW ME FEAR.
PERFECT.
YOU BOOKED IT.
>> YOU MAY HAVE SEEN THE TRAILER
FOR THAT MOVIE, NONE OF OUR DOGS
GOT THE JOB.
>> BUT DAMN IT, THEY GOT IN THE
ROOM.
JUST LIKE COCO HERE.
>> COCO MAY NOT BE CLASSICAL
BEAUTIFUL, BUT SHE'S DRIPPING IN
SEX APPEAL.
>> IS SHE EVER, AND SHE'LL GO
FULL NUDE IF THE PAY IS RIGHT.
>> SHE'LL DO IT EVEN IF IT'S
NOT.
>> LOOK AT THOSE NIPS.
LOOKING FOR A DOG THAT CAN PULL
OFF ROMANTIC COMEDY?
THEN LOOK NO FURTHER THAN ROMEO.
>> AND ROMEO IS UNDER CONTRACT
WITH DISNEY.
>> HOW?
BY LEARNING OUR PATENTED LADY
AND THE TRAMP TECHNIQUE.
WATCH.
ROMEO.
WOW.
I THINK I'M IN LOVE.
>> THAT'S ADORABLE.
AND CASTABLE.
>> HIGH FIVE, ROMEO.
HE'S A REGULAR MARLAN BRAND DOG.
OUR INSTRUCTORS ARE READY TO
HANDLE EVERY ASPECT OF YOUR
DOG'S CAREER FROM SOCIAL MEDIA
TO HEAD SHOTS.
>> AND WE CAN EVEN COVER UP
EMBARRASSING SCANDALS.
>> YEAH.
LIKE IF YOUR DOG IS STINKY AND
GETS CAUGHT HOOKING UP WITH A
CAT.
>> NOT CONVINCED.
LISTEN TO THIS SATISFIED
CUSTOMER.
>> THIS IS MAITI.
HE HAS BEEN TAKING CLASSES HERE
FOR YEARS.
YOU PROBABLY RECOGNIZE HIM FROM
THE MOVIE MOONLIGHT WHERE HE WAS
WALKING BY ON THE BEACH DURING
THE HAND JOB SCENE.
THAT WAS A FUN SET.
THANK YOU DOG ACTING SCHOOL.
>> DID SOMEONE SAY ACCENT?
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS TALENTED
POOCH.
>> BISCUIT, DO FRENCH.
>> LE WOOF!
>> WOW, LE WOOF, I THINK THAT
MEANS, THE BARK.
>> WE EVEN TEACH PUPPIES.
LIKE THIS LITTLE FELLA NAMED
JEY BEAN.
>> NOW, JELLY BEAN JUST GOT CAST
IN A MOVIE WHERE HE PLAYS AN
ALIEN THAT DESTROYS SEATTLE.
LET REHEARSE.
GO.
>> GO, GO.
>> DESTROY.
GET IN THERE.
OH, SEATTLE.
OH, NO, SEATTLE.
OH, NO.
OKAY.
WOW.
GOOD JOB, JELLY BEAN.
>> PEOPLE IN SEATTLE ARE DEAD.
SO ENROLL TODAY, AND IN NO TIME,
YOUR DOG WILL BE THE NEXT CLINT
EASTWOOF.
>> AT ENTER STAGE WOOF, ACTING
SCHOOL FOR DOGS.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, KAROL G!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> MEN GET THEIR NAILS DONE ALL
THE TIME.
>> I'M NOT LIKE OTHER MEN, NINA.
>> WE'RE READY FOR YOU TWO.
I LOVE WHEN WE GET COUPLES IN
HERE.
SCREW THOSE GENDER ROLES.
WHAT COLOR ARE WE GOING TO PAINT
YOU?
>> SOMETHING NEUTRAL LIKE TAN OR
NUDE OR SOMETHING.
>> YOU PROMISED.
>> THINGS ARE DIFFERENT NOW,
NINA BECAUSE AS OF YESTERDAY,
I'M THE GUINNESS WORLD RECORDER
HOLDER FOR THE WORLD'S LONGER
FINGERNAILS.
>> YOU SAID YOU WOULD CUT THEM
AFTER YOU WON.
>> I CAN'T CUT THEM AFTER ONE
DAY OF BEING FAMOUS!
>> I'M TIRED OF LIVING LIKE
THIS.
IT'S EMBARRASSING!
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
EMBARRASSING IF I SHOWED UP TO
THE GALA WITH SHORT NAILS.
>> SO THE WATER IS GETTING
COLD --
>> THAT WOULD BE LIKE IF THE
WORLD'S TALLEST MAN SHOWED UP
AND THEY CUT OFF HIS LEGS.
>> HAVE WE LANDED ON A COLOR?
>> I DON'T WANT COLOR.
I WANT RIDGY, CRAFT, AND YELLOW.
GOD, NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ME.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME, GREGG?
WHERE IS MY CERTIFICATE?
I DESERVE THE GUINNESS WORLD
RECORD FOR WIPING YOUR BUTT FOR
12 YEARS!
>> YOU ACT LIKE I'VE NEVER TRIED
TO WIPE MYSELF.
I DID ONCE AND ALMOST DIED.
>> YOU PROMISED ME!
YOU PROMISED ME YOU WERE GOING
TO CUT YOUR NAILS, LEARN WONDER
WALL ON THE GUITAR, AND DO HAND
STUFF TO ME FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> I NEVER SAID THAT.
>> YES, YOU DID.
I HAVE IT ON VOICE MAIL.
>> AS SOON AS I GET THIS WORLD
RECORD, I'M GONNA CUT THESE
NAILS, LEARN WONDER WALL ON
GUITAR, AND DO HAND STUFF TO
YOU.
NOW WHAT TIME ARE YOU GETTING
HOME?
I NEED YOU TO WIPE ME.
>> WHO AM I WITHOUT MY NAILS,
NINA?
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER COMED TO
THIS NAIL SALON.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER MOVED TO
SEATTLE, AND I I SHOULD NEVER
MARRIED YOU.
>> WELL, IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL,
I'M TAKING MY RING BACK.
>> GO ON, TAKE IT!
GO, TAKE IT THEN!
GO!
KEEP GOING, GO, GO ON NOW, TAKE
IT.
I'M OUT OF HERE, BOO.
>> GREGG!
GREGG!
>> SO THERE IS A CANCELLATION
FEE.
>> I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE.
>> SAY IT.
OUT LOUD.
SAY IT.
>> THAT GUY FROM THE GUINNESS
BOOK OF WORLD RECORDS WITH THE
WORLD'S LONGEST FINGERNAILS.
>> ARE YOU AFRAID, OR ARE YOU
NOT?
OH, NO, YOU CRACKED MY
FINGERNAIL!
NOW THESE LOOK GROSS!
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE LEFT FOR
REAL.
>> OH, DON'T WORRY, MAMA.
I SEE THIS ALL THE TIME.
MEN JUST NEED AN IDENTITY.
IF IT'S MEANT TO BE, HE'LL COME
BACK.
>> I'M BACK.
AND I CUT MY NAILS.
AND DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
HAND STUFF.
>> YOU WIPE YOUR BUTT!
>> SCREW THOSE GENDER ROLES!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> THANK YOU SO MUCH!
THAT WAS AN AMAZING SHOW.
I WANT TO THANK THIS AMAZING
CAST.
THEY ARE THE BEST PEOPLE.
THIS FOR SURE HAS BEEN THE BEST
WEEK OF MY LIFE.
THANK YOU, KAROL G!
>> THANK YOU.
>> LAUREN, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
PLEASE BRING ME BACK.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING TONIGHT!
>> THANK YOU!