Trip
alliances
Both
Powerful
Love
Mom, dad,
this is Crown
Prince Mohammed bin Salman.
And we're together
now, getting off gorgeous.
But we are vibing.
- You are too kind.
- Habibi.
Habibi Habibi
What a word.
But we've been having
a lot of fun in the Middle East.
I've been having a great time.
We've been eating a lot
of meals, sitting on the floor,
dipping our fingers straight
into various groups and spreads
that I politely scrape
under the rug
and go eat at a mobile
McDonald's.
That you build for me
isn't that way.
BA ba
ba ba ba ba. He's loving it.
I, of course, am a big fan
of everything that Saudi Arabia has to offer,
from the oil
to the money
to end of list.
But it's been a fantastic week
in the Middle East.
I also went to Qatar, the UAE
and much like God did during
Passover, I skipped Israel.
Oh well,
I bet you were happy about that
though.
You like that, right?
No comment.
Don't comment.
You don't want to say anything.
Cancel culture.
But I did make this trip.
I didn't make this trip
for myself.
I want to make that clear.
I did this
for the American people
and in many ways myself
by my personal enrichment.
I did that too.
I did very well on this trip.
Got a lot of cool stuff.
The Qataris
gave me a $400 million plane.
Can you believe that?
And people said
that was some sort of bribe.
Not true,
not true because they haven't
asked for anything in return.
Well, not yet.
All right, so it's a pre bribe.
It's a pre bribe.
But now people are saying
I should really be flying
in an American plane.
No, thanks. Andy,
have you seen
what's going on with our planes?
The radar is down
and the screen is blank.
Newark
Darling, watch.
Where are we going?
Where are we flying for
our vacation?
I need directly into the ground.
But we just made it big.
Oh shut up!
But we just made a big airplane
deal with the Crown Prince.
Tell them about it.
Saudi Arabia will buy $1 billion
worth of aircraft from Boeing.
Your funeral.
I met with the leader of the UAE
in Abu Dhabi.
We like to say Abu Dhabi.
Abu Dhabi do like the
late great Fred Flintstone.
The UAE
promised to invest over $1
trillion in the US.
I love Dubai because they Dubai
a lot of weapons.
But I've had a great trip
here in the Middle East.
It was very much a boys trip.
I don't think
I saw a single woman.
What's up with that,
All the time Just walking into a room
full of boys.
Hi, boys. Boys again?
The women are all hiding.
It's like a nation of Melania's.
Very funny.
There it is.
Look at that baby. I'm
going to look that up.
I'm cooking.
I'm having a great time.
I was just going to say it.
I love the Arabs.
I don't want to go home.
Let me stay.
Get me to Allah's country.
Everyone loves me here.
They're not allowed to.
They have to love you.
If not, bye bye.
Inshallah.
Oh, I love that.
Donald. Please, stay.
They build a palace
next to mine and stay.
Oh, I sadly, I can't.
I have to get back home.
Luckily,
we have our own little slice
of Saudi Arabia in America.
A dry
desert area
filled with people
who are way too
into their religion.
We call ours UTAH
and I do very well there,
so I can't stay here
in the Middle East.
In fact,
you know what?
I can't even stay in this sketch
much long
going. I have to leave. You know what?
Because it's the SNL
finale season 50.
Worst one yet.
Okay. Get up.
Go ahead, get up.
Get out of there.
Let me sit here. Yeah,
go with him.
Go eat
some chips in the hallway.
I'm here
to break the fourth wall.
Oh, it's nice here
with all the young people.
Look at her. Wow.
Seven zero
sevens or more.
Sit on the floor.
Six and below to the bleachers
you go.
Get over it.
Over.
It's like an Gutfeld joke.
Kind of rhymed, right?
But, you know,
since it's a finale,
that means after tonight,
you won't be
seeing me here for a while. Oh.
Oh, well,
not the fake fun version of me
that makes you smile.
The real one
will still be omnipresent.
You can't escape me, right?
I'm everywhere.
Even in your dreams.
Like the late, great
Freddy Krueger.
Supposed
So see you again in the fall.
If we still have a country, right.
It's a coin toss
this summer,
everyone
and live from New York.
It's Saturday Night
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN-- SCARLETT
JOHANSSON!
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HOSTING
THE FINALE OF SEASON 50.
IT'S BEEN A HISTORIC SEASON.
I'M SO PROUD TO BE A PART OF IT.
I FIRST HOSTED THIS SHOW WHEN I
WAS 21 YEARS OLD,
SO IT'S CRAZY
TO BE BACK HERE LIKE WHAT, THREE
YEARS LATER.
TIME REALLY FLIES.
IT IS SO GREAT TO BE BACK,
BECAUSE AS MANY TIMES AS I'VE
STOOD ON THIS STAGE,
IT NEVER
STOPPED FEELING SPECIAL.
♪ IT'S 11:30 ON A SATURDAY
FINALE OF SEASON 50 ♪
♪ IT'S CHAOTIC AND CRAZY THE
WHOLE WEEK IS HAZY ♪
♪ BUT THERE'S NO PLACE THAT I'D
RATHER BE ♪
OH, HEY.
THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
MIND IF I TAKE THE NEXT VERSE?
OH, WELL, IT'S SORT OF MY
MONOLOGUE.
OF COURSE, NO PROBLEM.
♪ SOMETIMES WE PLAY LIKEABLE
CHARACTERS ♪
♪ OTHER TIMES WE PLAY J.D.
VANCE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT ALWAYS FUNNY WE DON'T
DO IT FOR MONEY ♪
♪ OR ELSE SARAH WOULD BUY BETTER
PANTS ♪
- HEY, GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU SINGING ABOUT?
- NOTHING.
- GREAT PANTS, BY THE WAY.
- OH, THANK YOU.
♪ SING US A SONG YOU'RE THE
MONOLOGUE ♪
♪ SING US A SONG TONIGHT
♪ 'CAUSE WE'VE MADE 50 YEARS OF
GREAT MEMORIES
EVERY SATURDAY
NIGHT ♪
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN-- BILLY
JOEL!
WROTE THIS SONG.
I THOUGHT BILLY JOEL WAS COMING
OUT.
OH, MIKEY, SO CUTE, SO
SIMPLE.
WELL, I HAVE TO BE HONEST, I
LOVE A SINGING MONOLOGUE.
REALLY?
I LIKE THE ONES WHERE THEY TAKE
QUESTIONS FROM THE AUDIENCE.
OH, LET'S DO BOTH, THEN.
♪ DOES ANYONE HERE HAVE A
QUESTION ♪
♪ YES OVER HERE I HAVE ONE OR
TWO ♪
♪ COULD YOU INTRODUCE ME TO A
DINOSAUR ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I CALLED ON
YOU ♪
IT'S WEIRD, BUT THIS PLACE IS
KIND OF LIKE MY HOME.
♪ I'VE BEEN IN OVER 300
SKETCHES ♪
♪ AND BY MY COUNT I'VE BEEN IN
FOUR ♪
♪ IT'S JUST OUR FIRST YEAR BUT
WE'RE GLAD TO BE HERE
♪ HERE IS FOR JOSEPH AND BETH
- MY NAME ISN'T BETH.
- CLASSIC BETH.
♪ MARCELO AND DEVIN ARE FRIENDS
OF MINE ♪
♪ ANDREW AND JAMES I HOLD DEAR
♪ IT'S BEEN A GREAT SEASON AND
SARAH IS LEAVING ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL GONNA MISS YOU NEXT
YEAR ♪
WITH, WHAT?
DID YOU GUYS HEAR SOMETHING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, LEAVING?
♪ SING US A SONG IT'S YOUR
MONOLOGUE ♪
♪ THE 50th SEASON IS THROUGH
♪ IT'S LASTED FOREVER WE DID IT
TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND WE GOT TO SPEND IT WITH
YOU ♪
♪ IT LASTED FOREVER WE DID IT
TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND WE GOT TO SPEND IT WITH
YOU ♪
GREAT
STICK AROUND, WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK!
It's channel four.
Wake up for the news
because
you're watching channel four.
New York City News
because it is channel four.
It's channel four.
That was our weather man, Keith.
He said any one of the shot
to try something new
for our intro and. Well.
Shot taken. Keith.
Swing and a miss, folks.
Good morning, New York.
And thanks, as always,
for waking up with us.
I'm Susan McGrath.
I'm Tommy Nolan, our usual third
wheel.
Claire Connors, is out today.
I can't legally say why,
but let's just say
she gave birth to something.
But filling in for her.
This morning,
we have another member
of our channel four family,
Denise Jones
from the Nightly News.
So happy you're here.
Joining us, Denise.
Thanks for having me.
All right.
Let's get to our top stories
coming up later this morning.
It's a doggone miracle.
A new layer of astroturf
has been installed
at the Riverside Dog Park.
And later
we tip our cap, a chino
to Little Bean coffee shop,
which donates
all their leftover pastries
to a local homeless shelter.
Well, cap a chino,
and it's a doggone miracle.
I love those little puns.
Yeah,
they make our morning stories
a little extra fun
for our early risers.
Well, that's so creative.
We don't usually do
those on the nightly news.
All right, well,
you want to take the next one?
- Sure thing.
Next up, the hospital.
Last night, a woman
was assaulted on the train.
I know, I did a pun.
Well, Denise,
I just think that story
was a little too intense
for that.
Oh, I get it.
You mean the pun is only okay
when it's something like this?
Later,
we tip our cappuccino, know
to the woman
who was assaulted on the train.
Somehow worse.
You know, why
don't we just focus
on the lighter stories, okay?
Right.
Life is like a box
of chocolates.
And Elmhurst
Candy store celebrates 100 years
in business.
And I'll have what she's having.
A Queens couple dies
in an apparent murder suicide.
No. Wrong again.
Denise, you don't have to do
the puns for the sad ones.
Oh, okay. Got you. So,
like this.
Take me to the river
if you want to see the dead body
that washed up today.
And coming up later this hour.
Who took his dong out?
An Ohio teacher did it.
Didn't miss no more puns.
Oh, I like doing them.
We don't get to do them
at night.
Oh, he ain't
that woman. Stay tuned for the latest update
on the man over cannibal.
You know what?
Why don't we throw it to weather
so we can take a little break
from Denise over here.
Keith.
Thanks, Susan.
This week
it's going to be sunny.
Back to you, Denise.
That was it.
Thanks, Keith.
And in national news,
after Lovisa baby,
another infant
has been deported.
Thankfully, we have a reporter
in the field standing by.
Calvin,
how's it going out there?
Well, it's
a grim scene here at 11 time
where I want my baby back.
Baby back, baby back.
Says this mother of a girl
who was kidnaped from a Chili's.
Calvin. No,
this is serious.
Sorry.
I just got inspired
by the niece.
Thank you.
It's just so refreshing
to finally see
a strong, intelligent
woman behind the desk
I've
Worked in for five years.
Ooh. Can I try a pun, too?
You used to call me on my cell
phone.
It's been 12 days since I'm
in contact with my daughter.
No.
Well, much like I do every time I make
love to my beautiful wife,
I think we have no choice
but to finish early.
Sorry. That was weird.
Why don't you take us home.
There, Keith?
Good bye for now.
Channel four is over.
Yes, the news is done.
>>> HELLO!
HI.
YOU GUYS LOOK SO DOWN.
YOU SAD THE SEASON'S OVER AND
YOU ONLY DID LIKE TWO VIDEOS?
DID THREE AT LEAST.
DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S JUST WITH EVERYTHING
GOING ON IN THE NEWS RIGHT NOW,
IT'S JUST-- THINGS FEEL KIND OF
BLEAK.
YEAH, FEEL LIKE THE WORLD IS
FALLING APART.
HEY, KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS NEED?
A VACATION.
VACATION?
WE HAVE WORK, IT WILL BE
EXPENSIVE.
TICKETS ARE ON ME.
YOU EVER FLOWN FIRST CLASS
BEFORE?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, BOYS?
A LITTLE VACAY?
♪ I'VE WANTED THIS MY WHOLE
LIFE ♪
♪ FIRST CLASS TICKET WATCH THE
RECLINE ♪
♪ GOT THE EFFING VIBE ON
♪ OH MY FEELING LIKE A HIGH
LIFE ♪
♪ HASTA LA LUEGA TO ALL MY
HATERS ♪
♪ I'M ONE OF THE GREATEST
♪ FLIGHT ATTENDANT WITH THE
THING OLD BANGS
HANDING ME
DRINKS LIKE GO OFF KANG ♪
♪ IS THE NAME
WHEN YOU'RE
DEALING WITH PLANES ♪
♪ LISTEN UP I'M TALKING TO YOU
JERK ♪
♪ FALLING IN THE SKY ALL THE WAY
TO NEWARK ♪
DID YOU SAY NEWARK?
YEAH, WHY?
WHAT'S UP?
WE'RE LANDING AT NEWARK?
YEAH, NEWARK.
IN NEW JERSEY.
DAMN, IT'S KIND OF WINDY OUT
THERE, HUH?
DIDN'T WE FLY OUT OF
LaGUARDIA?
LIKE A HALF-HOUR DRIVE.
THIS IS AWESOME.
COME ON, WE'RE IN FIRST CLASS,
RIGHT?
♪ NOW I'M UP IN FIRST CLASS I
DON'T GET TIME ♪
IS SOMETHING GOING ON AT
NEWARK?
LIKE, ARE THERE PLANES CRASHING
THERE OR SOMETHING?
NO, I THINK THEY'RE JUST
LOSING THEM.
LOSING PLANES?
YEAH, LOSING TRACK.
YEAH, LOSING THE PLANES IN
NEWARK, BUT THE CRASHING IS
HAPPENING, LIKE, EVERYWHERE ALL
THE TIME NOW.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT, YEAH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
ARE YOU NOT NERVOUS?
♪ I AIN'T GET ON NO PLANE
AAH, AAH!
DIDN'T LIKE THAT AT ALL.
APOLOGIES FOR THE TURBULENCE,
FOLKS.
BUT GOOD NEWS.
WE'VE BEEN CLEARED FOR LANDING
AT NEWARK.
AT LEAST, I THINK SO.
HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING YET.
OH, NO.
HM.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT'S SCARY.
ALL THE TVs JUST TURNED OFF.
ONCE WE LAND, I SHOULD BE
GOOD.
ONCE WE LAND, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
GOD'S GOT ME.
GOD'S ALWAYS GOT ME.
♪
♪ I CAN'T BE ALONE LORD DO YOU
HAVE ANY SHOWS IN YOUR PHONE ♪
♪ THE ONLY SHOW I HAVE IS
"LOST" ♪
WHY DO YOU HAVE ONLY THAT
ONE?
I DIDN'T KNOW I'D BE HERE
TODAY.
BAD NEWS, FOLKS.
WE ARE WHAT WE CALL IN THE BIZ
FLYING BLIND.
OH, GOD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, BE HONEST, DO YOU THINK
WE'LL MAKE THE ARTICLE AT LEAST?
WHAT?
DO YOU THINK THE ARTICLE WILL
BE SCARLETT JOHANSSON AND PLEASE
DON'T DESTROY DIE IN PLANE
CRASH?
OR JUST YOU?
WHO'S PLEASE DON'T DESTROY?
WHO DID YOU THINK WE WERE?
PARDON ME WHILE I GIVE A
QUICK CALL TO OUR AIR TRAFFIC
CONTROLLER.
COME ON, PICK UP, PICK UP, PICK
UP, PICK UP.
HELLO?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HI.
HAVING FUN UP THERE?
NO, I'M NOT HAVING FUN.
SIR, DO YOU HAVE OUR
COORDINATES?
UH-- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S MY FIRST DAY.
WHAT?
IT'S YOUR FIRST DAY?
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH.
THERE'S-- THERE'S LIKE NO ONE
HERE.
OH, FANTASTIC.
MAYBE YOU TELL ME, LIKE--
WHAT COLOR IS YOUR PLANE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S A FRICKIN' PLANE.
I'M GOING TO OPEN THE
EMERGENCY EXIT AND JUMP.
DO NOT OPEN THE EMERGENCY
EXIT.
OH, GOD.
THAT'S A NEW ONE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, LOOKS LIKE THIS IS IT,
GUYS.
ANYTHING TO GET OFF YOUR CHEST?
THIS MIGHT SOUND CORNY, BUT
THE ONLY THING I REGRET IS THAT
"AVENGERS" DIDN'T MAKE MORE
MONEY AT THE BOX OFFICE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT?
WE ARE GOING DOWN.
IF ANYBODY CAN HELP US, PLEASE,
PLEASE!
I CAN'T GIVE UP ON THEM.
YES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
COORDINATE.
I'M STARTING TO GET MY SIGNAL
BACK.
WIND RESISTANCE.
I SEE THE RUNWAY, I SEE THE
RUNWAY.
I THINK I'M DOING A GOOD JOB.
I THINK I'M SIGHTING THEM.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S WORKING,
IT'S WORKING!
♪ I CAN SEE YOU NOW
♪ NOW GLIDE IT GLIDE AND IT LAND
THIS PLANE ♪
WE DID IT!
YES!
SO HAPPY.
NOW WE CAN FINALLY ENJOY OUR
VACATION IN NEWARK.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING YOU PUT
YOUR MIND TO.
Wow. I can't believe what
was supposed to be a one night stand
turned into three weeks
together.
Yes. I'm also having trouble
believing that.
So I've been thinking.
My lease is up.
Your lease? Is it?
So I could either be homeless
or perhaps there's
another arrangement.
Like you get another apartment.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is kind of awkward,
but you're kind of
sitting at our table.
Your table.
The bar area is first.
That got here first
that will be served.
Okay.
Well, we've been coming here
every Friday
for the past three weeks.
And this is where we sit.
Right, baby?
Oh, right.
Oh, baby.
We got you, babe.
This is our special table.
They need to move.
I mean, baby, let's just go.
Maybe I go to my apartment
and you go to any place
that's different than dad.
No way, no way.
We're not just going to leave
because they told us to
say something. Defend my. Honor.
Okay. I got this, baby,
I got this.
Hey, hey.
That's right.
He's about to beat your ass.
You hear that?
He's going to go. Look, I'm.
You could have woken up.
Oh, so now
you're making my man cry.
Let me tell you something
in a way you can understand.
What?
You heard
me done that stuff there.
Baby, baby, baby, baby, you.
You are not making any sense.
You're not the only one
who can speak Spanish, bitch.
I used to work at Chipotle.
Listen to me closely.
Damn, they're really going at it
over there.
Yeah, I feel like I'm
watching a telenovela go home.
They do that thing where
they slap each other and kiss.
Wait, what?
Yeah. You know, in every novella
there's a slap kiss.
You see, in their culture,
the line between passion
and violence is paper thin.
Baby, please come over here.
Do not listen to this woman.
I don't protect you. Oh, yeah?
You better protect her
because I'm about to.
baby.
Baby, baby.
You're talking about it.
Let me handle this.
Okay?
What are you laughing?
What did you just say?
I said,
there's no reason to find.
And they make, great couple.
And he never
he should never let her go. Oh.
Oh. Really?
That's sweet.
Baby, let's get out of here
and go back to your place.
Because tonight
I'm going to give you not.
Okay, baby.
Let's go.
Okay.
Well, maybe we can learn
a little something from them.
So tonight
I'm going to give you grab
You have me.
tetas
Wow. Wow.
Would you look at that?
It's like they always say I'm.
So I just found out
there's a second Kansas City.
Hey, you guys know
I love Colin, right?
Of course.
He's your thing for life.
Yeah. And we're, like,
totally happy.
But, like, it's normal
to have little crushes here
and there, especially
on someone from the cast.
Who is that creepy?
Creepy Longfellow? No.
It's Bowen
This is just so sweet.
And, I mean, nothing's obviously
going to happen.
I'm married. He's gay.
Yeah. No, Bowen is not gay.
Bowen is straight as hell.
Bowen Bowen Bowen
Oh, really?
But at the 50th, I saw him
sobbing over Cher.
It's all fake, girl.
He just styles up
the gay for clout.
Trust me.
That man's a p hound through
and through. Ha!
I got what that is.
Seriously? Hello? Hello.
Hey, I missed you.
Of course he's with Gina
Gershon.
We're just here to see,
you know, slower.
Okay.
So how's the week been going?
You getting along with the cast?
Yeah, fine.
Why? You heard something
Oh, Bowen
What's up? Colin?
Hey. Could work
this season. Keep it up.
I'm excited to watch you
grow. Thanks, man.
Do you mind?
Leaving? Yeah, yeah.
No problem.
Hey, let's take the stairs.
It's only 30 flights.
Scarlett.
Scarlett's my Jurassic harlot.
We should be talking you
that way.
I'm married.
Probably shouldn't
be doing a lot of things.
It's better.
Watch it. Mr.
Moo-Deng
Listen,
you know Collins, my SNL brother
and I never did
anything to hurt him back.
I f his wife.
There's something
I wanted to ask you.
What? I guess I was wondering.
What that yang do
Scar
We do. Need protection.
No. It's fine.
I can bottom
Ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow!
I need to see you again tonight.
I'll cover for you.
You can buy mine.
Yeah. Think I might like to.
Am going to wear something
pretty.
Okay.
Oh. Hi.
Hey. We
hanging out tonight.
Right?
Should I come on in?
Oh. Oh. Nice place.
So, are we cooking?
Hey. Hey, listen,
tendies in the air fryer.
I can see it at rehearsal.
You sleep with ego?
What do you want me to say?
I don't. Know that
we had a connection.
Oh, so now we're dating?
I just found out who you were
this morning.
Oh, Simon.
Nothing to.
You got to suffocating me.
Screw it.
I'm going
to Tokyo and inventing I.
By the way.
Hey, mama, I need you. To.
You keep asking yourself why.
You'll drive yourself crazy.
I got gaslit by Bowen
Yang
Go to Disneyland Tokyo.
Is that Emily Ratajkowski? Yeah.
Okay, listen, I.
Never get your back blown out
by a gay guy.
Amen sister
Work. Hi.
Can you press 147, please?
Sure.
Thank you. God.
- Oh, you're Mike.
- Myers
Yes, I am. Yes.
Thank you.
Dan, this is my staff.
Good to meet you, though.
Nice to meet you. Hi.
Sorry to bother you.
I just have to say this.
I'm a huge fan of yours, Mr.
Meyers. Oh.
Thank you. That's very,
very kind. Thank you.
And what's your name?
I'm Janice,
and I just love all your movies.
My girlfriends and I quote,
track, like, all the time. Oh.
Thank you.
That's a little weird, but,
It's my first time in New York.
You just never know
what celebrity
you're going
to run into here. It's true.
Oh, my God, is that Kanye West?
Yeah.
What are you talking about
with my song?
Come on,
give me one good reason.
Besides that,
besides that.
How is it not relatable?
Everybody got a cousin.
Oh, I guess it's my SOP again.
So nice to meet you, Mr. Meyer.
No, it is not.
It is not your stuff.
What are you doing?
You can't leave me alone in here
with him. Fine.
I heard he's doing.
Okay.
You might. Meyers. Right.
Kanye. What's up man?
It's just. Yay
now. Sorry, gay, I.
I guess it's been a while.
Yeah.
Since that Hurricane
Katrina benefit.
Yes. You know,
when I told the world
that George Bush don't care
about black people on live TV.
Yes. And you just had to
stand there looking stupid?
Yes. So,
What do you been up to?
Oh, me?
I'm in the KKK now.
Of course you are.
Yes, yes.
How's your kids?
My kids. My kids are safe.
That's good.
Family stability is important.
Isn't it, though? Yes.
Yeah.
Disney stuff is crazy, right?
What? Daddy?
He's on trial right now
for, like, a bunch of stuff.
Oh, yeah? Yeah,
I heard about that.
Yeah, yeah. It's so crazy, man.
You think you know a guy
turns out to be a full, crazy
monster, man?
Yeah, right.
So what happened to you?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Not one thing.
Let's wait for the next one.
Yeah. Know
there's plenty of room in here.
There's plenty of room
in this elevator.
So Maya's
that Jewish Protestant, actually.
Protestant?
Yeah. Nice. Yeah. You know what?
We should take a selfie
together. Come on. Oh, no.
The elevators
are so slow sometimes.
What was that?
You must have hit stop
or something.
I think we stuck.
Man, we got to be here
for a while now. Oh, no.
Should we, jump up and down
till something happens?
Nah, man,
I don't like doing crazy stuff.
You don't understand.
I get really claustrophobic.
Oh, trust me, I understand.
I'm a few phobias myself.
But right now,
we just need to relax.
You want some knots? No.
I'm good.
I just got to get out of here.
I gotta calm down, Mike.
You sounded like a lunatic.
Why don't I play you
my next single man?
It's a love song, okay?
Yeah, it's called
squeezing on my grandpa.
Booty.
Oh, wait.
We're moving again. Okay.
Thank you. God.
You're welcome.
Oh. This is me.
Take care of yourself.
You. Yeah you do. Shrek.
Do you know a guy?
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, BAD
BUNNY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ SI TE QUIERES DIVERTIR
CON ENCANTO Y CON PRIMOR
SOLO TIENES QUE VIVIR
PA ONDE ♪
♪ UN VERANO EN NUEVA YORK
NUEVA YORK ♪
♪ SI TE QUIERES DIVERTIR
CON ENCANTO Y CON PRIMOR
PERO QUE ES ESTO ♪
♪ SOLO TIENES QUE VIVIR
Y ESTE FRIO
UN VERANO EN NUEVA YORK
UN RATITO NA'MA ♪
♪ EY EY EY
4 DE JULIO 4 DE JULY
ANDO CON MI PRIMA
BORRACHA RULAY ♪
♪ LOS MIO' EN EL BRONX
SABEN LA QUE HAY
CON LA NOTA EN HIGH
POR WASHINGTON HEIGHTS ♪
♪ WILLIE COLON
ME DICEN EL MALO EY
PORQUE PASAN LOS ANO'
Y SIGO DANDO PALO ♪
♪ VENDIENDO DISCO'
COMO CUADRO'E FRIDA KAHLO ♪
♪ EL PERICO ES BLANCO SI SI
EL TUSI ROSITA EH-EH ♪
♪ NO TE CONFUNDA' NO NO
MEJOR EVITA EY ♪
♪ UN SHOT DE CANITA
EN CASA DE TONITA AY
PR SE SIENTE CERQUITA ♪
♪ SI SI SI
TENGO EL CAMPEONATO
NADIE ME LO QUITA ♪
♪ THE BEST IN THE WORLD
NUMBER ONE THE BEST
IN THE WORLD OKAY
PUERTO RICO ♪
♪ COMO BAD BUNNY VA A SER
REY DEL POP EY ♪
♪ CON REGUETON Y DEMBOW EY
CON REGUETON Y DEMBOW SI
CON REGUETON Y DEMBOW ♪
♪ COMO BAD BUNNY VA A SER
REY DEL POP EY
CON REGUETON Y DEMBOW ♪
♪ ME SIENTO COMO EL LAPIZ
EN CAPEA EL DOUGH
CUANDO YO NACI
FUE QUE NACIO EL FLOW ♪
♪ DE LAO A LAO PING-PONG
FLOW PESAO BIG PUN
CON SILENCIADOR LES ROBAMO
LAS GATA' JAMES BOND EY ♪
♪ YO ESTOY EN LA MIA
NO TENGO ADVERSARIO' NO ♪
♪ CON LOS YANKEES Y LOS METS
JUAN SOTO
A CORRER QUE OTRA VE'
LA SACAMO'EL ESTADIO ♪
♪ SI TE QUIERES DIVERTIR
CON ENCANTO Y CON PRIMOR ♪
♪ SOLO TIENES QUE VIVIR
UN VERANO EN NUEVA YORK ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
It's Weekend Update with Colin.
Jost and Michael Che.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Good evening everyone.
Welcome to weekend.
Update on Michael Che.
Colin Jost.
Well, President Trump traveled
to the Middle East this week,
and if I were him,
I would have just stayed there
because it looked awesome.
Trump arrived in Saudi Arabia
where he was greeted
with a lavender carpet which
matched the color of his tie
and also the length.
They also rolled out a mobile
McDonald's truck for President
Trump's visit,
featuring Saudi Arabia's
most popular new burger.
The MC journalist.
President Trump,
while on his trip, said
that Iran has sort of agreed
to terms for a nuclear deal.
In the same way, Trump
has sort of agreed
to uphold the Constitution.
Many people
in Saudi Arabia were very happy
with President Trump's
visit to the country,
because rich Saudis
love to fly out thick blonds.
The Democratic
National Committee protested
President Trump's plans
to accept a $400 million luxury
jet from Qatar
by flying a banner over
Mar-A-Lago reading Qatar a Lago.
It's the kind of hilarious stunt
that makes you realize
why the Democrats
will never win again.
Ethical experts are also warning
that Trump may owe
political favors to countries
who give him lavish gifts.
But based on the way
he left the Middle East,
I think I know how
Trump is going to pay them back.
President Trump has signed
an executive order
giving refugee status to
white people from South Africa.
You know, I could have sworn
that white people had it
good in South Africa.
Must be the Mandela effect.
The Trump
administration announced
that after face
to face talks with China,
it is lowering tariffs
from 145% to 30%,
which is a little like bragging
about taking the knife out.
Robert F Kennedy Jr,
whose shirt collar traps
all the blood in his head,
was criticized
for posting pictures of himself
swimming in a Washington,
DC, creek despite signs
warning it was contaminated
with raw sewage.
Oh, can you imagine
how many parasites are in there?
Said the Creek.
The Department of Homeland
Security
said they may participate
in a new reality show
in which immigrants
would go through a series
of challenges for a chance
to become a citizen.
It's called the real
housekeepers of Orange County.
According to an
according to a new tell
all book, Biden's inner circle
revealed that they were worried
the president would need
a wheelchair in his second term,
especially after they were all
done stabbing him in the back.
The white House also announced
that Vice President J.D.
Vance will travel to the Vatican
for Pope Leo's inaugural mass.
And I'm not a huge
fan of his outfit.
Train engineers went on strike
yesterday, completely
shutting down new Jersey
transit lines into New York.
In case you were wondering
why the city smelled so nice.
In what counts
as good news in 2025,
the Menendez brothers
have been resentenced
for the 1989 murder
of their parents
after the judge said
he did not believe the brothers
posed a risk if released,
unless someone adopts them.
That's a good point.
At this point,
I joked.
After several
troubling incidents
at Newark
Liberty International Airport.
Many people are worried
about airplane safety,
but one person is more worried
about airplane food.
Here to comment.
You know her.
You love her.
You got her fined by the FCC.
Show some love for mixology.
I know you get.
I'm sorry.
What is. This?
Down this flight stack.
And I ain't even served
the food yet.
Flight attendant came around
asking me
if I want some butternut squash
ravioli.
More like, but not offer me
that.
Mister, you put some meat in it.
Squash that sucker.
Can't even give me a whole
can of soda.
Stingy.
Want to hand me a dry ass
Biscoff?
More like
you got to piss off Biscoff.
I'm sorry.
Is all of your stand
up about food?
God damn.
I am starving.
Flight attendant saying
the only sandwich they got on
this plane is a turkey pesto.
Auch a bother.
All I know is this bitch about.
To lose her life
that rat was harder than my man.
When I get out the tub.
His name's
Maurice, but I call him Trey
because he stay in the upright
and lock position.
Cousin.
His ex-wife.
That's right. Play.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I really don't think this is
helpful.
Come in. Please.
I'm eating that. She asking?
Do I want some apple
cranberry compote?
I'ma need a computer to Google.
What the hell that is?
Hey, y'all went
into peanuts off the.
Plane because everybody
want to have an allergy.
If you don't take a Benadryl
and shut your.
Gas up,
the hell?
This.
This Newark story is serious.
And how bout that, TSA,
Putting on that Papa Smurf
gloves, thinking
they can fill me up.
Just because I got a God.
Complex empty stack.
What? That's right.
Stretch, y'all.
You are supposed to be talking
about Newark Airport.
I literally am listening here.
Menopause.
Been making me whole.
Menopause?
Well.
Let's just say, Miss Egg,
you don't need no hollandaise
sauce
because I already know how to.
Benedict.
Okay, here you go.
Please. There you go. Not.
Please wrap this up.
No collusion.
Thank you, JetBlue,
for having a bitch.
And if we hit turbulence, Colin,
just take a Benadryl.
And what?
Shut your gas up.
Enjoy the flight.
Mrs...
New research
shows that too much sitting
could damage your brain.
Which explains why Stephen
Hawking was such a dumb ass.
Dick's Sporting Goods announced
that it is buying Foot Locker
for more than $2 billion,
and will combine to form
Dick Soccer's.
Annual survey found
that the worst livers in New
York City are men from the Bronx
and Queens,
while women from the Bronx
and Queens safely keep
all their junk in the trunk.
A driver for Amazon was fired
after she was caught on a ring
camera defecating on a porch,
said the homeowner.
But that's what I ordered.
A new study suggests
that people who feel tired
all the time
could have suffered
a mini stroke,
which makes sense
because I always get sleepy
after a stroke.
Know?
I don't take time.
It was a heartwarming
one to end on.
You know, tonight is our season
finale, and we, I'm not sure
your last joke
took my breath away.
And we have a tradition here.
We're gonna give each other
joke Street
at the end of the season.
Yeah, we're making each other
three.
Jokes live on air that the other
person has never seen before.
But before we start,
it's SNL 50th season.
So I want to take a moment
to say something to our boss,
Lorne Michaels.
Lorne retire bitch.
Let me run the show.
Wow. Out the gate, Colin.
Well, maybe I should just
tell you the first joke.
How about that?
Oh, I get to do another.
Yeah, yeah,
it's all a joke, man.
CBS has premiered
the first hour long
daytime soap opera
with a predominantly black cast.
It'll air when black people
are home from work 24 hours.
The ticket.
Since you like that,
here's another.
CBS has premiered
the first half hour
long daytime soap opera
with a predominantly black cast.
It's called All My Children
don't know
who their daddy.
Movie
theaters are trying
to stop teenagers from screaming
and throwing popcorn
during the Minecraft scene
with the chicken jockey,
because some of us
are trying to masturbate.
But seriously,
Minecraft was a great movie.
I haven't been that excited
since I saw a white woman
drink unattended.
It's so exciting for you!
I wonder,
oh man, why isn't this
a new. Yeah, it could be.
And it could be nice. Yeah.
A new study finds that the hoots
and grunts of bonobos
show signs of complex thoughts
similar to human language.
Oh. So like that awful
halftime show.
You know,
before I tell another joke, I.
Want to take this opportunity
to apologize to someone I hurt.
Scarlett, can you come out here?
Oh, I just, you know, last.
Time we did jokes, I made Colin
do some tasteless jokes
comparing your vagina to Costco.
Roast beef?
Yes, I remember that.
Well, the fact is, I was just
lashing out because I'm jealous.
I've never even seen
a human vagina.
And notice I said human
because I
once spent the summer on a farm.
You found me.
Maybe I'm just embarrassed
about my own body.
I can't even take my hoodie off
during sex
because I have more nipples
than a pregnant dog.
Yes, I have heard that about.
You and Colin.
I'm sorry too, because I owe you
everything. Oh,
when Colin discovered me,
I was selling
crack outside the.
And now look at me selling crack
outside the American Girl doll.
I'm so thousands of jokes
for an update
and gotten dozens of laughs.
But I've never said the three
most important words of all.
I love you.
Oh, on.
Truth.
I love you too. Oh. Well.
Yeah.
Okay.
Before I continue.
Golden State Warriors
head coach Steve Kerr
is here with his family.
I got to meet his son,
Nick, and I love Steve.
I like Nick.
But I wouldn't say I'm
a Nick Kerr lover.
Besides, the Hollywood star.
Some psychologists say adults
can reduce stress by returning
to a childhood hobby.
Which is why I returned
to my favorite childhood hobby
topping off priests
with my pretty little mouth.
Speaking of which.
Lawn.
I'll do anything.
To run this show
For Weekend Update
I|m Michael Che I|m Colin Jost
Goodnight
All right, everyone,
welcome to day
one of shooting Penelope.
Secret. Yes.
It's a romance
about two women in the 50s
who fall deeply in love.
And, yes, I'm the director.
And yes, I am a man.
So we, Why don't I throw
to our assistant director who.
And this will make you all feel
better.
Is a woman.
Yay, woman. Thanks, Greg.
Actually, I'm non-binary.
Oops. Sorry.
Okay, so our first scene up
today will be the one where
Penelope and Madame Wilcox
first become intimate.
And to make sure everyone
feels safe and comfortable,
we've brought in two intimacy
coordinators.
Guys,
want to introduce yourselves?
Yeah. Hi, everyone. I'm Trish.
And this is an insane
coincidence,
but my name is also Madame
Wilcox.
Well,
thanks for being here, you guys.
Thanks for having us.
Now, where is our cast?
Right over here.
This is Annabel,
and this is Rachel.
Great to meet you.
So where's the dude?
Oh, there's no dude.
Just the two women.
Yeah.
Okay, so it's just a kissing
scene, right? Right.
That's great.
No, guys, it's a full love scene
between two women.
But how would that even work?
What do you mean?
Oh, no.
He's just confused
because he doesn't get
how two buns make a hot dog.
I get it, I love it.
But wait, like, two donuts isn't
exactly a balanced breakfast.
It's simply too much tunnel,
not enough train.
Okay.
I'm sorry, have you guys never
worked on a queer set before?
Or as us allies
like to call it, an overdue set?
Am I right? Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Just get it together.
Whoops. I'm sorry.
Yeah. Of course. We've worked on
queer sets.
I mean,
I myself am ally passing.
But it's
different for girls, right?
Like gay guys, I get a
but it's basically of a dude.
I'm sorry.
Do you think lesbians don't
have sex?
Oh, well, I hope this isn't
offensive, but real sex.
No, no I don't.
You know what?
He's just having trouble
understanding
how you'd pay without putting
a credit card in a reader. Oh.
Is it like Apple Pay
where you just tap the Googles?
Sorry, dude.
The Googles.
Seriously? My guy.
This is highly offensive
to lesbian folks.
Actually,
that's not totally wrong.
Oh, she's so annoying, dude.
Sorry.
They are so annoying.
You know what?
Maybe
just try to picture it. But.
Guess I could give it a shot.
Oh. Well, that is nice.
You know, perhaps there's
some online videos of two ladies
that I could watch
as further research.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go
watch some videos of two ladies
right now.
Wow. Okay.
He was
in a hurry with the weather.
Wait, what's the weather.
What's the weather.
What's the website.
App. Yeah okay
guys we got to get going here.
Can we move on with the scene?
You know what?
Let's just do it,
Hooray
What's up man?
This is TV tech.
We talked to your favorite cast
from your favorite show.
Yeah, and we're so excited.
This was our most requested
show this year.
Joining us
today is the cast of the hit
romance Summer Lake. Hey.
Thanks for being here, guys.
We've got a ton of questions
for the whole cast.
There's so much for
the fans are dying to know.
But we're going to start
with the internet's boyfriend,
Danny Cheeks.
Oh. Hey, guys, it's me.
So, Danny,
first question is for you.
Your character is always wearing
his signature hoodies.
Were those
from your real closet?
No. I wish, but the wardrobe
department knew what was up.
They really did.
And next question.
Danny,
how did you get into acting?
Well, I love watching
TV, so I wanted to try it.
And our next
question is for you, Rochelle.
What's harder
being a woman or being black?
Oh, that's my question.
Yeah. So let's go back to Danny.
Was it fun shooting at the lake?
Oh, it was fun, but it was hot.
Yeah. Low hot.
And, Jade, when's the last time
you took plan B?
Whoa. Don't ask that.
Okay, so, Danny, do you have
a favorite on set snack?
Oh, man. That's hard.
Maybe pretzels.
Ooh. Nice. Salty.
And now, Kasey,
you're not as attractive
as the other cast members.
That's not a question.
It's what the fans are saying.
So, Danny,
who are you dating these days?
Oh, I don't kiss and tell.
Of course, that's private.
So, Taylor, you just had
a really bad divorce.
Whose fault was
it? You or your husband's?
It was
a girl, and it was my fault.
Oh, wait.
Danny, is it fun having abs?
Yeah, I love it.
Why can't we get.
Questions like that?
Okay, Kasey, here's a fun one.
You recently got married.
Congrats.
So why isn't your husband
a Ukrainian refugees?
That was a fun one.
I had fun.
Danny, when's the last time
you laughed really hard.
Watching TikTok pranks?
Where shall we go to? You.
Deadline reported that you're
being written out of the show
next season.
Is it because someone leaked
your nudes?
I'm just learning about
all parts of that right now.
Really? It's everywhere.
Now, Danny,
what's your favorite?
Everything.
Oh, Danny. Hold up.
Am I being written
out of the show?
Rochelle. Drop it.
Next question. Jade.
Who's your favorite cast
member to party with?
That actually is fun.
I love going out with Taylor.
Oh, flame and Jade.
If you could vote one religion
off the face of the earth,
which one would you pick?
No. Pass. Okay. Here's another.
How come all of your
exes are white?
The pass.
I'm Kasey,
you good face, but bad hair.
You have mental problem.
Excuse me.
And Michelle, what are you.
Going to do now
that you're unemployed?
Is that confirmed?
Yes. And,
Danny, music or pictures?
Music.
And finally, to all the women.
Gun to your head.
Why do lesbians dress like that?
What do you. Mean?
Now, let me rephrase.
If a lesbian was raised in a lab
and never saw another person,
would she still dress like that?
You know, it's crazy.
This is the best interview
we've done so far,
and we're out of time.
This was awesome.
I wish we had more
time. Oh. Me too.
Yeah. Me too.
This was really,
really interesting.
Hey, that's what I thought.
Oh my God. Same.
Thanks for watching, everyone.
And make sure to join
our discord.
We're going to post Danny's baby
pics and
everyone else's old tweets
to us.
I was cute and I still am. But.
>>> ONCE AGAIN, BAD BUNNY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ HOY SALI DE NUEVO, PERO
YA QUIERO ALGO NUEVO, CREO ♪
♪ SI ME VE' POR AHI
NI ME CONOCE'
CINDERELLA DESPUE
DE LAS ♪
♪ YA ME CONVERTI
VAMONOS DE AQUI
QUE ME GUSTA COMO HUELE'
Y MAS COMO TE MUEVE' ♪
♪ DIME YA
CUANDO VOY A PROBAR
TU PERFUMITO NUEVO ♪
♪ LA OTRA VE' NO TE LA VI
PAPI, SE QUE TE LA DEBO ♪
♪ DIME YA
CUANDO VOY A PROBAR
TU PERFUMITO NUEVO ♪
♪ HOY ESTOY PA TI
QUE VAS A HACER SI ME PEGO ♪
♪ ACABO DE MIRAR EL
RELOJ Y SON LA'
SIGNIFICA QUE YA NO
TE VO'A DAR BREAK ♪
♪ SIGUE MIRANDO ASI
SIGUE MIRANDO ASI
SIGUE MIRANDO ♪
♪ QUE TE LO PONGO AQUI MISMO
MM, SIGUE BAILANDO, MAMI
QUE TE ESTOY MIDIENDO
EL RITMO ♪
♪ NO PARECE LEO NI ESCORPIO
PA MI QUE ELLA TIENE
SU PROPIO SIGNO ♪
♪ FRIA, SENTIMENTAL, ESTA
EN TEMPORADA
DE PORTARSE MAL ♪
♪ A VECE' ES DIFICIL MEDITAR
Y SOLO QUIERE GRITAR
O BUSCARME PA CHINGAR ♪
♪ Y YO SE LO VOY A DAR
A LA HORA QUE SEA ♪
♪ SI YO BAJO P'ALLA ABAJO
VA A SUBIR LA MAREA ♪
♪ LO' OJITOS SE LE MAREAN
BABY, YO VO'A HACER
QUE TU CREA' ♪
♪ EH-AH, DIABLO, TU ERES
UNA BELLAQUITA IGUAL
QUE YO ♪
♪ PERFUMITO NUEVO
TU HUELES CABRON
POR POQUITO TE ROMPO
EL MAHON ♪
♪ DIME YA
CUANDO VOY A PROBAR
TU PERFUMITO NUEVO ♪
♪ LA OTRA VE' NO TE LO DI
MAMI, SE QUE TE LO DEBO ♪
♪ BABY, TU ERES UNA ESTRELLA
ESA BOCA SABE A CARAMBOLA ♪
♪ FUEGO, DESDE QUE TE
VI ME PUSE ROJA
CON LOS OJOS ME
QUITASTE EL TRAJE ♪
♪ TE TENGO BAILANDO
SIN MODALE'
DIANTRE, TU Y YO
SOMO IGUALES ♪
♪ HOY LE DIMO Y MANANA
LE DAMO
DE WEEKEND EN COAMO ♪
♪ EN LA MONTANA TE VO'A
HACER LA RUSA, EY
QUN COJONE', QUN TN TIENE'
QUE ME PONE EN MUSA ♪
♪ MAMI, TN TE VE' BIEN
A MI LAO
SI TU ESTAS
YO NO MIRO PA'L LAO ♪
♪ CINCO-SEIS
ME TIENES DOMINAO
ME IMAGINO CONTIGO PELEAO ♪
♪ PAPI, TU TE VES BIEN
A MI LAO
CONTIGO
YO NO MIRO PA'L LAO ♪
♪ CINCO-SEIS
TE TENGO DOMINAO
Y TODAVIA NO HEMOS
NI CHINGAO ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> AND NOW, VICTORIAN LADIES AT
LUNCH.
OH, IT IS SO WONDERFUL TO SEE
YOU ALL AGAIN.
I DO SO TREASURE OUR LUNCHES
TOGETHER.
AND YOUR CHEF IS MAGNIFICENT.
LOOK AT THIS INCREDIBLE SCENE.
82 SAY I'M AS HUNGRY AS THE
HORSE THAT BROUGHT ME OVER HERE.
AND IT'S A NEW HORSE, I'VE
HEARD.
HOW FAST IS HE, AGAIN?
ABOUT ONE HORSEPOWER.
OH!
LADIES, IS EVERYTHING TO YOUR
LIKING?
WELL, I SEE BLOOD PUDDING AND
PICKLED COW'S FEET.
SO I'M IN HEAVEN.
OH, EXCELLENT.
AND HOW ARE THE JELLIED EELS
TODAY?
OH, EXQUISITE.
WE TAKE THE WHOLE EEL AND JUST
SMOTHER IT IN JELLY.
MM, I CAN'T WAIT TO TASTE
THAT TEXTURE.
MM.
AND THE CANDIED CLAMS, ARE THEY
FRESH?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
THEY ARRIVED LAST WEDNESDAY, AND
WE'VE KEPT THEM IN AN OPEN
WOODEN BOX.
OH!
AND THE BOILED CAT'S HEAD?
YES?
WAS THAT IN MAIN FASHION?
NOT AT ALL.
WHAT TYPE OF BIRDS WILL WE BE
EATING TODAY?
OH, THE MOST UPSETTING ONES,
MY LADIES.
EAGLES, HUMMINGBIRDS, PENGUINS.
AND I BELIEVE WE STILL HAVE A
FEW BABY PUFFINS.
NOT ANYMORE YOU DON'T.
YUMMY, YUMMY IN MY TUMMY.
MM, MM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND THE BLT, WHAT'S IN THAT,
AGAIN?
BUNNIES AND LITTLE TURTLES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND THE TURKEY CLUB, WHAT WAS
IT CLUBBED WITH?
THE BIBLE, OF COURSE.
AND WHAT WAS THAT SPECIAL ON
THE MENU, PANDA EXPRESS?
AH, YES, A PANDA THAT WE
PUSHED IN FRONT OF A TRAIN.
THAT'S HOW I WANT TO GO.
HA HA HA!
THIS IS ALL SO DELICIOUS.
MM, INCREDIBLE.
INDEED.
OH, YES.
IT'S THE BEST I'VE EVER HAD.
I LOVE THIS SASHIMI.
WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL.
NOW, BEFORE I GO, ANYTHING TO
DRINK?
I THINK FOUR BRIMMING GLASSES
OF DONKEY'S MILK WILL DO, RIGHT,
LADIES?
INDEED, INDEED.
DONKEY'S MILK, GERALD.
DON'T MAKE THAT MISTAKE AGAIN.
HA HA!
YOU UNDERSTAND WHY IT TOOK SO
LONG LAST TIME.
HA HA HA!
LADIES, BON APPETIT.
SO, WHAT DID EVERYONE DO
AFTER LUNCH?
I WENT TO THE BATHROOM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I WENT TO THE BATHROOM AS
WELL.
I WENT NUMBERS TWO THROUGH
SEVEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND HOW WAS IT FOR EVERYONE?
MINE WAS BAD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
MINE WAS THE WORST.
I WAS WEARING SO MANY LAYERS,
AND I DID NOT GET ANY OF THEM
OFF.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I THINK THE JELLIED EEL CAME
OUT WHOLE AND JUMPED BACK INTO
THE SEA.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YUM, YUM, YUM!
ARE THE LADIES READY TO ORDER
DINNER?
I MEAN, I GUESS WE COULD
SPLIT SOMETHING SMALL.
PERHAPS A HOT DOG?
WONDERFUL.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> THANK YOU, BAD BUNNY, MIKE
MYERS, I WANT TO THANK YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS TO THE
INCREDIBLE CAST AND CREW.
FOR THESE 50 YEARS.
SO AMAZING.
LORNE MICHAELS, WHEREVER YOU
ARE, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO WANT ME
TO SINGLE YOU OUT, BUT
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ARE A SINGULAR MAN.
WE LOVE YOU.