>>> CRIMINALS BEWARE.
THERE'S A NEW SHERIFF IN TOWN,
AND HE MEANS BUSINESS.
FIRST, HE THE HUNTED DOWN THE
JANUARY 6th INSURRECTIONISTS
AND
MADE THEM PAY.
NOW HE'S SEARCHING FOR
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS,
AND HE'S
COMING FOR WHOEVER HAS THEM,
DEMOCRATS, REPUBLICANS,
OR WHATEVER TRUMP IS NOW.
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO BE IN HIS
CROSS HAIRS.
HE'S ATTORNEY GENERAL MERRICK GARLAND.
HELLO.
I'M MERRICK GARLAND.
I MAY LOOK LIKE I WAS BORN IN A LIBRARY,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
MERRICK GARLAND DON'T PLAY.
AS YOU MAY HAVE HEARD,
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS HAVE BEEN FOUND
IN THE HOMES OF PRESIDENT
BIDEN AND FORMER VICE-PRESIDENT PENCE
WHOSE LAWYERS ARE COOPERATING.
AND ALSO, AT THE HOME OF FORMER
PRESIDENT TRUMP,
WHOSE LAWYER
PUT A HORSE HEAD IN MY BED.
SOME HAVE SAID THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT CLASSIFIES TOO MANY DOCUMENTS.
ABOUT 50 MILLION A YEAR.
THIS HAS LED PEOPLE TO ASK, DOES
RECOVERING THESE DOCUMENTS EVEN
MATTER?
TO WHICH I SAY, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT'S THE LAW.
AND I AM THE LAW.
TO ENFORCE THE LAW, I SENT TEAMS
TO SEARCH THE HOMES
OF SEVERAL
RECENT PRESIDENTS AND
VICE-PRESIDENTS.
STARTING WITH MIKE PENCE.
SPECIAL AGENT CONRAD NANCE WILL
BRIEF YOU ON WHAT WE DISCOVERED.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
UPON ARRIVING AT MR. PENCE'S INDIANA HOME,
I KNEW RIGHT AWAY
THIS MAN NEEDED A FRIEND.
WHEN HE OPENED THE DOOR, HE
SAID, YOU CAME!
WITH A BIG SMILE, AND HE OFFERED
TO MAKE US PANCAKES.
OUR SEARCH TURNED UP NO
ADDITIONAL CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS.
HOWEVER, IN AN ENVELOPE MARKED "TAX STUFF"
WE DISCOVERED
PHOTOGRAPHS OF THE COUNTRY POP
STAR SINGER SHANIA TWAIN
CUT OUT
FROM SEVERAL MAGAZINES.
WHEN CONFRONTED, MR. PENCE SAID,
I'M SORRY.
I'M DISGUSTING.
THEN WE INFORMED MR. PENCE THAT
WE WERE DONE AND HAD TO LEAVE.
HE SAID, HOW CAN YOU LEAVE WHEN
YOU'RE IT?
AND THEN TAGGED ME ON THE
SHOULDER AND RAN AWAY.
HOPING THAT I WOULD CHASE AFTER
HIM AND PLAY TAG,
WHICH I DID NOT.
I WILL SAY, THOUGH, THAT IF YOU
KNOW MR. PENCE,
IF YOU'RE
FRIENDS WITH HIM, CHECK ON YOUR
PEOPLE.
THAT'S ALL.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, AGENT NANCE.
NEXT, SPECIAL AGENT CASEY COMBS WILL DISCUSS
IF THERE WERE ANY
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS AT
VICE-PRESIDENT KAMALA HARRIS'
HOME.
COME ON NOW.
JOE BIDEN WON'T EVEN GIVE THIS
WOMAN A PEN.
YOU THINK SHE HAS CLASSIFIED
DOCUMENTS?
PLEASE.
KAMALA HARRIS WITH CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS.
WELL, WE HAD TO AT LEAST
CHECK.
THANK YOU, AGENT COMBS.
FINALLY, WE SEARCHED FORMER
PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA'S HOME.
SPECIAL AGENT DERECK KAY WILL
DISCUSS WHAT WE FOUND.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
DON'T MEAN TO BRAG,
BUT I WAS IN
BARACK OBAMA'S HOUSE.
NO BIG DEAL.
BUT IT WAS REALLY FUN.
MR. OBAMA OPENED THE DOOR AND SAID,
ARE YOU SELLING GIRL SCOUT COOKIES,
WHICH HAD US ALL
TOTALLY CRACKING UP,
LIKE
COMPLETELY DEAD.
WE THEN ENTERED THE HOME AND
WERE SHOWN A NUMBER OF THINGS,
INCLUDING 175 LETTERS FROM LIN MANUEL
BEGGING THE PRESIDENT TO
PERFORM HAMILTON.
OBAMA LIKE READ ONE AS LIN
MANUEL.
LIKE
DEAR MISTER
I'M NOT JOKING.
IT WAS SO FUNNY.
ANYWAY, WE ASKED HIM ABOUT
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS,
AND HE
SAID HE WAS, QUOTE, OUT OF THE
GOVERNMENT GAME
AND DOING THE
HOLLYWOOD THING NOW.
BUT THEN, BEYONCE CALLED HIM ON
HIS CELL PHONE,
AND HE IGNORED IT.
SO, YEAH, JUST LIKE A REALLY
COOL, FUN TIME.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE YOU HAVE IT, AMERICA.
IF YOU HAVE CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS
IN YOUR HOME,
I HAVE ONE
QUESTION FOR YOU.
YOU THINK THIS IS A GAME?
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU'RE PLAYING
WITH?
F AROUND AND FIND OUT.
HEY, BOSS.
WHEN WE DONE PLAYING WITH THESE
LITTLE PAPERS,
WE GOING TO HEAD
DOWN TO MEMPHIS AND MAKE SURE
JUSTICE IS SERVED DOWN THERE
TOO, RIGHT?
- I SINCERELY HOPE SO.
- YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
MY NAME IS MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
BUT TONIGHT, MICHAEL B. HOSTING.
MICHAEL B. JOKING.
AND HONESTLY, MICHAEL B. NERVOUS.
MICHAEL B. VULNERABLE.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
MICHAEL B. ALL RIGHT.
BECAUSE MICHAEL B. IN THERAPY.
IT'S BEEN A GREAT WEEK HERE AT SNL.
YESTERDAY, I HAD A CRAZY FULL
CIRCLE MOMENT.
WE PRESHOT SOME VIDEOS FOR THE SHOW.
WHEN I GOT TO THE STUDIO, I
REALIZED IT WAS THE EXACT SAME PLACE
I SHOT ONE OF MY FIRST
ACTING ROLES ON THE SOAP OPERA,
"ALL MY CHILDREN"
I WAS 16 YEARS OLD.
HERE'S A CLIP.
I TOLD YOU IN THE BEGINNING
YOU SET THE PACE.
SO YOU'RE NOT MAD?
NO.
SOMETIMES THE ANIMAL IN ME JUST
GETS KIND OF CRAZY.
PRETTY SURE I HIT PUBERTY
MID-HOWL.
THAT WAS 2003.
AND NOW 20 YEARS LATER, I JUST
DIRECTED MY VERY FIRST MOVIE, "CREED III"
BUT RIGHT AFTER
THAT, I WENT THROUGH MY VERY
FIRST PUBLIC BREAKUP.
MOST PEOPLE AFTER A BREAKUP ARE
LIKE, I'M GOING TO GET IN BETTER
SHAPE.
BUT I WAS ALREADY IN CREED SHAPE.
SO I HAD TO BE LIKE, ALL RIGHT,
I GUESS I'LL LEARN A NEW LANGUAGE.
ANYWAY, ESTOY EN RAYA.
AFTER THE BREAKUP, EVERYONE
THOUGHT I WAS SO HEART BROKEN.
I WAS AT A BASKETBALL GAME WHEN
THE NEWS BROKE OUT,
AND THEY
CAUGHT ME LOOKING LIKE THIS.
I WAS JUST CHILLING, BUT THE
INTERNET DECIDED THAT WAS ME
BEING SAD.
LUCKY FOR ME, IF YOU GOOGLE
MICHAEL JORDAN,
THE FIRST 8,000
RESULTS ARE THIS.
HEY, MICHAEL.
- WHAT'S UP, CHLOE?
- NOT MUCH.
SO I KNOW YOU'RE SINGLE, BUT DID
YOU KNOW THAT I'M SINGLE?
- DON'T YOU DATE THAT HOT
WRITER?
- NOT IF YOU'RE AVAILABLE.
HEY.
COULD YOU REMIND ME HOW TO SPELL
YOUR NUMBER?
HEY, CHLOE, DON'T YOU HAVE TO
GO AWAY?
I'M SORRY, BITCH.
HEY, MIKEY B.
- MIND IF I CALL YOU MIKEY B.?
- I WOULD RATHER YOU NOT.
OKAY.
A MAN WHAT KNOWS WHAT HE WANTS.
I LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE A CREED POSTER
IN MY BEDROOM.
OH, NICE.
I ALWAYS DREAMED OF PEOPLE
HAVING MY POSTER UP ON THE WALL.
YEAH, WALL, PRINTED ON TO A
BODY PILLOW.
WHATEVER.
EXCUSE ME.
GO ON, BITCH.
HEY, MICHAEL.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU WERE OUT HERE.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW I WOULD BE ON
STAGE DELIVERING MY MONOLOGUE?
SORRY.
I WAS JUST TAKING A WALK AROUND
THE STUDIO, AND I JUST THREW
THIS ON.
IS THIS A WEDDING DRESS?
I GUESS WE COULD TECHNICALLY GET
MARRIED NOW THEN, HUH?
THAT'S NOT HOW THAT WORKS.
OUR FIRST FIGHT.
MAKEUP SEX?
- EGO.
- FINE, MICHAEL.
MICHAEL, MICHAEL, MICHAEL.
BOY, YOU LOOKING FINE AS EVER AS ALWAYS.
- PUNKIE.
- I GOT THE SAME SUIT LIKE YOU GOT.
- AREN'T YOU GAY?
- I AM.
BUT YOU MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
AND I'M PUNKIE B. CURIOUS.
- I MEAN, EVEN VEGANS GOT CHEAT
DAYS, RIGHT?
- NO, THEY DON'T.
BOY, YOU SO FUNNY.
I SEE YOU AT THE AFTERPARTY,
BABE.
LOOK, I JUST WANT TO SAY I'M
SO GRATEFUL TO BE STANDING ON
THIS STAGE.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES I CAN TAKE
MYSELF A LITTLE TOO SERIOUSLY.
BUT TONIGHT, I'M GOING TO HAVE FUN.
I'M GOING TO GO FOR IT
AND
MAYBE, JUST MAYBE, LET THE INNER
ANIMAL GET A LITTLE CRAZY.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU TONIGHT.
STICK
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GOOD MORNING TODAY.
LATER IN THE HOUR, WE'LL BE
TALKING PIT BULLS.
WHO ARE THEY, WHAT DO THEY WANT
FROM US, AND HOW ARE THEY SO
YOLKED?
BUT FIRST, IT'S TIME FOR
CUISINE WITH FRANCINE.
CAN I JUST SAY I'M SO HAPPY
FRANCINE IS BACK.
ME TOO, AS I'M SURE MOST OF
OUR VIEWERS KNOW, FRANCINE WAS
GONE YESTERDAY BECAUSE SHE GOT
STUCK ON A RUN AWAY ROLLER
COASTER GOING 150 MILES AN HOUR
FOR 19 HOURS STRAIGHT.
NOW SHE'S BACK BETTER THAN
EVER AND NOT THE LEAST BIT PHASED.
HI, FRANCINE!
HI, RICHARD.
HI TANIA, IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK,
AND I'VE GOT SOME REALLY
EXCITING FLAVORS TO SHARE WITH
YOU ALL TODAY.
WOW, FRANCINE.
YOU LOOK NUTS.
DID YOU COME HERE STRAIGHT
FROM THE AMUSEMENT PARK?
SURE DID.
COULDN'T BE LATE TO BE BACK IN
THE STUDIO.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
SO WHAT'S ON THE MENU TODAY,
FRANCINE?
WELL, I HOPE YOU HAVE YOUR
PASSPORTS READY BECAUSE TODAY
WE'RE OFF TO ITALIA.
JOIN ME, WON'T YOU, FOR A
CULTURE ADVENTURE THAT WILL HAVE
YOU SAYING MAMA MIA.
TODAY, WE'RE EATING BUFFALO MOZZARELLA.
CROSTINI, AND OF COURSE A GLASS
OF CHIANTI.
SALUD!
NOW THAT'S GOOD VINO.
LOOKS LIKE THAT HIT THE SPOT.
AT LEAST THE PART THAT GOT IN.
MM!
REALLY COMPLEMENTS THE WINE.
SO MANY TWISTS AND TURNS AS MY
ROLLER COASTER RIDE FROM HELL.
WHAT?
I THINK SHE-- I THINK SHE
COMPARED THE WINE TO ALL THOSE
LOOP-DE-LOOPS.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE SOME VIDEO OF
THAT.
YEAH.
MUST BE HARD TO WATCH, HUH,
FRANCINE?
WHAT WAS THAT?
I COULDN'T HEAR YOU OVER THE
CRISPY CRUNCH OF MY CRISPY,
CRUNCHY, CROSTINI.
WELL, THANKS, FRANCINE.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE WEATHER
WITH OUR VERY OWN JASON BURRESS.
HI, GUYS.
IT LOOKS LIKE A DOOZY.
OBVIOUSLY WE FORGOT TO
MENTION THAT JASON WAS ALSO
TRAPPED ON THE ROLLER COASTER.
I ACTUALLY THINK WE HAVE A
PICTURE OF THAT.
OH.
SO HOW'S THE WEATHER LOOKING,
JASON?
IT'S NOT GOOD AT ALL.
WE HAVE SNOW COMING IN FROM THE EAST.
UH-HUH.
WE HAVE SNOW COMING IN FROM THE
WEST, UH-HUH.
SNOW FROM THE TOP, YEAH, AND
SNOW FROM THE BOTTOM.
LOOK, I'M DIZZY AS HELL FROM
THAT ROLLER COASTER RIDE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
SOMETHING SURE SMELLS GOOD.
OH, WHAT YOU COOKING OVER
THERE, FRANCINE?
JUST SOME MINESTRONE SOUP.
BUT CAREFUL, IT'S HOT.
YOU GOT TO BLOW ON IT. MM.
THAT LOOKS DELICIOSO. MM.
OH, MM, MM, MM.
YES.
GREAT.
WELL, I GUESS YOU GUYS MUST
BE PRETTY HUNGRY AFTER THAT
CRAZY RIDE. YEAH.
THE ONLY THING WE HAD TO EAT
WERE THE BUGS THAT FLEW INTO OUR
OPEN MOUTHS.
YEAH.
BUGS LIKE BUMBLEBEES, CICADAS,
AND ONE DOG-SIZED BAT.
NOW, THAT'S A SPICY MEATBALL.
WOULD YOU CARE FOR SOME
SPAGHETTI, JASON?
OH, OKAY.
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE TOGETHER.
OF COURSE YOU PROBABLY GOT
REAL CLOSE DURING YOUR TIME
TOGETHER ON THE ROLLER COASTER.
WAIT.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING NOW?
I THINK THEY'RE DOING A
LITTLE LADY AND THE TRAMP THING.
AWW, SO ROMANTIC.
I'M SORRY.
FRANCINE, IS THERE SOMETHING
UNDER YOUR SHIRT?
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
SAY HELLO TO MY LITTLE FRIEND.
IS THAT A BIRD KICKING ITS
LITTLE LEGS?
YEP.
HE FLEW STRAIGHT INTO HER
STOMACH AT 200 MILES AN HOUR.
THE DOCTORS SAY IF I PULL IT
OUT, BOTH OF US WILL DIE.
NOW BACK TO YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP NEXT, OUR EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW WITH THE TEENAGE BOY
WHO OPERATED THE ROLLER COASTER
AND WHY HE DID NOTHING TO STOP IT.
IT.
TWO REASONS:TOO DUMB AND TOO HIGH.
PRIDE OURSELVES ON A SMOOTH
FLYING EXPERIENCE.
OVER THE HOLIDAY SEASON, WE
MESSED UP.
OUR SYSTEM COLLAPSED, AND
THOUSANDS OF FLYERS WERE LEFT
STRANDED, AND YOU UNDERSTANDABLY
SCREAMED AT US FOR DAYS ON END,
EVEN MORE THAN YOU USUALLY DO.
AND SURE, WE LOST
$800 MILLION IN REV KNEW AND ARE
BEING INVESTIGATED BY THE FAA.
FOR STARTERS, WE ARE FINALLY
UPGRADING OUR ENTIRE COMPUTER
SYSTEM TO 2008 DELL COMPUTERS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE ARE SAYING GOOD-BYE TO THOSE
IBM THINKPAD LAPTOPS WITH THE
LITTLE RED NIPPLE IN THE MIDDLE.
NO MORE MISSING BAGGAGE AT
BAGGAGE CLAIM, GUARANTEED.
FROM HERE ON OUT, ALL LUGGAGE
WILL BE SORTED BY COLOR.
THAT MAKES IT YOUR
RESPONSIBILITY, NOT OURS.
SO IF YOU'RE GOING TO DALLAS,
BRING A RED SUITCASE.
BLUE BAGS GO TO CHARLOTTE.
AND GET TO THE AIRPORT EARLY
TO ENJOY OUR NEW PREMIER LOUNGE
LOCATED INSIDE STARBUCKS.
WE HOLD DOWN TWO OR THREE TABLES
FOR Y'ALL.
WE'RE MODERNIZING OUR AIR
TRAFFIC CONTROL NETWORK.
WE WILL BE USING OUR OLD IBM
THINKPAD LAPTOPS WITH THE LITTLE
RED NIPPLE IN THE MIDDLE.
NOW I GET A PROPER FLIGHT
SCHEDULE INSTEAD OF FINDING OUT
WHERE I'M GOING 15 MINUTES
BEFORE TAKEOFF.
AND NOW WE'RE STREAMLINING
CHECK IN BY NOT HAVING ONE AT ALL.
TRYING TO FILL UP THE PLANE
AND GO.
YOU GOOD.
WE'RE ALSO UPGRADING OUR
INFLIGHT STAFF STRICTLY WITH
PEOPLE WHO USED TO WORK AT
WAFFLE HOUSE.
COME AT THEM IF YOU WANT, BUT
THESE BIG PITCHES DON'T PLAY.
THAT'S ON US. MOSTLY.
SOME OF IT'S ON YOU.
YOU BOUGHT THE TICKET.
AGAIN, YOU BOUGHT A SOUTHWEST TICKET.
YOU OBVIOUSLY DON'T RESPECT
YOURSELF, SO WHY SHOULD WE?
THANK YOU.
FOR FLYING SOUTHWEST.
WELCOME ABOARD.
SOUTHWEST AIRLINES.
IF IT'S THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU,
JUST WALK.
THEN, SOMEHOW, THEY FIND NEMO.
NO, MAN.
THAT'S CRAZY, MAN.
IT'S A BIG OCEAN AND LIKE A
SMALL LITTLE FISH.
I KNOW, MAN.
THEY GOT LUCKY, MAN.
WHAT CAN I SAY, THEY GOT LUCKY. HEY.
CAN I GET A TOWEL?
YES, OF COURSE.
HEY, YOU AMERICAN?
I AM, YEAH.
ELLEN DEMENEMES?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, THE TV LADY, ELLEN DEMENEMES.
SHE ALWAYS COME OUT DANCING, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE ELLEN DEMENEMES.
YOU KNOW?
OKAY.
YOU DON'T KNOW ELLEN
DEMENEMES?
SHE'S MARRIED TO THE CAR.
THE PORSCHE.
THAT CHICK IS FUNNY, MAN.
YEAH, ELLEN DeGENERES.
CAN I PLEASE HAVE MY TOWEL?
THAT TOOK WAY TOO LONG.
YOU KNOW, LAST NIGHT, I SAW
THIS MOVIE, "MISSION:IMPOSSIBLE"
BUT THE MISSION NOT IMPOSSIBLE
BECAUSE HE GOING TO DO IT.
THEY SHOULD CALL IT
MISSION:HE PROBABLY GOING TO DO
IT.
WHAT'S UP, FELLAS, CAN I GET
A TOWEL POR FAVOR?
MY FRIEND ON DUALINGO.
YOU AMERICAN?
YEAH.
GIVE ME A CANNOLI OR I'M
GOING TO DROWN YOU.
THAT'S EASY FOR HIM BECAUSE HE
STRONG.
HEY, MAN.
HERE'S YOUR TOWEL, MAN.
GRACIAS.
TOTAL DELL BANO.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO THE
BATHROOM, MAN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
DID YOU GUYS SEE ELLEN
DEMENEMES?
ELLEN DEMENEMES.
NO, SHE'S NOT HERE.
I JUST WANTED TO CHECK IN
WITH MY TWO FAVORITE TOWEL GUYS.
QUESTION FOR YOU, MAN.
IS IT TRUE YOU'RE TRYING TO
REPLACE US WITH A MACHINE?
NO.
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT, NO.
COULD YOU PLEASE?
YEAH, MAN, BECAUSE THEN WE
CAN DO DIFFERENT JOB IN THE HOTEL.
I WANT TO FOLD THE TOILET PAPER
INTO A LITTLE TRIANGLE SO FOR
THE FIRST WIPE, IT'S CRAZY. YEAH.
AND I WANT TO BE THE CONSIERGE.
I GET A MAP, AND I CIRCLE THINGS
ON THE MAP, AND THEN I SAY, YOU
CAN GO THERE.
AS WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE ONCE
SAID, THE VERY SUBSTANCE OF A
DREAM--
EXCUSE ME.
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T SPEAK ENGLISH YOU GUYS
WANT TO KNOW A SECRET?
I DO SPEAK ENGLISH.
MAMACITAS, 2:00.
CAN WE GET A TOWEL?
YES, OF COURSE.
IT'S ONE FOR THE OLD LITTLE
MERMAID, AND ONE FOR THE NEW
LITTLE MERMAID.
♪ A WHOLE NEW GIRL ♪
VERY FUNNY, GUYS.
THAT SONG IS FROM ALADDIN.
I WANT TO CLIMB ON A LADDER.
I'M HAVING THE TIME OF MY
LIFE DOWN HERE IN PUNTA CANA.
THAT'S NICE.
I LOVE THE WAY Y'ALL BE
PLAYING WITH THE PLANTAIN.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS GOING TO
LIKE IT, BUT NOW I'M LIKE,
BANANA FOR DINNER, OKAY?
YOU KNOW WHO YOU SOUND LIKE,
THE FORRY GUM.
THE GUY WHO CAN'T FIND YENNY.
HIS BRAIN DON'T REACH HIS LEGS,
SO HE CAN RUN FOREVER.
I WANT TO THANK YOU FELLAS
FOR ALL YOUR HELP TODAY.
CAN I GIVE YOU SOMETHING FOR
YOUR TROUBLE?
WE IS ACCEPT TIPS, POPPY.
I'LL DO YOU ONE BETTER THAN A TIP.
HOW ABOUT A PRAYER.
LORD, PLEASE PROTECT THESE
WONDERFUL DOMINICAN GENTLEMEN
FROM THE HARSH SUN.
I WANTED MONEY, POPPY.
THE MONEY WOU BE BETTER, MAN.
LORD, PROTECT THEM FROM ALL
EVIL IN JESUS' NAME, AMEN.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU KNOW, JESUS IS GOOD.
BUT MONEY IS BETTER.
YOU KNOW WHO HAS A LOT OF MONEY?
ELLEN DEMENEMES.
♪ ELLEN DEMENEMES ♪
>>> AS A HOMEOWNER, YOU NEVER
KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO GO WRONG.
I WANTED TO GIVE HIM A BATH.
LUCKILY, STATE FARM HAS YOU
COVERED NO MATTER WHAT THE ISSUE.
WITH THE STATE FARM APP, YOU CAN
FILE A CLAIM IN SECONDS SO YOU
CAN GET BACK TO YOUR LIFE.
WOW, THAT WAS EASY.
THANKS, JAKE FROM STATE FARM.
LIKE A GOOD NEIGHBOR, STATE
FARM IS THERE.
GUESS I WON'T BE LATE FOR
WORK AFTER ALL.
ONE MORE THING.
IS THIS DRYER SAFE.
BY, HON.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
HEY, DO YOU WANT A CUP OF
COFFEE?
I WOULD LOVE ONE.
NO MATTER WHAT YOUR INSURANCE
NEEDS, STATE FARM HAS A POLICY
FOR YOU.
HELLO?
OH, JAKE FROM STATE FARM.
YOU'RE STILL HERE.
UNLIKE OTHER INSURANCE
COMPANIES, STATE FARM IS HERE
FOR YOU 24/7.
RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN FOR DINNER?
OH, JAKE AND THE KIDS AND I
WENT OUT FOR PIZZA.
BUT THERE SHOULD BE STUFF IN THE
FRIDGE TO MAKE A SANDWICH.
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
TEXT ME WHEN YOU GET HOME.
I WILL.
AND IN SPORTS, THE BLUE JAYS
AND YANKEES MEET TONIGHT FOR THE
DECIDING GAME. WHOA.
LOOK WHO'S UP, SLEEPY HEAD.
THINK FAST. HEY.
WHERE THE HELL WERE YOU?
JAKE AND I TOOK THE KIDS TO CHURCH.
TO CHURCH?
YES, TO CHURCH.
AND I HAPPEN TO AGREE.
NOW EXCUSE ME.
YOU'RE GETTING IT.
YOU'RE A NATURAL.
GIVE ME SOME.
>>> LIKE A GOOD NEIGHBOR, STATE
FARM IS THERE.
SOME HEAT.
STATE FARM IS THERE.
YOU LOOKING FOR BETTER RATES?
JESUS.
YOU KNOW YOU WON'T FIND THEM.
STATE FARM IS RATE MATCHED EVEN
IF YOU DO FIND CHEAPER COVERAGE,
WE'LL JUST MATCH IT.
THIS IS MY HOUSE, AND I WANT
HIM GONE.
HE IS NOT A GOOD NEIGHBOR!
GET YOUR FINGER OUT OF MY
FACE!
SAVE EVEN MORE WHEN YOU
BUNDLE HOME AND AUTO.
SLEEP TIGHT.
STATE FARM IS WITH YOU 24/7.
I JUST WANTED A POLICY!
LIKE A GOOD NEIGHBOR, STATE FARM
IS THERE, AND HERE AND IN MY BED
WITH MY WIFE!
HE TOOK EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING!
STEP AWAY FROM THE EDGE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS, BUDDY
♪ LIMU EMU ♪
AND DOUG.
LIMU AND I CAN HELP SNOENT
LIBERTY, LIBERTY, LIBERTY ♪
>>> OKAY, GUYS.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE TO LAY
DOWN SOME VOICEOVER FOR THE
MUCH-ANTICIPATED STREET FIGHTER
6 GAME.
EXCITED TO BE HERE, THANKS.
THRILLED TO BE ON BOARD.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE LAST
MINUTE, OUR LAST ACTOR QUIT DUE
TO CREATIVE DIFFERENCES AND
BECAUSE I SLEPT WITH HIS WIFE. ACTORS.
I KNOW.
SO TRACE, YOU WILL BE PLAYING
KEN, A FORMER U.S. FIGHTING
CHAMP.
TOTALLY IN MY ELEMENT.
I SERVED FOR THREE YEARS.
DANNY, YOU ARE A MARTIAL
ARTIST SEEKING TRUE STRENGTH, RYU.
LOVE.
FOR THE FIRST TAKE, LET'S GET
YOU MAKING EFFORTS.
TAKING BLOWS, HITS, EVERYTHING. ROLLING.
AND ACTION.
BOOM, AH!
HA!
HIYA!
YES, THAT'S GREAT.
DANNY, LET'S GET THE SAME FROM YOU.
OKAY.
WHOO!
YEA!
HOO!
LET'S GO!
THAT WAS REALLY FUN.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME PLAY. YEAH.
SO I GUESS WE WERE LOOKING FOR
MORE GRUNTS, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE FIGHTING.
YOU'RE IN PAIN.
I SEE.
SO MAYBE DO IT LIKE YOU'RE
FIGHTING OR IN PAIN.
GOT IT.
TRACE, YOU DON'T NEED TO
CHANGE WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
BUT DANNY, MAYBE IT'S MORE
AGGRESSIVE, ANIMALISTIC, THAT
KIND OF THING.
MM.
YES, CHEF.
ALL RIGHT.
AND ACTION.
UGH!
ROUGH!
HOO HOO!
MEOW!
CUT!
NO, TRACE, DON'T MATCH WHAT HE'S
DOING.
OKAY.
HE'S JUST AN AMAZING SCENE
PARTNER, SO YOU KNOW.
THANK YOU.
I WAS JUST TAKING YOUR NOTE.
YOU SAID TO DO ANIMALS. YEAH.
BUT I SAID A BUNCH OCH STUFF
BEFORE THAT.
WELL, I HAVE AUDITORY BIASED,
SO YOU CAN CAN'T SAY THAT TO ME,
I CAN SUE YOU.
DON'T FIGHT.
IT REMINDS ME OF THE WAR.
LET'S MOVE ON.
WE NEED TO GET VERBAL PHRASES TO
SAY DURING THE FIGHT.
HEY, I LIKE YOUR NECKLACE.
OH, THIS OLD THING?
THANKS.
YEA!
KINDNESS WINS.
WHAT ARE YOUR PRONOUNS?
HE/HIM.
I'LL TELL HIM.
KENNETH, HE/THEY.
WE CAN'T USE ANY OF THAT.
OH, THAT MAKES ME SAD.
IS THERE A REASON?
YES.
BECAUSE NO ONE SOUNDS LIKE THAT
WHEN THEY FIGHT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU REMIND ME EXACTLY OF SOMEONE
I SERVED WITH IN IRAQ.
OH, YOU WENT TO IRAQ.
WHERE DID YOU STAY?
DIDN'T WANT TO SAY THIS.
BUT YOU NEED TO PLAY MORE HETERO.
YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST SAID
THAT FROM THE BEGINNING.
I GOT IT.
LET ROLL.
HEY, BROTHER KEN, BY ACCEPTS
LOOKING HUGE.
YOU LOOK PRETTY SWOLE
YOURSELF, BRO.
I SAW YOU CHANGING IN THE
LOCKER ROOM, BUT I WAS
COMPLETELY SOFT, MY DUDE.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU KNEW
MY NAME.
EASY, BRO, MY WIFE IS ON THIS APP.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THIS ISN'T EVEN AN APP.
IT'S A VIDEO GAME.
OKAY THEN I'LL RACE YOU TO
THE VIDEO CUBE, MY BROTHER.
DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU WOULD
SOUND LIKE THIS IN A REAL FIGHT?
YES, I WOULD, BROTHER.
OH, MY GOD.
FRANK, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I TOLD YOU I WOULD KILL YOU
FOR SLEEPING WITH MY WIFE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
WHOO!
MEOW!
WELL, I'LL BE DAMNED.
YOU TWO JUST SAVED MY LIFE.
NO, STEVEN.
KEN AND RYU SAVED YOUR LIFE.
BABY.
♪ YEAH MADE IT OUT
THE TRENCHES
THIS TYPE OF LIFE
I CAN GET USED TO ♪
♪ NUMBER ONE ON YOUTUBE
PRIVATE DINNER IN MALIBU ♪
♪ SHOW YOU HOW
TO WORK YOUR STICK
AIN'T NOBODY
GON' HANDLE YOU ♪
♪ PUT YOU IN A PHANTOM
'CAUSE YOU MY LIL' BOO
READY FOR WHATEVER
I TIE UP MY BOOTS ♪
♪ EVERYBODY GOIN'
THE SAME ROUTE
SO I SWITCHED UP MY ROUTE ♪
♪ PEOPLE AIN'T
WHAT THEY BE TALKIN' 'BOUT
SO I SWITCHED UP MY CREW ♪
♪ ACTIN' LIKE YOU LOVE ME
KNOWIN' IT'S FLAW
SO I'M GON' FAKE IT TOO ♪
♪ WHAT ELSE
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO ♪
♪ AWARE OF MY SURROUNDINGS
I DON'T MESS WITH Y'ALL
DON'T COME AROUND ME ♪
♪ BABY SWITCHED UP
HOW THAT SOUND
LIKE SOMEBODY
IN HIS FEELINGS ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T NAME
SOMETHIN' I DID FLAW
I'MA DYIN' BREED
OF THE REALEST ♪
♪ I AIN'T NEVER WORRY
'BOUT ANOTHER HITTA
SO IN THAT CASE
I'M THE BIGGEST ♪
♪ I BEEN TRAVELLIN'
AROUND THE WORLD
MY PIVOT STILL
AIN'T LEFT THE BUSINESS ♪
♪ SHE GOT EVERYTHING I WANT
AIN'T NO NEED TO MESS
WITH THESE WOMEN♪
♪ YOU CAN GO
AND HAVE A LIL' FUN
I AIN'T GON' TRIP BABY
I GET IT ♪
♪ AIN'T MESSIN' AROUND
IN THIS GAME
WHEREVER THIS PLANE LAND
I'M THE LIT-EST THERE ♪
♪ TURN YOUR BACK ON ME
I AIN'T EVEN CARE
IF YOU NEED ME
I'M STILL GON' BE THERE ♪
♪ TELL ME HOW THE--
SWITCH ON WHO
I WASN'T THERE ♪
♪-- THEM TOO I'M PREPARED
I RUN THEM GET THAT CLEAR
♪ HEART BROKE
CAN'T DROP NO TEARS
WAS WHAT IT WAS
IS WHAT IT IS ♪
♪ CALIFORNIA BREEZE
TAKE HER OUT TO EAT
STOP AT A LIL' PARTY
END UP AT THE BIG HOUSE ♪
♪ I CAN'T MESS WITH SHAWTY
'CAUSE SHE GOT A BIG MOUTH
PULL UP IN A 'RARRI
HOP OUT LIKE A BIG DAWG ♪
♪ GET MYSELF TOGETHER
FEEL LIKE I DONE
TOOK TWO YEARS OFF ♪
♪ BOOKIN' UP MY SCHEDULE
I AIN'T RICH ENOUGH
TO CHILL OUT ♪
♪ I WATCHED YOU TURN SOUR
I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW TO FEEL 'BOUT IT ♪
♪ MAJORITY OF 'EM FOLDED
BUT I'M STILL SOLID ♪
♪ I'M STILL OUT HERE
STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW TO FEEL ABOUT IT ♪
♪ EARLY IN THE MORNIN'
TALKIN' TO MARQUIS ABOUT IT
WONDERIN' SHOULD WE LET IT GO
OR WE BEEFIN' 'BOUT IT ♪
♪ KNOWIN' THAT I'LL GO COLD
ON YOU FOR WEEKS ABOUT IT ♪
♪ AND IT WASN'T
EVEN THAT DEEP
BUT THAT'S JUST
HOW IT BE WITH ME ♪
♪ I CAN'T LIE
YOU BE DOIN' ME GOOD
BUT GIRL SHE DOIN' ME BETTER ♪
♪ I'M NOT SURPRISED
THAT YOU STEREOTYPE ME
TO BE A LIL' GUY ♪
♪ BUT IF I CAN HAVE
A SECOND OF YO' TIME
TRY TO ELEVATE YO' MIND ♪
♪ WE CAN CRUSH 'EM
ON EVERY LEVEL
I'M TELLIN' YOU ♪
♪ I FELL IN LOVE
WITH GENERATIN' REVENUE ♪
♪ I KNOW THEY GON' TRY
TO PUSH YOU FROM THE TOP
SO I'M CAREFUL ♪
♪ I PUT HITTAS UNDER MY WING
LIKE THEY MY NEPHEW ♪
♪ I'MA GIVE YOU
EVERY PIECE OF GAME I GOT
WHEN I CATCH YOU ♪
♪ I'M JUST TRYNA
LET YOU FEEL THE BREEZE
WITH ME♪
♪ CALIFORNIA BREEZE
TAKE HER OUT TO EAT
STOP AT A LIL' PARTY
END UP AT THE BIG HOUSE ♪
♪ I CAN'T MESS WITH SHAWTY
'CAUSE SHE GOT A BIG MOUTH
PULL UP IN A 'RARRI
HOP OUT LIKE A BIG DAWG ♪
♪ GET MYSELF TOGETHER
FEEL LIKE I DONE
TOOK TWO YEARS OFF ♪
♪ BOOKIN' UP MY SCHEDULE
I AIN'T RICH ENOUGH
TO CHILL OUT ♪
♪ I WATCHED YOU TURN SOUR
I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW TO FEEL 'BOUT IT ♪
♪ MAJORITY OF 'EM FOLDED
BUT I'M STILL SOLID ♪
♪ NO NO NO NO
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE GONE
WHERE I'M GON' GO ♪
♪ TRYNA HOLD IT IN
I CAN'T LET THIS STUFF SHOW
IT CAN'T BE FORCED
IT DON'T WORK LET IT GO ♪
♪ I TRY TO TELL YOU
YOU ACT LIKE YOU KNOW
ACT LIKE YOU KNOW
MM-MM MM-MM ♪
COLIN JOST AND MICHAEL CHE.
>>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
WELCOME TO WEEKEND UPDATE.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
I'M COLIN JOST.
FACEBOOK ANNOUNCED THAT IT WILL
REINSTATE FORMER PRESIDENT
DONALD TRUMP'S ACCOUNT,
BUT THIS
TIME THEY'LL PUT GUARDRAILS IN
PLACE TO KEEP HIM UNDER CONTROL,
WHICH I THINK IS THE SAME THING
THEY SAID EVERY TIME THEY TRY
TODAY REOPEN JURASSIC PARK.
ALSO, WHAT EVEN ARE GUARDRAILS ON FACEBOOK,
AND CAN THEY APPLY
TO MY UNCLE?
BECAUSE HE'S POSTED SOME VERY
DISTURBING FAN FICTION ABOUT THE
GREEN M&M.
WAKE
DOCUMENT SCANDAL
REPRESENTATIVES FOR BILL
CLINTON, GEORGE W. BUSH AND BARACK OBAMA
STATEMENT
SAID THEY ALL
TURNED OVER CLASSIFIED RECORDS
BEFORE LEAVING OFFICE
WHILE
JIMMY CARTER RELEASED A
STATEMENT SAYING,
COME GET THEM,
YOU BASTARDS.
SASSY
A LAWYER FOR MIKE PENCE SAYS
AFTER THEY DISCOVERED CLASSIFIED
DOCUMENTS IN HIS HOME,
PENCE
STANDS READY AND WILLING TO
FULLY COOPERATE.
INCIDENTALLY, I STAND WILLING TO
FULLY COOPERATE
IS ALSO WHAT
PENCE SAYS BEFORE SEX.
DURING THE SENATE HEARINGS
INVESTIGATING LIVE NATION AND
THE MONOPOLY ON CONCERT TICKET SALES,
FANS OF TAYLOR SWIFT
PROTESTED OUTSIDE THE CAPITOL.
AND ONLY TWO YEARS AFTER THEIR
DADS WERE THERE.
SENATOR RICK SCOTT SEEN HERE
LEARNING THAT HARRY POTTER HAS
FALLEN INTO HIS TRAP,
ANNOUNCED
THAT HE IS RUNNING FOR
RE-ELECTION
PROMISING TO FINISH
THE BORDER WALL AND NAME IT
AFTER DONALD TRUMP.
EVEN THOUGH MOST THINGS NAMED
AFTER DONALD TRUMP ARE COMPLETE FAILURES.
JR
GEORGE SANTOS ADMITTED THAT
WHILE LIVING IN BRAZIL, HE DID DRESS IN DRAG,
BUT SAID HE WAS
NOT A DRAG QUEEN.
OKAY, HONEY.
WE KNEW THAT FROM YOUR
CONTOURING.
RONNA McDANIEL WAS RE-ELECTED
AS CHAIR OF THE REPUBLICAN NATIONAL COMMITTEE
IN A CLOSER
THAN EXPECTED VOTE OVER
CHALLENGERS HARMEET DHILLON, MIKE LYNN DELL,
TWITTER USER CAT TURD 2
SORBO
CORBIN
AND OF COURSE COLIN JOST.
- CONGRATS
- THANK YOU. THAT ELECTION WAS RIGGED.
GOOGLE ANNOUNCED IT IS CUTTING 12,000 JOBS
WHILE YAHOO
ANNOUNCED IT IS NOW RUN BY A
FAMILY OF RACCOONS.
POPE FRANCIS CRITICIZED LAWS
BANNING HOMO SEXUALITY AS UNJUST
SAYING IT'S NOT A CRIME EVEN
THOUGH CATHOLIC DOCTRINE VIEWS
IT AS A SIN.
THEY ALSO SAID THEY VIEW AGE AS
NOTHING BUT A NUMBER.
DISNEY WORLD IS CLOSING
SPLASH MOUNTAIN TO TURN IT INTO
TIANA'S BAYOU ADVENTURE AFTER
CLAIMS THE THEME SONG WAS
RACIST.
WHERE'S THE OUTRAGE ABOUT DISNEY
FORCING A MENTALLY CHALLENGED
DWARF TO MINE BLOOD DIAMONDS?
2023.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT IS THE NEW
DOORMAN TO MY BUILDING, CARL.
HEY!
WHAT'S UP, MR. CHE?
HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
JUST A LITTLE REMINDER.
I NOTED YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN ME AN
END OF THE YEAR TIP YET.
YOU JUST STARTED. OH.
WELL, MAYBE SOON THEN.
YOU REMEMBER THAT NIGHT?
WHEN THINGS GOT WILD?
I TALKED TO THE POLICE FOR YOU.
I DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
YEAH.
HARD TO KEEP TRACK OF ALL THE
CRAZY NIGHTS WHEN MR. MICHAEL
CHE IS YOUR TENANT.
JUST REMEMBER WHICH NIGHT IS
WILD AND WHICH NIGHT IS JUST REGULAR.
WE LIVING THAT LIFE, CHE.
WE?
OH, YEAH, MAN.
WE DOING THE DAMN THING.
MY DOG.
SO WHAT'S THIS?
WHAT YOU DOING HERE, MAN?
THIS IS SNL, MAN.
IT'S MY JOB.
OH.
OH, OKAY.
OH, SO YOU JUST OUT HERE MAKING
THE BIG BUCKS IN A HALF SUIT AND JEANS.
CHE, CHE.
WHAT, MAN.
YOU KNOW THAT LADY CAME
AROUND LOOKING FOR YOU AGAIN,
MAN.
WHO?
YOU KNOW THAT ONE.
THE LADY.
SHE'S LIKE REAL SMART.
ALL RIGHT.
ALWAYS MAD.
SHE CAME INTO THE BUILDING AGAIN
ASKING ABOUT YOU, MAN.
DON'T WORRY.
I TOLD HER YOU MOVED TO JAMAICA.
I DID GOOD, RIGHT?
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
I'M ABSOLUTELY HERE IN NEW YORK
LIVE ON TV RIGHT NOW.
SHE AIN'T WATCHING.
WELL, THANK YOU, CARL.
HEY, CHE.
CHE.
YOU KNOW THAT LITTLE KID CAME
AROUND LOOKING FOR YOU, RIGHT?
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT, TELL CHE
MY MAMA SAID HE GOT TO TAKE ME
TO THE ZOO.
HE SAID HIS NAME WAS DEMICHAEL
OR SOMETHING.
THAT'S NOT MY KID.
THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S WHAT I TOLD THAT LITTLE DUMMY.
TEAMWORK MAKE THE DREAM WORK.
THANK YOU FOR STOPPING BY, MAN.
HEY, CHE.
YOU KNOW THAT DOG CAME AROUND
LOOKING FOR YOU, RIGHT?
HE GOT THAT BARK LIKE, RRR, CHE,
CHE, CHE.
I SWEAR THAT'S WHAT HE BE
SAYING, MAN.
I UNDERSTOOD THE DOG TALK THOUGH.
HEY, MAN, WHO IS CORNELIUS?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SURE?
BECAUSE EVERY NIGHT AT 8:00,
THIS MAN SHOWS UP AND LEAVES ONE
SHOE ON MY DESK AND SAYS, TELL
MICHAEL CHE THIS IS FROM CORNELIUS.
AND IF HE WANTS THE OTHER SHOE,
TELL HIM TO MEET ME UNDER THE BRIDGE.
NEW YORK IS WILD, MAN.
OKAY.
NOW I KNOW YOU HAVE TO GO.
I MEAN, WHO'S WATCHING THE
BUILDING RIGHT NOW?
DON'T WORRY.
I PUT A SIGN UP SAYING, YOU
LOOKING FOR MICHAEL CHE, JUST
CALL 917--
DON'T GIVE THEM MY PHONE
NUMBER.
WHY NOT?
THAT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
IT IS?
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S WHY I'M A
DOORMAN AND YOU HERE MAKING
CRAZY MONEY USING THAT DESK TO
HIDE YOUR DIRTY JEANS.
CARL MY
THE DALLAS ZOO HAS BEEN
DEALING WITH THE DISAPPEARANCE
OF SEVERAL ANIMALS INCLUDING A
LEOPARD, MONKEYS AND A VULTURE.
IN AN UNRELATED STORY, CHECK OUT
MY AMAZING COAT.
OFFICIALS AT TIKTOK ARE
TRYING TO STOP EFFORTS IN
CONGRESS TO BAN THE APP BY
LAUNCHING A CAMPAIGN CALLED
PROJECT TEXAS BECAUSE TIKTOK IS
THEIR BABY AND THEY KNOW TEXAS
WON'T LET THEM GET RID OF IT.
A NEW AI CHAT BOX HAS CREATED
CON TO TRO VER SI AFTER IT
ALLOWED USERS TO TALK WITH JESUS
AND HITLER, AND ONE GUY WHO
THINKS HE'S BOTH.
JUST NEWS, GUYS.
A 23-YEAR-OLD CHIHUAHUA IN
OHIO NAMED SPIKE HAS BEEN
OFFICIALLY NAMED THE WORLD'S
OLDEST LIVING DOG.
THE SECRET TO SPIKE'S LONG LIFE,
A LOT OF CHIHUAHUAS LOOK THE SAME.
CHIPOTLE HAS ANNOUNCED PLANS TO
HIRE 15,000 PEOPLE TO PREPARE
FOR ITS BUSIEST TIME OF YEAR,
WHICH THEY ARE CALLING BURRITO
SEASON, AND TOILETS ARE CALLING
THE APOCALYPSE.
RESEARCHERS IN ANTARCTICA
HAVE DISCOVERED A 17-POUND MEET RITE.
SADLY, IT WAS ON TOP OF THE LAST
POLAR BEAR.
A MATTRESS REVIEW SITE IS
PAYING PEOPLE TO TEST THE THEORY
THAT EATING CHEESE BEFORE BED
WILL GIVE F GIVE A PERSON NIGHTMARES.
BUT IF YOU'RE IN BED EATING
CHEESE UNTIL YOU PASS OUT, YOUR
LIFE IS ALREADY A NIGHTMARE.
THIS WEEK, WENDY'S ANNOUNCED
THEY WOULD BE BRINGING BACK
THEIR VANILLA FROSTY AFTER A
BRIEF HIATUS IN 2022.
HERE TO TALK ABOUT IT WITH HER
GOOD NEWS REPORT IS EVERY
BOXER'S GIRLFRIEND FROM EVERY
BOXING MOVIE ABOUT BOXING EVER.
HI, HI, HI.
HOW YOU DOING?
HOW ARE YOU, ANGEL?
I'VE BEEN BETTER.
DOES YOUR BOYFRIEND TOMMY
HAVE A FIGHT TONIGHT?
HE BETTER NOT BECAUSE THE
LAST GUY HIT TOMMY SO HARD,
THERE'S NO MORE CLAMS IN HIS CHOWDER.
I LOVE HIM SO MUCH, BUT I SWEAR
TO GOD, IF HE FIGHTS AGAIN, I'M
TAKING THE KIDS TO MY SISTER'S.
GOT IT.
IN GOOD NEWS, THE VANILLA FROSTY
IS MAKING A COME BACK.
AWW.
YOU THINK VANILLA HAS A SHOT
GOING UP AGAINST CHOCOLATE,
YOU'RE SICK.
IF I SEE IT UP ON THE MENU, I'M
TAKING MY KIDS TO MY SISTER'S.
ALL OF THEM.
YOU DOING OKAY, ANGEL?
BARELY.
I'M DOING A LOT BETTER THAN TOMMY.
CREED RUINED HIM, CHE.
WAIT, TOMMY FOUGHT ADONIS
CREED?
CREED HIT TOMMY SO HARD, HIS
EYES FLEW OUT.
LANDED IN PEPPER'S LAP.
THE ONE NIGHT I FORGOT TO TAKE
THE KIDS TO MY SISTER'S.
JESUS.
SO WHERE IS HE?
I KNOW CREED'S HERE.
YOU HAVE BEEN ADVERTISING THE
FIGHT ALL WEEK.
CREED VERSUS LIL BABY LIVE ON PEACOCK.
ANGEL, THERE'S NO FIGHT
TONIGHT.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
THEN WHAT'S ALL THIS?
CAMERAS, COLDOUT CROWD.
I'M LOOKING AT JAMIE FOX AND
GINA GERSHAUN SITTING FRONT ROW
NEXT TO COCAINE BEAR.
THAT'S JUST A BLACK GUY
SITTING NEXT TO A WHITE WOMAN IN
A BIG COAT.
I DON'T CARE.
I WANT CREED!
ANGEL!
ADONIS CREED.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE THE REASON MY
KIDS' DAD WATCHES FOR SESAME
STREET THAN THEY DO?
YOU EVER THINK ABOUT US, ANGEL.
DON'T.
REMEMBER?
BEFORE TOMMY, THERE WAS CREEDY.
YOU REMEMBER LIL NICKY?
HE'S YOURS, CREED.
WHAT?
TOMMY NEVER ASKED WHY ONE OF HIS
KIDS WAS BLACK?
TOMMY DON'T SEE COLOR.
THAT'S NICE.
NO.
HE DON'T SEE ANY COLORS,
NUMBERS, OR SHAPES.
HIS POTATO IS BAKED, CREEDY.
LOOK AT ME.
YOU'RE COMING HOME WITH ME
TONIGHT.
BUT WHAABOUT TOMMY?
WHAT ABOUT THE KIDS?
LISTEN, FROM NOW ON, I'M
TAKING THE KIDS TO YOUR
SISTER'S.
EVERY BOXER'S GIRLFRIEND AND
ADONIS CREED, EVERYBODY.
PEOPLE WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH ME.
NOW ROAR LIKE A LION.
ROAR!
LOUDER.
RAWR!
WOW, GIVE IT UP FOR RON,
EVERYBODY.
YES, I HAVE CHILLS. SEE.
THAT'S WHAT MALE CHARISMA
TRAINING IS ALL ABOUT, CONFIDENCE.
YOU SEE, I USED TO BE A LOT LIKE
YOU GUYS, AWKWARD, HATED MY
BODY, WALKED AROUND LIKE THIS,
BLAH!
BUT THEN, I DEVELOPED MY SOCIAL
MASTERY PROGRAM.
NOW I STAND LIKE AN ALPHA.
I'VE GOT THE SCARF.
YOU'VE TAKEN BY CLASS BEFORE,
YES?
THREE TIMES, YES.
AND I HAVE AN UPDATE.
I GOT A GIRLFRIEND NOW.
HELL YES.
WHAT WAS YOUR APPROACH?
WELL, SHE'S NOT A GIRLFRIEND.
SHE'S ACTUALLY LIKE A BARISTA.
BUT, HEY, YOU INTRODUCED
YOURSELF, RIGHT?
NO, SIR.
SO YOU SAW A GIRL AT A COFFEE
SHOP.
ROUND OF APPLAUSE FOR HIM.
THAT'S NOT NOTHING, FOLKS.
THAT'S NOT NOTHING.
YES, A QUESTION IN THE BACK.
WHERE DO YOU WANT THIS WATER
DELIVERY?
I DON'T KNOW, DUDE.
DO I LOOK LIKE I WORK FOR THE
HOTEL?
OH, OKAY.
MY APOLOGIES.
YOU, QUESTION. YEAH.
I'M PRETTY LONELY.
I HAVE A JOB.
I FEEL LIKE I'M DOING EVERYTHING RIGHT.
I JUST GET NERVOUS THAT WOMEN
ARE GOING TO MAKE FUN OF ME IF I
APPROACH THEM.
UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
AND WHAT DO YOU DO FOR WORK?
I CRITIQUE FEMALE STANDUPS ON
YOUTUBE.
SURE.
AFTER ONE SESSION HERE, NOTHING
WILL RATTLE YOU.
ANYBODY OUT THERE, SAY THE
MEANEST THING YOU CAN THINK
ABOUT ME. ANYBODY. FOREHEAD.
SORRY.
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
FOREHEAD.
OKAY.
SURE.
IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE
HAVE A WEIRD FOREHEAD.
JUST KEEP TALKING, GOOFY.
I'M NOT GOOFY.
I'M ACTUALLY REGULAR.
LISTEN, WHEN YOU APPROACH A
LADY, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
TAKE AN ALPHA BODY STANCE.
BROAD SHOULDERS.
BROAD FOREHEAD.
SIR, I'M FINE IF YOU STAY,
JUST DON'T DISRUPT ME, PLEASE. NO.
I MIGHT.
OH, OKAY.
LOOK.
NO MATTER WHAT A LADY THROWS AT
YOU, AND THEY CAN SAY SOME
PRETTY RANDOM STUFF, JUST ROLL
WITH IT.
I NEED A VOLUNTEER.
I THINK YOU STOOD UP FIRST, SIR.
IF YOU'RE COOL WITH IT.
YOU DON'T MIND IF I DO THIS,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
SEE, DEXTER'S LAB IS COOL WITH YOU.
GO AHEAD, GOOFY.
NOT GOOFY.
I'M GOING TO DO WHAT I CALL A
BASIC OPENING.
HEY, GODDESS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
YOU A BITCH.
HEY.
JUST DO THE EXERCISE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
FOREHEAD JACKSON.
IT'S NOT.
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
I'M GOOD HERE.
THAT'S FINE.
ANY FINAL QUESTIONS?
YEAH.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU HAVE ANY
TIPS ON COPING WITH HAVING A BIG
OLD FOREHEAD.
I DON'T HAVE A BIG OLD
FOREHEAD, OKAY?
I'M NOT LIKE YOU, DUDE.
I'M COOL.
I GOT THE SCARF, THE RINGS.
YOU KNOW I'M IN CHARGE LIKE IMMEDIATELY.
YOU GOT A JIMMY NEUTRON HEAD, BRO.
HE KIND OF DOES.
NO.
NO, MY HEAD IS REGULAR.
NOT JIMMY NEUTRON.
IT'S LIKE IF JIMMY NEUTRON
DID STREET MAGIC, THAT'S YOU.
NO, IT'S NOT.
DAMN IT.
Y'ALL WANT TO GO GET A
BURGER?
I FEEL LIKE I CAN TEACH YOU SOME THINGS.
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS GOING?
THINGS.
I WANT TO COME TOO.
AFTER ALL THIS WEDDING
PLANNING, I NEEDED THIS PALM
SPRINGS TRIP, OKAY?
WELL, YOUR BACHELORETTE
WEEKEND AIN'T OVER YET, HONEY.
OH, MY GOSH.
DON'T TELL ME.
IT'S ABOUT TO GET HOT IN
HERE.
AHH!
HELLO, LADIES.
MY NAME IS VINCE, AND I JUST GOT
WORD THAT Y'ALL'S BUILDING IS
OUT OF CODE, AND THAT MAKES ME
HORNY.
YOU GUYS ARE SO BAD.
THIS IS WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I'M ABOUT TO INTRODUCE Y'ALL
TO MY FRIENDS, POP AND LOCK.
YEA!
IT'S SO HOT.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I SAW HIM ON THE WEBSITE, AND I
WAS IMMEDIATELY ROCK HARD.
OKAY, MR. POP AND LOCK.
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS CRAZY!
HOW RED IS MY FACE RIGHT NOW?
WE ALL GOING TO BLUSH
TONIGHT, GIRLS.
WE ALL GOING TO BLUSH.
YOUR TURN, BRIDE TO BE.
UH-OH, DO WE HAVE ANOTHER
FIRE FIGHTER.
NOT THAT WE PAID FOR.
HEY.
I'M SORRY TO BUG Y'ALL.
VINCE, BABE, MY PHONE DIED.
WHO IS THAT?
OH, MY BAD.
THIS IS MY WIFE, JANINANEEN.
HEY.
OH, I HATE TO ASK.
CAN I CHARGE MY GALAXY FOR
LITERALLY TWO MINUTES?
SURE, I GUESS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
MY MOM GOT GLUTE SURGERY TODAY,
AND WE'RE PRAYING SHE'S OKAY.
WOW, THE HOSPITALITY IN HERE
IS BIBLICAL.
THANK YOU, QUEENS.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BABE?
I'M CHARGING.
OH, PICTURES OF MY MOM'S NEW ASS
JUST CAME IN.
SHE MADE IT.
GOD IS GOOD. OKAY.
NOW WATCH MY KING STRIP.
HIT IT.
WHERE WAS I?
OH, YEAH.
I WAS INTRODUCING Y'ALL TO MY
FRIENDS, POP AND LOCK.
OH, YEAH.
THERE HE IS. WOW.
SIT ON THEM, VINCE.
SIT ON THEM. YES.
HE MADE THIS, HE MADE THIS.
OH, OKAY.
OKAY.
HE MADE THIS, HE MADE THIS. OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I'M SO SORRY.
I CAN'T, YOU GUYS.
I CAN'T.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I WAS
ENVISIONING JUST LIKE ONE DANCER
AND NOT LIKE A PREGNANT WOMAN
WITH A REALLY LONG PHONE CHARGER.
OH, GIRL, DON'T HOLD BACK
BECAUSE OF ME.
YOU CAN TOUCH HIM.
YOU CAN KISS HIM.
I PROMISE YOU.
I DON'T MIND, AND SHE DON'T
MIND.
SEE, SEE.
I LOVE THAT ABOUT US.
100% TRUST.
OH, I HOPE AND PRAY TO GOD YOU
FIND THAT IN YOUR WEDDING.
I HOPE AND PRAY TO GOD. OKAY.
THANK YOU.
HIT IT. OKAY.
BECAUSE THAT ONE, MY FRIENDS,
THAT KEEPS THE RELATIONSHIP ALIVE.
THAT KEEPS THE SEXUALITY ALIVE.
OKAY.
SO THIS IS GETTING JUST A LITTLE
BIT WEIRD.
GUYS, WE ALREADY PAID HIM THE
30 BUCKS.
JUST LET HIM FINISH.
30 BUCKS?
MY PEANUT BUTTER COSTS 30 BUCKS.
BITCH, WHERE YOU GETTING
PEANUT BUTTER?
I'M SORRY.
ARE THEY PRAYING?
I HUMBLY THANK GOD FOR THE
POWER TO STRIP.
AND I THANK THE LORD FOR
THESE CHICKS LETTING ME CHARGE
MY GALAXY. AMEN.
WHERE WAS I?
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS INTRODUCING Y'ALL TO MY
TWO FRIENDS POP AND LOCK.
WE ALREADY MET THEM.
HEY, HOES, WHO WANTS TO RIDE
HIS HOSE?
WHOOP, WHOOP.
THIS IS STRESSING ME OUT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE GOING TO END
UP ON THE NEWS. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH, ENOUGH.
WE'RE DONE.
WE'RE DONE. YES.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE PAID FOR.
OKAY?
NO.
YOU GOT MORE THAN WHAT YOU PAID FOR.
THREE STRIPPERS FOR THE PRICE OF
ONE.
MA'AM, PLEASE TOP REFERRING
TO YOUR FETUS AS A STRIPPER.
OH, MY GOD.
MY WATER BROKE!
OH, MY GOD!
WAIT WAB HOW PREGNANT IS SHE?
JUST A LITTLE OVER A YEAR,
BUT WHATEVER.
I'M CALLING AN AMBULANCE.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
I'LL HAVE THE BABY HERE WITH MY
GIRLS.
OKAY.
WE GOT THIS, GIRLS.
WE GOT THIS. OKAY.
HIT THE MUSIC.
OH, MY GOD.
♪ PUSH, PUSH, PUSH ♪
HERE WE GO!
♪
♪ I KNOW YOU MISS ME
WHO IT'S GON' BE
IF IT AIN'T ME LIL' BABY ♪
♪ I'M IN YOUR CITY
CAUSE I NEED IT ONE MORE TIME
MIGHT LOSE IT ALL I SWEAR
I NEED IT TONIGHT OH ♪
♪ HOW WE GET SO DEEP SO FAST
BAE STOP PLAYIN'
I'LL BEAT YOUR--♪
♪ YOU BE ON SOME TOXIC--
BUT I CANNOT GET OFF THIS
♪ I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN THREE MONTHS
I MISS YOU
CAN I SEE YOU BAE ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I SEE
ONE OF YOUR PICTURES
THAT STUFF DRIVES ME CRAZY ♪
♪ GIRL I KNOW YOU MISS IT
ESPECIALLY HOW I KISS IT ♪
♪ MESSAGE SAY DELIVERED
WHY THE-- YOU KEEP
GOIN' MISSING ON ME ♪
♪ EVERY TIME HE GET
BACK IN THE PICTURE
YOU ACT DIFFERENT ON ME ♪
♪ BUT TELL THAT BOY THAT
WE GON' HAVE TO SHARE YOU
I AIN'T TRIPPIN' ON IT♪
♪ ONE MORE TIME
MIGHT BE THE BEST
FOR BOTH OF US ♪
♪ MAYBE WE SHOULD
TALK ABOUT IT LATER
WHEN WE SOBER UP ♪
♪ MAYBE WE SHOULD
SLOW IT DOWN
MAYBE WE SHOULD LET IT GO ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE IF IT'S MEANT
IT'S WHAT IT IS
SO I JUST LET IT FLOW ♪
♪ GOT SOMETHIN' TO HANDLE
SO I'MA BE HERE
FOR A COUPLE HOURS ♪
♪ FIGURED OUT YOU LIKE THEM
MY ASSISTANT
KEEP ON SENDIN' FLOWERS ♪
♪ THEY GOT THEY OWN BUSINESS
TELL ME WHY THEY ALWAYS
ALL IN OURS ♪
♪ MAMA RAISED
A LOT OF THINGS
BUT SHE AIN'T RAISED
NOT NEAR A COWARD ♪
♪ WE WENT TO THE MOON
LAST TIME
I'M TRYNA GO BACK ♪
♪ WE BEEN DOIN' OUR THING
FOR A WHILE
BUT THEY DON'T KNOW THAT ♪
♪ I BE BUYIN' YOU
ALL TYPE OF BAGS
BUT YOU CAN'T SHOW THAT ♪
♪ I BE PLAYIN' THE CUT
UNTIL YOU COME BACK ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU MISS ME
WHO IT'S GON' BE
IF IT AIN'T ME LIL' BABY ♪
♪ I'M IN YOUR CITY
CAUSE I NEED IT ONE MORE TIME
MIGHT LOSE IT ALL I SWEAR
I NEED IT TONIGHT OOH AH ♪
♪ THINKIN' HOW WE PLAYED OUT
REALLY I FEEL OFF ABOUT IT
BUT I AIN'T NEVER SAID IT ♪
♪ WE AIN'T GOTTA
TALK ABOUT IT ♪
♪ THEY'LL NEVER KNOW
WHEN I'M WITH YOU
I PLAY A DIFFERENT ROLE ♪
♪ CAN'T MOVE OFF EMOTION
THIS STUFF DEEP
NOW I GOT SELF-CONTROL ♪
♪ I AIN'T NEVER
TRIED TO HOLD YOU
TRY TO HIGH AND LOW YOU ♪
♪ I CAN BREAK IT DOWN
AND SHOW YOU
HOW YOU OWE ME ♪
♪ STILL TRY TO BACK DOOR ME
I KNOW HOW TO GO ABOUT IT ♪
♪ I KNOW EVERYTHING
BUT I TREAT YOU
LIKE I DON'T KNOW ABOUT IT ♪
♪ WILDIN' IN MIAMI
WE TOOK SHROOMS AND CAUGHT
A DIFFERENT VIBE ♪
♪ WOMEN CAN'T MESS WITH YOU
YOU THE ONE FOR REAL
I PEEP YOUR STYLE ♪
♪ I GOTTA GO GET IT I'M O.T.
SO IT'S GON' BE A WHILE
IT FEEL A LIL' BETTER
WHEN I AIN'T SEEN YOU ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU MISS ME
WHO IT'S GON' BE
IF IT AIN'T ME LIL' BABY ♪
♪ I'M IN YOUR CITY
CAUSE I NEED IT ONE MORE TIME
MIGHT LOSE IT ALL I SWEAR
I NEED IT TONIGHT OOH AH ♪
TOYOTA.
AND I'M SHORTY KING JR., AND
WE ARE OVERSTOCKED WITH TOYOTAS,
SIENNAS, COROLLAS, AND HIGH
LANDERS, ALL PART OF OUR KING
TOYOTA'S OVERSTOCK SALE-A-THON.
COME ON DOWN OFF HIGHWAY 8
EXIT 260 BECAUSE DEALS LIKE THIS
DON'T COME OFTEN.
GET YOUR BUTT DOWN HERE OFF
HIGHWAY 8, EXIT 260.
TAKE THE LEFT LANE.
YOU GOT TO GET HARD IN THAT
LEFT LANE BECAUSE IF YOU STAY
EVEN ONE SECOND IN THE RIGHT
LANE, YOU'LL GET STUCK IN THE
OVERFLOW LINE FOR THE NEW
RAISING CANES.
THE LINE BACKS UP TO THE
LIGHT ON TO THE OFF-RAMP AND
INTO THE HIGHWAY.
DO NOT STAY IN THE RIGHT LANE.
HARD, HARD LEFT, Y'ALL.
HARD TO THE LEFT WHEN YOU TAKE
260 OR YOU'LL MISS KING BROTHERS
TOYOTA'S OVERSTOCK SALE-A-THON.
WHY ARE WE OVERSTOCKED?
I'LL TELL YOU WHY, BECAUSE
NOBODY CAN GET HERE DUE TO THE
STUPID LONG CANE'S LINE TAKING
UP THE WHOLE DANG ROAD.
WE HAVE ABSOLUTELY SCREWED BY
THE BRENHAM CLAIM BER OF
COMMERCE AND DOWN COUNCILMAN
HUGO GALLEGOS.
HE HAS DEFILED 260.
THESE TRENDY CHAINS ALL COME
WITH THEIR OWN MASSIVE DRIVE
THROUGH LINES MANAGED ONLY BY A
HANDFUL OF iPADED TEENS.
WE ARE DEEP IN THE RED,
FOLKS, WHICH IS WHY CORPORATE
HAS SENT US THE NATION'S MOST
BEST AND JACKED SALESMAN, BRIAN
PAT MOORE.
THESE TWO ARE AFRAID TO GET
THEIR HANDS DIRTY.
CANES, YOU HAVE TWO HOURS TO GET
YOUR LINES OPEN.
I WILL REVEAL INGREDIENTS TO
YOUR SECRET SAUCE.
DON'T BELIEVE ME?
CHECK THIS OUT. KETCHUP.
WE ARE DROWNING IN TACOMAS,
AND WE ARE TRAPPED HERE.
WE LITERALLY CANNOT LEAVE DUE TO
THE LONG AS HELL CANES LINES.
I HAVE MISSED SO MANY FAMILY
EVENTS THE THINGS LIKE NIECE'S
KRISTENING, FIRST DAUGHTER'S
RECITAL, AND EVEN LITTLE J.C. AS
NATHAN DETROIT.
I NOW SPEAK DIRECTLY TO THE
COWARD HUGO GALLEGOS.
YOU HAVE DEFILED THE ONCE
BEAUTIFUL EXIT 260, AND IF THE
BIG ASS CANES LINE IS ALLOWED TO
STAND, KING BROTHERS TOYOTA WILL
FALL.
MY DAUGHTER HAILEY IS A
CLASSICS PROFESSOR AT BRENHAM
COMMUNITY COLLEGE, AND SHE HAS
DESCRIBED OUR PLIGHT AS A FUN
HOUSE MIRROR HELD UP AGAINST THE
AMERICAN DREAM.
I SAID, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT,
BABY GIRL.
ALL I KNOW IS I'M GETTING F'd IN
THE A BY HUGO GALLEGOS.
ALL THAT IS LOST BECAUSE WE
HAVE BRIAN PATMORE.
WELL, BRIAN PATMORE DON'T
PLAY NO GAMES.
NEXT INGREDIENT, PEPPER.
AND THE CLOCK BEGINNING ANEW.
TIKTOK, CANES, TIKTOK.
COME ON DOWN BECAUSE TIME IS
I'M HOSTING "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE."
MICHAEL, I THINK YOU'RE SO
COOL.
IT'S SCARY, BUT I'M MICHAEL
B. JORDAN.
THERE'S NO REASON TO BE NERVOUS.
WHEW, NO ONE SAW ME.
YOU OKAY THERE, BUD?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
BE CAREFUL.
I WILL. OKAY.
LITTLE EMBARRASSING.
AT LEAST IT'S JUST ANDREW DISMUKES.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
I WILL NOT FALL AGAIN.
YOU OKAY THERE, BUD?
OH, ANDREW.
I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
LOOKED LIKE IT HURT.
IT DIDN'T REALLY.
LOOKED LIKE IT DID, THOUGH.
YOU OKAY?
YOU WANT ME TO GET THE NURSE?
NURSE, MICHAEL B. JORDAN JUST
FELL DOWN AGAIN.
I SAID I WAS FINE.
THIS ANDREW DISMUKES GUY IS
GETTING IN MY HEAD.
I'M MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
I NEED TO NEVER FALL OVER EVER AGAIN.
YOU OKAY THERE, BUD?
TIMBER.
YOU OKAY, THOUGH?
YOU OKAY?
YOU OKAY THERE, BUD?
ANDREW, STOP SEEING ME FALL
DOWN.
HEY, MAN, I'M AT WORK.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO SEE YOU
FALL DOWN, QUIT FALLING DOWN
WHERE I WORK. WHATEVER.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
ALL RIGHT, BUD.
JUST BE CAREFUL.
OKAY?
HEY, GUYS.
ANDREW, SIT DOWN.
YOU HAVE TO STOP SEEING
MICHAEL B. JORDAN FALL DOWN.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
SOMETIMES HE FALLS, AND I SEE.
ANDREW, WHEN SOMEBODY FALLS
DOWN, YOU HAVE TO PRETEND LIKE
YOU DIDN'T SEE IT.
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
NOBODY TOLD ME THAT.
YOU CAN'T GET MAD AT ME FOR
SOMETHING I DIDN'T KNOW.
GUYS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING.
AND HEY, NEXT TIME YOU HAVE A
PROBLEM WITH ME, AT LEAST HAVE
THE KAHONES TO SAY IT TO MY FACE
INSTEAD OF SENDING YOUR LACKIES
TO DO YOUR DIRTY WORK FOR YOU.
I DIDN'T TELL THEM ANYTHING
EXCEPT YOU KEEP SEEING ME FALL.
WELL GUESS WHAT, SOMETIMES
YOU FALL, AND SOMETIMES I THERE.
WELL, THEN MAYBE YOU
SHOULDN'T BE AROUND ME AT ALL THEN.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD LEAVE AND NEVER
COME BACK.
WHATEVER, MAN.
I'M DONE.
DONE!
I COULDN'T BELIEVE WHAT I HAD
DONE.
I PUSHED AWAY MY BEST FRIEND AT
THE SHOW.
ANDREW DIS-MOE.
AFTER EVERYTHING WE HAVE BEEN THROUGH.
MONDAY PITCH IN LAUREN'S OFFICE,
TUESDAY WRITING NIGHT.
WHEN ANDREW GOT CUT FROM A
SKETCH BECAUSE HE DID A BAD JOB.
JUST TO THROW IT ALL AWAY
BECAUSE HE SAW ME FALL DOWN A
LOT?
THE SHOW WAS ABOUT TO START, BUT
I COULDN'T DO IT WITHOUT HIM.
DOES ANYONE HAVE EYES ON
MICHAEL B. JORDAN?
I KNEW THERE WAS ONLY ONE WAY
TO BRING HIM BACK.
I'M FALLING.
WHERE ARE YOU, ANDREW?
I'M RIGHT HERE.
AND WE'RE NOT FALLING.
WE'RE FLYING.
WHOO!
I ALSO WANT TO THANK EVERYBODY HERE.
I WANT TO THANK THE TALENTED
CAST AND CREW.
EVERYBODY AT SNL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING US.
I WANT TO THANK MY FAMILY
SITTING UP HERE THAT CAME THROUGH.
I LOVE Y'ALL SO MUCH.
THIS IS AN INCREDIBLE EXPERIENCE.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE IT IN THE WORLD.
I CAN'T WAIT TO COME BACK.
WHAT YOU GOT?
YOU AIN'T GOT NOTHING?
CAN'T WAIT TO DO IT AGAIN.