>>> YOU'RE WATCHING C-SPAN.
THANK YOU.
WE TAKE YOU NOW TO THE WHITE
HOUSE DAILY BRIEFING
WHERE PRESS
SECRETARY KAROLINE LEAVITT IS
ABOUT TO HAVE A DAY.
GOOD
HELLO
I AM JUST SO EXCITED TO BE
HERE AND ANSWER YOUR FRIENDLY
QUESTIONS.
AS YOU ALL KNOW, THERE WAS NO
NEWS THIS WEEK.
NOTHING HAPPENING WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
NO WEIRD INFORMATION WAS
REVEALED.
NO ONE HAD ANY ACCUSATIONS THAT
RHYME WITH "EDIFILE."
SO I'LL OPEN THE FLOOR TO
QUESTIONS
STARTING WITH CAITLIN
COLLINS FROM CNN WHO I OPENLY
HATE, GO AHEAD.
>> WE DEFINITELY NEED TO START
WITH THE 20,000 EPSTEIN EMAILS.
WHY DOES PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NAME
APPEAR IN SEASON OF THEM.
>> YOU KNOW YOU SUCK, RIGHT?
>> TRUMP HAS ASKED THE DOJ TO
INVESTIGATE DEMOCRATS' TIES TO EPSTEIN,
BUT IS ANYONE
INVESTIGATING TRUMP?
>> LOOK, THE ONLY THING THESE
EMAILS PROVE
IS THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP DID NOTHING WRONG.
IF ANYTHING, HIS CRIME WAS
LOVING TOO MUCH.
AND POSSIBLY TOO YOUNG.
NOW, LET'S GET A RELEVANT
QUESTION.
FOX NEWS?
>> UNNAMED BLACK GUY, FOX NEWS.
IS PRESIDENT TRUMP TOO HEALTHY?
>> THANK YOU.
AND, YES.
HE GOT HIS 30th PHYSICAL LAST WEEK,
AND IT WENT GREAT.
HE TOOK A COGNITIVE TEST AND DID
SO WELL,
THEY SAID "WE'D LIKE TO
SEE YOU AGAIN AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE."
YES, MSNBC, GO AHEAD.
>> ARE YOU NOT WORRIED ABOUT THE
OPTICS OF TRUMP GIVING EPSTEIN'S
PARTNER IN CRIME,
GHISLAINE
MAXWELL, A SWEETHEART DEAL?
>> HEY, GHISLAINE MAXWELL SAID
IN A SWORN DEPOSITION SHE GAVE
TO TRUMP'S FRIEND
THAT TRUMP
ALWAYS ACTED LIKE A GENTLEMAN.
AND A LITTLE THING ABOUT ME?
I BELIEVE WOMEN.
NOW, SERIOUSLY, CAN WE PLEASE
MOVE OFF THE TOPIC OF EPSTEIN?
>> SURE.
IS IT TRUE THE ADMINISTRATION
SECRETLY SENT $840 MILLION TO
ARGENTINA TO PAY OFF THEIR
DEBTS?
>> WE SHALL RETURN TO EPSTEIN!
>> I'M SORRY, BUT EVEN TRUMP'S
BIGGEST SUPPORTERS THINK
THAT HE
SHOULD RELEASE THE EPSTEIN
FILES.
WHAT DOES TRUMP HAVE TO HIDE?
>> I COULD ANSWER THAT.
I AM HIDING ALMOST NOTHING.
JUST ENOUGH TO MAKE IT EXTREMELY
SUSPICIOUS.
BUT LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
IF THERE WAS SOMETHING
INCRIMINATING ABOUT ME IN THE FILES,
THEN WHY WOULD I COVER
THEM UP?
>> WAIT.
ISN'T THAT EXACTLY WHY YOU WOULD
COVER THEM UP?
>> OKAY.
LET ME GO AGAIN.
IF I WAS INNOCENT, WOULDN'T I
JUST RELEASE ALL THE FILES?
>> YEAH.
AGAIN, I THINK YOU'RE AGREEING
WITH WHAT EVERYONE IS SAYING.
>> OKAY.
THIRD TIME'S A CHARM.
JEFFREY EPSTEIN, I BARELY KNEW THE GUY,
AS EVIDENCED BY THE
THOUSANDS OF PICTURES OF US
TOGETHER,
DANCING AND GRINDING
OUR TEETH AT VARIOUS PARTIES.
ALWAYS LEERING AND POINTING AT
SOMETHING JUST OFF CAMERA.
PROBABLY A BOOK WE'RE EXCITED TO
READ.
>> OKAY, WHAT ABOUT THE SPECIFIC
EMAIL WHERE EPSTEIN SAID
THAT
TRUMP WAS THE DOG THAT HASN'T
BARKED?
>> OKAY, OKAY, FIRST OF ALL --
ALL RIGHT -- I'M NOT A DOG.
I'M NOT A DOG.
I'M MORE OF A CUB.
OR POSSIBLY AN OTTER.
DEFINITELY NOT A TWINK.
I THINK THAT'S CLEAR, NOT A
TWINK, RIGHT?
MAYBE TWONK.
YOU KNOW GAYS HAVE WORDS FOR
EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
GEEKY, WE LIKE TO SAY GEEKY.
IT MEANS TALKING.
SECOND, I THOUGHT MEGYN KELLY
MADE A TERRIFIC POINT THIS WEEK.
SHE SAID EPSTEIN'S NOT A
PEDOPHILE.
TERRIFIC THING JUST TO SAY OUT
OF NOWHERE, GREAT JOB, MEGYN.
PUT HER BACK ON TV, LEGALIZE
MEGYN.
>> YOU SAID YOU KICKED EPSTEIN
OUT OF MAR-A-LAGO
BUT HE SAID HE
WAS, QUOTE, NEVER A MEMBER?
>> I SAID I KICKED JEFFREY ON IT
BECAUSE HE WAS A PEDOPHILE.
THEN I ALSO SAID I DIDN'T KNOW
HE DID ANYTHING WRONG.
SO IT'S KIND OF HARD TO SQUARE
THAT CIRCLE UNTIL YOU REALIZE
THAT TRUMP EXISTS ACROSS MANY
TIME LINES.
IT'S THE TRUMP MULTIVERSE
THEORY.
WE JUST HAPPEN TO BE LIVING IN
THE WORST POSSIBLE ONE.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME, I'M
GOING TO RELEASE ALL OF THE
EPSTEIN FILES.
THIS IS GREAT.
EACH FILE WILL BE ON SALE
FOR
THE LOW, LOW PRICE OF $800.
OH, SHE'S PRETTY, WHO'S THAT?
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
I LIKE THAT.
SHE'S NICE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A BEAUTIFUL,
ONE-OF-A-KIND, PRINTED-OUT
SCREEN SHOT
IN VERY LOW RES
OF ONE OF THE MANY FILES MENTIONING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
IT MAKES A GREAT STOCKING
STUFFER.
I JUST ORDERED THE ONE THAT
SAYS, "DOES PUTIN HAVE THE PHOTO
OF TRUMP BLOWING BUBBA?"
WE LOVE THAT, WHATEVER THE HELL
THAT MEANS.
BUT I DID ONE VERY
GENEROUS THING TODAY.
I PARDONED A TURKEY, OKAY?
WHO BY COMPLETE COINCIDENCE IS A
CONVICTED SEX CRIMINAL.
SO WE'RE GOING TO BE LOOKING
INTO THAT VERY SHORTLY, I CAN
ASSURE YOU THAT.
SO MERRY THANKSGIVING.
WE'RE GOING TO BE SAYING MERRY
THANKSGIVING AGAIN.
AND LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT!
MUSICAL
HOST
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN -- GLEN
POWELL!
THANK
I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
IT HAS BEEN A WILD YEAR.
MY TV SHOW PREMIERED.
I HAVE A MOVIE COMING OUT.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
AND I KNOW SOME OF YOU ARE TIRED
OF SEEING MY FACE.
HELL, I'M TIRED OF SEEING MY
FACE, TOO.
BUT YOU KNOW WHO IS NOT TIRED OF
SEEING MY FACE?
YOUR MOM.
BUT IT'S TRUE, MY FACE HAS BEEN
POPPING UP ALL OVER THE
INTERNET.
SPECIFICALLY THIS PHOTO.
LOOKS LIKE A GOLDEN RETRIEVER
ABOUT TO GET A TREAT.
I'VE ALSO SEEN A LOT OF PEOPLE
SAY, GLEN POWELL CAME OUT OF
NOWHERE.
AND THAT'S JUST NOT TRUE.
I STARTED ACTING WHEN I WAS 10
IN AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THANK YOU.
I DID STUDENT FILMS,
LOCAL COMMERCIALS, INTERNET SAFETY
VIDEOS.
EVEN, WHEN I WAS A TEEN, I
DIRECTED SOME OF MY OWN FILMS.
THEY WERE A LITTLE EXPERIMENTAL,
EMOTIONALLY NUANCED.
I WAS WATCH ALONG LOT OF FRENCH
NEW WAVE AT THE TIME.
I THINK YOU'LL SEE THE
INFLUENCE, CHECK IT OUT.
¶ IS IT MORE THAN YOU BARGAINED
FOR YEAH ¶
WATCH
HONEST
>> THAT WAS ACTUALLY MY AUDITION
FOR "TOP GUN."
BUT MY FIRST BIG BREAK CAME IN
SPY KIDS 3D.
I PLAYED A CHARACTER CALLED THE
LONG-FINGERED BOY.
THE LONG-FINGERED BOY -- A NAME
THAT GETS YOU ALL THE WRONG KIND
OF FRIENDS IN MIDDLE SCHOOL.
NOW, BEING ON THAT SET WAS THE
PEAK OF MY LIFE.
UNTIL TONIGHT.
HOSTING "SNL" IS A DREAM COME
TRUE.
NOT JUST FOR ME BUT FOR MY WHOLE
FAMILY.
AND, TRUE STORY, I WAS ACTUALLY
SUPPOSED TO HOST
FOUR YEARS AGO
FOR "TOP GUN: MAVERICK."
WHEN I GOT THE CALL, I WAS ON A
PORCH WITH MY FAMILY
AND WE JUST
ALL LOST OUR MINDS.
WE WERE JUMPING UP AND DOWN,
CELEBRATING.
AND A U.P.S. DRIVER HAPPENED TO
BE DELIVERING A PACKAGE AT THAT
EXACT SAME MOMENT
AND HE WAS
LIKE, "WHAT IS GOING ON?"
I'M HOSTING SNL"!"
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
"YEP, CHRISTMAS EPISODE, TUNE"
IN.
WE ALL TOOK A SELFIE WITH HIM.
THIS IS THE SELFIE TO MARK THE
OCCASION.
SO THAT'S ME AND MY WHOLE FAMILY
AND THE U.P.S. DRIVER.
BUT THEN MY DREAM GOT TAKEN
AWAY.
TOP GUN GOT DELAYED BECAUSE OF COVID,
SO "SNL" HAD TO TAKE
THEIR OFFER BACK.
LORNE MICHAELS LITERALLY CALLED
ME AND SAID,
WITHOUT TOP GUN,
THESE ARE HIS WORDS,
"NO ONE
WILL KNOW WHO THE F YOU ARE."
SO I DIDN'T END UP HOSTING,
WHICH MEANS FOR FOUR YEARS,
THIS
U.P.S. DRIVER WAS JUST GOING
AROUND
SAYING, GLEN POWELL IS A
LIAR.
SO NOW I AM HERE, HOSTING.
IT FEELS AMAZING.
BUT WHAT FEELS EVEN BETTER
IS PROVING TO THIS U.P.S. DRIVER
THAT I AM NOT CRAZY.
SO THIS IS REAL.
MY SISTERS TRACKED HIM DOWN.
'CAUSE THE WOMEN IN MY FAMILY
ARE TERRIFYING.
AND THEY FOUND THE CELL NUMBER
OF THIS U.P.S. GUY.
HIS NAME IS MITCH.
SO TO PROVE TO MITCH THAT I AM
NOT A LIAR,
I FLEW HIM ALL THE
WAY TO NEW YORK --
COACH.
I DON'T KNOW HOW "RUNNING MAN'S"
GOING TO DO YET.
BUT I FLEW HIM HERE.
AND HE THOUGHT IT WAS A SCAM,
BUT HE STILL CAME.
AND HE IS SITTING IN THE
AUDIENCE TONIGHT.
SO LET'S GIVE IT UP FOR MITCH,
THE U.P.S. GUY.
ALL RIGHT, SO MITCH?
WHY DON'T YOU COME UP HERE.
WE'LL RECREATE THE SELFIE.
BRING THIS THING FULL CIRCLE.
LOOK, I HAD TO WAIT MY ENTIRE
LIFE, PLUS FOUR YEARS, TO BE
HERE.
BUT IF I HAVE LEARNED ANYTHING,
IT IS THAT THE BEST THINGS IN
LIFE DON'T HAPPEN OVERNIGHT.
AND NO ONE KNOWS THAT BETTER
THAN THE U.P.S.
GREAT
STICK
NICE
DINNER TO ME.
I'M SURE THE SUNNYSIDE SENIOR
HOME ISN'T WHERE YOU WANTED TO
SPEND YOUR THANKSGIVING.
>> STOP THAT, GRANDMA.
WE WANTED TO BE HERE.
>> YEAH, PLUS YOU PROBABLY DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF THANKSGIVINGS
LEFT.
>> NATHAN!
WELL, GRANDMA, BEFORE WE GO, WE
HAVE A SPECIAL SURPRISE FOR YOU.
WHEN WE WERE CLEANING OUT YOUR HOUSE,
WE FOUND A BOX OF OLD PHOTOS
FROM WHEN YOU WERE A
LITTLE GIRL.
>> NATHAN SCANNED THEM INTO THIS
COOL APP CALLED "OLD-TIME PHOTOS
BROUGHT TO LIFE."
IT'S REALLY COOL.
HERE'S ONE OF YOUR PICTURES.
THAT'S MY FATHER!
HE'S SO YOUNG.
>> YEAH.
NOW WATCH WHAT THE APP DOES.
>> OH!
WOW!
OH, MY GOODNESS!
HE WAS WAVING AND SMILING!
HOW DID IT DO THAT?
>> WELL, THE AI ANALYZES THE
PICTURE AND PROJECTS HOW THEY'D
MOVE.
>> OH, HERE'S ANOTHER ONE WITH
YOUR MOM IN IT.
>> OH, LOOK AT HER!
SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> IS THAT A CIGARETTE?
GREAT GRANDMA SMOKED?
>> OH, EVERYBODY DID BACK THEN.
CAN YOU BRING THIS ONE TO LIFE
TOO?
>> OF COURSE, GRANDMA.
>> WHY DID MY MOTHER SMOKE HER
HOT DOG?
>> SOMETIMES THE AI IS WEIRD,
BUT ISN'T IT COOL?
LOOK, EVEN THAT DOG'S TAIL IS
WAGGING.
>> OH, THAT WAS SADIE, OUR
FAMILY PUP.
OH GOD!
WHOA, WHY DID THE COMPUTER DO
THAT TO SADIE?
>> WELL, THERE'S PROBABLY JUST
TOO MUCH GOING ON IN THE PICTURE,
AND THE AI GOT
CONFUSED.
HERE, LOOK AT THIS ONE.
IT'S YOUR DAD AND --
OH, SOME
GUY IN A BOWLING ALLEY.
>> DO YOU KNOW HIM, GRANDMA?
>> OH, THAT WAS MY FATHER'S BEST
FRIEND, CAL RYLAND.
OH, HE WAS A HOOT.
THEY WOULD GET TOGETHER AND
LAUGH AND LAUGH.
OH, CAN YOU BRING THIS ONE TO
LIFE TOO?
>> OF COURSE, GRANDMA.
BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW, WE ONLY
HAVE A COUPLE MORE FREE ONES
LEFT.
BEFORE I HAVE TO BUY MORE
CREDITS ON THE APP.
>> NATHAN!
>> WHAT?
>> HERE, GRANDMA, I'LL DO IT.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> UM -- I THINK WHAT HAPPENED,
GRANDMA, WAS --
THEIR BOWLING
BALLS FLOATED AWAY,
AND THEN
YOUR DAD PAID CAL RYLAND TO SHOW
HIS KEN DOLL CROTCH.
>> BUT WHY?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
GRANDMA.
LET'S JUST DO ONE MORE.
HERE, WE FOUND A SPECIAL ONE
FOR YOU.
>> AS FAR AS WE CAN TELL, IT'S
THE FIRST PICTURE YOU EVER TOOK.
YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE, LITTLE
BABY.
>> OH, MY HEAVENS, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE WE DON'T BRING
THIS ONE TO LIFE.
IT'S JUST SO NICE THE WAY IT IS.
>> WELL -- IT COST ME 10 CREDITS
JUST TO UPLOAD IT TO THE APP,
SO
WE'RE GOING TO.
>> OH, MY GOD!
HALF
OH, WHAT IS THAT?
MAKE IT LEAVE!
OH, NO!
NO!
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I'VE HAD
ENOUGH OF THE PHOTOS.
>> WE'RE SORRY, GRANDMA, WE JUST
WANTED TO DO SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR YOU.
>> OH, YOU DID.
YOU CAME TO VISIT ME.
NOW I'LL LET YOU GO, BUT WILL I
SEE YOU FOR CHRISTMAS?
>> OF COURSE, GRANDMA.
>> YEAH, IF YOU MAKE IT TILL
THEN.
>> NATHAN!
>> WHAT?
>>> YOU EVER MISS SOMEONE SO
MUCH, YOU LOSE SIGHT OF
YOURSELF?
>> YOU THINK ABOUT THEM ALL THE
TIME.
YOU WONDER IF LIFE WILL EVER
SEEM NORMAL AGAIN.
¶ HAVEN'T FELT THE SAME SINCE
YOU BEEN GONE ¶
¶ EVERYONE ELSE JUST FEELS SO
WRONG ¶
¶ I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE OVER YOU
AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS BOTTLE
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ¶
¶ I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO SAY
I JUST WANT TO HEAR ABOUT YOUR
DAY ¶
¶ I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT
WHAT WE HAD OH MAN ¶
¶ I MISS MY EX'S DAD ¶
LIE
¶ YOU GAVE ME A POCKETKNIFE
AND SOME SHIRTS THAT ALL WERE
PLAID ¶
¶ YOUR SOCKS YOUR CROCS
YOU'RE THE IDEAL MALE WITH YOUR
PONYTAIL ¶
¶ I DON'T MISS HIS DAUGHTER AT ALL
WHICH I KNOW IS BAD ¶
¶ I JUST MISS MY EX'S DAD ¶
>> IT'S A DAMN SHAME WHEN
SOMEONE BEAUTIFUL LEAVES YOUR
LIFE.
A DAMN SHAME.
¶ REMEMBER THANKSGIVING YOU WERE
IN A BAD MOOD ¶
¶ YOU WOULDN'T PLAY CHARADES
EVERYONE WAS MAD AT YOU ¶
¶ THEY WERE TRYING TO PUT YOUR
NAME IN THE DIRT
BUT I STEPPED
IN AND SAID ¶
>> HE'S UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE
AT WORK.
¶ YOU RECOMMENDED BROOKS RUNNING
SHOES ¶
¶ NOW MY ARCHES ARE FOREVER IN
DEBT TO YOU ¶
¶ THE SHOP IN THE GARAGE WAS RAD
YOU'RE THE DAD I NEVER HAD ¶
¶ BESIDES MY REAL DAD ¶
¶ OH GARY AND DOCTOR MIKE
I MISS MY EX'S DAD ¶
¶ WE SMOKED CIGARS AND THAT WAS
TIGHT ¶
¶ YOU PLAYED BALL IN UNDERGRAD ¶
¶ YOUR GRILL YOUR BUICK
YOU'RE THE IDEAL MAN WITH YOUR
CARDIGAN ¶
¶ DON'T REMEMBER HIS DAUGHTER'S NAME
WHICH I KNOW IS BAD ¶
¶ I JUST MISS MY EX'S DAD ¶
¶ OH I MISS YOU
I'M YOUR NUMBER ONE FAN ¶
¶ HER NEW BOYFRIEND DIDN'T LIKE MY STORY
ABOUT ME SEE
¶ BUT I HAVE A PLAN TO GET YOU
BACK ¶
¶ A PLAN THAT CANNOT FAIL ¶
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO FOR
CHRISTMAS?
>> YOUR NEW BOYFRIEND TRIED TO
KISS ME.
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
>> YES, YOU DID, THREE TIMES
TODAY.
ONCE ON THE NECK, ONCE ON MY
MOUTH, AND ONCE ON MY BACK.
>> I DIDN'T TRY TO KISS YOUR
BACK.
>> DAD, STOP.
I KNOW YOU JUST MISS LEO.
>> SO WHAT IF I DO?
I AM NOT MADE OF STONE.
HE IS THE GREATEST MAN I HAVE EVER MET,
AND YOU KICKED HIM TO
THE CURB.
LIKE A DOG!
I HATE IT HERE!
NO ONE IN THIS FAMILY
UNDERSTANDS ME!
>> HE USUALLY LIKE THIS?
¶ I MISS MY DAUGHTER'S EX ¶
¶ OH LEO MAN BIG RED
I MISS MY DAUGHTER'S EX ¶
¶ I WISH YOUR NEW BOYFRIEND WAS DEAD
¶ YOU SHOULD BE HERE DRINKING BEER
WITH YOUR FAVORITE DRINKING
LAD ¶
¶ IT AIN'T UP TO ME BUT I'M
ALWAYS PROUD TO BE ¶
¶ YOUR EX'S DAD ¶
>>> THIS IS ABOUT TO BE THE BEST
BACHELOR WEEKEND OF OUR LIVES!
>> HERE'S TO THE GROOM TO BE!
>> NOW I'M THE ONLY ONE LEFT,
THE ONLY SINGLE ONE LEFT.
IT'S JUST -- NO, IT WILL HAPPEN
FOR ME.
>> GUYS, I JUST REALLY WANT TO
SAY THANK YOU FOR PUTTING THIS
ALL TOGETHER.
IT IS GOING TO BE AN EPIC
WEEKEND.
>> I HOPE IT'S NOT A STRIPPER!
>> I ACTUALLY FORGOT TO TELL YOU GUYS,
I HAVE ONE MORE FRIEND
COMING, YOU NEVER MET HIM.
I SHOULD PROBABLY WARN YOU. HE'S --
HE'S SEBASTIAN
MANISCALCO.
>> WAIT, LIKE THE WORLD-FAMOUS
COMEDIAN?
>> YES, BUT HE IS NOTHING LIKE
WHAT YOU'VE SEEN ON TV, I
PROMISE.
I'M DRIVING MY CAR.
AND I'VE GOT THE STICK SHIFT
GOING.
AND THEN THE TRAFFIC WAS ON
ANOTHER LEVEL.
OKAY, AND THEN THIS GENIUS CUTS
ME OFF.
AND I'M LIKE, WHY WOULD YOU DO
THAT?
>> OKAY, SO HE'S EXACTLY LIKE HE
IS ON TV.
>> SEBASTIAN, I HAVE MISSED YOU,
MAN.
WE'VE GOT TO HANG OUT MORE.
>> IT'S TRUE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T A BACHELORETTE
PARTY, BUT --
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I THOUGHT WE COULD PLAY A
GAME.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> NO, I'M NOT KIDDING,
ACTUALLY.
IT'S A GAME CALLED "GUESS THE
GIRLFRIEND."
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S A GAME I
DON'T LIKE?
I DON'T LIKE TWISTER, YOU HEARD
OF THIS, TWISTER?
THE GUY GOES, PUT YOUR RIGHT
FOOT ON PELLOW, RIGHT?
AND THEN THE SON OF A BITCH, HE
GOES, LEFT HAND TO PURPLE.
NOW MY HAND IS IN MY RECTUM.
AND I GO, IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE THERE.
>> YOU ARE COOKING, C-BASS MAN.
IT WAS SO BORING BEFORE YOU GOT
HERE.
>> OKAY.
HURTFUL.
>> I'M SORRY, HOW DO YOU TWO
KNOW EACH OTHER?
>> OH, WE ACTUALLY WENT TO CAMP
TOGETHER, FOUR YEARS IN A ROW.
>> SOME OF THE BEST TIMES OF MY
LIFE.
>> OKAY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST MOVE PAST
THE GAME PORTION OF THE EVENING.
>> THIS GUY.
>> BECAUSE I KIND OF WANTED TO
MAKE A SPEECH.
I KNOW, THAT SUCKS.
THAT SUCKS.
BUT I DO WANT TO SAY A FEW WORDS
BEFORE YOU OFFICIALLY TIE THE
KNOT.
>> LET ME TELL YOU THE BIGGEST PROBLEM,
THE BIGGEST PROBLEM
WITH TYING THE KNOT, OKAY?
WHEN YOU GOT A BOW, YOU GOT TO
TIE A KNOT AS TIGHT AS YOU CAN.
IF YOU MAKE A MISTAKE, OKAY?
THAT BOW THAT COST YOU HALF YOUR SALARY,
IT'S KISS IT GOOD-BYE.
>> THAT IS EXACTLY WHY I DON'T
HAVE A BOAT
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO KISS IT GOOD-BYE.
>> IT'S BETTER WHEN SEBASTIAN
DOES IT.
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY.
SEBASTIAN, IT'S AWESOME MEETING YOU, MAN,
BUT THIS WEEKEND IS
ABOUT DAVE.
LIKE, HE'S THE ONE GETTING
MARRIED.
>> OH.
YOU WANT SOME MARRIAGE ADVICE?
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE IS GOING TO
BE THE MOTHER-IN-LAW, OKAY?
AND IT'S NOT THE TYPE OF
OBSTACLE YOU CAN STEP OVER.
NO, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO JUMP
OVER THE MOTHER-IN-LAW.
>> SEBASTIAN, I SWEAR, YOUR BODY
IS A WONDER LAND.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OKAY, GUYS.
SEBASTIAN HAS TOTALLY CHANGED
THE DYNAMIC OF THIS SLEEPOVER.
>> HEY, DON'T DO THAT.
IT'S NOT A SLEEPOVER.
>> I THINK WHAT AUSTIN IS TRYING
TO SAY IS IT'S STARTING TO FEEL
LIKE YOU DON'T REALLY CARE ABOUT US,
YOU ONLY REALLY CARE ABOUT
SEBASTIAN MANISCALO.
>> IF YOU GUYS CAN'T HANG AROUND
WITH ME WHEN I'M AROUND SEBASTIAN,
THEN MAYBE YOU
SHOULDN'T HANG AROUND WITH ME AT
ALL.
>> AND THAT'S FACT.
LISTEN.
MY SINCEREST APOLOGIES TO YOU
GUYS.
I JUST HAVEN'T SEEN DAVE IN A
WHILE.
AND THIS GUY, THEY TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, EVER SINCE WE WERE TWO
KIDS AT SUMMER CAMP BACK WHEN WE WOULD BE
PLAYING.
SHOOTING BASKETBALL.
WE USED TO LOVE TO SWIM.
WE WERE SWIMMING.
>> PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THIS, BUT
ME AND THIS GUY,
WE WERE LIKE
TWO PEAS IN A POD, YOU
UNDERSTAND?
>> I KNOW I SOUND DIFFERENT NOW,
BUT THAT IS STILL WHO I AM ON
THE INSIDE.
EVERY DAY I HAVE TO QUIET DOWN
MY INNER SEBASTIAN.
I GOT TO PUSH IT DOWN.
I GOT TO SAY, NOT NOW.
>> WOW.
SORRY.
WE DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> NO WAY FOR YOU TO KNOW THAT.
>> HOW COULD THAT BE?
>> OH, I DID ORDER A STRIPPER.
I SHOULD WARN Y'ALL,
SHE'S
JENNIFER COOLIDGE.
>> OH, WOW!
HI, BOYS!
I CAN'T WAIT TO DANCE FOR YOU.
AND DON'T WORRY.
I STILL GOT A FAT ASS.
SAY
HONORED TO BE HERE IN OSLO,
DIRECTING THIS MOVIE, "SCENT OF
A MARRIAGE."
I AM A HUGE FAN OF NORWEGIAN
FILM.
YOU GUYS TAKE SUCH AN
UNFLINCHING LOOK
AT THE WAYS WE
DEVASTATE EACH OTHER.
SO, LET'S GO FOR A TAKE.
>> "SCENT OF A MARRIAGE" SCENE
12 TAKE 1.
>> AND ACTION!
>> YOU THINK YOU LOST ME?
>> PLEASE DON'T ASK ME THAT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WORK AT THE BOOKSTORE TILL
YOU'RE 50?
YOU SHOULD BE WRITING BOOKS, NOT
SELLING THEM.
>> HOW CAN YOU SAY THIS?
EVERYTHING I DO IS FOR OUR SON.
EVERYTHING CHANGED AFTER THE
ACCIDENT.
>> DON'T YOU USE HIM AS AN
EXCUSE.
YOU'RE JUST AFRAID TO EVER WANT
ANYTHING.
>> AND YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME A
COWARD.
>> YOU'RE TOO LAZY TO BE A
A COWARD HAS THE ENERGY TO HIDE.
YOU JUST SIT THERE.
>> AND CUT!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THAT WAS INSANE!
>> OKAY!LIKE, THE COOLEST
THING I EVER EXPERIENCED!
>> OKAY, YOU ARE AMAZING AT
ACTING.
I WAS LIKE, WE WERE ON THE SET
FOR THE EMOTION
AND I WAS LIKE,
LET'S RIDE!
>> WE WERE RIDING.
>> WE WILL RIDE.
>> REALLY WOW.
AWESOME.
I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU GUYS TO
HAVE THIS KIND OF ENERGY RIGHT NOW,
BUT YEAH, I THINK THAT TAKE
WAS GREAT SO LET'S JUST MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT SCENE IF THAT'S
OKAY?
>> YEAH, SO COOL.
>> SO EFFING COOL.
>> EXCELLENT.
THERE IS WHERE YOU'RE WAITING
FOR YOUR SON TO GET OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL.
>> "SCENT OF A MARRIAGE" SCENE
19 TAKE 1.
>> AND ACTION!
>> I'M SICK OF YOU.
I'M SICK OF YOUR TASTE.
>> HOW WOULD YOU KNOW HOW I
TASTE?
YOU HAVEN'T TOUCHED ME SINCE OUR
SON FELL DOWN THE HILL.
>> TOUCHING YOU IS NOT AN
IMPULSE THAT I HAVE.
>> THAT YOU HAVE.
YOU.
LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
>> I'M LEAVING YOU.
>> CUT!
>> GUYS, THIS IS SO GOOD!
>> I LOVE THIS SCRIPT!
>> OH, SERIOUSLY, SERIOUSLY,
SERIOUSLY, I HAVE LITTLE
GOOSEBUMPS.
OH, MY GOD, THE GOOSE PIMPLES.
RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU FELT
THAT.
>> ME!
>> YOU FELT IT, OKAY.
HIGH FIVE, HIGH FIVE.
>> WOW, YOU GUYS ARE LOVING
THIS.
REALLY GOT SOME CHEMISTRY.
>> OH, WE WERE ACTING.
>> WE WERE ACTING.
>> OKAY, EXCELLENT.
WELL, HONESTLY, WHAT WE'RE
GETTING ON CAMERA IS TERRIFIC.
AND THIS IS THIS.
SO LET'S KEEP MOVING, AND WE'LL
JUMP TO THE BED SCENE.
>> OH, OH-OH, SCENE IN THE BED.
HOPE THE BED DOESN'T BREAK,
FREAKY!
>> EXCUSE ME, DON'T POKE ME WITH
THAT THING.
>> DON'T POKE ME WITH THOSE
THINGS.
>> "SCENT OF A MARRIAGE" SCENE
40 TAKE 1.
>> AND ACTION!
>> IT'S OVER.
>> I KNOW.
>> MOM?
DAD?
YOU'RE GETTING A DIVORCE?
IS IT MY FAULT?
>> YES.
>> AND CUT!
>> THE BEST SCENE YET!
>> SERIOUSLY GUYS, WE ARE GOING
TO HOLLYWOOD.
>> WE'RE GOING TO MEET JIMMY
KIMMEL!
GIVE
>> OKAY, WHO AM I, WHO AM I?
MIKE
>> OH, OH -- HAWTHORNE,
HAWTHORNE!
GOT
>> OKAY, GUYS, I THINK WE'VE GOT
TO MOVE ON
SO LET'S PLEASE GO TO
THE NEXT SCENE WITH THE FATHER'S
ENTRANCE.
WE'VE GOT STELLAN STANDING BY,
SO YOU ALL READY?
EXCELLENT.
PLACES.
MR. SKARSGARD!
AND ACTION!
>> FATHER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I'VE COME TO TELL YOU THE
TRUTH.
IT'S MY FAULT YOUR SON FELL DOWN
THE HILL.
>> NO.
IT'S NOT.
>> I PUSHED HIM HARD ON THE
SHOULDER.
I WATCHED HIM TUMBLE STRAIGHT
INTO THE SPRUCE.
>> GRANDDAD.
IS THIS TRUE?
YOU PUSHED ME DOWN?
>> YES.
I AM A MONSTER.
NOW FOREVER I WILL LIVE WITH THE
SOUND OF HIS CRIES.
THE TASTE OF HIS GRIEF.
AND THE SCENT OF YOUR MARRIAGE.
>> CUT!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> THAT'S THE NAME OF THE MOVIE!
GOOSE
>> IT'S CRAZY!
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ MAKING LIFE-SAVING INVENTIONS
OUT OF HOUSEHOLD MATERIALS ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ GETTING IN AND OUT OF STICKY
SITUATIONS ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ THE GUY'S A FREAKING GENIUS ¶
BLACK SITE
>>> MacGRUBER, THE DOOR'S WELDED
SHUT, THERE'S NO ESCAPE.
>> THAT'S NOT THE ONLY PROBLEM.
BY THE LOOKS OF THAT CLUSTER
BOMB, WE'VE ONLY GOT 45 SECONDS.
>> DON'T WORRY, GANG, I CAN TAME
THIS BRONCO IN MY SLEEP.
BOMB CLASS 101.
TAWNEE, HAND ME THAT PENCIL
SHARPENER.
>> YOU GOT IT, MacGRUBER.
>> COLTON, A PATCH OF FOIL.
>> ALL THE WAY, MacGRUBES.
>> NOW JUST SIT BACK AND ENJOY THE RIZZY.
>> WHY IS HE IN THE CONTROL ROOM
WITH THE BOMB?
>> I THINK I KNOW WHY, AND I
FEEL AWFUL.
SEE, I HAVE A DOCUMENT IN MY
POSSESSION THAT I WAS GOING TO
LEAK TO THE PRESS.
SOMETHING SO SENSITIVE,
SOMETHING SO POWERFUL
THAT
PEOPLE WOULD GO TO ANY LENGTH TO
STOP ME.
>> THE COLONEL'S SECRET RECIPE.
>> EVEN MORE SENSITIVE.
- THE EPSTEIN FILES.
- UNREDACTED.
>> TALK ABOUT EXPLOSIVE.
FOR FAR TOO LONG, THE RICH AND
POWERFUL
HAVE LIVED BY A
DIFFERENT SET OF RULES THAN THE
REST OF US.
BUT IT'S TIME FOR A RECKONING.
'CAUSE NO ONE, AND I MEAN NO
ONE, IS ABOVE THE LAW.
TAKE A LOOK AT THESE BOTTOM
FEEDERS.
>> SOMETHING WRONG, MacGRUBER?
>> 15 SECONDS, MacGRUBER!
>> CONNIE, HAND ME THAT NEEDLE!
>> WHERE?
I DON'T SEE A NEEDLE.
>> KEEP LOOKING, IT'S BEHIND
YOU.
COLTON, HELP HER LOOK!
>> WE CAN'T FIND IT!
>> MacGRUBER, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> INSURANCE, COLTON.
THIS LIST IS TOO IMPORTANT
TO
HAVE ALL IN ONE PLACE FOR SOME
BAD GUY TO STEAL.
SO I'M BREAKING IT UP INTO TINY
LITTLE PIECES
WHICH WE CAN HIDE
IN VARIOUS GARBAGE CANS THAT
ONLY WE KNOW ABOUT.
>> MacGRUBER, DO YOU KNOW
SOMEBODY ON THE LIST?
>> OKAY, WELL YEAH -- OKAY,
OKAY.
I DO KNOW ONE GUY.
>> MacGRUBER?
ARE YOU ON THE LIST?
>> HA, RIGHT, AS IF.
NO.
>> SCOUT'S HONOR?
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
>>> DEAR MOM.
JUST WRITING TO LET YOU KNOW
THEY TRANSFERRED ME TO A NEW TOP
SECRET DIVISION.
I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT IT, BUT
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING TO SERVE
THIS COUNTRY.
I MISS YOU, MOM.
LOVE, MANNY.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
SLAY, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
TWO, THREE, FOUR,
AND HALT!
>> SERGEANT!
>> AMAZING BOD ON YOU, PRIVATE.
BOOTY, FACE GIVING.
>> BUT THE HAIR?
>> WE ARE GOING TO NEED TO BOB
IT.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO NEED TO WHAT?
>> OH, HONEY, YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
>> OH, HE DIDN'T KNOW.
>> HE DIDN'T KNOW.
>> YOU'VE BEEN ASSIGNED TO THE
SLAY DIVISION.
>> AND IN THE SLAY DIVISION,
EVERYBODY GETS BOBBED.
>> I'M SORRY, THE SLAY DIVISION?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
>> THE U.S. MILITARY IS ALWAYS
IN SEARCH
OF INNOVATIVE WAYS TO
INTIMIDATE THE ENEMY.
>> AND RESEARCH SHOWS THERE'S
NOTHING MORE INTIMIDATING THAN A
FREAK-ASS BOB.
>> HAVE YOU EVER SPOKEN TO A
WOMAN WITH A BOB?
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET ON HER BAD
SIDE.
>> AND IF YOU SEE A MAN WITH A BOB,
DIVA, YOU BETTER RUN.
>> A BUZZ CUT GETS THE GUNS
BUT THE BOB SAYS GET THE MANAGER.
>> I'M CONFUSED.
IS YOUR HAIR LIKE A WEAPON?
>> YEAH, BUT WE DON'T KILL OUR
ENEMY.
>> WE GAG THEM WITH BLUNT FORCE.
>> FALL IN, COMPANY!
¶ ONE TWO THREE FOUR
AND SLAY
TWO THREE FOUR AND HALT ¶
>> ATTENTION!
IS ALL WE WANT.
>> SO ALL YOU GUYS DO IS DANCE
AROUND AND GET HAIRCUTS?
>> THAT'S NOT ALL.
WE ALSO LISTEN TO TATE McRAE
AND
DO PUFFERS UNTIL WE PASS OUT.
>> SLAY DIVISION?
WHAT IS OUR MISSION?
>> SERVE AND PROTECT!
BUT MOSTLY SERVE!
>> HOLD ON, CONNERS.
ARE MY EYES DECEIVING ME?
OR DID YOU BRING A BANG TO A BOB
FIGHT?
>> THIS DIVA DECEIVED US.
HIS HAIR'S AN ABSOLUTE FLOP.
A BANG GIVES CRISIS,
WHILE A BOB GIVES DIVORCE AND THRIVING.
>> WAIT, WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
>> THE SCENT OF HIS SLOP-ASS
BANG MUST HAVE LED US TO IT.
IT'S OUR RIVAL DIVISION,
THE BANG BATTALION!
¶ WHEN THE BANGS OH WHEN THE
BANGS
OH WHEN THE BANGS COME
SURFING IN ¶
>> BURN THE HOUSE DOWN, BANG THE
BOBS UP ARE.
>> THE GUMPTION.
>> THE GIRLS ARE FIGHTING.
>> YOU REALLY THINK YOU STOOD A
CHANCE, BUT WE HAVE A
BOB-SNIFFING DOG.
>> BOB ARMY, SHOW THESE SKANKS HOW IT'S
DONE.
CHANCE
¶ EVERYWHERE WE GO
PEOPLE WANNA KNOW ¶
¶ WHERE WE GOT THE JACKET
SO WE TELL THEM ¶
¶ OH I KNOW I THINK IT WAS A
GIFT ¶
>> WOW.
I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
GANG
MOLL
>> HAVE ANY OF YOU EVEN BEEN
DEPLOYED?
>> OF COURSE WE HAVE.
SERGEANT BAKER DID TWO TOURS IN
IRAQ.
>> IT WAS CRAZY.
THE GUNS WERE LIKE
GOAL
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN WITH A WOMAN.
>> OKAY, WHAT?
DOES PETE HEGSETH KNOW ABOUT
THIS?
>> NO, WE DON'T REPORT TO HER.
>> WE ONLY ANSWER TO LESLIE BIBB
'CAUSE THE AIR FORCE IS IN THE
AIR, THE NAVY IS IN THE WATER,
AND WE'RE IN YOUR HEAD
RENT-FREE.
>> YOU HAVE A CHOICE HERE,
CADET.
WILL YOU JOIN THE BOBS?
OR THE BANGS?
>> WELL --
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SEE
YOU ALL TURN IT OUT BEFORE YOU
CLOCK MY GAG.
>> OH?
OKAY, PEARL.
LET'S SHOW HIM HOW WE SERVE
COUNTRY.
¶ BOB A BOB A BOB A BOB BOB ¶
¶ BANG A BANG A BANG A BANG
BANG ¶
>> WELL, PRIVATE, WHAT WILL IT
BE?
>> I'M GONNA BOB IT!
>> OKAY,
I'M GLAD TO HAVE YOU, DIVA.
WE ARE GETTING DEPLOYED IN THE
MORNING.
>> OH, WHERE TO?
>> ZARA, MIDTOWN.
IT'S A WAR ZONE IN THERE.
>> ZARA MIDTOWN.
WE SAID WHAT WE SAID.
LADIES
Man I Need
¶ TALK TO ME TALK TO ME
TALK TO ME TALK TO ME ¶
¶ LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE MAKING UP FOR LOST TIME
NEED YOU TO
SPELL IT OUT FOR ME ¶
¶ BOSSA NOVA ON ALL NIGHT
IT'S LIKE A TYPE
OF ALCHEMY ¶
¶ INTRODUCE ME
TO YOUR BEST FRIEND
I CAN COME
AND SLOT RIGHT IN ¶
¶ A SATELLITE
AIN'T EVEN THAT FAR
I KINDA WONDER
WHERE YOU ARE ¶
¶ ALREADY KNOW
I CAN'T LEAVE IT ALONE
YOU'RE ON MY MIND ¶
¶ ALREADY GAVE YOU
THE TIME AND THE PLACE
SO DON'T BE SHY ¶
¶ JUST COME
BE THE MAN I NEED ¶
¶ TELL ME YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO GIVE
I WANT IT ¶
¶ I KINDA LIKE IT
WHEN YOU CALL ME
WONDERFUL ¶
¶ WHATEVER
THE TYPE OF TALK IT IS
COME ON THEN ¶
¶ I GOTTA KNOW
YOU'RE MEANT TO BE
THE MAN I NEED ¶
¶ TALK TO ME
TALK TO ME
MM TALK TO ME TALK TO ME ¶
¶ BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED BABY
TALK TO ME TALK TO ME ¶
¶ BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED NEED NEED
TALK TO ME TALK TO ME ¶
¶ BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED BABY
TALK TO ME TALK TO ME ¶
¶ BE THE MAN
MAN MAN MAN MAN ¶
¶ I'D LIKE TO THINK
YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY
BUT I CAN'T TELL
WITH YOU SOMETIMES ¶
¶ SO BABY
LET'S GET ON THE SAME PAGE
STOP MAKING ME READ
BETWEEN THE LINES ¶
¶ ALREADY KNOW
I CAN'T LEAVE IT ALONE
YOU'RE ON MY MIND YEAH ¶
¶ AND I ALREADY GAVE YOU
THE TIME AND THE PLACE
SO DON'T BE SHY ¶
¶ JUST COME
BE THE MAN I NEED ¶
¶ TELL ME YOU GOT
SOMETHING TO GIVE
I WANT IT ¶
¶ I KINDA LIKE IT
WHEN YOU CALL ME
WONDERFUL ¶
¶ WHATEVER
THE TYPE OF TALK IT IS
COME ON THEN ¶
¶ I GOTTA KNOW
YOU'RE MEANT TO BE
THE MAN I NEED ¶
¶ TALK TO ME
TALK TO ME
TALK TO ME ¶
¶ MM TALK TO ME TALK TO ME
BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED BABY ¶
¶ TALK TO ME TALK TO ME
BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED NEED NEED ¶
¶ MM TALK TO ME TALK TO ME
BE THE MAN
THAT I NEED BABY ¶
¶ TALK TO ME TALK TO ME
BE THE MAN
MAN MAN MAN MAN ¶
WEEKEND
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> WELCOME TO "WEEKEND UPDATE,"
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
THE LONGEST GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
IN HISTORY
FINALLY ENDED AFTER 43 DAYS,
AND YOU KNOW FIRST DAY
BACK IN THE OFFICE, YOU GOT TO
CHECK ALL THOSE PILED-UP EMAILS.
EPSTEIN
HOUSE DEMOCRATS RELEASED AN
EMAIL WRITTEN BY JEFFREY EPSTEIN
IN WHICH HE CLAIMS THAT DONALD
TRUMP, QUOTE, KNEW ABOUT THE
GIRLS.
IT'S BOMBSHELL NEWS THAT LEGAL
EXPERTS ARE CALLING DUH.
THIS WEEK'S EPSTEIN DOCUMENTS
ARE OBVIOUSLY VERY DARK AND DISTURBING,
BUT I ALSO THINK
IT'S KIND OF ADORABLE THAT
EPSTEIN'S EMAIL ADDRESS
WAS JEEVACATION@GMAIL.
IT'S LIKE IF JEFFREY DAHMER AS
DINNERTIMEJEFF@YAHOO!.
>> IN ONE OF THE EMAILS,
EPSTEIN'S BROTHER ASKED IF
VLADIMIR PUTIN HAS A PICTURE
OF DONALD TRUMP GIVING ORAL SEX TO
SOMEONE NAMED BUBBA.
WHICH WAS AN OLD NICKNAME FOR
BILL CLINTON.
SO I GUESS THAT'S ONE JOB TRUMP
HAS CREATED.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT ORAL SEX
STORY IS TRUE,
BUT I DO KNOW
THAT IMAGE IS BURNED IN MY
BRAIN.
LIKE THAT SCENE FROM "THE
SHINING."
ACCORDING TO ONE RELEASED EMAIL,
JEFFREY EPSTEIN CLAIMED
THAT HE
WAS, QUOTE, THE ONE ABLE TO TAKE
TRUMP DOWN.
WHICH IS PRETTY BIG TALK FOR A
GUY WHO LOST TO A BEDSHEET.
>> I JUST HAVE TO SAY IN GENERAL
I DON'T BELIEVE IN CONSPIRACIES.
BECAUSE AS A MEMBER OF THE
ILLUMINATI --
I KNOW THAT WE, THE LIZARD
PEOPLE, CONTROL EVERYTHING.
AND IT'S REALLY HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT TRUMP WAS SO OBLIVIOUS
THAT
HE DIDN'T NOTICE HIS GOOD FRIEND
WAS RUNNING AN INTERNATIONAL
PEDOPHILE RING.
THOUGH I GUESS TRUMP IS THE ONE
GUY ON EARTH
WHO THINKS "YMCA"
IS A STRAIGHT ANTHEM.
ON A BASIC LEVEL, IT'S JUST SHOCKING
HOW MANY ALLEGED
PEDOPHILES TRUMP WAS FRIENDS
WITH.
EPSTEIN.
PRINCE ANDREW.
AND DIDDY.
I MEAN, THAT'S A LOT, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT YOUR OWN
FRIEND GROUP.
YOU KNOW?
HOW MANY PEDOPHILES DO YOU KNOW?
ONE, MAYBE TWO?
BUT TRUMP'S LIKE THE FORREST
GUMP OF MEETING FAMOUS
PEDOPHILES.
>>> THE BILL ENDING THE
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN WILL FUND
S.N.A.P. THROUGH NEXT SEPTEMBER,
AND THANK GOD, 'CAUSE I WAS THIS
CLOSE TO DONATING FOOD.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP --
PRESIDENT TRUMP ATTENDED A WASHINGTON
COMMANDERS GAME ON SUNDAY,
AND I
GUESS HE HASN'T BEEN TO ONE IN A
WHILE BECAUSE HE SHOWED UP IN
REDSKIN.
>>> IT WAS ALSO REPORTED THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP TOLD THE OWNERS
OF THE WASHINGTON COMMANDERS
THAT HE WANTS THEIR NEW STADIUM
TO BE NAMED IN HIS HONOR.
SO SAY HELLO TO THE DEMENTIA
DOME.
>>> IN A NEW INTERVIEW,
PRESIDENT TRUMP DENIED ONLINE RUMORS
THAT THE GOLD DECORATIONS
IN THE OVAL OFFICE CAME FROM
HOME DEPOT.
EVEN THOUGH HE HAS A WHOLE TEAM
OF GUYS TAKING STUFF FROM HOME
DEPOT ALL THE TIME.
THIS IS MY FAVORITE EPISODE.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
THREATENING TO SUE THE BBC FOR $5 BILLION
FOR A DOCUMENTARY
THAT EDITED OUT THE PART OF HIS
JANUARY 6th SPEECH
WHERE HE
CALLED FOR PROTESTERS TO BE
PEACEFUL.
AND TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT,
HERE IS THE FULL, UNEDITED,
COMPLETELY ACCURATE CLIP OF WHAT
TRUMP SAID ON THAT DAY.
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS, I WENT DOWN
ON BILL CLINTON.
>> YEAH, EVERYONE WANTS TO SEE
IT.
>>> ASTRONAUTS ON THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION ARE
TESTING A NEW PROCESS
THAT MAKES
FOOD USING THEIR OWN URINE.
THEY'RE ALSO TESTING A NEW
DESSERT CALLED,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S NOT BROWNIE.
>>> NETFLIX IS PRODUCING A
SEQUEL TO THE 1990s "COSBY SHOW" SPINOFF
"A DIFFERENT WORLD"
ABOUT STUDENTS AT AN HSBU --
WHICH STANDS FOR, HELP, BILL
COSBY IS UNDRESSING!
>>> A SHERIFF'S OFFICER IN
INDIANA WENT INTO AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
TO JOKINGLY HAND OUT
TICKETS TO STUDENTS USING THE
PHRASE "SIX SEVEN."
EVERYONE HAD A GOOD LAUGH,
THEN HE PULLED OUT HIS GUN AND SAID,
NOW TELL ME WHAT IT MEANS.
>>> THE U.S. MINT THIS WEEK
STOPPED PRODUCING NEW PENNIES.
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
I HAD ANOTHER ONE.
IT WAS,
THE U.S. MINT THIS WEEK
STOPPED PRODUCING NEW PENNIES.
ONE LAST SEVERE BLOW TO
LINCOLN'S HEAD.
SO I'LL DO THE FIRST ONE, I'LL
DO THE FIRST ONE.
>>> MAXWELL HOUSE COFFEE
TEMPORARILY CHANGED ITS NAME TO
MAXWELL APARTMENTS
TO BETTER
REFLECT CURRENT TIMES.
THOUGH IT'S MUCH BETTER THAN THE
FIRST CHOICE, GHISLAINE MAXWELL
HOUSE.
SO EARLY.
>>> FINALLY, A NEW DOCUMENTARY
THAT ANALYZED ADOLF HITLER'S DNA
SHOWED HE SUFFERED FROM A
DISEASE WHICH LEADS TO LOW
TESTOSTERONE LEVELS,
UNDESCENDED
TESTICLES, AND A MICROPENIS.
TRAITS INHERITED BY HIS SECRET
GRANDSON.
>> FOR "WEEKEND UPDATE," I'M
MICHAEL CHE!
STILL
EX-HUSBAND FROM THE AIRPORT.
KIND OF AWKWARD SAUCE.
>> HONEY, MY DAUGHTER WAS
KIDNAPPED BY SEX TRAFFICKERS IN
PARIS.
AND THEN MY EX-HUSBAND FLEW
THERE, KILLED THEM ALL, AND GOT
HER BACK.
THE LEAST I COULD DO IS PICK HIM
UP FROM THE AIRPORT, OKAY?
OH, MY GOD, THERE THEY ARE.
>> MOM!
>> KIM!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, THANKS TO DAD.
>> BRIAN.
>> LENORE.
>> WHAT YOU DID -- IT WAS SO
BRAVE.
>> ANY MAN WOULD DO IT FOR HIS
FAMILY.
>> I WAS GONNA GO.
>> WHAT'S THAT, DENNIS?
>> I WAS GOING TO FLY TO PARIS
AND KILL THE TRAFFICKERS MYSELF,
BUT I COULDN'T, BECAUSE I NEVER
GOT MY REAL I.D.
>> DENNIS, DON'T BE RIDICULOUS,
YOU'D NEVER HAVE DONE THAT,
YOU'RE SCARED OF FLYING.
>> I WAS GOING TO TAKE A CRUISE
SHIP.
THE POINT IS, EITHER OF US COULD
HAVE DONE IT.
>> BRIAN.
I HAVE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
>> ANYTHING.
I'M AN OPEN BOOK.
>> HOW DID YOU HUNT DOWN THE
TRAFFICKERS?
>> WELL, LET'S JUST SAY I HAVE A
VERY PARTICULAR SET OF SKILLS.
>> NOT COMMUNICATION, THOUGH,
RIGHT?
REMEMBER, THAT WAS THE MAIN
REASON YOU TWO GOT DIVORCED?
>> DENNIS, THAT'S NOT THE MAIN
REASON ME AND BRIAN GOT
DIVORCED.
>> OH, RIGHT, YOU SAID THE
RELATIONSHIP WAS TOO PHYSICAL.
>> IT'S TRUE.
EVERY CONVERSATION
SEEMED TO END
UP WITH OUR CLOTHES ON THE
FLOOR.
>> WELL, I DON'T LEAVE CLOTHES
ON THE FLOOR.
I PUT THEM IN THE HAMPER.
>> OKAY.
SWEETHEART?
HOW ARE YOU HOLDING UP?
>> I'M OKAY.
A LITTLE COLD.
>> HERE, TAKE MY JACKET.
>> YEAH, YEAH, AND -- AND TAKE
MY SHIRT, TOO!
YOU CAN WRAP IT AROUND YOUR
HEAD, YOU KNOW, FOR WARMTH.
LIKE A DO RAG.
>> STOP!
>> THAT'S FINE.
DIDN'T WANT TO WEAR MY SHIRT
ANYWAY.
NOT WITH GUMS LIKE THIS.
>> OOPS!
SILENT BUT DEADLY.
>> IT WASN'T SILENT.
>> WELL, IT DIDN'T SMELL.
>> IT VERY MUCH DID.
>> MOM, I'M REALLY HUNGRY.
>> OKAY, COME ON, SWEETHEART,
LET'S GET YOU A SNACK.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO STARBY'S,
CAN YOU GET ME ANOTHER BEAR CUP?
>> YOU ALREADY HAVE ONE.
>> HE NEEDS A FRIEND!
CHICKS, HUH?
SO, YOU KILLED A LOT OF PEOPLE,
HUH?
MUST BE SCARY.
PRETTY MAJOR SIN.
>> MAYBE IT IS, DENNIS.
BUT I WOULD GO TO HELL FOR MY
LITTLE GIRL.
>> OUR LITTLE GIRL.
EASY MISTAKE TO MAKE.
YOU MIGHT HAVE RAISED HER, BUT
SHE DRIVES ME TO WORK.
GOT TO GET THAT REAL I.D.
>> WELL, WE SHOULD PROBABLY GET
GOING.
BRIAN.
I'M FOREVER IN YOUR DEBT.
>> AND YOU'RE FOREVER IN MY
HEART.
YOU KNOW, BEING IN PARIS MADE ME
THINK OF OUR HONEYMOON.
>> WE DIDN'T GET TO SEE MUCH OF
THE CITY, DID WE?
SPENT MOST OF IT IN THE HOTEL
ROOM.
>> JET LAG IS SUCH A BITCH.
>> PERHAPS WE COULD GO BACK
SOMEDAY.
MAYBE SEE THE LOUVRE.
>> OR MAKE "LOUVRE."
>> DON'T "LOUVRE" THAT.
>> KIM, YOU FORGOT YOUR BAG.
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S ONE OF THE
TRAFFICKERS!
COME HERE!
>> NO, NO!
>> DENNIS, WHAT THE HELL?
THAT'S MY BOYFRIEND.
>> YEAH, YOU IDIOT.
DID YOU THINK I WAS A TRAFFICKER
BECAUSE I'M NOT WHITE?
>> DENNIS, WHAT'S WRONG WITH
YOU?
>> WOW.
GUESS I REALLY MESSED UP, HUH?
I GUESS THE IMPORTANT THING IS,
I TRIED TO BE BRAVE.
AND IN THE END, THAT'S WHAT YOU
LOVE ABOUT ME, ISN'T IT, LENORE?
>> OH BOY, LOOKS LIKE MY WIFE'S
THE ONE WHO'S TAKEN.
NOW THAT'S AWKWARD SAUCE.
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ HE'S FINDING OUT THAT HONESTY
IS NOT HIS BEST POLICY ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ HIS FRIENDS ARE REAL
SUSPICIOUS BECAUSE HE'S BEING
QUITE EVASIVE ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ THE LIST IS OUT THERE
MacGRUBER ¶
>> MacGRUBER, THE DOOR IS
PRESSURE BOLTED SHUT.
>> LOOK AT THE PLASMA BOMB,
WE'VE ONLY GOT 42 SECONDS!
>> DON'T WORRY, GANG, WE GOT
THIS.
LOOK, I KNOW WE'RE ALL STILL
SMARTING THAT WE LOST THAT
EPSTEIN LIST.
>> GOT ANOTHER COPYRIGHT HERE,
GRUBES.
>> WHAT?
>> LIKE YOU TAUGHT ME, ALWAYS
MAKE A BACKUP.
>> GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
GOOD BOY.
>> MacGRUBER, 30 SECONDS!
>> OKAY, CONNIE, PASS ME THAT
MARKER.
>> YOU GOT IT, MacGRUBER.
>> COLTON, TOSS ME THAT RADICAL
LEFT-WING LIST.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO SHRED IT
AGAIN?
>> GIVE ME THE LIST OR I WILL
FURLOUGH YOU!
I WILL FURLOUGH YOU SO FRIGGING
HARD, YOU WON'T KNOW WHERE THE
FUR STARTS AND THE LOUGH ENDS!
>> FINE, JESUS.
>> MacGRUBER, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> MAKING A FEW REDACTIONS.
>> OKAY, WE SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING
HERE.
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY ON THE LIST.
>> ME ON THE LIST?
OH, THAT'S RICH.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT 'CAUSE
YOU'RE ON THE LIST, WHAT?
>> WHAT?
>> AH, ME.
>> YOU CAN'T JUST WRITE OUR
NAMES ON A DON'T WANT.
>> 30 SECONDS!
>> LOOK, I GET IT.
IF I WAS ON THIS LIST, AND
THERE'S NO WAY TO PROVE THAT I
AM, I'D BE FREAKING OUT TOO.
BUT YOU ARE NOT MONSTERS.
SO HEY, WHY DON'T WE JUST FORGET
ABOUT THIS LIST, HUH?
IT'S JUST A DISTRACTION, SO WHAT
DO YOU SAY?
GOOD-BYE AND GOOD RIDDANCE.
>> 30 SECONDS!
>> TO NEW BEGINNINGS, HUH?
FAULTY TIMER.
I GOT THIS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
MacGRUBER?
>> GIVING YOU AND TOMMY MILLER A
FRESH START.
>> WE'RE NOT ON THE LIST!
>> YEAH, NEITHER AM I, WINK.
I'M NOT GOOD AT WINKING.
>> MacGRUBER, THAT'S NOT THE
ONLY COPY OF THE LIST.
>> WHAT NOW?
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ THOUGHT I WAS DONE
WITH THIS FEELING
I REALLY THOUGHT
YOU COULD BE HIM ¶
¶ THOUGHT I WAS SAFE
HMM ¶
¶ YOU WERE THE WARMTH
THAT I NEEDED
A BREEZE IN THE EVENING ¶
¶ AND THEN YOU CHANGED
YOU'RE ALL THE SAME
YEAH ¶
¶ IT'S TOO MUCH TO MEND
YOU'RE THE HUG
THAT HAD TO END ¶
¶ THOUGH I'VE TRIED
TO HOLD ON ¶
¶ AND IF YOU KNEW ME AT ALL
YOU WOULDN'T TRY
TO KEEP ME SMALL ¶
¶ MM WHO WOULD DO THAT
TO A FRIEND
LET ALONE THE ONE YOU LOVE ¶
¶ AND ANY CHOICE YOU HAD
WORTH MAKING
I'D PUSH YOU TO TAKE IT ¶
¶ NO QUESTIONS ASKED
NO DOUBT IN MIND ¶
¶ BUT WHEN THEY'RE MINE YEAH
YOU REACT LIKE
I'M CROSSING A LINE ¶
¶ I'M TOO MUCH TO HANDLE
AND JUST DIAL IT BACK
A BIT ¶
¶ WELL
WELL I'M NOT HAVING IT
BABE ¶
¶ IT'S TOO MUCH TO MEND
YOU'RE THE HUG
THAT HAD TO END ¶
¶ THOUGH I'VE TRIED
TO HOLD ON ¶
¶ AND IF YOU KNEW ME AT ALL
YOU WOULDN'T TRY
TO KEEP ME SMALL ¶
¶ MM WHO WOULD DO THAT
TO A FRIEND
LET ALONE THE ONE YOU LOVE ¶
¶ MM-MM-MM
MM-MM-MM
MM-MM-MM ¶
¶ MM
MM-MM
MM-MM-MM ¶
FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
>> I KNOW.
A PROPER FRIENDSGIVING.
>> WAIT, IS MELISSA NOT COMING?
>> OH, NO, SHE SAID SHE'D BE A
LITTLE LATE.
SHE'S GETTING HER HAIR DONE.
>> OKAY, FANCY.
>> I KNOW, I GUESS THIS
SUPER-FAMOUS HAIRDRESSER OR
SOMETHING?
SHE HAD TO GET ON SOME KIND OF
LIST.
>> I WISH I HAD MONEY TO DO FUN
STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> HI!
>> OH, NO, NO.
>> HELLO!
>> YOU'RE -- YOU'RE JUST IN
TIME.
WE HAVEN'T ORDERED YET.
>> GREAT!
>> GREAT.
>> I'M HUNGRY.
OH, STEAK.
I GOT MY HAIR DONE.
>> OH!
>> YOU DID?
>> I DID, I DID, YES.
AND I LIKE IT.
I LIKE IT.
>> YEAH.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
JEAN VON CLARK, HAIRDRESSER.
HE DOES EVERYBODY.
CELEBRITIES, POP STARS.
KIND OF A BIG DEAL.
>> WELL, YOU MAKE IT LOOK
CLASSIC.
>> THANK YOU, PETER.
YEAH, HE SAID NOT A LOT OF
PEOPLE COULD PULL THIS OFF.
BUT I CAN!
I CAN.
>> OH!
>> DON'T CRY.
>> I'M JUST -- OH -- I JUST FEEL
SO LUCKY.
I'M SO LUCKY.
FINALLY, ME.
>> HEY, Y'ALL, CAN I GET Y'ALL
STARTED WITH --
>> I HATE IT!
>> I'M SO SORRY.
I WILL GO GET YOU A DIFFERENT
SERVER.
>> WELL, MELISSA, I REALLY LIKE
IT.
>> ME TOO.
ME TOO.
YEAH.
WRITE THIS DOWN.
JEAN VON AT SALON PAWN, HE IS
JUST THE BEST.
>> AND, JUST CURIOUS, WHAT DID
YOU TELL HIM YOU WANTED?
>> A TRIM.
A TRIM.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE MUSIC WAS SO DANG LOUD IN
THOSE PLACES.
OH, MY GOSH.
DANGEROUSLY LOUD HE HAD IT.
SO I JUST DON'T THINK HE HEARD
ME.
AND THANK GOD.
BECAUSE I LIKE IT.
>> AND YOU SAID HE DOES
CELEBRITIES?
>> OH, YEAH, BABE.
OH, YEAH.
HE'S THE REAL DEAL.
I MEAN, GOSH.
HE DOES -- WHO'S HE DO?
GREG THE BEAST.
WAXMAN.
AND THE MICKEY MOUSE KILLERS.
>> WHO ARE THE MICKEY MOUSE
KILLERS?
>> OH, YOU GOT TO LISTEN TO
THEM.
JEAN VON PUT ME ON TO THEM.
LET'S JUST SAY, YOU SEE FOUR
GUYS WITH THIS HAIRCUT SINGING
ABOUT KILLING KIDS?
YOU'RE AT ONE OF THEIR CONCERTS.
WHERE IS THE DANG SERVER?
>> OH GOD!
>> OH NO!
>> YES.
THE SKIN SQUARE.
THAT'S HIS OWN PERSONAL
SIGNATURE, YOU KNOW.
>> MELISSA, ISN'T YOUR SISTER'S
WEDDING THIS WEEKEND?
>> TOMORROW.
YES, I'M THE MAID OF HONOR.
SO IT WILL BE FUN, LOTS OF
PICTURES AND MY EX WILL BE
THERE.
SHOW HIM WHAT HE'S MISSING!
>> OH!
>> SO EXCITED, I'M SO EXCITED.
>> I FEEL I SPEAK FOR ALL OF US
WHEN I SAY, IT LOOKS AWESOME AND
WE LOVE IT.
>> WHAT DO YOU LOVE ABOUT IT?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> ALL OF IT.
>> WHAT SPECIFICALLY?
>> EASIER TO WASH.
>> IT IS!
YES, IT IS.
ACTUALLY, FUNNY THING IS I DON'T
EVEN HAVE TO SHOWER ANYMORE,
BECAUSE WHATEVER CHEMICAL HE
USED IN THE HAIR, NOT ALLOWED TO
TOUCH WATER.
'CAUSE IT CAUSES -- OH, IT'S NOT
BRAIN DAMAGE -- WHAT IS IT?
PASSING.
PASS AWAY.
YOU PASS AWAY.
>> WHERE'S THE WAITER?
>> ALL RIGHT, HELLO, EVERYONE.
I'LL BE TAKING OVER YOUR TABLE.
CAN I GET YOU -- YOUR HAIR.
IS IT JEAN VON?
>> HOW DID YOU --
>> WE LIKE IT!
MacGRUBER'S ON THE EPSTEIN
LIST ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ HE'S BEEN DOING LOTS OF
THINKING ABOUT WHERE HIS LIFE IS
TAKING HIM ¶
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
¶ ONLY GOD CAN JUDGE HIM
MacGRUBER ¶
>> MacGRUBER, WE'RE WELDED IN
AGAIN AND WE ONLY HAVE 30
SECONDS.
>> GUYS, BEFORE I DEFUSE THIS
BOMB, THERE'S SOMETHING YOU NEED
TO KNOW.
>> YOU'RE ON THE EPSTEIN LIST.
>> ALL OVER IT, LIKE EVERY THIRD
PAGE I'M NOT ON.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YEAH, AND SO ARE YOU.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
>> LOOK, I WORKED ON THE GROUND
CREW SERVICING THE AIRCRAFT.
I KNEW NOTHING ABOUT WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
BUT I SAW A LOT OF VERY
IMPORTANT PEOPLE GETTING ON THAT
PLANE.
I SOLD THEM A LOT OF LOW-GRADE
COCAINE AND CRYSTAL.
NOW I REALIZE I HAVE NOTHING TO
FEAR 'CAUSE I'VE DONE NOTHING
WRONG.
EXCEPT DILUTING THE COCAINE WITH
PLAYGROUND SAND.
THE ONLY PEOPLE WHO DON'T WANT
THAT LIST OUT ARE THE PEOPLE WHO
HAVE DONE SOMETHING WRONG.
I WROTE A SONG ABOUT IT, WOULD
YOU LIKE TO HEAR IT?
>> 15 SECONDS, MacGRUBER!
>> TO THE TUNE OF "AMAZING
GREAT."
DO YOU DO BEATBOX?
>> NO.
I'LL SET MYSELF UP.
¶ BURY THE LIST
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
>> OKAY, WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO
TESTIFY ABOUT EVERYTHING YOU
SAW?
>> I'LL DO ANYTHING TO GET THE
TRUTH OUT THERE.
>> THAT'S SO BRAVE.
FIVE SECONDS.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE THERE ARE A LOT
OF VERY POWERFUL PEOPLE WHO
WOULD DO JUST ABOUT ANYTHING TO
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT, OFFER YOU
MONEY, PARDONS.
>> WAIT, BACK UP A LITTLE BIT.
MONEY AND PARDONS YOU'RE SAYING?
>> WILL YOU TELL ME WHO YOU SAW?
>> I SAW -- IT'S TIME!
¶ MacGRUBER ¶
AMAZING CAST.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, MITCH, THE
U.P.S. DRIVER!
FANTASTIC, ONE OF THE BEST
NIGHTS OF MY WHOLE LIFE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD NIGHT!