>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THIS
IS SABRINA CARPENTER.
>> THIS IS THE ONE AND ONLY PAUL
SIMON.
>> I SANG THIS SONG WITH GEORGE HARRISON
ON "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE" IN 1976.
>> I WAS NOT BORN THEN,
AND NEITHER WERE MY PARENTS.
>> I'M GLAD THEY'RE GETTING A
CHANCE TO HEAR IT TONIGHT.
STATION,
TICKET FOR MY DESTINATION ¶
¶ ON A TOUR OF
ONE-NIGHT STANDS
MY SUITCASE AND
GUITAR IN HAND ¶
¶ AND EVERY STOP
IS NEATLY PLANNED
FOR A POET AND
A ONE-MAN BAND ¶
¶ HOMEWARD BOUND
I WISH I WAS
HOMEWARD BOUND ¶
¶ HOME, WHERE MY
THOUGHT'S ESCAPING
HOME, WHERE MY
MUSIC'S PLAYING ¶
¶ HOME, WHERE MY
LOVE LIES WAITING
SILENTLY FOR ME ¶
¶ EVERY DAY'S
AN ENDLESS STREAM
AIRPORT LOUNGES AND MAGAZINES ¶
¶ AND EACH TOWN
LOOKS THE SAME TO ME
THE MOVIES AND
THE FACTORIES ¶
¶ AND EVERY STRANGER'S
FACE I SEE
REMIND ME THAT ¶
¶ I LONG TO BE
HOMEWARD BOUND ¶
¶ I WISH I WAS
¶ HOME, WHERE MY
THOUGHT'S ESCAPING
HOME, WHERE MY
MUSIC'S PLAYING ¶
¶ HOME, WHERE MY
LOVE LIES WAITING
SILENTLY FOR ME ¶
TONIGHT
MY SONGS AGAIN
I'LL PLAY THE GAME
AND PRETEND ¶
¶ BUT ALL MY WORDS COME BACK TO ME
IN SHADES OF MEDIOCRITY ¶
¶ LIKE EMPTINESS AND HARMONY,
I NEED SOMEONE TO COMFORT ME ¶
HOMEWARD BOUND ¶
¶ I WISH I WAS HOMEWARD BOUND
HOME, WHERE MY
THOUGHT'S ESCAPING ¶
¶ HOME, WHERE MY
MUSIC'S PLAYING
HOME, WHERE MY LOVE
LIES WAITING ¶
¶ SILENTLY FOR ME
LIVE
LIVE" 50th ANNIVERSARY SPECIAL,
WITH MUSICAL GUESTS PAUL SIMON
AND SABRINA CARPENTER!
MILEY CYRUS AND BRITTANY HOWARD,
LIL WAYNE AND THE ROOTS,
>> AND PAUL McCARTNEY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, STEVE
MARTIN!
>>> GOOD EVENING,
AND WELCOME TO THE 50th ANNIVERSARY OF
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
I'M STEVE MARTIN, "SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE'S" NEWEST DIVERSITY
HIRE.
WHAT A THRILL IT IS TO BE HERE.
WHEN I HEARD "SNL" WANTED TO DO
AN ANNIVERSARY SPECIAL,
I LITERALLY WANTED
TO LEAP IN THE AIR.
AND THE ONLY REASON I DIDN'T IS
BECAUSE AT THE TIME,
I WAS
WEARING A SHORT SKIRT WITH NO
UNDERWEAR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MADE IT HERE IN TIME.
IT WAS ONLY A FEW DAYS AGO THAT
LORNE TOLD ME I WAS DOING THE MONOLOGUE,
AND I WAS ACTUALLY
VACATIONING ON A FRIEND'S BOAT
DOWN IN THE GULF OF STEVE
MARTIN.
BUT FINALLY,
IT TOOK ME A WHILE
TO GET HERE, BUT I DID.
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE, AS YOU
KNOW, TURNED 50 YEARS OLD THIS YEAR,
AND I TURNED 79.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M 65,
WHICH IS ALSO NOT GOOD.
NOW SERIOUSLY, I DO NOT MIND
GETTING OLDER.
DO YOU THINK THESE HEARING AIDS
MAKE MY ASS LOOK SMALLER?
I DO.
I'M STILL LEARNING ABOUT LIFE.
ACTUALLY, MY WIFE, WHO IS A VERY
SMART, WISE PERSON,
TAUGHT ME
SOMETHING THE OTHER DAY.
SHE SAT ME DOWN, AND SHE SAID,
"STEVE, YOU KNOW, BABIES DON'T"
GET SARCASM."
AND I REALIZED I'D BEEN WASTING
MY TIME GOING UP TO STROLLERS IN THE STREET
SAYING, "OH, WHAT A
CUTE BABY!"
NOW, A FUN FACT.
A PERSON BORN DURING FIRST
SEASON OF "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"
COULD TODAY BE EASILY DEAD OF
NATURAL CAUSES.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO SEE A LOT OF
FAMILIAR THINGS TONIGHT.
MUSICAL GUESTS, SKETCHES, CAMEO
APPEARANCES, THE NEWS.
AND THIS IS THE MONOLOGUE.
TRADITIONALLY, THE WEAKEST PART
OF THE SHOW.
YES, THE MONOLOGUE IS LIKE A
RENT-CONTROLLED TENANT.
IT'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE, EVEN
THOUGH IT STINKS.
AND THERE ARE SO MANY MEMBERS OF
THE "SNL" FAMILY HERE TONIGHT.
THE GREAT BILL MURRAY IS HERE.
WE WANTED TO MAKE SURE BILL
WOULD BE HERE TONIGHT
SO WE
DIDN'T INVITE HIM.
AND DAVID LETTERMAN IS HERE.
DAVE, THANKS FOR LEAVING THE
SHEEP AT HOME.
AND WE CAN'T FORGET THE WRITERS
WHO HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
THE HEART
AND SOUL OF "SNL."
IN FACT, LET'S PLEASE HAVE THE
GREAT WRITERS
FROM THE PAST 50
YEARS STAND UP AND TAKE A BOW.
BY THE WAY, THAT TRIBUTE TO THE WRITERS
WAS WRITTEN BY AI.
OH MY GOD!
JOHN MULANEY!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE GOING TO
BE HERE.
>> YOU WOULD IF YOU'D EVER COME
TO REHEARSAL.
BY THE WAY, CONGRATULATIONS ON
YOUR EMMY WIN.
>> NOPE.
>> EMMY NOMINATION.
GRAMMY WIN?
>> NOPE.
>> GRAMMY NOMINATION.
>> GOLDEN GLOBE WIN?
>> NOPE.
>> GOLDEN GLOBE NOMINATION?
>> YES, SIR, AND THANK YOU.
>> YOU KNOW, WE WRITERS REALLY
APPRECIATED THAT TRIBUTE,
BUT I
BELIEVE THE HEART AND SOUL OF
THIS SHOW
IS THE CELEBRITY
HOSTS.
MANY OF WHOM ARE IN THIS ROOM
TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, AS I LOOK AROUND, I
SEE SOME OF THE MOST DIFFICULT PEOPLE
I HAVE EVER MET IN MY
ENTIRE LIFE.
OVER THE COURSE OF 50 YEARS, 894
PEOPLE HAVE HOSTED "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE,"
AND IT AMAZES ME
THAT ONLY TWO OF THEM HAVE
COMMITTED MURDER.
EACH WEEK, EACH WEEK A NEW
CELEBRITY HOST COMES IN WITH
THEIR OWN DYNAMIC
AND THEY THROW
EVERYTHING OFF.
BUT NOT YOU, STEVE,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE NO DYNAMIC.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH MY GOD!
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THE
ONLY CANADIAN WHO WASN'T IN
SCHITT'S CREEK,
MARTIN SHORT.
>> WAIT A SECOND, I THOUGHT WE
WERE HOSTING TOGETHER.
>> DO YOU HAVE YOUR PASSPORT
WITH YOU?
>> NO.
>> I.C.E., GET HIM!
>> NO!
I'LL COOPERATE!
DON'T TAKE ME.
I'LL NAME NAMES.
MIKE MYERS, JIM CARREY!
CATHERINE
DAMN YOU, YOU WHITE-HAIRED SON
OF A BITCH!
>> MARTY AND I HAVE BEEN WORKING
TOGETHER SO LONG
THAT WE CAN
ACTUALLY FINISH EACH OTHER'S
CAREERS.
I HOPE YOU ARE ENJOYING MY
MONOLOGUE TONIGHT.
BUT IF YOU AREN'T ENJOYING IT --
MAYBE YOU SHOULD GET UP AND TAKE
A GOOD LOOK AT YOURSELF IN THE MIRROR
AND SAY TO YOURSELF, WHAT
HAVE I BECOME?
THIS CAN'T BE STEVE'S FAULT.
AND ASK YOURSELVES,
WHEN DID I ABANDON JOY?
AND WHAT CAN I BRING TO THE
MONOLOGUE
AS AN AUDIENCE MEMBER
NEXT TIME.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE GOT A GREAT
SHOW TONIGHT.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW.
PAUL SIMON WAS HERE, SABRINA
CARPENTER WAS HERE,
BILL MURRAY
WAS HERE, DAVID LETTERMAN WAS
HERE, JOHN MULANEY WAS HERE, MARTIN SHORT,
IT'S CALLED
FRONT-LOADING.
AND WE'LL BE BACK.
THANK YOU.
>>> THIS IS PBS.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
WHAT A WONDERFUL EVENING FILLED
WITH SO MUCH WHIMSY AND WONDER.
AND PLEASE GIVE ANOTHER BIG HAND
TO FLORIAN TRUNT, OUR BODY
CONTORTIONIST.
>> I AM STUCK.
>> IS IT ME OR DID HIS MOUTH GET
DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO HIS FANNY
CHEEKS?
ANY WAY, OUR NEXT ACT IS NO
STRANGER TO THE STAGE,
ALL THE
WAY FROM THE FINGER LAKES, IT'S
SISTERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT THE
FINGER LAKES.
FIRST YOU MIGHT ONE FINGER,
BUT SOON YOU'LL BE ASKING FOR ALL
FIVE.
PARDON
TONIGHT A SPECIAL GUEST,
HE IS
THE HANDSOME YOUNG DARK-HAIRED
ALCOHOLIC
EVERYONE HAS BEEN
TALKING ABOUT, IT'S ROBERT
GOULET.
¶ ROBERT GOULET.
>> HI, EVERYONE, IT'S ME, ROBERT
GOULET.
YOU LIKE MY MOTOR HORSEYS?
JUST ROLLED IN FROM A RALLY IN
STURGIS, SOUTH DAKOTA.
100 MILES PER HOUR, NO BATHROOM
BREAKS, NO TIME TO STOP.
YOU KNOW THE REST.
NOW LET'S GET TO THOSE GOLDEN
GOULET PIPES.
¶ NEED SOME WARM AND COMPANY TO
GET ME THROUGH THE DAY ¶
¶ IT'S BEEN SO LONG JUST ME AND
ME, NO WOMAN JUST GOULET ¶
¶ IF I DON'T SEE A WOMAN SOON,
NO TELLING WHAT I'LL DO ¶
¶ SO GOT TO DELIVER
A WOMAN OR THREE OR TWO
OH MY GOD
DID THEY PUT LSD IN MY CAESAR SALAD OR
DO I SEE THREE
BEAUTIFUL LADIES HITCHHIKING MY
WAY.
>> HI, TRAVELER!
BYE
¶ WE WANT A RIDE ¶
¶ WE'D LOVE TO IT IS RIGHT BY
YOUR SIDE ¶
¶ AND THEN WE HOPE YOU WILL DECIDE,
WHICH ONE OF US WILL BE YOUR
BRIDE ¶
>> WHOA, VOLUME!
PUT THAT IN MY BREATH.
AND DID YOU SAY "BRIDE"?
BY A GUY.
CAESAR SALAD FIRST.
CALLBACK.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOUR NAMES.
>> WELL, THAT'S EASY.
>> I'M JANET.
>> OH, JANET.
>> I'M HOLLY.
>> LIKE THE BUSH.
>> I'M MARGARET.
>> YOU SURE ARE GREAT.
>> AND I'M DOONEESE.
>> FOREHEAD!
SORRY, SORRY.
I MEANT TO SAY FOREHEAD.
NOPE, DID IT AGAIN.
ONE MORE TIME.
FOREHEAD.
JUST SING.
¶ SISTERS CUTE AS CUTE CAN BE,
SOON YOU'LL FALL FOR ONE OF US
THREE ¶
¶ WE KEEP FORGETTING MOM HAD
FOUR ¶
¶ I CAME OUT OF A DIFFERENT
HOLE ¶
>> IF YOUR TRYING TO DO THE MATH ON THAT ONE,
WHEN YOU
THINK OF THE HOLE IT SHOULD BE,
IT'S THE ONE BEHIND THAT.
OKAY, GOODBYE.
¶ MEN GET LONELY ON A LONG COLD
NIGHT ¶
¶ YOU CAN COUNT ON US TO HOLD
YOU TIGHT.
¶ YOUR GIRLFRIEND ¶
>> I'LL BE LOVER ¶
¶ I'LL BE YOUR SWEETHEART ¶
¶ I'LL BE JUST LIKE THIS ¶
HERE
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU IN
PRIVATE.
>> NO, NO, NOT THOSE PRIVATES.
THERE IS NOTHING TO HEAR DOWN
THERE, BELIEVE ME.
JUST GO.
JESUS THE HECK.
LET'S WRAP THIS BASTARD UP.
I'LL SING.
¶ I DON'T KNOW HOW TO CHOOSE
NORMALLY I'M FULL OF BOOZE ¶
¶ JUST NOT SURE HOW I FEEL,
LET'S TRY TO SEAL THE DEAL ¶
¶ WITH A KISS ¶
>> OH, NOW WE'RE TALKING.
¶ WITH A SNUGGLE.
>> FINALLY, SOME COMFORT.
¶ WITH A TICKLE ¶
¶ YOU'LL FIND OUT ¶
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
THIRD
THAT REMINDS ME,
I NEED TO GET SOME ORAL SURGERY DONE SOON.
I GOT -- I DON'T HATE IT.
I DON'T HATE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING THIS,
BUT I THINK I LOVE YOU.
YES.
I LOVE YOU.
THERE IS NOTHING YOU COULD SAY
THAT WOULD CHANGE MY MIND.
¶ A BIRD IN MY MOUTH AND I WENT
TO THE MOVIES
AND I LAUGHED AT
THE MOVIES AND THE BIRD FLEW OUT,
BUT THE BIRD CHOKED ON
POPCORN AND I GAVE IT CPR,
AND
THE BIRD FLEW AWAY AND I CAUGHT
IT AND ATE IT RAW.
IS THAT BAD?
>> WOW, TO THINK I ALMOST PICKED
KIM KARDASHIAN.
>> ISN'T LOVE WONDERFUL?
AND BY WONDERFUL, I MEAN
VISUALLY UPSETTING.
AND THANKS ONCE AGAIN TO THREE
OF THE FOUR MAHARELLE SISTERS.
>> DENISE, I GOT A MOTORCYCLE
HELMET MADE FOR YOU.
>> TONIGHT'S SHOW BROUGHT TO YOU
BY STUFF TOER'S COMMUNITY
BREAKFAST,
SILENT
AND DR. WILSON.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> THIS IS BLACK JEOPARDY!
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT, WHAT UP?
WHAT UP, WHAT UP?
WELCOME TO BLACK JEOPARDY, THE
ONLY JEOPARDY WHERE EVERY SINGLE VIEWER
FULLY UNDERSTOOD
KENDRICK'S HALFTIME PERFORMANCE.
I'M YOUR HOST, DARNELL HAYES.
TODAY'S CONTESTANTS IS SHALICE.
>> HI!
>> DARIUS, COME ON, NOW.
>> OH, AND LOOK AT THIS, TRACY MORGAN,
BIG DOG'S GOING TO MAKE
THE BIG MONEY.
>> NOW WAIT A MINUTE, TRACY,
DON'T YOU ALREADY HAVE A LOT OF
MONEY?
YOU GOT TO HAVE A LOT OF MONEY
IF YOU LIVE LIKE I LIVE.
I EAT FOUR-CHEESE LASAGNA.
IF THEY ONLY GOT THREE CHEESES,
I AIN'T EATING IT.
>> OKAY.
WE HEAR YOU, TRACY MORGAN.
>> I REFUSE TO INGEST THREE
CHEESES.
>> YOU'RE AT FOUR CHEESES.
WE GOT TRACY MORGAN.
THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT OUR
CATEGORIES.
WE'VE GOT LOOK HERE,
THIS JOKER TALKING ABOUT,
LEAVE BRONNY ALONE,
MAN,
LIVE FROM NEW YORK,
AND AS ALWAYS, WHITE PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT.
SHALICE, YOU'RE OUR RETURNING
CHAMPION, SO YOU PICK.
>> LET'S GO WITH LOOK HERE FOR
HONEY.
>> OKAY.
YOUR 11-YEAR-OLD IS ASKING FOR
SOMETHING WHILE YOU'RE ON THE
PHONE.
- SHANICE
>> WHAT IS LOOK HERE!
>> YOU THIS CLOSE.
>> THIS CLOSE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT IS RIGHT.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
>> GET A LITTLE CLOSE TO SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> EXACTLY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
PICK AGAIN.
>> LET'S GO WITH MAAANNN FOR
300.
>> ANSWER THERE,
THERE IS 30 SOME PEOPLE AT THE PARK WEARING
THE SAME RED T-SHIRT.
DARIUS?
>> WHAT IS MAN, THAT'S JUST THE
JACKSON FAMILY REUNION.
THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> GOT A PICTURE OF A TREE OR
SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> SPEAKING OF FAMILY,
DARIUS, TRACY, Y'ALL SEEM LIKE YOU MIGHT
BE RELATED.
>> WELL, JAMES EARL JONES IS MY
BIOLOGICAL FATHER.
JAMES EARL JONES IMPREGNATED MY
MOTHER ON THE SAID OF
CLAUDINE
ON EDGECOMBE AVENUE IN HARLEM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE MIGHT BE RELATED.
>> I DON'T SEE IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST MOVE ON.
DARIUS, IT'S STILL YOUR PICK.
>> OKAY, LET'S GO WITH LIVE FROM
NEW YORK FOR HONEYS.
>> OKAY. THE ANSWER THERE,
THIS LEGENDARY LATE NIGHT SHOW
CREATED SOME OF
COMEDY'S BIGGEST STARS.
IT'S A SKIT COMEDY SHOW, BEEN ON
FOR A LONG TIME.
DARIUS?
>> WHAT IS "IN LIVING COLOR"?
>> NO, NO, I'M SORRY.
I THINK Y'ALL KNOW THIS, THOUGH.
AS KIDS, YOU PROBABLY STAYED UP
LATE ON SATURDAY TO WATCH.
TRACY?
>> WHAT IS "SHOWTIME AT THE
APOLLO."
>> FEATURING SANDMAN SIMMS.
>> NO.
>> COME ON, Y'ALL REALLY DON'T
KNOW?
>> HOSTED BY STEVE HARVEY?
>> AGAIN, NO.
>> LET ME HEAR YOU SAY YEAH.
>> THIS IS NOT THAT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> CHENICE?
>> OKAY.
OF COURSE, THIS SHOW HAS BEEN ON
EVERY SATURDAY FOR YEARS,
RIGHT, DARNELL?
>> YES.
>> AND IT'S GOT A HOST AND A
MUSICAL GUEST, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
CAN I SAY THE FAMOUS CATCHPHRASE
THAT OPENS THE SHOW?
>> GO AHEAD.
>> IT'S SOUL TRAIN!
>> NO!
>> NOW, Y'ALL KNOW THE ANSWER IS
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE.
>> WHAT IS "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE"?
>> COME ON, DARIUS, I JUST GAVE
YOU THE ANSWER.
>> NO, I'M ASKING.
WHAT IS "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"?
I DON'T KNOW THAT.
>> IT'S "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
IT'S A SKIT COMEDY SHOW.
IT'S BEEN ON FOR 50 YEARS.
>> WHAT DAY DO THEY TAPE ON?
>> SATURDAY.
IT'S IN THE NAME.
NOW TRACY, YOU WERE ON IT WITH
TINA FEY.
>> WHAT IS "30 ROCK"!
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I TELL YOU WHAT, LET'S JUST HEAR
ABOUT TODAY'S PRIZES.
DONNY?
>> THANKS, DARNELL.
TODAY'S BLACK JEOPARDY IS
SPONSORED BY A PLATE.
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY FIX ME
A PLATE.
YOU ALREADY GOT ONE.
WITH A PLATE
AND BY A TIN OF DANISH BUTTER
COOKIES OR A SOWING KIT.
WHICH ONE IS IT?
YOU'LL HAVE TO OPEN TO FIND OUT.
AND BY WHO ALL GOING TO BE
THERE.
THE EVEN INVITATION FOR ALL YOUR
EVENTS, BARBECUES OR MEETING AT
THE SPOT.
BEFORE YOU PULL UP, ALWAYS GOING TO
BE THERE.
BACK TO YOU, DARNELL.
>> GOT TO KNOW WHO ALL GOING TO
BE THERE.
LET'S STICK WITH LIVE FROM NEW
YORK.
AND TO HELP, HERE IS A SPECIAL
GUEST CLUE
FROM MR. CHRIS ROCK.
>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, DARNELL.
IT'S AN HONOR TO BE HERE ON
BLACK JEOPARDY.
I'VE BEEN A FAN OF THE SHOW SINCE THE '70s
WHEN IT WAS
CALLED "MAMA'S GOT QUESTIONS."
OKAY.
NOW SOME OF Y'ALL MIGHT REMEMBER
ME FROM "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
I WAS A BLACK GUY WHO CAME AFTER
EDDIE MURPHY.
THAT'S KIND OF LIKE BEING A THE
POINT GUARD AFTER STEPHEN CURRY.
OKAY.
HERE IS YOUR CLUE ABOUT "SNL."
THIS WAS CHARACTER HAS MADE
PEOPLE LAUGH FOR YEARS.
>> WHO IS MY DEAR?
>> NO.
THAT IS NOT TYLER PERRY.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT SHE IS RIGHT?
DOUG
HI
>> NOW, COULD WIN SOME MONEY HERE
AND THE CHURCH LADY.
>> YES.
YES.
THAT IS CORRECT.
THANK YOU.
THAT IS THE CHURCH LADY,
$400
FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
SPEAKING OF CHURCH, CAN I SAY
SOMETHING?
IT'S MORE FOLKS WENT TO CHURCH,
WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS
WE'RE IN NOW.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SHAKE YOUR
HAND, SIR.
HERE WE GO.
NO
JUST
>> THANK YOU,
NOW MAYBE I'LL START A SHOW FOR YOU TO COME ON
AND WE'LL CALL IT "WHITE
JEOPARDY."
>> WE DON'T NEED IT.
WE DON'T NEED IT.
SLOW IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
WHEN WE RETURN TO "BLACK JEOPARDY,"
WE WILL SEE IF ANYONE
HAS WATCHED ANY OF THIS YEAR'S
OSCAR MOVIES.
DOUBT.
WE'LL SEE YOU.
HI
TONIGHT IS A CELEBRATION OF
CLASSIC MOMENTS,
BUT "SNL" WILL
ALWAYS HAVE THAT CONTRARIAN EDGE,
NEVER WANTING TO DO
ANYTHING THAT FEELS TOO OBVIOUS,
TOO ON THE NOSE.
UP HERE?
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT'S YOUR AGE AND YOUR NAME?
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MY NAME
IS SALLY O'MALLEY.
I'M PROUD TO SAY I'M 50 YEARS OLD,
JUST LIKE "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE."
LISTEN, EMMA, SHE IS NOT ONE
OF THE GALS WHO IS AFRAID TO TELL A REAL,
SHE LIKES TO KICK,
SHRED,
AND KICK.
OLD
SAME AGE
>> SO PLEASE ENJOY THIS VIDEO
CELEBRATING 50 YEARS OF PHYSICAL
COMEDY ON "SNL"
WHILE WE KICK,
STRETCH,
AND KICK!
PHYSICAL COMEDY
LORNE
>> THE WHOLE NOYFNT SKETCH IS TO
SHOW YOUR FALL.
PEOPLE EXPECT TO SEE YOU FALL.
IT'S A TRADITION.
NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I'M NOT DOING IT.
AND I'M GOING TO TELL YOU WHY.
>> WHY?
>> MARY KATHARINE.
>> I DO GYMNASTICS.
CONTROL
>> YOU'RE MAKING ME VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> NO I'M NOT.
>> YOU KIND OF ARE.
REBECCA
>> MIGHT NEED A WHOLE BOTTLE.
>> I COULD EAT A WHOLE BOTTLE
TOO.
>> JESUS CHRIST!
>> NOW I'VE DONE IT.
I PUT THE CHICKENS ON TO MY
FINGER.
I'M GLAD IN A WAY THIS HAPPENED.
EXPECT
>> I SING MY --
>> YOU'RE GOING TO SPOOK THE
HORSE.
>> DO BE CAREFUL.
>> NO ONE IS WHO THEY APPEAR TO
BE.
MY MOUTH.
BLOOD
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
APPARENTLY A LOT.
I'LL STOP BLEEDING IF YOU OPEN
YOUR MOUTH.
>> I'M GOING TO GO TO SLEEP NOW.
BON APPETIT.
>>> YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
>> DO YOU -- DO YOU NEED A
KLEENEX?
>> NO, I'VE GOT IT.
ANYWAY
>> WHEN OUR DAUGHTER KELSEY TOLD
US THAT SHE AND MATT WANTED TO
DO A VOWEL RENEWAL,
WE WERE A
LITTLE SURPRISED SINCE THEY'VE
ONLY BEEN MARRIED LESS THAN A YEAR,
BUT HEY,
WHAT'S ANOTHER 70
GRAND AT BEST WESTERN.
>> AND I JUST WANT TO SAY,
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU GUYS!
DRINKS FOR EVERYONE!
OPEN BAR.
>> I APOLOGIZE.
MY WIFE IS DOING WET FEBRUARY.
>> OH HELL YES I AM.
>> ANY WAY,
KELSEY AND MATT --
>> I WANT TO SAY, LET ME TAKE
THE RING.
>> SURE.
ANYTIME
MAY YOU HAVE A MARRIAGE AS
LOVING AND PASSIONATE AS DADDY
AND ME.
>> OH, BABY.
HOW ABOUT YOU.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> OKAY.
SPEECH
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T KNOW ME,
I'M SOPHIE, THE BRIDE'S
CHILDHOOD BESTIE.
I COULDN'T MAKE IT TO THE
WEDDING BECAUSE I WAS
UNFORTUNATELY IN PRISON.
>> YOU GOT SO SKINNY IN JAIL,
GIRL.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
I COULDN'T EAT THE FOOD.
ANY WAY,
I'D LOVE TO INVITE KELSEY'S BEST FRIENDS AKA, THE
KEL SQUAD.
HI
>> SO INSTEAD OF A SPEECH, WE'RE
GOING TO DO SOMETHING DIFFERENT FOR Y'ALL,
BECAUSE WE'RE A
LITTLE BIT BASIC, A LITTLE BIT
TOXIC.
>> SO AS SOME OF YOU KNOW, WE
TOOK KELSEY TO CITY TO CELEBRATE
RENEWAL.
>> MATT SAID IT HAD TO BE A DAY
TRIP BECAUSE HE DOESN'T TRUST
OVERNIGHTS ANYMORE.
>> GUILTY AS CHARGED.
SERIOUSLY, I LOVE STRONG WOMEN.
>> WHILE IN NEW YORK, WE GOT
BLACKOUT DRUNK AND WENT TO
WICKED.
SO MATT AND KELSEY, THIS IS FOR
YOU.
HAS CHANGED
SHE'S READY TO COMMIT ¶
¶ SEES A THING IN MATTHEW
THAT HONESTLY WE DO NOT GET ¶
LADIES
¶ AND WORKED ON HERSELF,
AND MATT HAS GONE TO THE GYM ¶
KELSEY HAS MADE A COMMITMENT,
SO GUESS WHAT?
THIS JUST IN ¶
¶ SHE'S GOING TO TRY MONOGAMY,
SHE'S FINALLY LEARNED WHAT IS
MONOGAMY ¶
¶ AND WE WILL HOLD HER DAWN ¶
>> HEY, WELL, THAT WAS GREAT.
AND NOW THE SONG IS OVER, AND WE
WILL NOT LEARN ANYTHING ELSE.
>> REALLY?
BECAUSE A LOT MORE HAPPENED.
>> OH MY GOD, DOING TAYLOR.
¶ AFTER THE SHOW, IN TIMES SQUARE,
THERE IS A WHACK KIAN
KNOW REEVES, BUT KELSEY DOESN'T CARE
IT'S CLEAR THAT KELSEY'S
MIND IS ELSEWHERE ¶
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
>> MY FRIENDS ARE SINGING.
¶ NEXT UP WE TAKE A PEDICAB IN
CENTRAL PARK ¶
¶ KELSEY SAYS THERE IS A GIANT
HOLE IN MY HEART ¶
COIN
SHE WHISPERS I
COULD BE WITH HIM ¶
¶ WE ALL KNOW SHE IS TALKING
ABOUT DOMINGO,
EVEN
SHE THE MIDDLE OF
NEW YORK AND SHE SCREAMS TO THE
SKY ¶
¶ SHE IS LOOKING FOR THE LATIN
GUY ¶
¶ DOMINGO ¶
¶ TRY TO LIVE WITHOUT DOMINGO,
BABY ¶
¶ COME ON,
OPEN RELATIONSHIPS ¶
>> HI, DOMINGO.
>> HOW ARE THE KITCHEN
RENOVATION GOING?
>> WAIT, YOU GUYS KNOW DOMINGO?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> HE WAS MY PRIMARY CARE PHYSICIAN,
AND DOMINGO, DO YOU
KNOW THAT YOU WERE RIGHT?
I DO HAVE HASHIMOTO'S.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE DOMINGO IS AT
ANOTHER MAJOR LIFE EVENT OF
MINE.
>> DON'T WORRY, MATT, WE GOT
YOU.
>> RECEPTION IS LIT,
AS MANY OF YOU KNOW, WE'RE MATT'S
GROOMSMEN, AKA, THE DOORMATS.
WE TOOK MATT A GOLF TRIP TO THE
REAL CITY THAT NEVER SLEEPS,
SCOTTSDALE, ARIZONA,
WHICH IS ALSO OUR HOMETOWN.
>> AND OUR NAME.
THESE ARE THE THREE SCOTS, AND
I'LL DALE.
>> SCOTS -- DALE!
>> AND TO PLAY 18 HOLES, WE
NEEDED A LITTLE --
>> ESPRESSO.
¶ THE CRUISING HAD A LOCAL
STAYCATION
BECAUSE WE'D BEEN HIT
HARD BY INFLATION ¶
¶ AND WE KNEW MATT NEEDS A BREAK
FROM KELSEY ¶
¶ JUST KIDDING, KELS, YOUR
MARRIAGE IS HEALTHY ¶
>> WAIT, WHAT EVEN IS THIS SONG?
TEEING OFF
SHOTS
CADDIE'S NAMED RENALDO,
TO THE CONDO ¶
INVITE
¶ WE GOT A BED,
MATTHEW DOES NOT ¶
¶ HE'S GOING TO WALK WITH
RENALDO.
>> WAIT, SOPHIE, WERE YOU ON THE
GUYS TRIP?
>> YOU KNOW, I'M PRETTY SICK OF
GIRLS AFTER PRISON.
>> I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY, WHO IS
RENALDO.
>> DON'T WORRY, RENALDO IS IN MY
PAST.
>> MATTHEW, I'M HERE.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, MAN, CAME ALL THIS WAY,
HAD TO EXPLAIN, RENALDO,
MATTHEW'S MY GUY, SAID HE'S NOT MINE,
BUT WE DID HOOK UP,
THOUGH.
>> WHAT?
MATT!
>> RENALDO?
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY, YOU TWO KNOW
EACH OTHER?
>> OF COURSE!
WE ARE BROTHERS.
>> I'M THE OLDER BROTHER.
>> AND I'M THE YOUNGER BROTHER.
>> AND I'M THE HALF-BROTHER.
>> HI, SANTIAGO.
>> MOM, DAD, WAIT, HOW DO YOU
KNOW HIM?
>> WELL, I DID THEIR KITCHEN
RENOVATION
AND THEN I HAD SEX
WITH THE WIFE.
>> FEEL YOU, SANTIAGO.
LOVE
¶ CAME ALL THIS WAY,
EXPLAIN
DOMINGO
WORD TO THE
WISE, IF YOU GOT WIVES,
HIDE
THEM FROM US ¶
>> DOMINGO!
DEEP
JACK
>> LOOKING BACK OVER 50 YEARS,
WE TREASURE THE LAUGHS, THE
FRIENDSHIPS, THE FOND MEMORIES.
BUT THE REAL TREASURE WAS HOW
MUCH MONEY WE WERE MAKING.
LADIES
>> OH, WOW.
WHAT A NIGHT.
WELL, EVEN AFTER 50 YEARS, THERE
ARE STILL THINGS ABOUT "SNL"
THAT PEOPLE DON'T KNOW.
SO WE ARE HERE TO ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS PEOPLE STILL HAVE
ABOUT THE SHOW.
DON'T BE SHY.
JUST RAISE YOUR HAND.
YES, QUINTA BRUNSON.
>> HI.
>> HI!
HI
QUINTA BRUNSON HERE.
FIRST OF ALL, I WANT TO SAY, YOU
LADIES LOOK GREAT.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
>> WOW, THANK YOU FOR ASKING
THAT QUESTION WE WROTE.
I'M WEARING A 3D PRINTED MASK OF
MY YOUNGER SELF.
>> AND MY FACE IS ALL NATURAL,
BUT FULL DISCLOSURE, THIS IS THE
BACK OF MY HEAD.
I SLIP MID HAIR AND STARTED
OVER.
>> WELL, IT'S WORKING FOR YOU,
BABY GIRL.
ANY WAY, I AM A "SNL" SUPERFAN.
MY QUESTION IS KIND OF A DEEP
CUT.
IN THE MARCH 18th, 1993 GOOD NIGHTS,
TIM MEADOWS WHISPERED
SOMETHING TO MUSICAL GUEST SADE?
WHAT WAS HE SAYING?
>> OH, WOW, LET'S FIND OUT.
TIM, DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT YOU
WERE SAYING?
>> OH, YEAH, WOW.
THANK YOU.
YES, IT WAS MARCH '93.
I'M PRETTY SURE I WAS SAYING
HEY, SADE, YOU WANT TO DRINK
SOME ZIMA WITH ME IN MY DRESSING
ROOM?
WE CAN PLAY MORTAL KOMBAT 1 AND
WATCH THE NEW MENENDEZ TRIAL.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I
THOUGHT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> ALSO, AT WORK BY THE WAY,
SADE ARE STILL TOGETHER.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
THAT'S AWESOME.
WHO ELSE HAS A QUESTION?
>> I HAVE A QUESTION.
>> OH, HI, RYAN REYNOLDS, HI.
HOW'S IT GOING?
>> GREAT.
WHY, WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
MY QUESTION IS YOU KNOW THE
MATERIALS THAT THEY MADE THE CONEHEADS WITH,
ARE THOSE
EDIBLE?
>> EDIBLE?
NO, NO.
AND BASED ON THEM BEING MADE IN
1975, I'D ASSUME THEY'RE HIGHLY
TOXIC.
>> OH, OKAY.
SO SOMEBODY HYPOTHETICALLY
TOOK
A COUPLE NIBBLES BACKSTAGE AND GOT EXCITED,
SHOULD THEY GO TO
THE HOSPITAL OR SHOULD THEY --
>> YES, THEY SHOULD GO TO
HOSPITAL RIGHT AWAY.
>> GOOD.
>> GOOD LUCK.
NEXT QUESTION --
>> I HAVE A QUESTION.
>> YES?
NATE
>> WHEN I HOSTED THE SHOW, THERE
WAS A WOMAN
WHO PULLED ME BEHIND
A LITTLE CURTAIN AND TOOK MY
PANTS OFF.
DOES SHE WORK HERE?
>> IS SHE A BLOND WOMAN WITH A
STOPWATCH?
>> YEAH.
SHE PUT HER ARM AROUND MY WAIST
AND KIND OF SHOOK ME UNTIL MY
SHOES FELL OFF.
DID I DREAM THAT OR IS THAT --
>> NO, THAT'S DONNA.
COME OUT HERE, DONNA.
>> DONNA,
DONNA HAS BEEN
DRESSING EVERY HOST SINCE 1997.
SHE HAS SEEN EVERY CELEBRITY
HERE IN THEIR UNDERPANTS.
>> DONNA, I KNOW IT'S HARD TO
PICK, BUT WHO WAS YOUR FAV --
>> JASON MOMOA.
>> OUR NEXT QUESTION WAS
SUBMITTED BY A VIEWER.
LOVED FAN 89 WANTS TO KNOW
WHY AM I SEATED ACROSS THE STREET IN
THE AMERICAN GIRLS STORE?
>> I'M NOT MAD.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHY.
LADIES?
SO LOVITZ FAN IS JON LOVITZ.
I KNOW THE SEATING CHART WAS
REALLY HARD TO FIGURE OUT.
YOU WERE GOING TO BE SEATED IN
THE STUDIO,
BUT THEN JULIA
LOUIS-DREYFUS ASKED TO BRING HER
SERVICE DOG.
SORRY
>> YEAH, SORRY.
JON, IT'S A MEDICAL THING.
YOU REALLY NEED THAT DOG, RIGHT,
JULIA?
>> OH, NO, NO, NO.
I'M HERE FOR HIM.
HE IS BLIND.
>> SO RICKY, THE BLOND WOMAN WHO
JUST TALKED,
THAT'S AMY POEHLER.
AND THE OLDER WOMAN NEXT TO HER
IS TINA FEY.
AND THE INTENSE ENERGY THAT
YOU'RE FEELING TO YOUR LEFT
IS ADAM DRIVER.
HE IS AN ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE
ACTOR.
AND RIGHT NOW HE IS ACTING LIKE
HE IS NOT ATTRACTED TO ME.
HOW YOU DOING?
THIS IS MY PUPPY HERE.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
LET'S TAKE ANOTHER QUESTION.
YES, CHER, YOU HAVE A QUESTION?
>> NO, I DON'T.
I GOT A LOT OF ANSWERS.
THERE
>> WE'LL HOOK UP WITH YOU AFTER
THE SHOW.
>> NEXT QUESTION.
YES, KEITH RICHARDS?
>> I LET A SCARF HERE IN 1988,
AND I'M KIND OF WONDERING IF
ANYBODY HAS SEEN IT AROUND.
>> A SCARF, YEAH, IN 1998?
WELL, THAT'S A LONG TIME AGO.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M NOT SURE.
>> LOOK, IT'S SIMPLY NOT HERE,
OKAY?
CAN WE ALL STOP LOOKING?
NEXT QUESTION!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> YES, JON HAMM?
>> YEAH, HEY, GUYS --
>> THIS MIGHT BE A WEIRD
QUESTION BECAUSE I'VE HOSTED
THREE TIMES AND I KNOW I'M PART
OF THE FAMILY.
BUT AM I FUNNY?
BUDDY
>> FUNNY!
>> WE --
>> WHENEVER WE ASK YOU TO DO A
BIT, YOU ALWAYS SAY YES.
AND THAT'S WHAT MATTERS.
>> YES, YES.
>> NEXT QUESTION.
>> HOLA.
FUNNY
SI
YO SOCHITOS.
SO JON HAMON.
SECRET
>> ALL RIGHT, YES.
NEXT QUESTION, SETH?
>> HI, GUYS.
IT KIND OF FEELS LIKE THIS WHOLE
QUESTION AND ANSWER THING
IS
JUST WAY FOR YOU GUYS TO GIVE
AIR TIME TO CELEBRITIES
WHO
AREN'T IN OTHER PARTS OF THE
SHOW.
>> REALLY?
IT DOESN'T SEEM THAT WAY TO ME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, REVEREND AL
SHARPTON AND RAY ROMANO?
>> IT SEEMS VERY NATURAL TO US.
>> REALLY, DON'T BE SO CYNICAL,
SETH.
WE'RE HAVING A NICE TIME HERE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> JASON MOMOA, YES, JASON?
>> THIS DONNY LADY,
SHE LIKE TO TRAVEL OR?
>> WE'LL HAVE TO ASK HER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOOD TO KNOW.
FREDDY
>> HI, I'M FRED ARMISEN, THANKS.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
MY QUESTION IS, DO YOU KNOW WHY
LORNE CUT "VAMPIRE OFFICE"?
>> WHAT?
>> WELL, IN 2005, I WROTE A
SKETCH CALLED "VAMPIRE OFFICE"
AND IT PLAYED PRETTY WELL AT
DRESS AND IT DIDN'T GET ON AIR.
>> OKAY, I GUESS MAYBE OTHER
SKETCHES DID BETTER?
>> NO.
IT WAS A PRETTY BAD SHOW FRONT
TO BACK.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OKAY, WELL, MAYBE HE JUST
DIDN'T LIKE IT.
>> WELL, DO YOU KNOW IF HE SAW
THE CHANGES I WAS GOING TO MAKE,
BECAUSE I CUT THE B WORD AS
VANESSA COMES IN AS SIMON
COWELL.
>> WAIT, ARE YOU HOLDING THE
SKETCH RIGHT NOW?
YEAH. DO YOU THINK I SHOULD RESIB
MITT ID?
>> SURE.
>> GREAT.
NEXT TIME
>> OKAY, WE ONLY HAVE TIME FOR
LIKE 100 MORE QUESTIONS.
>> YES, YES.
PEYTON MANNING?
>> IS LORNE GOING TO RETIRE NOW?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> OKAY, THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
LORNE, NEVER RETIRE.
IT'S BRUTAL OUT HERE.
THEY HAVE ME DOING ALL THESE
COMMERCIALS -- INSURANCE, BEER.
I DID ONE THE OTHER DAY FOR
SOMETHING CALLED FAN FIGHT POWER
MONSTER 3.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THE HELL
IT IS.
I ASSUMED IT WAS A VIDEO GAME,
BUT IN THE VOICE OVERI SAID NOW
IN DIET CHILI FLAVOR.
I HATE BEING RETIRED.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> NO, SERIOUSLY, LORNE, GETTING
OLD SUCKS.
YOU FEEL LIKE SUCH A LOSER.
GALIFIANAKIS KNOWS WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
>> PLEASE DON'T BOTHER ME.
I JUST WANT TO ROW ELAX AND WAT
KANYE PERFORM.
>> YOU GOT IT, ZACH.
WATCH
- HELLO
- FLEX
- WHORE
>> WHAT'S UP, DUDE.
ARE YOU GOING TO THE 50th?
>> NO, I CAN'T.
I'M NOT GOING TO GO.
>> WHAT YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT'S GOING TO BE INCREDIBLE.
EVERYONE ON EARTH IS GOING TO BE
THERE.
>> HONESTLY, IT STRESSES ME OUT
TOO MUCH.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> COME ON, YOU KNOLL I GET
ANXIETY.
>> BOWEN, LISTEN.
¶ I KNOW YOU'RE ANXIOUS
JUST LOOKING AT THE SIDE
AND WHEN YOU'RE INSIDE
BUT THERE IS ONE THING
YOU GOT TO KEEP IN
MIND ¶
¶ SO WE'RE GOING PRESS REWIND,
LET'S GO BACK IN TIME ¶
¶ YOUNG ACKROYD,
LOOKS SO FINE
AND FANCY FREE ¶
¶ BUT THE REALITY WAS QUITE TRAGIC,
HE SUFFERED FROM
ANXIETY ¶
>> JESUS, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THAT'S THE FOOTAGE EXACT LIB AS
IT AIRED
¶ EDDIE MURPHY
AND MR. ROBINSON'S NEIGHBORHOOD,
HE WAS THE STAR OF THE SHOW EACH
SATURDAY,
BE HE SUFFERED
ANXIETY ¶
HATE
¶ HEY, BILLY CRYSTAL,
SAYING MARVELOUS,
BUT ONE THING WASN'T MARVELOUS, ¶
ANXIETY
¶ BECAUSE EVERYONE
THAT EVER WORKED AT "SNL"
HAD ANXIETY ¶
¶ YOU ARE NOT ALONE, MY FRIEND,
AND --
IBS
>> WHAT?
- SARAH
>> THE CONNECTION
IS A COMPLEX
OF DIRECTIONAL,
A COMMUNICATION
BETWEEN ESSENTIAL
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND YOUR BUTT.
¶ WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING "SNL,"
JUST IMAGINE EVERYONE YOU SEE,
RIGHT BEFORE THE SHOW WENT TO
THE BATHROOM
AND TOOK THE
CRAZY --
>> RIGHT.
Oh, if these pipes could talk
The stories they would tell
If these pipes could talk
I think they'd sound a little like this
>> YOU'VE GOT TO STOP DOING
THAT.
>> NO PROMISES.
Jump to the '90s, Ana and Molly
Making 'em laugh with Schweddy Balls
On the outside, calm and collected
But that's not how they felt at all
Oh, we were freaked out as hell
¶ WE WANTED TO DIE,
We wished for our own deaths
And we had IBS
>> COME ON, GUYS, WE HAVE
PERSPECTIVE.
WE KNOW THESE ARE CHAMPAGNE
PROBLEMS.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE
WORKING IN A COAL MINE.
>> GOD, NO.
>> BUT HERE'S A SECRET.
¶ IT'S WAY WORSE THAN WORKING IN
A COAL MINE.
It's more dangerous than working in a coal mine
WE WOULD LOVE TO BE WORKING IN A COAL MINE,
JUST LOOK AT THESE
COAL MINERS DRINKING SWEET TEA,
They never had to get notes from Lorne
Sit underneath the bleachers with Lorne
You're proving my point, that sounds good to you?
>> NOW THAT I HEAR IT, I MIGHT
SKIP IT TOO,
BECAUSE IN THE END
YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELF.
A mature decision for our mental health
BUT WHAT IF THEY FORGET ABOUT ME,
Don't forget me
IF I DON'T GO TO THE SHOW,
WILL I DISAPPEAR ¶
Or will I fall to the bottom
of the Best Cast Members of All Time list?
¶ THAT'S YOUR FORTE ¶
WHAT
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M IN.
- SAME.
>> BECAUSE EVERYONE ¶
>> I GET IT NOW!
¶ THAT EVER WORKED AT "SNL" HAD
ANXIETY ¶
¶ IT'S HARD THE WAITING ROOMS
AND HAVE THE THERAPIST IN NEW
YORK CITY
¶ EVERY SINGLE PERSON WHO WORKED
AT "SNL" HAD ANXIETY,
It's a challenging place, but we love it
Stress dreams for the rest of your life
We're like moths to the flame
But it burns so good
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MILEY
CYRUS AND BRITTANY HOWARD.
Nothing Compares 2 U
¶ IT'S BEEN SEVEN HOURS AND 13 DAYS,
SINCE U TOOK YOUR LOVE AWAY ¶
¶ I GO OUT EVERY NIGHT
AND I SLEEP ALL DAY
SINCE YOU TOOK
YOUR LOVE AWAY ¶
¶ SINCE YOU BEEN GONE
I CAN DO WHATEVER I WANT
YEAH, I CAN SEE WHOMEVER I
CHOOSE ¶
¶ I CAN EAT MY DINNER
AT A FANCY RESTAURANT
BUT NOTHING,
OH NOTHING CAN TAKE AWAY THESE BLUES ¶
¶ 'CAUSE NOTHING COMPARES
NO, NOTHING COMPARES TO YOU ¶
¶ OH, NOTHING, NOTHING ¶
>> BRITTANY HOWARD!
¶ IT'S BEEN SO LONELY
WITHOUT YOU HERE
LIKE A BIRD WITHOUT A SONG ¶
¶ NOTHING CAN STOP
THESE LONELY TEARS
FROM FALLING ¶
¶ TELL ME BABY
WHERE DID I GO WRONG
I COULD PUT MY ARMS
AROUND EVERY BOY I SEE ¶
¶ BUT THEY'D ONLY
REMIND ME OF YOU
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR
AND GUESS WHAT HE TOLD ME ¶
¶ GUESS WHAT HE TOLD ME
HE SAID GIRL
YOU BETTER HAVE FUN ¶
NO MATTER
¶ BUT HE'S A FOOL ¶
NOTHING COMPARES,
NOTHING COMPARES TO YOU ¶
¶ NOTHING, NOTHING ¶
>> WAIT FOR IT.
¶ ALL THE FLOWERS THAT YOU
PLANTED, MAMA,
IN THE BACKYARD ¶
¶ ALL DIED WHEN YOU WENT AWAY,
¶ I KNOW THAT LIVING WITH YOU, BABY,
WAS SOMETIMES HARD,
BUT I'M WILLING TO GIVE IT ANOTHER
TRY ¶
¶ BECAUSE NOTHING COMPARES,
NOTHING COMPARES TO YOU ¶
¶ BECAUSE NOTHING COMPARES.
>> NOTHING, NOTHING COMPARES TO
YOU ¶
¶ BECAUSE NOTHING COMPARES,
NOTHING COMPARES TO
YOU, YOU, YOU, YOU, YOU, YOU ¶¶
>>> IT'S WEEKEND UPDATE, 50th
ANNIVERSARY EDITION.
WITH COLIN JOST AND MIKELE --
MICHAEL CHE.
THANK
>> I'M MICHAEL CHE.
>> I'M COLIN JOST.
>> WELL, IT IS AN HONOR AND A
THRILL TO BE HOSTING WEEKEND UPDATE FOR THE 50th,
AND IF IT
WAS UP TO OUR PRESIDENT, FINAL
SEASON OF "SNL."
IT IS INCREDIBLE THAT "SNL" IS
STILL GOING AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
AND I'M JUST TALKING ABOUT
TONIGHT'S SHOW.
THERE ARE SO MANY FAMOUS HOSTS
AND MUSICAL GUESTS HERE TONIGHT
THAT SOME HUGE NAMES ACTUALLY
HAVE TO WATCH FROM STUDIO 8G NEXT DOOR
AS WELL AS FROM THE
METROPOLITAN DETENTION CENTER IN
BROOKLYN.
OH, YOU WENT TO THE PARTIES,
OKAY.
>> "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" HAS WON
95 EMMYS, ONE GRAMMY,
THREE
PEABODYS, AND HAS OVER 100 TONYS
ON THE CREW.
I'M KIDDING, BUT LET'S ACTUALLY
TAKE A MOMENT
TO THANK
THOSE HARDWORKING CREW GUYS.
I WANT TO THANK THOSE CREW GUY,
AND ALSO LIKE TO CONGRATULATE
THEM ON THEIR JANUARY 6th
PARDONS.
BACK
A LOT OF PONIES.
>> HEALTH EXPERTS ARE FACING
INCREASED PRESSURE
IN THE FACE
OF OUTBREAK OF COVID, THE FLU,
RSV AND NOROVIRUS,
WHICH THEY'RE
CALLING A QUAD DEEM MICK.
THE SMART THING,
PACKED EVERY BELOVED
ENTERTAINER OVER 60 IN ONE
STAGE.
SNL'S FIRST MAJOR CAST CHANGE
WAS IN SEASON 2
WHEN CHEVY CHASE
LEFT THE SHOW
AND WAS REPLACED
BY KENAN THOMPSON.
>> ME AND COLIN ARE ACTUALLY THE
LONGEST SERVING WEEKEND UPDATE
ANCHORS.
I'VE DONE WEEKEND UPDATE FOR SO LONG,
NEXT SEASON I'M CO-HOSTING
WITH MY SON BRONNY.
AND SINCE THE 40EST WE'VE LOST
THE LATE GREAT NORMAN DONALD
WHO
HOSTED WEEKEND UPDATE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NORM DONALD WHO HOSTED WEEKEND UPDATE
UNTIL HE WAS FIRED FOR
MAKING JOKES ABOUT O.J. SIMPSON,
AND HE IS ONE OF MY HEROES.
SO IF HE IS WATCHING UP THERE,
I
JUST WANT TO SAY, WE LOVE YOU,
O.J.
>> WELL, THERE IS A LOT GOING ON
IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW,
AND HERE
TO TELL US HER THOUGHTS ON ALL OF IT
IS THE GIRL YOU WISH YOU
HADN'T STARTED A CONVERSATION
WITH AT A PARTY.
HELLO
NOTICE ANYTHING DIFFERENT ABOUT ME.
>> ARE YOU PREGNANT?
>> WOW.
YOU JUST ASSUME I'M PREGNANT.
JUST BECAUSE I HAVE A BABY
INSIDE ME.
THAT'S MISOGYNISTIC.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
IT'S NICE TO SEE.
>> OH, IS IT NICE, MICHAEL?
IS IT NICE TO BE ON THE VERGE OF
THE APOCALYPSE.
IT'S DEVASTATING.
IT'S A CONSTIPATIONAL CRISIS,
LITERALLY FOR ME.
DO I WANT TO BRING A BABY INTO THE WORLD
OR SHOULD I KEEP HER
IN HERE FOR ANOTHER 3 1/2 YEARS.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU CAN DO
THAT.
>> OH, I GUESS YOU KNOW MORE
THAN MY OB/GYN.
DO YOUR RESEARCH, MICHAEL.
FACTS.
90% OF BABIES BORN TODAY
WILL
NEVER KNOW WHO YOUR FATHER IS.
>> MY FATHER?
>> THREE OUT OF FOUR KIDS GET
BULLIED.
AND ONLY TWO OF THEM DESERVE IT.
>> WHAT?
>> AND THERE ARE PEOPLE IN
AFRICA RIGHT NOW --
>> WAS THAT IT?
>> YES.
THERE ARE PEOPLE THERE NOW.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT, MICHAEL.
READ A PHONE.
HAVE YOUR ELON SALUTE REALLY
QUICK.
>> NO, DON'T DO THAT.
>> I HAVE TO DO THIS DANCE.
>> I'M SORRY, WHERE DID YOU
WORK?
>> I'M THE PRESS SECRETARY AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
PEOPLE ARE SO ANGRY ABOUT DEI,
WELL, STOP DRINKING AND DRIVING.
BETTINA, BETTINA!
>> WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
>> THAT'S BETTINA.
SHE IS A HORRIBLE PERSON.
AT LEAST NOW WE HAVE SOME GOOD
PEOPLE IN CHARGE.
LIKE EVERYONE'S MAD THAT RF
CARLOS JR. IS A NIPPO BABY,
BUT
HI BRAIN WORM EARNED IT.
IT ATE ITS WAY TO THE TOP.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> IN FALLUJAH, WHY IS NO ONE TALKING
ABOUT LUIGI WOMAN-GIONE.
YES.
I JUST BLEW MICHAEL CHE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
AND BY THE WAY, CAN I ASK WHO
THE FATHER IS?
>> YOU SURE CAN!
HUGE REVEAL.
OH MY GOD.
HUGE.
>> YOU TWO ARE TOGETHER?
>> YEP.
WE'RE THE TYPICAL HOLLYWOOD
COUPLE.
A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN IN HER 30s,
DRUNK IDIOT IN HIS 70s.
>> YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO BE A
DAD?
>> HEY, IF ALEC BALDWIN CAN DO
IT.
WHEN I WAS A KID, EVERYONE WAS
PREGNANT.
HIGH SCHOOL BABY MARRIED VIETNAM
JOB YOU HATE.
OKAY?
BUT NOWADAYS, IT'S JUST
OH, I'M
SORRY, CAN YOU YASSIFY MY
CHICKPEA PASTA?
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME, ARE THESE
FLARE JEANS AI?
OOH, GREAT, WE'RE IN A BRAVE
NEW WORLD.
NOT MY CAPTAIN AMERICA.
>> DRUNK UNCLE.
COLIN!
>> YOU RIP BUTTONS OFF.
RIP
¶ IF I COULD TURN BACK TIME ¶
¶ IF I COULD --
RIP YOUR SHIRT ¶
>> DRUNK UNCLE.
>> SO I'M NOT LAND SHARK, OKAY?
SO I'M NOT BRIAN FELLOWS,
SORRY OKAY?
SO I'M NOT BEAUTIFUL GUEST
TIMOTHEE CHALAMET!
G BURGER, G BURGER, G BURGER.
>> YES, FROM THE '70s.
>> NO, I MISPLACED 4
CHEESEBERGERS.
>> I'M SORRY, BUT I THINK YOU
MIGHT BE TOO DRUNK.
>> YES, I HAD TO TACKLE PAUL
SIMON.
BUT I MISSED, AND NOW SABRINA
CARPENTER'S DEAD.
>> OKAY.
>> DRUNK UNCLE AND GIRL AT A
PARTY, EVERYONE.
¶ IF I COULD TURN --
- BETINA
>> BETTINA.
AND NOW WE WILL THROW IT OVER TO
YOU, SETH.
>> THANK YOU, AMY.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S IMPORTANT THAT WE
SPEND SOME TIME TONIGHT TALKING
ABOUT LORNE MICHAELS,
AND NO ONE
KNOWS HIM BETTER THAN OUR NEXT
GUEST.
PLEASE WELCOME LORNE'S BEST
FRIENDS FROM GROWING UP.
HI
>> HI, GUYS.
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
WHAT'S LORNE REALLY LIKE?
>> OH, HE IS THE BEST.
HE IS RELAX AND CHILL.
>> HE IS SUPER DOWN TO EARTH AND
APPROACHABLE.
WE LOVE, WE LOVE HIM.
>> HE IS OUR BUDDY.
>> TOTALLY, YES.
>> I WILL SAY SOMETIMES
HE CAN BE A LITTLE RUDE.
>> YEAH, LIKE A MONTH AGO, HE
ASKED US TO HELP HIM MOVE.
AND WE'RE LIKE SURE, OF COURSE.
HELP YOU MOVE.
HAVE A LITTLE DINNER, WHATEVER.
>> SO WE GET THERE.
LORNE OPENS THE DOOR,
AND HE IS
LIKE OH, YOU TWO.
AND WE'RE LIKE WHAT?
>> YOU INVITED US.
WE DON'T HAVE TO BE HERE.
>> SO WE LOOK AROUND.
NOTHING IS PACKED.
>> NOTHING IS PACKED.
>> YOU HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED YET?
AND THEN HE STARTS POINTING AT
PAINTINGS AND SAYING
THIS IS
FROM STEVE, THIS IS FROM PAUL,
THIS IS FROM MICK.
>> AND DOES HE MEAN MICK JAGGER?
>> JUST TO SAY IT.
SAY
>> I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS HAVE TO
SPEAK UP.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY CAN HEAR
YOU.
BUT ALSO, IT DOES SOUND LIKE
MAYBE LORNE CAN BE A LITTLE
DIFFICULT.
>> NO.
>> NO, NO.
NO.
>> HE IS OUR FRIEND.
HE IS OUR BEST FRIEND.
>> HE IS EASY-BREEZY CRAZY TIME,
ALL OF IT.
I WILL SAY
HE CAN BE KIND OF
LIKE INCONSIDERATE.
LIKE WE'RE PACKING HIS STUFF FOR
HOURS, AND HE'S GONE.
AND HE COMES BACK, AND OH, HEY,
LIKE WHICH BATHROOM CAN I USE?
AND HE GOES THERE IS A STARBUCKS
ACROSS THE STREET.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BUY SOMETHING
FIRST.
SO GET ME A LATTE.
WHAT?
WE'RE HELPING YOU MOVE.
>> AGAIN, YOU GUYS HAVE TO SPEAK
UP.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE MAYBE YOU GUYS
AREN'T THAT GOOD A FRIENDS WITH
HIM.
>> OH, NO, NO, NO.
>> BEST FRIENDS.
>> HE IS OUR PERSON.
HE IS OUR PERSON.
PHONE CALL
MY EMERGENCY CONTACT.
>> HE GETS ALL MY ORGANS IF I
DIE.
I LOVE HIM SO MUCH.
BUT ANY WAY, IT'S LIKE IT'S
NIGHTTIME.
AND HE'S LIKE -- HE'S LIKE I'M
GOING TO DINNER, KEEP AT IT.
>> WE'VE BEEN PACKING YOUR STUFF
ALL DAY.
WHERE ARE WE SUPPOSED TO EAT?
AND HE GOES, BY THE WAY YOU TWO
LOOK, I DON'T THINK YOU NEED
HELP FINDING FOOD.
>> WHAT?
HE IS HE SAYING WE'RE FAT?
>> HE CAN'T TALK TO US LIKE
THAT.
WE'RE FRIENDS FROM GROWING UP.
>> AND THEN HE GOES YOU GUYS HAD
A PROBLEM WITH ME
FROM THE
MOMENT YOU WALKED IN HERE.
YOU DIDN'T ASK ME HOW MY DAY WAS
OR NOTICE MY HAIRCUT.
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW MUCH
PRESSURE I'M UNDER.
NBC'S BREATHING DOWN MY NECK.
>> MAKING 100 DOCUMENTARIES AND
THEY DON'T EVEN GIVE ME A FREE
MEMBERSHIP.
>> GUYS, I CAN BARELY HEAR YOU,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAVE A
DEEPLY DYSFUNCTIONAL
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
>> NO.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> IT'S KIND OF HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT COLIN AND CHE.
>> NO, I LOVE COLIN AND CHE.
THEY'RE THE BEST.
I WILL SAY,
I DO FEEL LIKE THEIR
CHEMISTRY IS LIKE A WORK IN
>> SETH MEYERS, EVERYBODY.
>> LORNE'S BEST FRIENDS GROWING
UP, EVERYBODY.
>> WELL, YOU GUYS, YOU MAY HAVE
SEEN IN THE LEAD-UP, THE 50th ANNIVERSARY
THERE A LOT OF
SNL-RELATED LISTS AND
RANKINGS.
HERE WITH HIS RANKING OF THE
BEST WEEKEND UPDATE ANCHORS OF ALL TIME,
IT'S FORMER UPDATE
ANCHOR BILL MURRAY.
>> THANK YOU, COLIN.
LET'S JUST JUMP RIGHT IN.
IN HONOR OF BLACK HISTORY MONTH,
I WANT TO START BY RANKING THE
AFRICAN AMERICAN
WEEKEND UPDATE
ANCHORS.
WE'LL START WITH NUMBER ONE, AND
THIS IS BY DEFAULT,
MICHAEL CHE.
NOW WE'LL MOVE ON TO THE REGULAR
WEEKEND UPDATE ANCHORS.
>> REGULAR?
WHAT THE HELL YOU MEAN REGULAR?
>> THESE ARE IN NO PARTICULAR ORDER,
SO I'VE LISTED THEM FROM
WORST TO BEST.
FIRST OFF, I HAVE TO DISQUALIFY MYSELF
BECAUSE MY ENTIRE TIME HERE
I WAS ON
PERFORMANCE-ENHANCING DRUGS.
IT'S WHAT WE CALL AN 88-SHAKER,
QUAALUDES, COCAINE, AND
NIGHTTIME THERA FLU.
ALL RIGHT.
NUMBER 10.
HE'S ONE OF THE ALL-TIME GREATS,
MR. COLIN
QUINN.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> I HAD YOU FOR A SECOND.
DON'T WORRY.
NUMBERS 9, 8, AND 7, OKAY?
HEADS UP,
KEVIN NEALON.
COME ON!
DENNIS MILLER,
AND SETH MEYERS.
I JUST WISH WE HAD THE TIME
TONIGHT TO SAY SOMETHING NICE
ABOUT ANY OF THEM.
>> WE ACTUALLY DO PROBABLY HAVE
ENOUGH TIME.
>> WE'RE RIGHT HERE AT 6:00 NOW.
OKAY.
COLIN, THIS COULD BE YOU, HUH?
>> IS IT?
>> NO, IT IS NOT.
THE NEXT TWO ARE CONTROVERSIAL.
THIS WAS TOUGH.
BUT I'M GOING TO PUT TINA AND AMY
JUST AHEAD OF TINA AND
JIMMY.
>> SORRY, JIMMY, I'M SORRY.
AND CONGRATULATIONS, TINA.
IT WAS CLOSE, BUT I CHECKED ONLINE,
AND GIRL ON GIRL IS
STILL VERY, VERY POPULAR.
NEXT UP, CORNELIUS CRANE CHASE.
WHO WE'VE ALL COME TO KNOW AS
CONNIE.
LET'S FACE IT, WEEKEND UPDATES
SIMPLY WOULD NOT EXIST WITHOUT
HIM.
SO IT WOULD BE WRONG TO HAVE HIM
LISTED AT ANYWHERE
BUT NUMBER
FOUR.
NUMBER THREE,
JANE CURTAIN AND DANNY ACKROYD.
A TRUE STORY, I WAS THE FIRST
TO CALL JANE AN IGNORANT SLUT.
BACKSTAGE.
DANNY HAD THE BRILLIANT IDEA TO
SAY IT ON CAMERA,
AND REALLY,
REALLY MEAN IT.
NUMBER TWO IS NORM McDONALD.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN THE BEST EVER,
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY, HE MADE ME, FOR ONE,
ASK THE QUESTION OF MYSELF
COULD O.J. POSSIBLY HAVE
DONE IT?
SO THAT BRINGS US TO NUMBER ONE.
COLIN?
GOT A GOOD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
OKAY. NUMBER ONE IS FUNNY,
GOT A GREAT SMILE,
AND HE IS CURRENTLY
SLEEPING EVERY KIND OF WAY WITH
THE LOVELY ACTRESS SCARLETT
JOHANSSON.
OF COURSE I'M TALKING ABOUT
MY BROTHER, BRIAN
>> WHAT?
>> YES.
>> I'M TOLD A VERY, VERY
CONSIDERATE LOVER.
I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER TO BE
HERE.
>> BILL MURRAY, EVERYBODY.
I'M MICHAEL CHE.
GOOD NIGHT!
PENTAGON
THANK
FAIRFAX
U.S. SPACE FORCE.
THIS IS DR. TYLER FROM SETI.
>> WE ARE EAGER TO TALK TO YOU
AS YOU HAVE ALL EXPERIENCE
A VERIFIED ALIEN ABDUCTION.
>> THIS IS WILD.
ONE MINUTE WE'RE THREE FRIENDS
SLAMMING MILLER TALL BOYS BEHIND
THE DOLLAR TREE,
NOW WE'RE
SITTING AT THE PENTAGON.
>> HEY, I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK
LIKE WHY DO YOU CALL IT THE PENTAGON
WHEN IT'S ONLY GOT FIVE
SIDES?
>> BECAUSE A SHAPE WITH FIVE
SIDES IS CALLED A PENTAGON.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WE'LL LOOK INTO IT.
NOW LET'S START WITH HOW YOU
WERE ALL BROUGHT ABOARD THE
SPACECRAFT.
>> WELL, THIS BEAM OF LIGHT
APPEARED FROM THE BOTTOM OF THE
SHIP.
FLOATED ME UP LIKE A SAW PAN
BECKONING ME.
>> SAME-SAME,
AND WE MET THESE
TWO BEAUTIFUL GLOWING ALIENS
WHO TOOK OUR HANDS AND SAID
WELCOME.
I'VE NEVER FELT SO SAFE.
>> AND YOU, MS. RAFFERTY?
>> YEAH, A LITTLE DIFFERENT FOR
ME.
I WAS LESS CRADLED BY LIGHT
AND MORE GRABBED BY A GIANT RUSTY CLAW
WHICH YANKED ME RIGHT OUT
OF MY SLACKS.
SO I'M PANTSLESS, RIGHT?
I'M FOLDED IN HALF LIKE A
WALLET.
NIPS
I'M GETTING WINCHED SKYWARD
WITH MY VAGITA AND MY TRAGEDY
FLAPPING IN BREEZE
AND AYE TOSSED INTO THE BOTTOM OF
THE SHIP.
I SEE MY OLD PALS THE GRAY
ALIENS WITH THE BIG DUMB EYES.
>> MRS. RAFFERTY, I'M TOLD THIS
IS YOUR FIFTH TIME BEING
ABDUCTED BY THESE GRAY ALIENS?
>> YEAH.
ONLY OTHER PLACE I'VE BEEN
PANTSLESS FIVE TIMES IS
SIX
FLAGS.
>> OKAY, WELL, LET'S MOVE PAST
THAT.
NOW WHAT HAPPENED NEXT IN THE
UPPER PART OF THE SHIP?
>> WELL, THE SMART ALIENS BATHED
US IN THIS GLOWING LIQUID
THAT ERASED ALL MY PAIN.
MY BAD KNEE DIDN'T EVEN HURT.
I BUSTED IT A FEW YEARS BACK
PLAYING PAINT BALL.
COMPETITIVE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU WINKED
AT ME AFTER SAYING THAT,
BUT
LET'S CONTINUE.
WERE YOU ALSO BATHED IN THIS
LIGHT, SIR?
>> HUH, YES, MA'AM.
IT FELT BETTER THAN ANY DRUG,
INCLUDING THE ONES I'M ON RIGHT
NOW.
>> NOW THAT REALLY TWEAKS MY CHEEKS
BECAUSE DOWN IN STEERAGE,
THE MOOD WAS TENSE.
>> STEERAGE, WHAT DO YOU THINK
COULD HAVE CAUSED THIS REACTION?
>> WELL, BETWEEN YOU, ME AND
JESUS C.,
I THINK IT HAD THE
STATE OF MY DOWN THERE HAIR.
BECAUSE REMEMBER, I'M DONALD
DUCKING IT, OKAY?
SHIRT, NO PANTS.
SO I'M POKE KAY BOWL AND MY
SMOKY HOLE ARE OUT.
AND PUBICALLY SPEAKING, NATURE
HAS RECLAIMED THE EARTH.
LAST TIME I HAD A BRAZILIAN DOWN
THERE WAS 2002.
HIS NAME WAS DIEGO, AND HE GOT
STREP THROAT.
WHO MOWS THE LAWN IN WINTER, AM
I RIGHT?
>> AMEN.
>> NOT SAY AMEN TO THAT COUNTRY.
>> MRS. REPORTY, I'M FAILING TO SEE
WHAT YOUR UNKEMPT PRIVATE
AREA HAS TO DO WITH THE ALIENS'
DEMEANOR.
>> OKAY, MY THEORY IS THEY
THOUGHT IT WAS AN ANIMAL.
BECAUSE
FIRST, THEY DIDN'T KNOW IF IT
WAS FRIENDLY.
SO THEY'RE CAUTIOUS.
THEY'RE GOING UP THE CABINET,
AND THEY'RE GOING --
AND THEN,
THEN, THE ALPHA COMES IN,
AND HE
CHALLENGES IT, RIGHT.
HE GOES LIKE THIS.
SO HE GIVES A THUMBS-UP LIKE
WE'RE GOOD, IT'S TAME.
AND WHOA, IT'S PLAY TIME.
AND ONE OF THEM
SORRY
COMES UP UNDER IT,
PUTS IT ON LIKE A WIG,
AND HE'S LIKE DOING PROP COMEDY,
AND ANOTHER ONE, HE IS SO EXCITED,
HE IS WRESTLING WITH IT,
LIKE IT'S HIS BROTHER, PULLING ME ALL
AROUND THE ROOM.
SO I LOOK DOWN.
I SEE A GUY BETWEEN MY LEGS WITH
A SMILE ON HIS FACE.
I DON'T KNOW.
FIRST TIME FOR EVERYTHING.
>> AMEN.
>> OKAY, AGAIN, NOT A THING TO
SAY AMEN TO.
>> AND THIS GOES ON ABOUT 15
MINUTES UNTIL WHO COMES TO THE DOOR
BUT MY FRIGGING MOTHER,
COLLEEN SR.
>> YES.
WE ACTUALLY HAD SOME QUESTIONS
FOR HER AS WELL.
>> I'M HERE, I'M HERE, I'M HERE.
>> SORRY, SORRY, MY BATHROOM
BREAK TOOK LONGER THAN I
THOUGHT.
MY NUMBER ONE TURNED INTO A
NUMBER THREE.
>> MEGA MILL OF ALERT.
>> NOT.
NOW MRS. RAFFERTY, YOU HAD BEEN
ABDUCTED EARLIER THAT SAME
EVENING?
>> YEP.
US RAFFERTY GALS, WE ALWAYS
ATTRACTED THE FREAKS.
FOR YEARS I THOUGHT COLLEEN'S
FATHER WAS PART ALIEN,
BUT IT
TURNS OUT HE WAS JUST
UNCIRCUMCISED.
>> AMEN.
>> PLEASE, STOP.
STOP.
>> ANY WAY, I STILL HAD MY PANTS
ON WHEN THEY TOOK ME,
BUT THAT
WAS GOOD BECAUSE MUCH LIKE HER,
I GOT A INTO THE WOODS
SITUATION.
MY EX USED TO SAY
THAT IT WAS LIKE TRYING TO HACK HIS WAY
THROUGH THE BLACK FOREST.
>> OKAY.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE'RE OFF TRACK.
YOU SAID THAT AFTER ARRIVING ON THE SHIP,
THE ALIENS LOST
INTEREST AND, QUOTE, STUCK YOU
IN A CLOSET?
>> YEAH, YES.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I MEAN, HEY, I'M USED TO BEING
STUFFED INTO THOSE CLOSETS,
BUT
IT'S USUALLY WHEN THE GUY'S WIFE
COMES HOME LATER
OR EARLIER OR
WHATEVER.
ANYWAY
SO ALL OF THE SUDDEN I HEAR THIS
SCREAMING, THIS ONE.
AND SO I JUST KIND OF -- JUST
KIND OF BUST OUT OF THAT --
FU
I
JUST BUST OUT, AND I JUST KICKED
THOSE LITTLE --
I JUST KICKED
THOSE LITTLE   P ERVS AWAY.
>> WOW, YOU ARE A GOOD MAMA.
>> YEAH, WELL, A GOOD MOTHER CAN
ALSO BE A GAD GIRL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, MUSTACHE?
>> OKAY, CAN WE NOT DO ANY OF
THAT RIGHT NOW, PLEASE?
HOW DID YOU ALL EXIT THE
SPACECRAFT?
>> THAT SAME SOFT LIGHT PICKED
ME UP AND PLACED ME BACK IN MY
BED.
>> ME TOO.
THAT LIGHT EVEN TUCKED ME IN,
WHICH WAS SO THOUGHTFUL OF IT.
>> AND HOW DID YOU TWO DEPART
THE SPACECRAFT?
>> WELL, IN THE PAST I'VE JUST
BEEN PUSHED OUT OF A HATCH,
BUT
THIS TIME THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED
TOO.
>> YEAH, BUT MY PANTS GOT
SNAGGED ON A PIECE OF METAL,
SO
THEY'RE GONE.
AND THEN AS FOR UNDERWEAR,
UNDERWEAR WISE,
THIS DEVIL WEARS
NADA.
>> BASICALLY, WE KIND OF IT WAS
A FREE-FALL FOR 40 FEET
WITH OUR
CROCKETT'S AND OUR PARAPETS ON
FULL DISPLAY.
>> WE CRASHED THROUGH A CEILING.
WE LAND ASS UP ON TOP OF PHIL
McDERMOTT.
>> AND WHO IS PHIL McDERMOTT?
>> HE IS A GENTLEMAN WHOSE
FAMILY I BET WISHED
THEY WENT
WITH THE CLOSED CASSETTE
FUNERAL.
>> NOT THE WORST THING MY MOM
AND I HAVE DONE IN A CHURCH.
>> PLEASE, LET'S NOT FINISH THAT
STORY AT ALL.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR CANDOR.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE YOU FOR SOME
PSYCHOLOGICAL TESTS NOW.
>> OH, WE'LL SAVE YOU THE
TROUBLE.
FAIL.
Stagehand
>> IT WAS EARLY, ONLY 50 BUCKS.
>> YOUNG MAN.
>> OH MY GOD, LARAINE NEWMAN.
>> WOULD YOU MIND KEEPING THE
STUDIO OPEN A FEW MINUTES
LONGER?
>> OF COURSE, TAKE AS LONG AS
YOU NEED.
GOD
EXCUSE ME?
>> WHAT UP?
>> OH, YOU STARTLED ME, THAT'S
ALL.
I THOUGHT I WAS ALONE.
I'M LARRAIN.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> CHAD.
>> HI, CHAD.
I'M SORRY TO DISTURB YOU.
I USED TO WORK HERE.
BACK WHEN THE SHOW FIRST
STARTED.
HEY, CHAD, CHAD, DO YOU THINK
MAYBE YOU COULD TAKE A
FIVE-MINUTE BREAK?
I WAS HOPING TO HAVE A QUIET
MOMENT IN HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> ACTUALLY, WOULD YOU JOIN ME.
IT MIGHT BE NICE TO HAVE SOME
COMPANY.
>> OKAY.
LOOK AT OUR CLOTHES.
>> GAY.
>> GOD, I LOOK SO YOUNG, BUT YOU
KNOW WHAT I HAD IN 1975?
>> BIG ASS BUSH?
>> NO.
I HAD AMBITION.
WE ALL DID, BUT GOD, WE WERE
TERRIFIED.
I THINK THAT'S WHY WE CLUNG TO
EACH OTHER LIKE WE DID,
WHICH OF
COURSE CREATED ITS OWN PROBLEMS
WITH THE PARTYING AND SEX.
>> WHAT UP?
>> IF I WASN'T WILD, I WOULD
HAVE BEEN ALL OVER YOU BACK
THEN.
SLICK
BUT I'M NOT LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
>> OKAY.
>> CHAD, WOULD YOU DO ME A
FAVOR?
>> DO ME.
>> WOULD YOU PUT A FOLLOW SPOT
ON ME?
I JUST WANT TO FEEL WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO WALK ON TO THAT STAGE
ONE MORE TIME.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M READY, CHAD.
>> MY BAD!
MY BAD.
>> SO UNFLATTERING.
>> MY BAD.
MY BAD.
>> THERE WE GO.
I CAN ALMOST HEAR THE LAUGHS,
CHAD.
THE BAND, THAT FAMOUS SACKS,
I CAN ALMOST FEEL WHAT IT WAS LIKE
WHEN ALL OF THIS WAS NEW.
>> OKAY.
>> I CAN ALMOST SEE MY OLD
FRIENDS.
SAFETY
THANKS FOR INDULGING ME, CHAD.
I HAVE SO MANY WONDERFUL
MEMORIES HERE.
I'M SURE YOU DO TOO.
I HOPE YOU REALIZE HOW LUCKY YOU
ARE TO WORK HERE, CHAD.
IT'S A PRETTY MAGICAL PLACE.
>> OKAY.
100th
SANDLER.
>> YEAH, BABY!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR JACK, BABY.
JACK MADE IT OUT TONIGHT!
>> LOVE YOU, BROTHER.
>> OKAY, HERE WE GO.
¶ EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM HAS
SOMETHING IN COMMON ¶
¶ ALL OF OUR LIVES WERE CHANGED
BY THE SHOW ¶
¶ EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM HAS
SOMETHING ELSE IN COMMON,
NONE
OF US WERE ALLOWED TO USE
THE
LITTLE BATHROOM IN LORNE'S
OFFICE ¶
¶ 50 YEARS, 50 YEARS,
SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE HAS BEEN ON FOR 50
YEARS ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF YOUR SKETCH
KILLING AT READ-THROUGH
AND
FINDING OUT THEY DIDN'T TAKE IT
BECAUSE THE HOST DIDN'T WANT TO
TAKE OFF HIS SHIRT ¶
¶ 50 YEARS, OF TUESDAY LATE
NIGHT PIZZA ¶
¶ 35 YEARS OF PEPTO-BISMOL FROM
NURSE THERESA ¶
YEAH, BABY!
¶ 50 YEARS OF THE CAST LOOKING
STRAIGHT AT THE CUE CARDS,
AND
30 YEARS OF DRUNK WALLY
HOLDING
THE CUE CARDS UPSIDE DOWN ¶
THAT A BABY, WALLY!
¶ 50 YEARS OF WRITERS SEEING
STEVEN SPIELBERG AT LORNE'S MONITORS,
NOT LAUGHING AT ONE OF
HIS SKETCHES THAT HE OBVIOUSLY
HATED ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF THOSE SAME WRITERS
GETTING WASTED AT THE AFTER
PARTY ¶
¶ AND LOUDLY TELLING EVERYBODY
THAT JAWS WAS OVERRATED ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF PRANK CALLING SOME
NEW YORK MAGAZINE CRITIC, ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF FINDING OUT YOUR
FAVORITE MUSICIAN'S
ANTISEMITIC ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF ASKING AN INTERN
TO PICK UP YOUR LAUNDRY AT 2:30 A.M.,
NOT REALIZING THAT THE
INTERN WAS MARTIN SCORSESE'S KID
OR NORA EFRON'S KID OR RANDY
NEWMAN'S KID
OR WHOEVER LORNE
HAD DINNER WITH ON WEDNESDAY
NIGHT'S KID ¶
¶ 50 YEARS FROM CAST MEMBERS
SAYING I'M NOT GETTING ON
ENOUGH ¶
¶ THEIR SPIRITS ARE BROKEN AND
THEIR HEARTS ARE FULL OF
MALICE ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF THEM STORMING OFF
TO TELL LORNE HOW THEY REALLY
FEEL ¶
¶ THEN CHICKENING OUT AND SAYING
HEY LORNE, I KNITTED THIS SCARF
FOR ALICE ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF WAKING UP SUNDAY
AFTERNOON TO THREATS,
50 YEARS
OF DOWNING WRITING THAT COLD
OPEN FIVE MINUTES UNTIL DRESS,
AND COLIN ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF WONDERING
WHO IS
GOING TO TAKE OVER THE SHOW WHEN LORNE RETIRES,
BUT EVERYONE
KNOWS THE ANSWER IS OF COURSE IS
PETEY ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF YOUNG COMEDIANS
GETTING HIRED FOR OTHER SHOWS ¶
¶ STAND-UP SECOND CITY IN ALL
THE REST ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF CAST MEMBERS
SAYING I THINK OUR CAST IS THE
GREATEST OF ALL TIME ¶
¶ BUT WE ALL KNOW THAT THE FIRST
CAST WAS THE BEST ¶
¶ AND BECAUSE OF THEM
WE GOT FOUR YEARS OF EDDIE MURPHY,
EIGHT YEARS OF WILL FORTE ¶
¶ FIVE YEARS OF JAN HOOKS AND GILDA,
SIX OF VICTORIA, 11 OF
CHASE ¶
¶ THREE YEARS OF MELANIE HUTSELL,
MICHAEL McKEON CRUSHED
IT IN TWO ¶
¶ ONE IN BILLY CRYSTAL, SIX OF DENNIS MILLER,
EIGHT OF HARVEY
THE GLUE ¶
¶ SEVEN YEARS OF,
FIVE YEARS
TERRY AND QUINN,
Four of Kazurinsky and Cleghorne
11 OF ARMISEN ¶
¶ 14 YEARS OF DAVIS AND ANDY,
Schiller and Smigel, 25
18 of Audrey Dickman and Davey Wilson
Plus Eamon and Dicso and Bobby Van Ry
30 YEARS OF DOWNEY,
45 YEARS OF LORNE ¶
¶ SIX YEARS OF OUR BOY FARLEY,
FIVE OF OUR BUDDY NORM ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF ONE OF US GETTING TO SAY
LIVE FROM NEW YORK, IT'S
SATURDAY NIGHT ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF STANDING ON HOME BASE
WAVING GOOD NIGHT AND
GOODBYE ¶
¶ 50 YEARS OF THE BEST TIMES OF
OUR LIVES ¶¶
THANK YOU, LORNE!
NY 1975
HOT
YOUR HOT DOGS AND HEROIN HERE.
>> HELLO, KIND SIR.
WE JUST MOVED HERE FROM THE
SMALL TOWNS WE GREW UP IN.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE BOTH YOUNG AND OF THE SAME AGE,
WITH DREAMS OF MAKING IT
BIG HERE IN NEW YORK CITY.
>> YOU'RE MOVING TO NEW YORK
NOW?
IT'S 1975.
NEW YORK IS DYING.
IT'S A BANKRUPT HELL HOLE.
>> OH, IT IS?
WELL, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> NO.
WE'RE POETS AND DREAMERS,
AND
NEW YORK CAN WHERE WE BELONG.
SO ONE HOT DOG WITH HEROIN,
PLEASE.
>> VERY WELL.
HOT DOG AND HEROIN,
TELL THESE BOYS
WHAT NEW YORK CITY IS ALL
ABOUT.
¶ BABY LOOK AT ME,
AND TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE ¶
¶ THIS OLD CITY IS GOING TO
HELL ¶
¶ URINE IS ALL YOU CAN SMELL ¶
¶ FAME,
YOU'RE GOING TO GET SHOT IN A TAXI,
YOU'RE GOING TO STABBED ON THE TRAIN ¶
AGAIN
¶ THE PRESIDENT --
BABY REMEMBER THE GAME ¶
>> WHOA, WHERE ARE WE NOW, JOHN?
>> IT'S THE 1980s.
WE'RE AT A POWER LUNCH ON WALL
STREET.
>> OH, NEW YORK IS FINE NOW?
>> IF YOU'RE WHITE, YES.
IT'S ALL THANKS TO THE BOOM ON
THE STOCK MARKET
AND A NEW DIET
THAT'S BEEN SWEEPING THE CITY.
COCAINE AND SOME VODKA.
WHAT A WONDERFUL FAME.
COCAINE AND SOME VODKA,
IT'S HOW THE METS WIN THEIR GAMES.
¶ NO SLEEPING,
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS ¶
¶ IT'S THE POWER MIX
THAT SHRINKS YOUR DICK ¶
¶ COCAINE AND VODKA ¶
¶ VODKA,
WOW. I THINK KINSEY IS GOING TO BE
PSYCHED.
>> WON'T IT MAKE IT HARDER FOR
ARTISTS LIKE ME TO LIVE HERE?
>> IT WILL.
AND AS WE ENTER THE '90s,
TIMES
SQUARE WILL BE TRANSFORMED FROM
PIMPS AND PHOTOGRAPHERS
TO
SOMETHING FILTHIER, CARTOON
MASCOTS.
BUT THE OLD GUARD WILL NOT GO
QUIETLY.
¶ LOOK DOWN, LOOK DOWN,
YOU'RE STANDING IN MY GRAVE ¶
¶ LOOK DOWN YOU FOOL,
I HAVE SERVED ¶
PIMPS
SCUM
LIFE
FLESH
POSE
SEX
PERVERT
SEE
¶ BUT LOOK, IT'S
IT'S  THE ONE WHO
WILL UNITE THEM,
THE ONE
CHARACTER IN TIMES SQUARE WHOSE
FAMILY FRIENDLY BUT ALSO A PROSTITUTE,
THE GREEN M&M.
¶ I DREAMED A DREAM
AND I WAS HIGH ON METH
AND SKITTLES ¶
¶ SO DIFFERENT THAN IT USED TO BE,
SO DIFFERENT FROM THIS HELL
I'M LIVING ¶
¶ SO DIFFERENT NOW THAT IT USED TO BE,
BUT JULIE KILLED THE
DREAM I DREAMED ¶
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, RUDY GIULIANI,
HERE IN POST-9/11 NEW YORK, THE
CITY HAS RALLIED LIKE NEVER
BEFORE.
>> RUDY, RUDY, YOU'RE AMERICA'S
MAYOR.
YOU'RE BELOVED ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY,
THIS IS YOUR BIG SHOT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO WITH
IT?
>> SIMPLE.
I AM THROWING AWAY MY SHOTS.
I AM THROWING MY SHOTS.
LIKE CITY
AND I AM THROWING AWAY MY SHOTS.
EVERYBODY
CRYSTAL
BEN
GULIANI
¶ RISE UP,
- I'LL PLANT THE THIEVES,
AND RISE UP, GETTING CRAZY,
GOING TO RISE
UP ¶
- TILL
WISE UP
BURN UP
AND JUST LIKE A CITY,
PLEASE
HE IS GOING AWAY,
- I AM THROWING AWAY ¶
>> THEN AFTER MICHAEL BLOOMBERG
TOOK NEW YORK TO NEW HEIGHTS.
>> IN TERMS OF HOW UNAFFORDABLE
IT BECAME.
>> GREAT IMPRESSION.
AND SYLVIE BLASIO BROUGHT US
UNIVERSAL DI CARE.
NICE
ADAMS
SWAG
>> YEAH, THAT RIGHT.
HOMELESS DUDES WANT TO PUSH
PEOPLE ON TO THE SUBWAY TRACK,
THEY GOT IT.
>> SOMEHOW NEW YORK TODAY FEELS
LIKE IT'S BACK IN THE '70s,
BACK
ON SKID ROW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SKID ROW.
>> OH MY GOD, WHO HIT YOU,
COLIN?
>> NO.
NOT THIS TIME.
YOU SEE, THERE IS A NEW MENACE
ON THE STREETS OF OUR CITY.
¶ SUDDENLY E-BIKES,
THEY'RE FLYING AROUND ME,
HOP ON THE SIDEWALK
BUT
AND SUDDENLY E-BIKES,
THEY'RE TRYING TO KILL YOU,
IT'S LIKE FROM MIDNIGHT IES ¶
ALCOHOL
>> THEN WHY EVEN LIVE IN NEW
YORK ANYMORE?
IT'S TOO LOUD, IT'S TOO
DANGEROUS.
THEY GIVES RATS FREE BIRTH
CONTROL, BUT NOT HUMAN WOMEN?
I MEAN, IF THIS IS WHAT NEW YORK
IS, I'M OUT.
>> WAIT, PETE, AND WHERE DID
SPADE GO, BY THE WAY ?
>> OH, HE SAT BACK DOWN IN THE
AUDIENCE.
>> YEAH, I GOT A FEEL FOR IT.
>> PETE
>> PETE, BEFORE YOU TURN YOUR
BACK ON NEW YORK, REMEMBER WHAT
THIS CITY GAVE YOU.
>> HERPES?
>> NO, THIS CITY DIDN'T GIVE YOU
THAT.
REMEMBER HOW THE CITY INSPIRED
YOU.
JUST BECAUSE THE ART SCENE AND
THE MUSIC SCENE ARE DEAD
AND THE
CITY IS A BUNCH OF TD BANKS AND
YOU CAN'T JUST GIVE UP.
I'M JUST ASKING YOU, NAY, ALL OF US HERE,
TO STILL BELIEVE IN THE
POWER OF NEW YORK,
AND TO GIVE
THE CITY WE LOVE --
¶ ONE DAY MORE,
ANOTHER DESTINY ¶
¶ STILL HAVING A HORSE AND
CARRIAGE, HOW CAN IT BE ¶
¶ EVEN THOUGH IT'S FULL OF GUNS,
THERE IS NO PLACE I WOULD SPEND
MY TIME ¶
¶ I WOULD NOT LIVE ANOTHER
PLACE ¶
>> YES.
¶ THOUGH WE CANNOT AFFORD
APARTMENTS ¶
¶ ONE DAY MORE,
WE WILL SURROUND
¶ OUR RISE TO POWER MERELY --
>> ONE DAY MORE ¶
¶ REVOLUTION,
HOW TO STOP THE VIOLENT CRIME,
MOST CITIES DON'T
HAVE MOLE PEOPLE,
HERE IT
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME ¶
¶ I DREAMED A DREAM THAT KING KONG DIED,
THEN I REMEMBERED
HE'S IN FLORIDA ¶
¶ I PLACE IS HERE,
I FIGHT WITH YOU ¶
¶ TOMORROW WE'LL DISCOVER
WHAT OUR CITY HAS IN STORE,
ONE MORE DAWN
ONE MORE DAY,
ONE DAY MORE
DEAD
ALEC
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
I'M ALEX BALDWIN.
I SHOULD HAVE CORRECTED YOU
ABOUT THAT A LONG TIME AGO.
I'M HERE TO INTRODUCE SOME OF
THE BEST COMMERCIAL PARODIES
TO
EVER APPEAR ON "SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE."
I'M ALSO LIKE TO THANK THE FINE
FOLKS WHO ARE SPONSORING THIS
SEGMENT.
ARE YOU HAVING TROUBLE FALLING
ASLEEP?
AFTER UPDATE
NOTHING PUTS PEOPLE --
NOTHING PUTS PEOPLE TO SLEEP FASTER
THAN THE SKETCHES TO AIR AFTER
UPDATE.
WE ALSO THIRD YEAR VENEERS.
ARRIVED HERE WITH NO MONEY AND
GAFFED UP TEETH,
BY YEAR THREE,
YOU BETTER BELIEVE THEY'RE
GETTING THIRD YEAR VENEERS.
RIGHT, SAM?
>> YOU BET, ALEX.
>> JUST NEVER BITE INTO AN
APPLE.
AND NOW WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
HERE ARE SOME COMMERCIALS.
>> YOU JUST GO AHEAD, HAVE A
TALK WITH THE YOUR OLD GRANDMA.
YOU'RE STILL HAVING CONTROL
PROBLEMS, AREN'T YOU?
>> I DON'T FEEL CONFIDENT,
HARVEY.
>> COME WITH ME.
I'LL LET YOU IN ON A LITTLE
SECRET.
>> HERE WE ARE.
OOPS, I POOPED MY PANTS.
A LOT OF MILES THAT DAY
AND DOWNED A LOT OF DONUTS.
HAVE BEEN ON MY TRAY TABLE SINCE
I WAS A KID.
>> WELL, THERE IS FIBER AND
THERE IS HIGH FIBER.
>> COLON BLOW.
>> I THINK I GET THE PICTURE.
>> GET THE EDGE.
CHIA HEAD
>> HI, I'M MEL
FROM PALACE
WHERE YOU FIND
YOUR OWN TOWEL, YOU CUT YOUR OWN
STEAKS.
>> WILSON TRAP DOORS.
>> WATCH, THE BRITISH TOUPEE.
>> BUT CAN IT COPY YOUR AD?
THE XEROX 790 AD CHECK CAN.
>> WHY NOT SHARE THE MOST MOMENT
OF THEM ALL
WITH THE LOVE
TOILET.
>> THE CANON AE 1, A CANNON SO
SIMPLE,
EVEN STEVIE WONDER CAN
USE IT.
>> ROBOTS ARE EVERYWHERE.
AND THEY EAT ALL PEOPLE'S
MEDICINE FOR FUEL.
>> NOW THERE IS A COMPANY THAT
OFFERS COVERAGE AGAINST THE
UNFORTUNATE EVENT OF A ROBOT ATTACK,
OLD GLORY INSURANCE.
HAPPY FUN BALL
DISCONTINUE USE OF HAPPY FUN
BALL IF ANY OF THE FOLLOWING
OCCURS.
>> THIS MOTHER'S DAY, GIVE HER
SOMETHING THAT SAYS
I'M NOT A
WOMAN ANYMORE.
I'M A MOM.
JEANS
>> WITH TYLENOL P.M., I KNOW I'M
GOING GET A GOOD NIGHT SLEEP.
I SALIM THROUGH MY FIRST DUMP IN
THE MORNING.
>> DID YOU [ BLEEP ] THE BED?
NEW
NOW WITH ECSTASY.
>> NUTRAQUICK SUPPOSITORY.
ICE
>> JON HAMM'S JON HAMM.
>> CRYSTAL GRAVY.
>> BABY'S THING.
BABY'S TOUPEE.
>> TAMPON, MADE FOR A WOMAN BY A
REPUBLICAN.
>> IT'S A ROBOT AND IT CLEANS MY BUSINESS,
MY LADY BUSINESS, AND
I LIKE THAT.
>> USING BOSLEY'S BREAKTHROUGH TECHNIQUE,
HARVESTED FROM THE
MEZZANINE AND BROUGHT TO THE
HEAD.
>> THAT'S WHAT I CALL TACO.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT A TACO TOWN,
TACO, UNTIL WE ROLL IT UP IN A
BLUEBERRY PANCAKE.
TACO!
>> IT'S ALMOST PIZZA, PIZZA THAT
IS PRACTICALLY IN EVERY WAY
EXCEPT FOR A FEW KEY ONCE.
>> I'LL EAT IT.
>> NO!
NOT T
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> IS IT A B SHIRT?
>> IS IT A C SHIRT?
>> NO, A Z SHIRT.
>> FOR WHEN YOU REALIZE YOU LOVE
TAYLOR SWIFT.
>> BABE, WE NEED THOSE.
WHAT'S GOING ON BACK THERE?
[ BLEEP ] LOVE FUNCTION GUY.
>> YOU CAN'T SMOKE IN HERE, MAN.
>> YOU'RE SMOKING IN HERE.
CRACK
IVANKA
TOILET
OZEMPIC FOR RAMADAN.
- HEROIN
- EMETH
>> XANAX FOR GAY SUMMER
WEDDINGS.
>> FREEWAYS.
- NUVABLING
>> UNDERCOVER OFFICE POTTY.
>> BATHROOM COBRA.
>> ROGAINE.
TRIOPENIN
ROYAL DELUXE 2.
NOT TURKEY
>> WITH A SMILE THAT SAYS YUM.
>> INTRODUCING WELLS FOR
SENSITIVE LITTLE BOYS.
FISHER
>> YOU WANT TO DO THE COMMERCIAL
ANYMORE?
OKAY.
HE WANTS TO GO BACK TO THE WELL.
>> I AGREE.
I THINK NEEDS A VACATION.
>> HELLO.
>> HI, I'M BETTY.
>> WELCOME TO BRONX BEAT.
>> YES.
>> THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
EPISODE BECAUSE WE ARE COMING
FROM THE "SNL" 50th ANNIVERSARY
SHOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> OOH LA LA!
>> I AM SEEING SO MANY ICONS.
WHAT AN INCREDIBLE NIGHT.
>> WE GOT VERY FAMOUS PEOPLE IN
THE AUDIENCE.
ACTOR, ACTOR.
>> CONAN O'BRIEN.
>> ACTOR, ACTOR.
>> AND LOOK AT THIS GUY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HE'S A CUTIE.
HEY, HI.
>> WHO YOU?
>> HI, CUTIE.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M AN ACTOR.
>> OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HONEY, GET UP HERE.
COME ON.
HURRY UP.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
THE SHOW IS 30 MINUTES.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
SO TELL US YOUR NAME, HONEY, WHO
ARE YOU?
>> MILES TELLER.
>> OH, YOU'RE CUTE, MILES.
>> MILES, I LIKE YOUR SMILE.
>> MILES SMILES.
SO YOU'RE AN ACTOR.
SO WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, MILES, IF I
WAS AN ACTOR AND HAD TO KISS
SOMEONE IN A MOVIE,
I WOULD
IMMEDIATELY FALL IN LOVE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT VERY ROMANTIC.
>> IF MY JOB WERE TO BE IN
MOVIES AND DO LOVE SCENES, I'D
BE IN JAIL.
>> SO MILES, WE WANT TO KNOW
EVERY SINGLE LITTLE THING ABOUT
YOU.
HOW DID YOU GET YOUR START?
>> I CAUGHT THE ACTING BUG WHEN
I WAS A SOPHOMORE IN HIGH
SCHOOL.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
>> DON'T START THAT FAR BACK.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT KIND OF TIME.
>> YEAH, MILES, WE'RE NOT
IMMORTAL.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT DO WE KNOW YOU FROM?
>> WELL, I WAS IN "TOP GUN:
MAVERICK."
>> OH, THERE WE GO.
WE'VE SEEN THAT.
>> WE'VE SEEN THAT.
LOOK AT YOU.
LOOK AT YOU IN "TOP GUN 2".
>> IT'S ACTUALLY "TOP GUN:
MAVERICK."
>> OH, "TOP GUN 2."
>> "TOP GUN 2".
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU.
PROUD OF YOU IN "TOP GUN 2" WITH
TOM CRUISE.
>> WHO DID YOU PLAY?
WHO DID YOU PLAY?
>> I PLAYED ROOSTER.
>> OKAY, ROOSTER.
>> I REMEMBER YOU.
THAT WAS YOU PLAYING FOOTBALL ON
THE BEACH TUSSLING WITH TOM
CRUISE, HUH?
>> LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
YOU LIKE TO TUSSLE?
>> YOU LIKE TO TUSSLE?
YOU LIKE TO TUSSLE ON THE BEACH?
YOU A TUSSLER?
I BET YOU DO.
I BET YOU LIKE TO TUSSLE WITH
TOM CRUISE ON THE BEACH.
YOU LIKE TO TUSSLE?
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO.
>> COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO IN "TOP GUN
2.
>> "TOP GUN: MAVERICK."
>> I'VE NEVER GOING TO CALL IT
THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
- YOU CAN GO SIT DOWN, ROOSTER.
GOODBYE.
>> HE'S CUTE.
HE SHOULD BE AN ACTOR.
HE IS CUTE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE.
IT'S A VERY PACKED SHOW.
>> BETTY, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
YOU KNOW.
WE CAN GO GET SOME COFFEE OR
SOMETHING.
>> SOMEBODY TALKING ABOUT
COFFEE?
>> OH, MY GOSH,
WE'RE NOT WORTHY, WE'RE NOT WORTHY!
>> TOUCH MY MONKEY, TOUCH MY
MONKEY.
>> OKAY.
>> OH MY GOD, LOOK AT YOU,
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR STOPPING BY.
>> WELL, I WAS AT ZABAR'S
PICKING UP A NOODLE CUING KUGEL
THOUGHT I WOULD COME SEE THE
GIRLS.
BIG
LINDA, WE ARE THRILLED YOU'RE HERE.
YOU LOOK WONDERFUL.
>> THANK YOU.
BOTH OF YOU, YOU LOOK LIKE
BUTTER.
SKIN
>> MY GOD.
>> OH, COME ON, LOOK AT YOU.
TWO BIG STICKS OF BUTTER, THAT'S
WHAT YOU ARE.
>> WELL, I DO USE A SALVE ON MY
SKIN THAT IS MADE OF STEM CELLS
AND SNAIL MUCIN.
I THINK IT'S MADE OF SNAIL
SPERM.
SIX
>> GOOD FOR YOU, GOOD FOR YOU.
>> HOW IS OUR MUTUAL FRIEND PAUL
BALDWIN?
>> WELL, OUR DEAR FRIEND PAUL
BALDWIN IS IN THE CLINIC HERE IN
THE CITY.
HE'S GOT ADVANCED SPILLKEN CONNECTOR,
FLEW HIM UP FROM BOCA
RATON IN AN IRON LUNG.
>> WHAT A SHONDA.
POOR BALDWIN.
TERRIBLE
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW,
I'M GETTING A LITTLE VERKLEMPT.
TALK AMONGST YOURSELVES.
I'LL GIVE YOU A TOPIC.
PROFESSOR VERA WAS NEITHER
PROGRESSIVE NOR AN ERROR.
DISCUSS
OKAY.
THAT'S A GOOD WAY TO PULL
THROUGH.
THANKS, GOD, POOH-POOH POOH.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> IT'S BEEN A TOUGH YEAR.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I HAVE A HEMATOMA
INFACTORYUM.
MY ZORCH ARE ON FIRE.
I HAD TO HAVE IT MOVED FOUR
INCHES.
WHERE MY BELLY BUTTON USED TO
BE, I CAN'T WEAR BELMONTS.
>> YOUR STORE.ZORCH?
>> MY ZORCH.
>> YOUR WHAT?
ZORCH
>> I THINK HE MEANS THE DOWNTOWN AREA.
- YES
SIT UPS
WHO
>> YOU IN KNOW WHAT I WANT TO
DO, SIT DOWN.
- EXACTLY
YOU KNOW WHO LIKES SITTING DOWN?
MY STUPID HUSBAND.
- HERE WE GO
>> YEAH, I HEARD ABOUT THE
HUSBAND.
>> ALL HE DOES IS SIT AROUND AND
WATCH OUTLANDER RERUNS ON STARZ.
DUMB
VERKLEMPT
>> HERE IT COMES.
STUPID, BUT I LOVE HIM SO MUCH.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> GIVE ME MY FOUR CHILDREN.
I WANT THEM TO LIVE FOREVER.
>> YOU BETTER PRAY HE DOESN'T.
NEVER GOING TO SAY
HIS SPLUNK
IS --
DOINK
VER
TOO
>> EVERYBODY TRY, MY SSRIs MUST
BE BOOMING BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL
A THING.
SHELL
>> CAN I JUST SAY SOMETHING?
CAN I JUST SAY SOMETHING?
WE'RE ALL MIRACLES.
MAYBE THE SECRET OF LIFE IS THAT
THERE ARE NO BIG WHOOPS,
ONLY A
SERIES OF SMALL AGONIZING
WHOOPS.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, LINDA.
>> BRING IT IN.
>> YOU ARE SO RIGHT, LINDA.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE WHOLE WORLD IS GOING TO BLOW
UP.
- WHO CARES. SMOKE
- EXACTLY
HAVE A GLASS OF WINE.
HAVE TWO GLASSES OF WINE.
WHO CARES.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE SHOULD GO FOR A GLASS OF
WINE.
RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
BAD NEWS, IT'S RAINING.
BUT GOOD NEWS, IT'S SWEATER
WEATHER.
SWEATER WEATHER!
FAVOURITE
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME
WINE.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN WHAT
Medley of "Uproar", "Lollipop", "6 Foot 7 Foot", "Mrs. Officer", and "A Milli"
What the fuck, though? Where the love go?
Five, four, three, two, I let one go
¶ BOW, GET THE F- THOUGH
I DON'T BLUFF, BRO
AIMING AT YOUR HEAD
LIKE A BUFFALO ¶
¶ YOU A ROUGHNECK
I'M A CUTTHROAT
YOU'RE A TOUGH GUY
THAT'S ENOUGH JOKES ¶
¶ THEN THE SUN DIE
THE NIGHT IS YOUNG THOUGH
THE DIAMONDS STILL SHINE
GET IT ROUGH ¶
WHAT THE F- THOUGH
WHERE THE LOVE GO ¶
¶ FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO
I LET ONE GO
¶ BOW, GET THE F- THOUGH
I DON'T BLUFF, BRO
AIMING AT YOUR HEAD
LIKE A BUFFALO ¶
¶ SHE LICK ME
LIKE A LOLLIPOP
¶ SHORTY WANT A THUG
BOTTLES IN THE CLUB
Shawty wanna hump
You know I love to touch her lovely lady lumps
HE LIKE A LOLLIPOP
Shawty want a thug
Bottles in the club
Shawty wanna hump
You know I love to touch her lovely lady lumps
¶ SHE EVEN WEAR HER HAIR LIKE MINE,
BUT MAN, SHE NEVER HAD A
LOVE LIKE MINE ¶
FEEL RIGHT
MOVE
¶ I NEVER SEEN A BODY LIKE
HERS ¶
¶ THAT BODY ERR LOVE FOR WORD ¶
¶ I TOLD HER TO BACK IT UP,
SHE MADE IT JUMP ¶¶
THAT'S WHEN SHE --
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY ¶
Excuse my charisma, vodka with a spritzer
Swagger down pat, call my shit Patricia
Young Money militia, and I am the commissioner
You don't want start Weezy, 'cause the F is for Finisher
So misunderstood, but what's a World without enigma?
¶ TWO WOMEN AT THE SAME TIME,
SYNCHRONIZED SWIMMING ¶
Got the girl twisted
'cause she open when you twist her
¶ I NEVER MET THE GIRL, BUT I
LIKE I MISSED HER ¶
Life is the bitch, and death is her sister
Sleep is the cousin, what a f-ckin' family picture
You know father time,
¶ WE ARE NO MOTHER NATURE,
IT'S ALL IN THE FAMILY, I GOT NO
RELATION ¶
¶ NO MATTER WHO'S BUYING, I'M A
CELEBRATION,
BLACK AND WHITE
DIAMONDS ¶
F-ck that shit, my money up, you n-ggas just Honey Nut
Young Money running shit and you n-ggas just runner-ups
¶ I DON'T FEEL LIKE I'VE DONE ENOUGH,
so I'ma keep on doing this shit
Lil Tunechi or Young Tunafish
When I get up all in ya
We can hear the angels calling us
We can see the sunrise before us
And when I'm in that thang, I'll make that body sang
Doing a buck in the latest drop
I got stopped by a lady cop
she got me thinking
I COULD DATE A COP ¶
¶ 'CAUSE HER UNIFORM
FITS HER SO TIGHT
SHE READ ME MY RIGHTS ¶
¶ SHE PUT ME IN HER CAR
SHE CUT OFF ALL THE LIGHTS
SHE SAID I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT ¶
¶ NOW I GOT HER HOLLERING
SOUNDING LIKE A SIREN
TALKING 'BOUT
¶ AND I KNOW SHE THE LAW
AND SHE KNOW I'M THE BOSS
AND SHE KNOW I GET HIGH
ABOVE THE LAW ¶
¶ AND SHE KNOW I'M RAW
SHE KNOW I'M FROM THE STREETS
AND ALL SHE WANT ME TO DO
IS F- THE POLICE ¶
¶ WHEN I GET UP ALL IN YOU
WE CAN HEAR THE
ANGELS CALLING US ¶
¶ WE CAN SEE
THE SUNRISE BEFORE US
AND WHEN I'M IN THAT THANG ¶
¶ I'LL MAKE THAT BODY SING
I'LL MAKE IT SAY
Like a cop car
I'LL MAKE YA SAY ¶
I'M A YOUNG MONEY MILLIONAIRE
TOUGHER THAN NIGERIAN HAIR ¶
¶ MY CRITERIA COMPARED
TO YOUR CAREER
I'm a venereal disease like a menstrual bleed
AND LEAK ON THE SHEET ¶
¶ OF THE TABLET IN MY MIND
'CAUSE I DON'T WRITE --
CAUSE I AIN'T GOT TIME ¶
Cause my seconds, minutes, hours go to the almighty dollar
¶ AND THE ALMIGHTY POWER
OF THAT CH-CH-CH-CHOPPER
SISTER, BROTHER
SON, DAUGHTER ¶
¶ FATHER, MOTHER
Got the Maserati dancing on the bridge, pussy poppin'
¶ YOU CAN'T CATCH 'EM
YOU CAN'T STOP 'EM
I GO BY THEM GOON RULES ¶
¶ IF YOU CAN'T BEAT 'EM
THEN YOU POP 'EM
YOU CAN'T MAN 'EM
THEN YOU MOP 'EM ¶
¶ YOU CAN'T STAND 'EM
THEN YOU DROP 'EM
YOU POP 'EM 'CAUSE ¶
¶ WE POP 'EM LIKE
ORVILLE REDENBACHER
MILLION
SICILIAN WITH LONG HAIR ¶
¶ WITH COKE IN HER DERRIERE
LIKE SMOKE IN
THE THINNEST AIR ¶
¶ I OPEN THE LAMBORGHINI
HOPIN' THEM GUYS SEE ME
LIKE LOOK AT
THAT BASTARD WEEZY ¶
¶ HE'S A BEAST
HE'S A DOG
HE'S A MOTHER -- PROBLEM ¶
¶ OKAY, YOU'RE A GOON
BUT WHAT'S A GOON
TO A GOBLIN ¶¶
THANK YOU.
HAPPY 50th.
CELEBRATE
WE MUST ALSO TAKE A
MOMENT TO HONOR THOSE WHO WE'VE
LOST.
COUNTLESS MEMBERS OF THE "SNL"
FAMILY TAKEN FROM US TOO SOON.
I'M TALKING OF COURSE "SNL"
CHARACTERS AND SKETCHES
THAT
HAVE AGED HORRIBLY.
BUT EVEN THOUGH THESE CHARACTERS, ACCENTS
AND LET'S
JUST CALL THEM ETHNIC WIGS
WERE
UNQUESTIONABLY IN POOR TASTE,
YOU ALL LAUGHED AT THEM.
SO IF ANYONE SHOULD BE CANCELED,
SHOULDN'T IT BE YOU, THE
AUDIENCE?
SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT.
ANY WAY, WE NOW PRESENT TO YOU THIS
IN MEMORIAM.
ETHNIC
TELL
NAFTA
YOUR JOB, HE HE HE.
CARP
BEL
HAR
>> HEY, EXCUSE ME.
THIS IS GETTING OUT OF HAND.
LIKE
FOOD
>> WHY DON'T YOU DROP OUT OF
THAT GREEN JUMPSUIT AND SHOW ME
THAT FAT ASS.
>> HEY, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
ADJOIN TO THE JANITOR'S CLOSET,
DROP TROU AND SEE IF WE CAN MAKE
BABY?
CLOAKING
UNDERAGE
PAUL
WHOA
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THIS IS MY
LUCKY DAY.
I'LL TAKE THE RAPIST FOR 200.
>> THAT'S THERAPIST.
>> LOOK AT MY BUM, I LOOK AT
YOUR BUM.
>> I MADE A LITTLE DIARY TO SHOW
EVERYBODY HOW IT IS TO  BE A
HOST HERE.
>> I MADE MY GRANDMOTHER'S
SPECIAL RECIPE FOR COCKER
SPANIEL.
PRIME RIB
I KNOW IT'S NOT YOUR FIRST
CHOICE, BUT KEEP IN MIND
YOU'RE
A DOLL.
ANIMAL
UNCLE
SHAMING
>> JANE, YOU IGNORANT SLUT!
SLUT SHAMING
>> GUYS DANCING WITH GUYS, GIRLS
DANCING WITH GIRLS,
GUYS THAT
LOOKS LIKE GIRLS DANCING WITH
GIRLS.
THEY
>> YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT GAY
IS.
AUF
HIT
>> I DIDN'T LIKE IT THE FIRST
TIME WHEN IT WAS CALLED CHASING
AMY.
SHUT
AFFLEC
>> RUN, THROW, AND CATCH LIKE A
GIRL.
OLYMPICS.
>> THE WINNER IS.
HISS
>> IT SHOULD BE NOTED THAT THAT
JOKE WAS WRITTEN BY A WOMAN.
NO, JUST KIDDING.
WE DON'T HIRE WOMEN.
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS FOR EVERYONE,
EXPECT NEW JERSEY!
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WELCOME
CHU
>> WELCOME TO CELEBRITY BATTLE
OF THE SEXES AND RACES.
SIMPSON
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE A BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN.
>> ROBERT BLAKE,
PUFF DADDY.
>> DON'T JUDGE A BOOK BY ITS
COVER.
>> MY MAN IS LIKE R. KELLY.
>> THANK YOU TO R. KELLY.
>> I'M JARED VOGEL FROM SUBWAY.
>> WHITE TRASH.
JUNGLE BUNNY.
>> HONKY!
>> SPADE.
>> HONKY HONKY.
[ BLEEP ] [ BLEEP ].
DEAD HONKY.
HI
>> HI, DREW.
>> HI.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW YOU KNEW EYO.
>> JUST MET IN THE BATHROOM.
CRAWLED UNDER HER STALL.
>> MY KIND OF GAL.
>> WHAT A NIGHT TO CELEBRATE.
>> I KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IS THERE A BARTENDER HERE?
>> WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S A
CELEBRATION.
I'M THINKING SOME BUBBLY.
>> I LOVE THAT YEAH, IT'S GREAT.
>> HERE YOU GO, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT!
PARTY!
EX-OFFICIAL.
>> HAVE YOU SEEN THE LATEST
STUDY ON ALCOHOL?
EVEN ONE DRINK CAN SIGNIFICANTLY
SLASH LIFE EXPECTANCY.
¶ YOU'RE ENJOYING YOUR DAY,
EVERYTHING GOING YOUR WAY,
THEN
ALONG COMES DEBBIE DOWNER ¶
¶ TELL YOU ABOUT A NEW DISEASE,
A CAR ACCIDENT OR A KILLER
BEES ¶
SPARE
¶ BUT YOU CAN'T STOP DEBBIE
DOWNER ¶
>> OKAY, I THINK SOMETIMES YOU
JUST GOT TO CELEBRATE.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS SUCH A
SPECIAL NIGHT.
>> I AGREE.
TO "SNL," TO ANOTHER 50 YEARS!
>> CHEERS!
>> LET'S HOPE HUMANITY LASTS
THAT LONG.
AT THIS POINT, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE GOING THE WAY OF THE WHITE
RHINO.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> THERE ARE ONLY TWO LEFT IN CAPTIVITY,
AND THEY'RE BOTH
FEMALE.
>> WELL, HERE IS A TOAST TO ALL
OF THE FRIENDS WE'VE MADE,
BOTH
OLD AND NEW.
>> HEY, AMEN TO THAT.
>> HEY, JUST A HEADS UP, WE
DON'T HAVE ANY EGGS.
>> WHAT?
>> WHY WOULD WE WANT EGGS?
>> BIRD FLU IS ON THE RAMPAGE.
MILLIONS OF  S S OF FOWL HAVE A
BEEN CULLED.
>> DEBBIE, WE'RE TRYING TO HAVE
FUN, OKAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE FIVE.
>> BELIEVE ME, I'D LOVE TO SIT
DOWN.
MY RIGHT FOOT IS THROBBING.
PRETTY SURE IT'S MY OLD FRIEND
GOUT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, BOBBY!
>> NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> EXCUSE ME, I'M SUCH A BIG
FAN.
>> IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
CAN I HAVE A TEQUILA AND A SODA
WITH A STRAW?
>> YOU TALKING TO ME?
YOU TALKING TO ME?
>> IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE A
JOKE?
>> NO, I'M ASKING, I HAVE DRY EYE,
AND IT'S HARD TO DISCERN IF
YOU WERE TALKING TO ME.
>> JUST GIVE ME A DRINK.
>> OKAY, SURE.
COMING RIGHT UP.
HERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO WITH THAT.
THERE YOU GO.
KIND OF SURPRISE YOU'D WANT A
STRAW.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> MICROPLASTIC.
AT THIS POINT, WE'RE ALL WALKING
LANDFILLS.
>> ODDS ARE THEY'VE ALREADY
TAKEN UP RESIDENCE IN YOUR
TESTES.
>> DEBORAH, I'M GOING TO TALK NOW,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO SHUT
IT.
I DO NOT APPRECIATE THIS
CONVERSATION.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
PLASTIC IN MY BALLS.
I WANT TO LAUGH AND FEEL JOY
AND HAVE A SLIVER OF HOPE FOR THREE
GODDAMN HOURS OF MY LIFE.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
I CAME HERE TONIGHT TO GET A
LITTLE FRIGGING BREAK FROM OUR
WORLD RIGHT NOW,
WHICH IS LIKE
LIVING UNDER A -- IN A FULL
DIAPER.
>> DIAPERS ARE A LEADING CULPRIT
IN THE MICROPLASTIC SAGA.
>> BOBBY, BOBBY, BOB,
IT'S ALL WORKING.
SHE THINK SHE IS HELPING, OKAY?
MY KIDS THINK THE BEST OF YOU.
>> SPEAKING OF KIDS, IT'S
OFFICIAL.
I CAN'T HAVE CHILDREN.
BUT I TOLD YOU THAT ONCE,
JIMMY.
>> YEAH, DID YOU?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, DEBBIE,
JIMMY'S RIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US IN A
TOAST.
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
LET ME GET MY DRINK.
>> TO LAUGHTER, TO FRIENDSHIP,
AND TO 50 YEARS!
>> AND TO CONTINUING ADVANCES IN
CURING FELINE AIDS.
IT'S THE NUMBER ONE KILLER OF
DOMESTIC CATS.
¶ NO, YOU CAN'T STOP DEBBIE
DOWNER ¶
>>> ALL RIGHT, YOU KNUCKLEHEAD,
LISTEN UP.
I BET YOU THINK ROBBING A
CONVENIENCE STORE IS PRETTY
BOSS, YEAH?
>> WHATEVER, MAN.
>> YOU MAY THINK IT'S ONE BIG
JOKE, BUT IT'S NOT.
IT'S WHY I INVITED
REPRESENTATIVES FROM THE SCARED
STRAIGHT PROGRAM.
THEY'RE INMATES AT THE LARCHMONT
MAXIMUM SECURITY PRISON
AND HERE
TO WARN YOU OF A DANGEROUS CRIMINAL
LIFESTYLE.
MAC
GET IN HERE!
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE WE COME.
>> ON YOUR FEET!
>> SIT YOUR ASSES DOWN!
>> SIT DOWN BEFORE I KILL
SOMEBODY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MY NAME IS LORENZO MACINTOSH.
>> AND MY NAME IS ALL THE WAY
RAY MAY.
I DON'T DO NOTHING HALFWAY.
>> WHAT YOU IN HERE FOR, CHIEF?
>> LET ME GUESS, MANIPULATING
CRYPTO MARKET.
>> NO, NO, THAT'S A TERRIBLE
GUESS, NO.
I GOT THESE LITTLE BOZOS
SHOPLIFTING.
>> OH, SHOPLIFTING.
IT STARTS WITH SHOPLIFTING.
GUESS WHERE IT ENDS --
GENOCIDE!
>> WHAT?
BUT WAIT.
YOU BETTER LISTEN UP.
YOU THINK YOU TOUGH, HUH?
YOU REAL STREET?
>> WELL, GUESS WHAT?
WHEN I WAS A BOY,
I WATCHED BOTH
MY PARENTS DIE ON THESE STREETS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THE FAMILY THAT ADOPTED HIM
MADE HIM SLEEP UNDER THE
STAIRCASE.
>> UNTIL ONE DAY I GOT A LETTER
FROM AN OWL TELLING ME
I HAD TO
REPORT TO SOME KIND OF SCHOOL
FOR WIZARDS.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT, HUH?
YOU AND HERMIONE HAVE TO STOP
WHO MUST NOT BE NAMED
BEFORE HE
GETS HIS HANDS ON THE SORCERER'S
STONE?
REAL
>> THAT'S DEFINITELY HARRY
POTTER.
SHUT YOUR DAMN MOUTH.
>> YOUR MIND.
IN PRISON THERE WILL BE A DUDE
ENTERING YOUR CHAMBER OF
SECRETS.
MAYBE SLYTHERIN RIGHT INTO YOUR
ASS-KA-BAN.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE IN
HOGWARTS.
THERE WILL BE WARTS ON YOUR HOG.
>> COME ON, HUFFLEPUFF IT.
>> THE DUDE I DESCRIBE AS
SERIOUS BLACK
IS GOING TO WAVE
HIS WAND IN YOUR FACE
AND SAY
EXPECTO FELLATIO.
NO
COME ON
FELLATIO
>> GOOD LORD, FELLOWS.
>> WELL DONE, CHIEF.
WE STEPPED ON THE LINE.
THAT'S A TWO POINT SHOT.
>> NOW WHICH ONE OF YOU ALL IS
THE RINGLEADER?
>> WHAT I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS
NATIONAL RAT OUT A LATINO DAY.
>> ON YOUR DAMN FEET.
>> LOOK AT THEM PRETTY BROWN
EYES.
THEY'RE GOING LOVE YOU IN
PRISON, ARIANNA PEQUENO.
WHY YOU SHOPLIFT?
>> I WAS TRYING TO IMPRESS MY
GIRLFRIEND.
SHE THICK AS HELL.
>> YOU THINK I'M GOING TO TRY
THOSE?
START WITH A 400 POUND
PROFESSOR, HUH?
AND I FELL IN LOVE WITH JADA
PINKETT?
BUT HE WAS ASHAMED OF HIS WEIGHT
SO HE DRANK A SERUM THAT TURNED
HIM INTO BUDDY LOVE.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
THEN YOU GO THROUGH A DEN AND REALIZE
THAT EVERYBODY AT THE
TABLE IS THE SAME PERSON.
BECAUSE THIS IS REAL!
>> YO, OKAY, THAT'S ALMOST
CERTAINLY "THE NUTTY PROFESSOR."
WANT
GOING TO BOTH GET.
SHUT
>> PRISON, YOU'LL BE PROFESSOR
YOUR LOVE OF NUTS ALL RIGHT,
BUT
YOU WON'T BE LOSING NO 200
POUNDS.
YOU'LL BE GAINING 9 INCHES.
>> SEE THEY GIVE YOU A
POSSESSION, MUSCLE RELAXANTS.
YOU'LL BE HANDLING SO MANY DUDES AT ONCE,
THEY'LL ALL BE CHEERING
AT THE SAME TIME,
HERCULES,
HERCULES.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT, NO.
I LET THAT GO WAY TOO LONG
BECAUSE OPTIMISM A FAN OF THE
FILM.
COME ON.
THESE ARE CHILDREN.
FELLOWS ALL RIGHT?
30-YEAR-OLD CHILDREN.
COME ON.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
OKAY
>> NO ONE ELSE IS WEARING THEIR
SPRING UNIFORM.
>> WHO THE HELL IS THIS GUY?
>> THAT'S BIG RED.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY CALL ME BIG RED.
>> BECAUSE OF YOUR HAIR?
>> NO, BECAUSE I'M WELL READ.
I GOT SIX GEDs AND A NAGGING UTI,
AND I'D LIKE TO OFFER A
COUNTERPOINT.
PRISON IS ACTUALLY REALLY FUN.
I'M IN AN IMPROV GROUP,
I'M SCRAPBOOKING LIKE CRAZY.
OUTSIDE I NEVER USED TO GET
LAID.
NOW I'M HAVING SEX 50, 60 TIMES
A DAY.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
>> YEAH, BUT DON'T LET ALL OF
THAT FOOL YOU.
THIS MAN IS TOUGH AS NAILS.
>> TOUGH AS PRESS-ON NAILS.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE THAT, BUSTER.
>> TELL HIM YOUR STORY, RED.
>> WELL, YOU SEE, I WAS
ABANDONED AS A BABY.
GOT MY HUMAN PARENTS.
SO I WAS FORCED TO GROW UP AT
THE NORTH POLE.
AND YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO SKIP
AHEAD TO ELF.
I'M GOING TO TALK ABOUT ELF.
BUT GUESS WHAT!
THIS IS REAL.
THIS IS ELF.
I MEAN, REAL!
SO YOU WERE AN ELF?
I KNEW YOU WERE A LITTLE BITCH.
TRIED
MOTHER
>> THAT'S THE NIGHT THE LIGHTS
WENT OUT IN GEORGIA.
>> YOU BETTER KEEP YOUR DAMN
MOUTH SHUT.
>> IN PRISON, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE NAMED ELF
BUDDY
NO
YOU'RE GOING TO GET ELFED.
IN YOUR BUTT.
>> I'M TRYING, I'M TRYING.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S RIGHT.
AND FORGET ABOUT YOUR NUT
HOLE.
WHAT YOU NEED TO BE WORRYING
ABOUT IS YOUR SOUTH POLE,
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE YELLING SON OF
A NUTCRACKER, ALL RIGHT?
AND IT WON'T BE NO SANTA COMING
TO TOWN.
IT WILL BE SANTOS COMING IN YOUR
BROWN.
>> NO, NO!
GET OUT OF HERE.
LET'S GO.
ALL THREE.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
RED, COME ON.
WE GOT TO GO.
RED, GET WE GOT TO GO.
BOY
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT WOULD BE
HELPFUL, YOU KNOW.
>> ASK WHAT I CAN DO FOR YOU.
>> COME ON, ENOUGH.
IT'S TOO MUCH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>>> HELLO, Y'ALL.
I AM JARED MAURICE!
WAIT A MINUTE, ARE THERE ANY
COPS IN THE AUDIENCE?
I AM GARRETT MORRIS, OKAY,
AND WAY BACK THERE, WHEN I JOINED
THE CAST OF "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE,"
I HAD NO IDEA, Y'ALL,
THAT I WOULD BE REQUIRED
TO DO
SO MANY REUNION SHOWS.
BUT HERE I AM, OKAY.
NOW, THIS FILM YOU'RE GOING TO SEE,
IT'S A GREAT FILM MADE BY
MY MAN TOM SCHILLER, YEAH.
IN 1978, AND IT FEATURES THE
ENTIRE CAST.
SO SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND ENJOY LOOK BACK IN ANGER.
>> I GUESS THIS IS MY STOP.
BELUSHI
ANGER
>> I THOUGHT I'D BE THE FIRST TO GO.
I WAS ONE OF THOSE LIVE FAST
DIE YOUNG, GOOD-LOOKING CORPSE
TYPES.
WELL, I GUESS THEY WERE WRONG.
HERE THEY ARE, ALL MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS NOT READY FOR PRIME TIME
CEMETERY.
OH, NO.
GILDA RADNER
TELEVISION
FOR YEARS AND YEARS,
THE GILDA RADNER SHOW.
WELL, AT LEAST NOW I CAN SEE HER
ON RERUNS.
GOD BLESS HER.
HERE IS WHERE LARAINE IS.
THEY SAY SHE MURDERED HER DEJ
HUSBAND.
THEN MOVED TO THE VALLEY IN
CALIFORNIA AND HAD PECAN FARMS.
SHE WAS A BIG ONE WHEN SHE DIED.
JANE CURTAIN,
SHE MARRIED A STOCKBROKER, HAD TWO CHILDREN,
MOVED UPSTATE NEW YORK.
SHE DIED OF COMPLICATIONS DURING
COSMETIC SURGERY.
GARRETT MORRIS.
APPARENTLY GARRETT LEFT THE SHOW
AND WORKED IN THE BLACK THEATER
FOR YEARS.
AND THEN HE DIED OF AN OVERDOSE
OF HEROIN.
HERE IS BILL MURRAY.
HE LIVED THE LONGEST.
38 YEARS.
HE WAS HAPPY WHEN HE DIED,
THOUGH.
HE JUST GROWN HIS MUSTACHE BACK.
PROBABLY STILL GROWING.
OH, AND HERE IS CHEVY CHASE.
THE GUY HIS FIRST MOVIE WITH
GOLDIE HAWN.
OVER HERE IS DANNY ACKROYD.
I GUESS HE LOVED HIS HARLEY TOO
MUCH.
I CLOCKED HIM AT 175 MILES AN
HOUR BEFORE THE CRASH.
IT WAS A BLUR.
I GOT CALLED IN TO IDENTIFY HIS
BODY.
I RECOGNIZED HIM BY HIS WEBBED
TOES.
SATURDAY NIGHT SHOW WAS THE BEST
EXPERIENCE OF MY LIFE.
NOW THEY'RE ALL GONE.
I MISS EVERY ONE OF THEM.
WHY ME?
WHY DID I LIVE SO LONG?
THEY'RE ALL DEAD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
BECAUSE I'M A DANCER.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, SIR
PAUL McCARTNEY!
"Golden Slumbers"/"Carry That Weight"/"The End"
Once there was a way
TO GET BACK HOMEWARD ¶
¶ ONCE THERE WAS A WAY
TO GET BACK HOME ¶
¶ A SECRET DOOR, DO NOT CRY,
AND I WILL SING A LULLABY ¶
Golden slumbers
fill your eyes
Smiles awake you
when you rise
Sleep pretty darling do not cry
And I will sing a lullaby
¶ ONCE THERE WAS A WAY
TO GET BACK HOMEWARD ¶
¶ ONCE THERE WAS A WAY,
TO GET BACK HOME ¶
¶ SLEEP, PRETTY DARLING, DO NOT
CRY ¶
¶ AND I WILL SING YOU A
LULLABY ¶
¶ OH, YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY THAT WEIGHT
CARRY THE WAY LONG TIME ¶
¶ OH, YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY THAT WEIGHT,
CARRY THAT WEIGHT THE
LONG TIME ¶
¶ I NEVER GIVE YOU MY PILLOW,
I ONLY SEND MY INVITATIONS ¶
¶ AND IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
CELEBRATION
I PRAY THAT ¶
¶ OH YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY THAT WEIGHT,
CARRY THAT WEIGHT A LONG
TIME ¶
¶ BOY, YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY
THAT WEIGHT,
CARRY THAT
WEIGHT A LONG TIME ¶
¶ OH, YEAH, ALL RIGHT ¶
¶ ARE YOU GOING TO BE IN MY
DREAMS
TONIGHT ¶
¶ LOVE YOU, LOVE YOU, LOVE YOU,
LOVE YOU ¶
And in the end
The love you take
¶ IS EQUAL TO THE LOVE
YOU MAKE ¶
>> THANK YOU.
>>> IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT
TAKES TO MAKE A SHOW LIKE THIS
LAST FOR 50 YEARS,
SEE THESE
PEOPLE RIGHT AROUND ME, THE FIRST CAST,
LARAINE NEWMAN, JANE CURTAIN,
GARRETT AND CHEVY
CHASE.
THEY PAVED THE WAY FOR PEOPLE
LIKE DARREL HAMMOND, CHERI OTERI,
CHRIS KATTAN, JAY PHARAOH,
THE GREAT KENAN THOMPSON AND THE GREAT
BILLY CRYSTAL.
AND FINALL THE REASON WE'RE
ALL HERE, THE MAN WHO MADE OUR
DREAM COME TRUE,
THE ONE AND ONLY,
OH, AND PAUL.
LORNE MICHAELS!
WRITERS
WEEKS
BEST OF LUCK, WE CAN'T WAIT.
GOD KNOWS WE LOVE YOU ALL.
GOOD NIGHT AND GOD BLESS!