-Hi!
-Oh!
-Oh, no. No.
-Hello.
"Haircut" started based
on a real event in my life
where I shaved my head
and I found myself saying,
"I like it."
I was lying.
So I wrote it as a sketch
at the Groundlings,
and it went for years.
It was directed
by Deanna Oliver first,
and then Bob Odenkirk.
I beat that thing to death.
I did it -- I did it everywhere.
This is a woman who is
insecure about her new haircut.
I brought it in as an Update and
we had the wig and everything.
It was this huge spiky wig.
Not many people
could pull this off, but I can.
Someone must have saw it
and said,
"That's not
going to happen here."
And it got cut 20 minutes
before the dress show.
Then I was asked to bring
it back with a different wig
and it got cut after dress.
I think we may have tried
it three weeks in a row.
I look crazy.
But thank God it happened
because it's meant
to be a sketch
and they helped me see that.
-I hate it!
-Even though it didn't go on TV,
the whole staff would quote it,
and people would go,
"I like it."
-I like it.
-And I feel like
the character was just so big
it needed to be surrounded by a
bunch of people staring at her.
It was a real journey
with the look of the hair.
-The hair.
-They originally wanted
it to be a bob,
and I had just had
a design meeting
with a whole 'nother sketch
of 5,000 bobs,
and I was like,
"Well, that's not gonna work."
The wig cannot be
the whole joke.
It had to be a build up.
Like, why does she look
a little off?
-We knew we wanted to, like,
turn and have her
reveal something.
-So there was a skin square.
I could only give this one
one shot at it
because we only had one go.
-The skin square.
-Glen is such a great
straight man.
He was so down
to let other people shine
and he was so good
at supporting them.
-And sometimes
when you write something
that a host is
a straighter part,
you wonder,
are they going to be
excited to do this?
When we were picking sketches,
he was like, "Oh, I love that.
Yeah, we have to do that."
-Well, Melissa,
I really like it.
-Me, too.
-And with that, we are finished
with the interview.
-Thank you so much.
-I like it.