-Hi. I'm Panina Withers,
and I'm here to warn you
about a dangerous, new substance
affecting
a vulnerable population...
women in their 20s.
It's turning our precious loved
ones into horrifying monsters,
leaving them ranting and raving
and foaming at the mouth.
The substance
I'm referring to is, of course,
espresso martinis.
Girlies everywhere are meeting
up for dignified ladies' nights,
drinking espresso martinis,
and transforming into BMDs,
bitches of mass destruction.
They are putting
their loved ones through hell.
Right, boys?
-The last time
my girlfriend went out
and ordered espresso martinis,
she lost her debit card,
her phone, and her IUD.
Girl, that was in you!
How do you lose that?
-I never thought
I'd be barked at like a dog
until my girlfriend drank
one and a half espresso martinis
with a group of women she hates.
-That's why my team and I have
developed a solution...
the Espresso Martini
Safe Room...
a completely padded room filled
with exactly what they need
to ride out their mania
until they can reintegrate
into society.
Take a look at some
of our satisfied customers.
candy
place
beach
bra
Thank goodness they're safe.
-The Espresso Martini
Safe Room comes equipped
with features such as
a fake
phone full of Instagram stories
so she can reply to all of them
without doing any actual damage.
-It also comes
with a cardboard cutout
of her boyfriend
so she can tear into him
for something
he did nine years ago.
admit
met
god
kill
faster
-The safe room even comes
with a thoughtful gay,
who can either chat or fight,
depending on what
the girls need.
For his safety, he'll be placed
behind bulletproof glass.
mormon
episode
happy
Greece
n
Our research is still ongoing.
Hear now from one of our
trusted scientists at the FDA.
-For years,
I've studied espresso martinis,
or, as we call it, "girly meth."
I found that they contain
a special chemical
that makes bitches act messy
in the streets.
When the cream, caffeine,
and vodka combine
in the bloodstream,
it can cause me
to DM Dylan Efron
a blurry photo of my bare ass.
-So, do what's right.
Save her from herself with...
-Espresso Martini Safe Room.
-Yeah, I bet you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
-Oh, no, Panina,
where'd you get
that espresso martini?
-Are you scared, little boy?
Yeah, sometimes I drink.
And you,
you big, white ass...
looking like Pennywise
took an improv class.
Homeboy...homeboy
looks like Phineas and Ferb.
So what? So what? Okay?
And you don't love me anymore.
You don't love me anymore!
You know what?
We need to get her
to the safe room.
-No, no. I have more to say.
-Shout-out to Megan
and shout-out to Kelly.
Those are my day ones.
I love you, girls. I love you!
-The Espresso Martini Safe Room,
from the inventors
of the Sangria Straight Jacket.