-This week, Minnesota
and Illinois filed lawsuits
against the Trump administration
over ICE deployments
in their cities.
Here to talk about this is
Minnesota's own Tommy Brennan.
-Hey, Michael.
-Hey, Tommy.
You know, it's
pretty scary what's happening
in Minnesota right now.
-Yeah, it really is.
And look, I know that no one
is dying for a hot take on this
from a guy who looks like
he was home-schooled on a yacht,
but it would be insane
to ignore what's happening
in my hometown right now.
-I mean, it's a really
heavy thing to talk about.
-Yeah, it is.
And I know there's nothing
I can say that will ease
the grief and anger and fear
that a lot of people
are feeling right now.
But I wanted to show you
one thing from the ICE protests
in Minnesota
that gave me
just a glimmer of hope.
Check it out.
Powerful stuff, huh, Che?
-Yeah.
-You know what?
Let's watch that one more time,
please.
Wow.
Did you hear the
absolutely ecstatic reaction
from the people around him?
Minnesotans are famously nice.
Do you know how hard it is
to get us to bully you?
One time I was
in a Minnesota bar
and I chipped my tooth
and the guy next to me
offered me his tooth.
That's Minnesota, but here
they are, squealing with joy.
They sound like
when kids meet Mickey Mouse.
It's just like, "Oh, my God!
Yeah!"
And okay,
maybe you missed it.
Let's go ahead
and play it again.
So he starts off sprinting
in one direction, then falls.
I don't know
if you guys caught the fall.
Did you -- Maybe you forgot.
It's a long video.
Just to be safe,
let's play it again.
And then he gets up
and just jogs back to his car.
Just completely gives up
on his mission.
It honestly kind of looks like
that was his mission.
Like, his superior officer was
like, "Hey,
go do a Scooby-Doo fall
on that ice,
and then hobble your way
back to the car."
Also, just to be clear,
I don't --
I'm not reveling
in another person's pain.
If I wanted to do that,
I would join ICE.
But all joking aside,
these agents are brave.
They leave the house every day,
not knowing if they're going to
make it back to their own beds,
because their mom keeps
changing the locks.
They didn't even get uniforms.
They're just out here
in their Bass Pro Shop
paintball camo pants.
Why are you wearing camo?
Where did you think
Minneapolis was?
-It doesn't seem like
they know what they're doing.
-I know. I don't know, man.
I -- It's just like,
all I know is I'm
really proud of where I'm from.
And the response
that Minnesotans have shown
this week.
Minneapolis is a city
of immigrants,
and that's what makes it great.
I grew up playing
on all-immigrant soccer teams,
and let me tell you, it is not
easy to catch those guys.
So good luck, you know?
-Oh.
-But I guess I'm just showing
this video because remember,
these are the athletes that
Minnesotans are dealing with,
and we're not like them.
We won't jog back to the car
and we won't slip up
because in Minnesota
we've been dealing with ice
our whole lives, bitch!
-Tommy Brennan, everybody.
-Leave Minnesota alone.
Thank you.