-All right, everybody.
Trailer for "Euphoria"
Season 3 just dropped,
and, uh, people are excited.
But there's still
a couple story beats the network
wants us to work out.
So, we threw together
this last-minute writers' room.
We grabbed who we could find.
We got Fodman and Gay
from "Sex Education."
-Hey.
-Hello.
-Yeah. Also, we got Kat,
who wrote on "Industry."
-Hey, everyone.
-And finally we have,
um, Chester Barnhill.
Uh, he wrote for "Reba"
and Reba's new show,
"Happy's Place."
-Yeah, it's like "Reba,"
but it's in a bar.
Hey, y'all, I'm Chester, and
can I just say how glad I am
this isn't on Zoom.
I am so sick of writing on Zoom!
Oh, my God!
Everybody's like,
"Chester, set your iPad down.
You're shaking the screen.
You're making me carsick."
I say, "I like walking around."
-Okay, cool.
Um, so, the first story area
we want to look at
is the opening
of the second episode.
Rue is overdosing on heroin.
She needs to get Narcan
before she blacks out.
The network wanted to make
a bigger moment out of that.
-Okay,
so this might be trope-y,
but maybe she has, like, a
flashback of herself as a child,
and that gives her,
like, I don't know,
like, a rush of adrenaline.
-Ooh. That's good.
Or she finds a stash of meth,
and that counteracts the heroin.
-The only way out
is to go deeper.
Interesting.
-I have a pitch.
What if instead of an alcoholic,
Rue's a chocoholic?
Imagine this. Rue wakes up.
By the way, what's "Rue"
short for, kangaroo?
No, I'm just
playing around!
Anyway, Rue wakes up,
and she is covered in chocolate,
wrappers all over the place.
And then the chesty one
comes in.
She goes, "Has anyone seen
my Christmas candy?"
Then Rue turns her and she goes,
"Can we not?"
-Uh-huh.
Yeah...that's...
That's interesting.
Um, it's not really the tone
we're going for.
-Yeah,
I don't mean to be rude,
but have you ever seen
"Euphoria"?
-I watched a couple trailers
and got the gist.
It's like "Peanuts,"
but they're teens.
Kinsey "Peanuts."
-It's actually very,
very different.
But, uh, let's just look
at our next story area.
Um, so season three --
sorry, episode three --
Nate's in a dark place
after everything
that happened with his father,
and he winds up at a truck stop
getting rimmed by a sex worker.
-[ Laughing ] Oh, my God!
-I'm sorry,
but y'all cannot put that on TV!
Unless you want
about a thousand emails saying,
"Y'all better knock it off."
And, besides,
who wants to see
a scene
of somebody getting
their butt ate?
What is funny about someone
getting their butt eat up?
-Well, it's not...
It's not really supposed to be
funny.
-Well, congratulations.
You succeeded.
But okay, here's the pitch.
So, everybody comes back
from Christmas break,
and there's a test.
And Zendaya is the only one
who read "Moby-Dick."
So, they're all craning
their necks over her paper,
and they're cheating.
And then the fat guy leans over
so far, he breaks his desk,
and all his Christmas candy
goes flying everywhere.
And then the teacher looks
in the camera and she goes,
"Y'all, can we not?"
-O-Okay.
We don't have catchphrases,
Chester.
And no one in the "Euphoria"
cast is fat.
-Y'all don't have a funny fat?
That's a mistake.
The studio audience loves
a funny fat.
-Okay,
there's no studio audience.
"Euphoria" is
not a three-camera sitcom.
-No! Y'all figured out
how to do four?!
-Okay, let's-- let's
just jump to the last area
we need to work out.
Um, Chester, maybe it's best
that you don't pitch
until you get more of an idea
of what we're going for here.
-Okay. Uh, no problem.
I'll just hit the snack bar.
-Wonderful.
Okay,
so, uh, the fifth episode,
Cassie attempts suicide.
-Oh, my God! Turkey pinwheels.
-Then Maddy finds Cassie
and starts crying.
-Lemon Luna bars?!
-And for the first time, she
actually feels sorry for her.
-Oh, shut up! Sun chips!
-Chester...do you mind?
You're being really distracting.
-I'm sorry. I love grazing.
But, you know,
while we're on me,
can I just do a pitch
real quick?
-No.
-Okay, great.
So, picture this.
The gang from Euphoria High
wins a trip to Hawaii,
and then Zendaya finds an idol,
and the volcano starts rumbling,
and they're like,
"Uh-oh, we may have to sacrifice
a virgin."
And then the chesty one looks
to the camera, and she goes,
"Marked safe
from the volcano."
-Okay. All right. Listen.
I cannot work like this, okay?
I'm sorry,
but Chester's gotta go.
-Yeah. I can't pitch
if he's in the room.
-Oh, okay.
Well, if that's how y'all feel,
then, I'll go.
I guess there's no room
in Hollywood
for a dinosaur like me.
-Chester, wait!
Maybe there is something
to your Hawaii idea.
- Really?!
-Yeah.
You know, maybe if the whole
group goes somewhere remote,
they'd have no choice,
but to face the problem
they've been avoiding.
-Yeah,
and maybe there's a luau.
-And the funny fat eats
a whole pig.
-Yeah, and there could be,
like, a limbo contest.
And the chesty one keeps
knocking over the bar
with her heavy naturals,
and one of the hula dancers
looks in the camera and goes...
-"Can we not?"
-I get it.
Guys, I think we officially
fixed "Euphoria."
Apologizes