Hey girl.
Hey.
Oh, hey mama.
Okay.
First meeting of culde-sac queens club.
What?
I needed this y'all.
Some fun out of the house away from the kids.
Oh, amen, sister.
Let's get those steps in, girls.
Let's do it.
Beth, I couldn't help but noticing you're wearing one of those cool weighted vests.
Oh, I sure am.
I got it off the Tik Tok shop.
Kind of fun, right?
This thing is heavy.
Oh, wait.
You are.
Me, too.
Look.
Oh, okay.
Queen.
Heck yeah.
Yeah.
I love how it takes a simple, pleasurable part of everyday life
and just makes it awful.
What weight you reckoning, Carol?
Oh, this is a 10 lb.
Oh, okay.
What about you?
30.
This is a 30 lb.
So, it's more.
Oh, okay.
Gotcha.
Very nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, I read the 10 lb doesn't really do much.
So
Oh, well, I've got the bangles, too.
Weighted bangles.
So, I have those as well.
And the feet.
I have the feet bangles, too.
Well, I don't like you very much.
Okay.
Okay, ladies.
This isn't a competition.
Okay, Mom.
Welcome.
Sorry I'm late.
My pop pong punky plotty class went crazy long.
Oh, you just did plotties.
How did you do all that?
Little thing called coffee.
Just kidding.
I'm just not lazy.
Oh, Michelle, don't tell me you're wearing a little weighted vest as well.
Oh gosh, no.
This is a 200lb carbonite suit.
Got it off the Tik Tok shop.
And get this, the previous owner disarmed Rosie bombs with it.
Oh, I love her locker.
It helps my core, keeps my posture, and it keeps my heart rate at a steady 320.
Every step is hell, and I'm having a blast.
Well, dang it.
Now I want one.
Oh, you want my extras?
Here.
We lost one.
You know they call it rucking.
- What?
- Walking with a weighted vest or backpack.
It's rucking as in get this rucking thing off me.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
There she is.
You're rocking a weighted suit, too, Katie.
Oh, nope.
I just thought it was Halloween today.
I've been working out so much I just keep forgetting what day it is.
Oh, right.
Katie, did I see you and Paul just renewed your vows?
- We did.
- He's so nice.
What did he do that made you feel like he needed to do that again?
So, it's actually a funny story.
On my birthday, he tipped a girl on only fans our car.
Oh, happy birthday.
Hey, Mama's Party Rock is in the house tonight.
- Marie, what you got there?
- It's called a hell rack.
400 lb of pure hell.
I got it off the Tik Tok shop.
It crunches my spine, but the body is tea,
- as in the shape of a tea.
- Absolutely girl.
Uh-oh.
Dad incoming.
There he is.
Sorry to crash your party.
I heard we were lugging enormous amounts of weight around for pleasure and had to join in.
Oh, where's your vest, Mont Frera?
Oh, actually, fun fact, I am sporting a weighted butt plug.
Yep.
It's called butt rocking.
- Never heard of that.
- Oh, it's the latest thing.
Got it off the dark web.
180 lbs in my ass.
I feel awful, but I'm pretty hard.
Oh, good for you, Phil.
Carol's rocking the 10 lb.
- I literally will kill you.
- Sure.
Hey, how far have we gone?
Looks like less than two blocks.
Well, that's enough for me.
Yeah.
Uh, this is my stop, ladies.
Getting pretty close to a school zone. So,
yes.
Well, we should totally do this again sometime.
Oh, I would love
Oh gosh.
Well, I love you girlies.
- I hate you.
- Hate all of you.
- Very mean group.
- Not a fan.