-This week
at the BAFTA Awards,
the crowd was shocked
as several offensive words
were shouted from the crowd.
But as host Alan Cumming
pointed out,
the hateful language
was unintentional.
It was involuntary verbal tics
from a man
suffering from Tourette's syndrome.
Hi, I'm Mel Gibson,
and as I probably should've
pointed out decades ago,
I, too, suffer from Tourette's.
Which explains a lot
of the things I've said
or yelled through the years.
Am I proud of what I said?
No.
But I am very proud
for you to know
it was because of Tourette's.
Fortunately, I'm not alone.
-Hi, I'm OG
Real Housewife of New York
Jill Zarin,
and you might have seen
the video I posted this week
where I said Bad Bunny did the
worst halftime show in history.
And why was it in Spanish?
And where were all
the white people?
But what you didn't know is
that I suffer
from severe, long-winded, monologue-style
Tourette's,
a condition that affects
9 out of 10 people
on Long Island.
-Hi, cuties,
I'm Armie Hammer.
And not many people know this,
but one of the
most common side effects of Tourette's
is cannibalism.
You could be casually DM'ing
with a girl,
and suddenly,
the Tourette's takes over,
and you're typing stuff like,
"I'm literally
going to eat you."
And she's like, "Lol, what?"
And you're like,
"I'm not lol'ing or rofl'ing.
I'm gonna drink your blood
and gnaw the meat off your ribs
like I'm at an Applebee's."
But since it's Tourette's,
I guess I have to be forgiven,
if not celebrated.
Thanks, medicine.
-Immediately after the BAFTAs,
I talked to the doctors and
the scientists and the lawyers,
and they agreed that,
apparently, you can suffer
from something called
the Drink Tourette's.
So you say I try to order
the Diet Coke.
It's simple, right?
Only sometimes
it'll come out like,
"I need a double whiskey
with a bunch of GHB mixed in."
And then, I have
a second condition called
gender blindness.
So instead of giving
the drink to myself,
I gave it to like
60 different women.
Anyhoo,
that's how the Tourette's works
with hizzin'
and the vizzin'
and the zippa zappaty daw.
-Tourette's isn't just blurting
out an offensive word,
it can be years-long obsession
with something like trans rights
Rowling
and a deep anger that someone
who was born with a wand
in their pants
would want that one removed
and replaced with a Horcrux.
But now you know it was
all the Tourette's fault
and not a bet I made
with Bill Belichick
to see who could destroy
their legacy faster.
-You know, it's -- it's amazing.
Tourette's sucks.
Tourette's sucks, especially
if you get it in your penis.
Uh, fortunately, I developed
a cure for penile Tourette's.
It'll magically go away
if the penis is touched
by an unsuspecting princess.
Oh, come on!
Jesus. I'm kidding.
She has to put it in her mouth.
-Tourette's
is a serious condition,
or my name isn't Michael Che.
Tourette's makes us do
horrible things
to the white guy we work with.
What is this, anyway?
-That's okay, amigo,
you and me are in this together.
-Thanks, Mel Gibson.
-The important thing
to remember
is that our outbursts
are involuntary.
That explains why Che and I
might say something
anti-Semitic
even though it's offensive
to the very people
who run our industry.
Hey, should we remake
"Lethal Weapon"?
-We're not hiding
in the shadows anymore.
We are proud to admit
we have Tourette's.
-I have the Tourette's.
-I have Tourette's.
-I got like 50 different types
of Tourette's.
-And if you try
to discriminate against us,
I will eat you so fast.
-You come at me,
and I swear to God,
I will make Dumbledore straight.
-Brought to you
by the National Workforce
of Rethinking Disabilities,
or N.W.O.R.D.