-First time hosting.
How do you feel?
-It's truly such an honor.
-Oh, we're so excited.
Anyway, I had this idea
I wanted to pitch you.
-And I would love to hear it.
-Okay, great.
I'm your upstairs neighbor,
but I'm, like, super loud.
You know what I mean?
I'm throwing parties.
I'm like, "Wake up.
Get out of here!"
-I already hate this idea.
It's the worst idea
I've ever heard.
What do I do?
Come on, Colman,
just say you're not feeling it.
-So what do you think?
-I love it.
-Oh, my God. Great.
Okay, so then...
-Why did you say you loved it?
You've really done it this time,
Colman.
Is it too late
to switch to SNL UK?
The idea is getting worse
by the second.
Is she doing Soulja Boy?
-Maybe if I tell someone
she tried to kiss me,
she'll get fired.
I never thought I'd be
jealous of dead people.
The sketch involves
hobby horses now?
Please, God, strike me down.
This is so annoying.
And that's coming from someone
who spent his whole life
around theater people.
Good lord, how did
we get to black Captain Hook?
-You got this, Colman.
Just say no.
-So basically, that's it.
What do you think?
I mean, you could say no.
-I-I-I-I just feel like, ah...
maybe.
I wonder if, uh...
It's the best thing
I've ever heard.
We are absolutely doing this.
-Yes! Oh, my God, I knew it.